<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1499</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only useful for basic dungeons where you easily steam roll everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good neighbors are a godsend but an HOA won't make your good neighbors better, just make your bad neighbors worse. (And discourage "undesirables", but that can be sketchy) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do cars have a tolerance usually? I pieced together my car from 2 different cars and nothing lit up but the airbag (I suspected it was the yellow box computer I suspect is in of airbags had black scorch marks on its port) but after taking the computer and the computer from the other car to a mechanic, and reinstalling it it was all good with no lights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I killed a good few of them bc they were stuck in a door way and were not moving, poor Lydia she didn't last long at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just downvote it if it's a repost you have seen, eventually you will see less stuff like this bc downvoted posts don't make it to the front </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they coated the heads in lime too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something like EVE online and (now gone) DUST? They were trying to combine them but the DUST part didn't work out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> India really has this problem  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally still am a bit weirded out that the emails are such a big deal. A good portion of past government personal including cabinet member of both republicans and democrats have used private emails... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't tell is you are a red cap or /s... that's kinda sad that I would think that a red cap would believe in that whole heartedly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So punish the victims? Or are you suggesting something more akin to universal healthcare for children?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy FFX other world
But also black mages: those who fight further

Oh sound track, X, XII
(Tactics not as much as Eli played tactics so many times I am somewhat sick of the music) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [US] NASCAR came from prohibition, with smugglers trying to ditch police. There could be a lead there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all do but mine are tears of joy I hope :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were saying things such as holding my sides from laughter. That was unnecessary and all it could do is inflame others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Admin spying of the AP, IRS harassment. Of course how could I forget that... no mate this is not new cloths for the emperor, do not imply others are not worthy to converse with others just bc they don't have the same bullshit as you do. (A little harsh but please don't pressure others unreasonably) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mate stop unnecessaryly antagonizing people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why we need more gun control is what you are implying? /s but overall the program was shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of shit that you said is more than the amount of reason you put into your statement. Come on mate, if you make claims that are not common knowledge, especially outlandish ones, back them up, preferably with a source that is not shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right it's the parents fault for not being able to afford better coverage (yeah I'm twisting the image itself a bit to healthcare but I believe the image is already twisted to healthcare) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The better better court or the higher higher court? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it speaker of the house and then if he is dead some general? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even the Japanese head admiral did not believe even an optimistic result from Pearl Harbor would cripple the US for long, only buy time for the Japanese before the US fleets would recover and grow stronger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rome had some massive armies though afterwards Europe had smaller armies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can you tell it's poisonous? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice illustration  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks it opened my eyes a tad bit more  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had one O saw, it was.. ok. Router is nice and all but I don't do a whole lot of drywall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your last part: is it stating that fiber optics cables light pulses overlap but that's ok bc they are different colors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reverse image search? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have FTTH with CCI and for the most part it's great but around 4 times a day I experience distruptions for 10-40 sec. (on occasion longer but rare) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure it is the PD's fault, and after such an experience I don't think anyone can laugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity what would be an appropriate settlement? Do note that this guy will have difficulty landing a job, with romantic interests, was held in a dangerous situation, and the other things that come with a really screwed up reputation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, thanks for the insight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This feels worse than the banister one

https://www.reddit.com/r/OSHA/comments/68rkyh/a_stepup_on_the_traditional_ladder/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lean to the right, slide all the way to ground floor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I have a saw, isn't easier to just use a knife with replaceable blades? (I don't do drywall for others, I just on occasion patch holes in my walls that I create when doing electrical work.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised that this was so big. A relative who is close to me works for USPS and he carries dog spray, usually that's usually enough to make the dog go away. if a situation occurs that looks like it's long term he informs his supervisor and it seemed much more low-key. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His name will never be clean, being accused for pedophilia can ruin your reputation for life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The damage to reputation right there is big, being accused of such crimes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see if the girl is traumatized but even so for the guy in jail there should be a recourse to pursue to get out faster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 09:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first time playing fanatical purifiers I thought the same, however it was my first war after centuries of growth so I cleansed around 8-10 planets in one go. No one talked to me for the rest of the game but the fanatical purifiers in the federation I made (and one spiritualist pacifist so I could block stupid wars) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 08:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The wars that are most fun are 3 way wars when all 3 parties are around the same strength so no one wants a real fight so it's mostly hit and run and until you maneuver yourself into a better position, but the AI tries to do that as well. (Fun fact most wars in the past were mostly maneuvering and sieging, with the occasional battle.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 08:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aye but republicans still have to cater to trump to an extent. If they piss him off and he starts vetoing in revenge, which I will say is not above him, they will get little done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 08:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now post a "after 4 years" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 08:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cause it's blatant and not thought out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 08:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are tears of joy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 08:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were living in a bad neighborhood, SAD.

we just assisted them moving into a new better better one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 08:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might as well put him on drugs to see if it can get worse ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see a blind man banging his head if that wasn't there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can make your own, though mine cracked after first use and I swore never to use them again (I lied l, I needed to move the car back) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see points on why one would say CA with its autonomy has done disagreeable things such as pension was a mess a few years back, and to a lesser extent the drought could have been better managed but good things do come out of CA autonomy such environmental regulations, workplace regulations. (In general the US political system grants states a hefty amount of autonomy) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow what a nice answer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you keep posting well thought out articles you might as well get a flair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While often as a CA I feel disappointed in other sections of the country, I would not support even a partial split from the union (as in given more autonomy) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently Spain I think claimed it as its territory  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome link thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm intrigued and I am definitely not anything close to a mathematician and more of an amateur, but I like learning and could you show me and or explain the math so I don't repeat the same mistakes (and satisfy my math curiosity) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me the Firon Burst (one of the best) ate most of the Gigas and later the cyclops  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to bother you but what does SOL'd mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have the free time please post the outcome I am interested  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay 9.8 m/s/s is the acceleration of a free falling object, so just take the height in meters and multiply against 9.8 m/s/s

Now acording to airdrop wiki this would be a low-velocity airdrop. Typical height for said drop is 500 ft acording to globalsecurity.org. 152.4 meters is 500 ft. So the cargo hits the ground at around 1493.52 m/s. That in feet would be around 4900 ft/s or 3340.909 miles per hour. Granted There would be other factors in play such as air resistance and the parachute partially working

TLDR: around 3,340 miles per hour they hit the ground

Edit: wind resistance is a big thing so this is incorrect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Late game was scary with the petrify spam ( only 3 people were alive, 3 dead, the rest petrified.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Party was the following:

II Firon with his burst     VII Aerith White Materia 

Advanced tactics (bc after using it he promptly died)  XI Ekkio

XI Zidane (rune tooth)    Ystol Asylam 

Tyro dancer (and always late Wall)    OK (as a healer/ debuffer) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> About the FF tactics 220 MP... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did most just focus and bursting down the boss? My party first knocked out the daemons. Though with only 2 real damage dealers it took about 20 min to finish with all stars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a CS minor I have been more gearing myself for C and C++. Darn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 09:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an intriguing idea, despite some potential counter arguments i like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 09:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty cool, thanks for the hard work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 09:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you ever at times get pretty much caravans of speeders? I recall at one point in the desert I joined  a group of ~20 cars that were going 100+ (pretty sure none really knew each other, just random strangers that piggybacked off one another) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 08:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Removal reason nope"

That seems to have a story behind it, or is that a reason that was created just now?

Edit: I checked below removals, that guy whose posts are removed must be doing quite a few stupid things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 08:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they are the ones who write the laws, they (congress in general) are not masochists that would write a law that would hurt them (congress in general). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 07:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the higher ups in police or DEA in Sacramento, I can't remember his name, is quite ambitious at the moment and is trying to get credit so he can be promoted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't want to get in the way of a cop no thanks. Otherwise I would have to watch my back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A relative of mine in sac was raided as a result of a targeted sting, I only saw the aftermath and I thought they were douchebags, like why empty half of all the liquids into the sink, baking soda ect, selectively rip up the carpet. It's a sting you already have the information you need.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aye the news arrived late though. (It often feels like a war over nothing [as impressment issue was solved] that achieved nothing)

Edit: forgot about the British forts that were removed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of these ships were taken down by one lucky hit (due to horrible ammo storage practices) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 10:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't bother upgrading the federation fleet most of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 10:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try to plan to simultaneously invite as much as members as I find useful at once for federations. After that I know it will be hard to get another member. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 10:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to https://www.brennancenter.org/analysis/vrm-department-motor-vehicles-databases Vermont is in the process of updating their databases to be able to share with NY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 10:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also heard you can write some of it off your taxes as "loss not covered under insurance". Is that true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 10:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder, would replacing the engine and transmission, practically the front part of a car; with one that has 40,000-60,000 less miles make a difference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have gotten my eyes opened by MP often. Often a build that looks weird and idiotic to me, when the battle actually starts I am oh dam, I didn't think about that ( Terra OSB for current Octopus, Argeis (the FF tactics knight [i butchered her name] for the XII MP) 

At this point I should get a flair along the lines of "Bane of all Names" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not link you a book, somebody with the approval and input of the /r/history mods took the time to develop and write the response and reviewed the links that the bot provided, potentially in that response is your "concrete" example.

Furthermore I believe the history buffs known as the mods of /r/history did at least a preliminary analysis or at least left the analysis  to a trusted source </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah I thought that 60 hours was with grinding  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard to say, the weapons, ammo, etc was stored in a very improper way, anyways sabotage or not, if the ammo dump was managed correctly this would have not happened </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/legaladvice  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't recommend any of them because I most likely never read any of them, however being provided a link and then asking to be spoon fed information leaves a gritty taste to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taiwan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's an okay monitor with 22" or higher, and 60 hertz refresh rate? Or what general direction should I go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heard it was also the intimidation factor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lacrosse has its roots as it was used as a proxy war for Native Americans. (Not the lacrosse we know and play today, this one could have hundreds of participants and large fields; just imagine this mega lacrosse.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch, relevant but not quite history yet (but much history can be applied here) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch, relevant but not quite history yet (but much history can be applied here) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> click on the dam links the bot provided if you are so interested, otherwise do note no one is insulting you so your pride will not be hurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weren't the Minoans naval based? Perhaps the tsunami wiped out their fleets and ships (fishing and other) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh lucky the summers may be intense but only for 2-3 weeks, otherwise it's just moderately hot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've melted my glasses last summer (the plastic frame) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FIRE, not dead yet? FIRE AGAIN, still not dead? KEEP FIRING </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zantetsuken was useful to me. During battle of the big bridge event, it's death proc'ed 3 times for me. (Was super confused at first) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 10:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ai it's quite rare, I pored 23 stones into Terra OBS sword and only got a major 2 times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 09:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the grinder, hell I was lv 60 before raithwel on XII on my first play through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
