<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2991</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 09:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I believe it's true  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 09:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jamaican?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 09:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick call in the rest of the mudmen to take out this pest! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 09:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lord of the Flies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 09:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> B00bs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the theories are true, and the speed of light is slowing down, what would happen to what we believe about the universe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 08:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 08:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is he so angry?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 07:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mother's Day.......how ironic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 07:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was a piano piece before it was a guitar piece, just so you know  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movie title sounds better when said sarcastically? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 07:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A blonde takes her car to the repair shop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 22:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One day after a huge hailstorm, a blonde took her car into the repair shop to fix all of the dents that the hailstorm had created. Upon arrival, the auto-repair men saw the extensive damage and did not want to repair the car regardless of the amount of money they would get. Seeing that she was blonde, the auto-repair men decided to have a little fun. 

They told her, "Oh you don't need us! All you need to do is take the car home, park it, and start blowing into the tail pipe and all those dents will pop right back to normal!"
The blonde was thrilled by this and hurried home. 

A little while later, the blonde's neighbor, who was also blonde, saw what was happening and came over. "What are you doing?" She asked. 

The blonde replied, "I'm trying to get the debts out by blowing into the tailpipe. But I keep blowing and blowing and nothing is happening!" 

Her neighbor looked at her and back at the car and exclaimed, "Oh you silly! You got to roll up the windows first!"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 20:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always known the joke as female, but I didn't want to specify, although apparently I did.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 08:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Some will appear to be looking through her bedroom window." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 08:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're asking him to go to her house and draw her through the window? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 07:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Through her window? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A blonde, a brunette and a redhead go hunting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 07:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A blonde, a brunette and a redhead all went out camping and hunting together. After setting up camp the brunette left to go hunt. 24 hours later the brunette came back with a deer. The others were in awe of the brunette and asked, "How did you do it?"

The brunette replied, "Found tracks, followed tracks, shot the deer."

The next day the redhead went out and returned 48 hours later with a bear. The blonde and brunette were in complete awe and asked, "How did you do it?"

The redhead replied, "Found tracks, followed tracks, shot the bear."

The next day the blonde went out and returned three days later completely broken, bruised, and bloody. The brunette and redhead were shocked and horrified asking, "What happened!?"

The blonde replied, "Found tracks, followed tracks, got hit by a train." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 06:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never thought of that. Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 06:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do speedometers have such high numbers when the car isn't capable of going that fast and no speed limit is that high? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 21:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf dude?!?!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reverse psychology  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Transportation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what if I'm lying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black Angels by George Crumb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ???????????? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe it had something to do with milk at a younger age </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this keyboard?! I have never seen it?!???! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not planning on taking over the world, and I'm definitely not going to use a virus which doesn't have a cure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A softball injury </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During a softball game, one of the girls was struck in the vagina by the ball. After taking her to the hospital the doctor informed them that the damage was severe and the would have to do surgery to remove different parts of the vagina that were too damaged. 

The surgery went well, but unfortunately the nurses mixed her pain medication with another drug which caused the girl to have vivid hallucinations. She ran out of the hospital and into the street in nothing but her underwear. After running around for a while still racked by hallucinations, she took shelter in a restaurant, but was unfortunately kicked out. 

After all, no shirt, no shoes, no cervix! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That poor husband has to put up with nine wives for nine lives! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TGIF  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, he's been in the business sixty years.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PLEASE I HAVE THE RAY GUN! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
