<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3944</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. My bad. I'll replace those asap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Album of Space [4256x1796] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 09:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/jq1HkuW.jpg 


like this? sorry it's 3:30 am and i'm tired lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me_irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're stupid idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 09:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i haven't been able to finish a game of overwatch since november. i tried to enjoy it 3 times and ended up leaving tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deneedleed Christmas tree (Douglas fir) safe for conure? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My tree has pretty much dried out. Think it would be safe for my sun conure once deneedled and pruned of all small branches? Would sap be a damning hazard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PC bug, still can't start Blood Drive or Clocktower in private game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 18:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the season pass, every other DLC map works fine... googled this issue, one guy said it was resolved, the other fell off the face of the planet.. Any fix for this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [east non-ladder] ISO Hammerdin gear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 06:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need:

Spirit paladin shieldx2

paladin torch

annihilus

p combat gcs

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which ACNL Amiibo series has the rarest villagers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, looking to buy some Amiibo cards for my sister, but I don't know anything about the game really. I know that some villagers are highly sought after, though. I've searched through google for a few days now, to no avail... so, can anyone tell me what Amiibo series would be the best to buy in bulk?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> During Primal Rage, E should be an ability. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 11:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, Primal Smash, pound the ground and send every enemy around you into the air.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keep this flower on the bush or remove it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 23:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... I never beg, especially on Reddit. But if anyone gets a code for Dovahkiin armor on ESO that they don't want.. Would they be willing to part ways with it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 03:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leeching Shield Reward from ICP quest can't be enchanted... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 22:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bug or intended? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 21:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AHOY!! The Gold Coast Marauders is a highly social guild based on the PC North American Megaserver. We have our roots established in the Ebonheart Pact, but for the most part, are accepting of all factions. We have veteran players, new players, PVPers, PVEers, crafters, traders, and other relatively nice guys. 

We have a trader on and off, but due to some tragic/dramatic nonsense, the guild leadership is kind of in shambles. I wanted to wait until the event is over before recruiting again, but if you think you have what it takes to become an officer, I'd love for you to consider coming aboard. We currently have around 130 members, down from 160 since the mess with an officer who threw a tantrum and was subsequently removed. Let me know if you're interested in helping me restart our guild. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 00:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can you beliEVE WE HAVE TO REGISTER TO ENTER THE CITY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 00:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wtf, the picture is flipped horizontally... this is going to fuck a bunch of people up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 22:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> people qqing about Reaper? whot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 23:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bruh, look around the map for yourself. there's only two of these shimmering balls. i wouldn't be at all surprised if sombra controls drones or something, why would sombra be a ball on a goal in the summer games trailer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> guess the summer games distortion was just air as well? or? am i missing something that makes that floating ball of shimmering light different from these? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so everyone sees a ball of distortion in the summer games trailer and that = sombra? it's probably a drone or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if this is just heat distortion... They are two, nearly perfect circular spots of distortion. Heat distortion would've been spread across more than just two spots of the map, IMO.

Also, I have this higher quality video. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DkZLBEKnKMs

It's still hard to tell, I'd recommend going into the map yourself and looking at it, you can see that they are two circles, and not just random waves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sombra spotted on Numbani? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
