<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2577</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 12:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like 10 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My son asked me, "Dad, what's an alcoholic?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 02:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I said, "Do you see those four trees? Well, an alcoholic would see eight."

He replied, "But Dad, I only see two." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 01:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact Ron Swanson has one brother, he told me so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 00:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a group of 5 super close friends (4 guys, 1 girl), who I would see at least 3 times a week (as we all live nearby) and we would always holiday together. After 6 years guy 1 dated the girl and I'm not even joking, I saw them 4 times in the two years that they dated.

They broke up and the girl stopped talking to us all. So then I was down to 4.

Then Guy 2 started dating someone, not seen him in literally a year.
Guy 3 started dating an Australia, after 6 months her visa ran out so he quit his fantastic job and moved to Australia to be with her.
i have not seen him since.
Guy 4 hasn't dated in this time so I see him a lot.
Guy 1 bought a house with a girl he'd been seeing for 6 months (met the same week guy 2 met the australian), and I have seen him exactly twice since then, one was his birthday and the second time his girlfriend was abroad.

I get you fall in love but whenever I'm in a relationship I always make sure to still hang out with my friends.

Since whatsapp was invented I feel that people consider that being in touch and forget they haven't actually seen you for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 00:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 9/10 my one paragraph answer turns into an essay, honestly I've hit to word limit fairly often if it's talking about a serous issue. And then when I hit the limit and am no-where near done, then I just think I can't be bothered to edit and shorten this, no-one is gonna read/comment on something this long anyway. Especiallys as I'm writing on the front page; there are way too many comments before me that are gonna get liked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 22:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was anyone half expecting an animal to be what he stopped traffic for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 22:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking him to gaol for jay walking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 22:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure in 60 years people will still know pokmon like we all know Mickey Mouse.

I mean it's been 20 years and everyone knows pokmon quite well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 22:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing fast and loose with the term literally there. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 18:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I truly can imagine an episode of curb ending like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 16:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Spain we still used the Garrotte until the 70s! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 15:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People act like phones make people later, they don't do that. All they do is mean you get a text to say the other person is gonna be late, that used to happened pre-phones. You just didn't know how late the other person was gonna be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 15:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've literally never met anyone that liked it, how in the hell did it last soo long? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 14:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt it's reflected the white bashing that you hear behind closed doors /in private conversations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 14:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well my fellow bingers, we did it.
As much as I loved episode 9, I wasn't prepared for an hour long episode out of nowhere :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 14:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well my fellow bingers, we did it.
As much as I loved episode 9, I wasn't prepared for an hour long episode out of nowhere :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 11:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about you guys but I eat a ton when I'm sad and hardly eat when I'm happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 11:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this ama is really on an advert for your new show but you should have put more effort than 6 words per reply, has your assistant never written any public statements for you before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 11:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this ama is clearly just an ad for your show, but you could have said more thatn 6 words a reply :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 20:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Austin Powers 1   2 are my favourites movies of all time. Goldmember ruined my childhood, such a bad movie :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 19:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The police were incredible slow for a public area no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 19:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greedo shot first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 16:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was not expecting to see this on the front page; didn't think people outside of the UK knew who Ainsley was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 11:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Inbetweeners

A warning to all, only watch the original inbetweeners and never the american remake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 11:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His surname was Muhammad so usually he was called that.
He was affectionately known as 'blank' by a lot of people though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 01:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit, I wish they were advertising jobs I could do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 01:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went to an NFL game and they charged 10 bucks for a bottle of beer.

The craziest drink rule I've ever seen is that when you go to watch the tennis at wimbledon you are allowed to bring in one bottle per person. And by bottle they generally mean a whole bottle of wine but if you want you can bring a whole bottle of whiskey etc.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 17:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use to work in a primary school and there was a 5 year old who didn't actually have a first name because his parents hadn't got round to doing it yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 13:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why not be the Pope? Vatican is an absolute monarchy.

Because that's a full time job, people want to kill you and you can't have sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 12:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President of the Vatican city.

* Population of 800 or so people.
* Pope exists so he can do all the meet and greets/travelling to see world leaders.
* Can't mess up the economy as you're always guaranteed tourists.
* Decent weather + can visit Rome whenever you like.
* Get to see all the secret religious archives that they have hidden away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 12:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Murdering puppies?   

 I'm not sure that's a job, as such...
'Wanted: puppy murderer. Enquire within.'

Some Middle Eastern countries kill their stray dogs, this would include puppies. Though the term destroyed rather than murdered is used. Which I think actually sounds worst.

I know that in Mauritius they'd kill not only stray dogs but also owned dogs (with collars) that were wandering the streets, all so you can have an idyllic holiday. The news here ran a story about it and showed pictures of dead puppies, which I thought was a bit much to show on the news.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 02:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God to be a fly on the wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't quote Wheatcroft, as I said I've quoted Rdiger Overmans.
Again with the name calling, we're having an adult discussion, there's really no need to be uncivil.

My Eastern   Western front numbers aren't wrong, they're even the same numbers on [Wikipedia.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/German_casualties_in_World_War_II)

Now you've changed the calibre for what makes my statistics. We are talking about Nazi soldiers killed. You've now added Captured/POW along with civilian casualties. 

When you're having a debate about Nazi soldiers killed, not Soviet war efficiency, civilians, pow, suicides, cowardice, the holocaust etc.

The fact of the matter is that you've added irrelevant data to the debate to come up with a percentile that is completely irrelevant to Nazi soldiers killed by the Soviets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wont have to live a lie forever but as many can testify coming out when you're still at home can be a disaster.

Officially coming out when you've moved out and financial stable, when your family are anti gay, is usually your best bet.

As for the religious aspect, I always see religion like this. God is their and he loves us all.

Organised religion on the other hand is just the word and rules of men from thousands of years ago. We don't follow the same rules and laws that we did in Roman times, as that would be barbaric.

So why does it make sense to follow religious rules from the same time; the answer is, it doesn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So again no facts or sources from you.

Overmans gives us the following stats, taken from battles.
Nazis killed on Eastern Front up until Hitler's death 2,742,909
Nazis killed on Western Front untill Hitler's death 339,957

Again the statement remains that most people think of it as the Allies winning the war when the Soviets are responsible for nearly all Nazi soldier deaths. It doesn't matter how many casualties the Soviets had, their efficiency isn't relevant to my statement.  

Again having to resort to insults, this time with a child analogy. I hope the irony of this has not been wasting on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red heads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because 90% is accurate if your know your history.

The fact that you have to resort to insulting me just shows that you believed our Allied propaganda that we killed all the Nazis.

Show me any source that doesn't put Nazi soldiers killed by Soviet soldiers at close to 90%. Even the most edited of stats won't drop below 80%.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone might need to explain the joke to the Americans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My supermarket in England sells them for around a quid. Everything in Norway is expensive though, right. Isn't a beer like 10? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That the western allies won world war II when it was the Soviets who literally killed over 90% of Nazis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were exactly 3 people in my school that knew the mew cheat and we all agreed we'd not tell anyone :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fight club, 90 minutes of almost completely silent scenes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys have been swiping all this time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to date a girl that was an English major and to wind her up I would add semi colons to group chats as I knew no-one else would know I'd used them incorrectly but it would annoy her :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've caught a fair wad today, so yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spanish borrows heavily from Arabic and we're super phonetic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Dimbleby will host two Question Time Election Specials (Theresa May and Jeremy Corbyn will appear on 2nd June) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbf it's illegal to be gay in more countries than it's legal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Question: How is the monarchy currently seen in Spain. They seem quiet distant from the people and , dare I say it, do not have the traditional Spanish look .

Older Spaniards liked the old King (Juan Carlos) because Franco groomed him to be Spains next dictator, once he died, but when he did die JC declared that Spain will be becoming a democracy. So for that the people were eternally grateful. It was due to this that people looked the other way for his very public mistresses and general law bending ways. Once the older generation started dying off and the younger liberals had more power the people turned against him and so he quickly rushed his son in to become King.

Our current King, Felipe (VI), is basically just there and avoiding all the scandals that have turned the people against most of his relatives. He married a 'commoner' but people weren't particularly bothered about that as they are with Kate.

So at the moment most people don't care about the King, as long as he doesn't get into any major scandals. Then I'm sure the monarchy would be over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fusion of Dan   Nate, but with less money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that no-one has said she's Elizabeth Hurley. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok then :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's not way Lily wouldn't have paid for his education, even if she had to do it behind everyone's back.

Obviously we just ignore this as he needed to be kept in new york for the show's sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you lived in a world where gossip girl was a thing you would definitely keep your phone locked at school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My school actually had one, it was super popular and it got to the point where is it expanded to include 2 other schools but then police got involved and shut it down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seasons 1   2 are the strongest seasons, it drops in quality in season 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: That 12% Of People Dream Exclusively In Black And White. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stephen Fry faces up to 25,000 blasphemy charges in Ireland, a law that was introduced in 2009. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely the tradition of being a cowboy would have come to Mexico via Spain as horses aren't native to the americas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That being gay is a choice and a sin, and you'll burn in hell. Good thing the Catholic church no longer believes that nonsense... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Class System </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same just with custom icons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need Chikoritas? Richmond Park has a couple </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 10:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dated a girl named Isis. Now she's an ex if she comes up in conversation my friends and I call her Daesh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wifi Passwords From Airports And Lounges Around The World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 10:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry the train is delayed as there are leaves on the track.
Amazing a war was won tbh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the map down for anyone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had an awful last 3 years, just the worst. I accept that bad things happen to good people but that doesn't lessen the blow if I'm honest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same reason why during sex men are much more likely to say yes to something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> European here; apparently my 20s started in my teens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what is it you feel? I understand danger because you're scared you'll die or get hurt but what exactly is going through people's head when they have to talk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twist: he just had the same interview as you and he did that so you wouldn't go, thus making him the only viable candidate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look forward to tomorrow's submission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always relied on myself to get jobs but I've always found the one's to give 'tips' are the one's who got their jobs because of family members. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't understand why soo many people are afraid of public speaking. What is it that people are nervous about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As some without unliimted data love this tip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a millennial my understanding of the 80s was the AIDS was the big killer, drugs did not come to mind for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Shanghai people ride motorbikes on the pavement and it's completely normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 10:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was half expecting them to start talking about the benefits of fight milk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today is the 80th anniversary of the bombing of the Spanish civilian town of Guernica by Nazi forces. The tragedy inspired Picasso's most famous work 'Guernica'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I googled president Carter, as a European and 90s kid I didn't know anything about him.

I think it's easy enough to talk about his presidency and all that it entailed for a riveting political evening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It says no men's... we're allowed to have one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 00s was really when we saw the explosion of mobile tech, internet on the go, broadband etc.

11-17 (20) saw the fight against fast moving tech and a liking for a simpler time i.e. the rise of the hipster.

Edit: Also the 00s was the time of indie rock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the fact most americans don't consider the war of independence to be a civil war, even though it clearly was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you try to steal a motorbike but Tom Hardy is watching. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think flat earthers do much thinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a [Kardashian filter]
(https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/kardashian-filter/kbnhlagadnlfihhgjkmcaffjadkadoap?hl=en) on chrome which removes all articles (hides them in a way that you don't notice) about the Kardashian's (and whatever the rest of them are called) on all websites. You can also add other 'celebs' too.

Honestly it's my favourite extension. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what do North Korea have that China want? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me you can't be a millennial if you/your peers didn't have a smart phone whilst in school.

It might seem trivial but having access to such tech really changes your schooling experience/formative years.

Mid 30s grew up without apps, internet on the go etc. They've got more in common with generation X than us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally just completed red dead yesterday and I was looking forward to that last bit thinking, yes I've got full weapons, ammo and meds. Chuck and couple of dynamite and use the explosive rifle to kill them all.

Then the cut scene played :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a millennial, a 35 year old is definitely not one of us. You can't have a 15 year window for a generation, it's 10 tops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we're being honest, being a white male in a first world country is basically cheating in a game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love coke with real lime, drink it all the time. Lime coke however doesn't taste of lime and just tastes weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does the red pill work, do I get a six pack and never need to eat or drink. Otherwise it's no sleep for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barley? ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also arsehole and not asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't even know it was possible to confuse myself with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a ton of interests but have barely enough money to live, let alone have fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lionel Messi scores his 500th goal for Barcelona to beat bitter rivals Real Madrid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always get green, which is a bugger as they don't run where I live :(
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm bilingual, Spanish family but I was born and raised in London.
I'm fluent in both and actually studied Spanish all the way to degree level. What I noticed is that people like me (bilingual from birth) can switch in and out of both languages very easily, especially in the same sentence.

People on my course who learnt Spanish as teenagers, no matter how much they studied over the years, never learnt that ability. 

Even now when I talk to my uni buddies, when they switch languages there's always this pause before they do so, almost like they're pulling a lever in their head to switch languages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 11:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Illegal on london underground, national rail it's legal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you want ID cards, of course no it's an invasion of privacy.

Do you want this popular phone app but we will require access to all of you details, your contacts, your calls, your e-mail, your photos, basically everything about you.....sure why not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is definitely anti Brexit but that the sacrifice she's made for the power of PM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For over a decade BBC news was my most visited website so I've definitely noticed the ridiculous start+increase of clickbait recently. It's actually made me think less of BBC news and it's now my 3rd most used website, soon to be 4th. Seriously BBC write your articles as if they are serious and not as if I'm a teenage boy looking for the latest top tip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
