<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3750</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh crap I geniunely forgot Noah was on the Knicks my bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would I do in MTTs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cash game microstakes player, a beginner in poker. I break even on cash games but how would I fare in MTTs since I saw a post that the field is a lot softer. I play freerolls when I watch movies just so I dont get bored and playing cash games would take up much of my atention, and I do quite well in freerolls best I places third out of 2700 players but since the beginning is a shove fest its more luck than anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah you got Mitchell now, and you only had to give up half of the galaxy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He looks like he has a bit of a beagle in him, the snout and ear shape points to it and the white tipped tail is a big clue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have just decided that Roger is the best name a dog could ever have </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont make me hate the Jazz because of you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  with the shot boy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fuckin love Scary Terry but the only thing I like about Maple Dick is his nickname </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear to god, Brad looks like the most generic white person ever lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You make 100% of the shots you dont take - Wayne Gretzky" - Michael Scott </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 11:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know, probably the second or third best clay courter in history, but all I can remember is the french finals and the losses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right, that did sound awful. I keep reading it but the death of his sister and the word "lucky" close together just make me feel a bit sick  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a shit joke  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best surface to be a neutral spectator on, and probably the most fun of them all. However I am a Federer fan and I hate it with all my guts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HE REMEMBERS ME </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isnt this a story from that Mike Khoury guy on twitter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played it before but my ankle gave up, and so did I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THE LITTLE GUY!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full court is my area of expertise. Im a 6ft point guard with a huge vertical (for a white guy around my place) so transition offense is my jam. I have nice speed and handles, and my vision is the Rondo of pickup basketball but I cant shoot to save my life and my post game is literally non-existent so going 160mph after catching a rebound for a layup on the other side is heaven for me. But since we dont play it I usually play much worse in halfcourt, fml </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wall could find my will to live with a pass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in the Balkans and no one here plays full court with their friends. Whenever you go out to play hoops its a halfcourt game which is less tiring and more fun and exciting cause the score is closer cause no one would ever play transition defense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 13:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC it happened in a womens game somewhere and counter as a two </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LeBron is riggin the league, I just saw it live and I wont be quiet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing it fast and loose with the word contenders arent we now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He is a bad man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  LeBron may have gotten away with a travel there

What? LeBron? Noooo that doesnt sound like him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why am I waiting till april for the playoffs only to watch a fat guy drumming on a ladder?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If its anything like pokerstars he will catch running queens for quads against a set od of aces and win the election </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have it at home, recommended to me a lot of times, and since now I am turning a new leaf its next on my list, thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recommend me a book </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A complete opposite to an avid reader, 18 year old, mostly read only literature written by my native writers so pretty much only the Balkan area, decided I wanted to educate myself on a lot of areas including reading. From foreign books that I liked, I would mention Catcher in the Rye, Jules Vernes books but that was when I was younger and I glanced the Brothers Karamazov and currently im reading To Kill a Mockingbird. Fire away, prefferably with drama, crime and even horror novels but only the realistic ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 10:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they fall and go over the line, is it a bet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats exactly what I am afraid of. Either the price will drop if they start amazingly or I wont have the balls to put 1/2/3k or however much I would have on a single bet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are stacked right now, especially our offense  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does any betting site offer odds on NE Patriots perfect season this year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On bet365 it isnt offered </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come to think of it, I really am a moron.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That depends if my flair makes the playoffs and someone puts the Bulls on TNT. Bulls on TNT along with playoff Rondo he might fuck around and get 32 you never know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I concur. Fuck the Jets! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a little effort from the supporting cast and LeBron will dad dick the entire conference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Boston wins a game raps are third. If we win more than the Cavs we are first. Anything else and we are second, Cavs first, Raps third </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cant wait to see the battle between Westbrooks dancing and Hardens weird ass celebrations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BREAKING NEWS: KYRIE RETIRING AND TAKING HIS TALENTS TO SOUTH BEACH TO PLAY FOR THE DOLPHINS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
