<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1239</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a supreme lack of Leo Tolstoy on this list </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they legitimately believe they will reap spiritual rewards for it. There is even the belief that the children killed are compensated in the afterlife by going to paradise, so there's no real damage being done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PvP spell idea to fight roll spam (that we obviously will never see at this point) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want a spell that makes something like a ring of those way of white discs or some fire around you that heavily damages/stuns either player if they walk through it. Provided the person is within range, you can lock them into a small arena they can't roll spam out of, forcing both players to actually fight. However, if you miss and they dodge outside of it, you're stuck throwing ranged attacks at each other, which is obviously in favor of the player who dodged outside of it as the trade off, since they can fill that space with Chaos Orb Lava/element storm you to death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want a spell that makes a ring of those discs around you that damages/stuns either player if they walk through it. Provided the person is within range, you can lock them into a small arena they can't roll spam out of, forcing both players to actually fight. However, if you miss, you're stuck throwing ranged attacks at each other, which is obviously in favor of the player who dodged outside of it as the trade off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone seems to forget these are still way better than the robotic, clip-happy animations of the originals. The audio and lip movement was out of sync, lighting would change every time it changed focus to the other face in dialogue, characters always randomly pulled avenger rifles out of their asses, the guns they had in their hands would randomly morph into a totally fm different weapon....etc.

Honestly these aren't nearly as bad as the originals  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Georgie! Want a balloon?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (ME:A Spoilers) Cora Harper, Biotic God. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, we do.

I work in an ambulance and frequently drive through dangerous, seedy parts of town. This is to say nothing of the various addicts and psych patients that I have to transport that actively try to hurt me while I'm stuck in the back of the truck with them. Have you ever been stuck in the back of an ambulance by yourself with a violent PCP user hell bent on getting out of his restraints to strangle you? 

Additionally, the amount of hostility we receive because cop-hating types assume we're a form of police officer is more than I'd like.  We get a lot of the glares, threats, attitude, and hostility cops face while driving to the same seedy, crime filled areas but have absolutely no means of self defense. 

It's ridiculous I can't carry my CCP while working. There have been times I've really wished I had it, and thankfully I didn't end up needing it in that situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Friend and I were talking on the phone. Suddenly a recording of our entire call started playing over the line while we were still talking. What the hell happened? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: this was a landline phone, pressed the "private call" button so nobody could pick up one of the other phones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time I checked America wasn't a Christian theocracy like you seem to think it is. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you expand the scope for Christians to the world at large, you're more likely to find them being massacred by Muslims than you are to find them acting like jihadists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't conflate fundamentalist right wingers with Islamism. Once US Protestants start carrying out suicide bombings daily, publicly executing apostates, jailing and torturing turning journalists and bloggers that criticize the state, subjecting rape victims to  flogging for indecent behavior, mutilating en masse the genitals of young girls, marrying children with old men, and the general killing an oppression of millions and millions of people, then you can get all "but white people, though!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was expecting a horror story about horrific abuse flashbacks, so I'm weirdly enough pleasantly surprised at the actual outcome. Sorry OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 12:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try, boss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is about Muslims, so of course nobody is going to up vote this. If a bunch of white students said this to a Muslim teacher, it would be top page with 50k up votes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to hear that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you've had a nice experience here. There really are some stellar people here who provide great data and advice. 

Unfortunately, my experience has been 99% negative. I'm glad you've avoided  he toxicity  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was very informative, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am, I'd still like a more in depth explanation so I understand the science more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I recalculate my 1RM for the 531 program every week/month? If not, why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The long version: 

Im currently doing the 531 program with the BBB supplement. I'm also doing push-ups, pull-ups, and running in case I decide to act on my interest in the military. At the moment, I'm 5'9" at 150 and trying to gain strength, with the secondary goal of getting some mass along with it. Thus, I've been trying to eat excess calories. My goal is to be stronger, more dexterous, and hopefully not look so scrawny and small (I'm smaller than 99% of the guys I know, and it's certainly not a hit with the ladies to say the least). Given that in previous programs I've been told to add weight whenever possible for strength training, why do I only add 5 lbs as part of this program instead of recalculating my 1RM? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprised everyone isn't furious at this blatant "islamophobia"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 01:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh oh. I triggered Reddit by complaining about Americas lackluster school system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the school system favoring immigrants while allowing native born students to stagnate under a broken education system is a good thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You kill the final boss...but it doesn't drop anything. Suddenly, a door opens in the back of the room. Light peaks through the crack. As you walk up to the door and open it, you see a strange contraption of levers, buttons and screens inside. The screens show different places and moments through the entire Souls series.

There, sitting in a chair, pulling the levers, is a Shibe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You better share that with him, or else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
