<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2013</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How fitting, considering the Mughals were descended from Tamerlane.  https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mughal_Empire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens if the consumer is unaware of the actual risk of driving a car without an airbag?  What if car companies have spent his entire life telling him that airbags kill babies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How could the most famous philosopher of his time never write anything, eccentric as he may be?

Jesus Christ, that does sound weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, and I consider that a necessary evil, not an awesome system to be implemented where it doesn't already exist.  What is the benefit to your system, exactly?  Why would the populous feel more represented when your system takes away literally all of their additional representation?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, your system sounds massively worse.  You want California's 13 million votes to have the same worth as Wyoming's ~230K? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do not, my friends, become addicted to government services!  It will take hold of you, and you will resent its absence!  -Immortan Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, if by equal you mean 1/64th as great, then yeah, I guess?  http://nymag.com/daily/intelligencer/2017/04/gop-voters-love-same-attack-on-syria-they-hated-under-obama.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't it be great if Trump ended up like Buu from Dragonball Z?  We need a Hercule to start hanging out with him and teach him that hurting people is wrong, and then he'll turn over a new leaf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 05:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing once this is over it's going to be a story the Republicans never talk about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fabst Dlue Ribbon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With questions like that, they're probably eating spit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the bright side, it gave us this Jenny Yang sketch: http://tv.fusion.net/video/355357/jenny-yang-fox-news-racism-asians/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "They're just going to print what they want, so we might as well have a contest where they print what we tell them, because those two ideas are clearly compatible." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "My son's teacher has breasts?!  I demanded he be taught by genderless robots *only*!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot a reference to how his electoral college win was the biggest ever and impossible for a Republican. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone knows bank accounts are like Pythagoras cups.  Once you fill them up too much, everything spills out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, how would you feel about an electoral college based on something like, say, race, that gives disproportionately greater voting power to minorities, so that the smaller races have their voices heard?  Would that still be a good idea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope this becomes the new "When pigs fly." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unsure if this is too Doylist, but Jake Solomon has said that XCOM 1 happened, just like, alternate timeline. 

Solomon: Yeah, I view it as  you can already hear the designer bullshit coming out in my voice, but  this is the way I view it, and I think its fair, when we were talking about this idea we were like,"You know, the setting for XCOM 2 is actually going to be if XCOM lost the first game." And I think a lot of people had this reaction of, "Wait a minute, I just invested all this time and I beat XCOM." To me it feels like every time you start a new game of XCOM, youre kind of spinning off an alternate universe  and so, in the worlds where you beat XCOM, there just never was an XCOM 2, you know? This is just in case somebody actually lost a game of XCOM, which has happened, and this is a chance to go to that world and try it out. 

http://www.usgamer.net/articles/interview-the-death-of-interceptors-iron-man-mode-and-xcom-2s-next-step </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the Ethereals are directly controlling all of their troops, rather than just saying, "Hey, go kill their guys or we'll make your brains explode like a microwaved grape," wouldn't they all have similar behavior?  Instead, we see different actions from Sectoids, Mutons, Thin Men, Chryssalids,  c.  And wouldn't the Ethereals make them commit suicide rather than go through interrogation?  I think they're generally left to do their own thing rather than micromanaged constantly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, in the last mission of XCOM, the Ethereals describe the Sectoids thusly.

The New One faces the earliest effort of the Ethereal Ones, the first failure. Though possessed of a certain brilliance they are marred by their cowardice and frailty which made them cruel and ultimately useless.

So, they're brilliant, cowardly, and cruel.  All traits that I think you'd need sentience to possess.  A Sectoid Commander also appears to be in charge of the alien base in XCOM, and it'd be pretty dumb to leave an ape in charge, so he's gotta be intelligent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the Jedi Council had made Anakin be Jar Jar's press secretary, his turn to the Dark Side would have been *way* more believable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd watch that on Netflix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish my job interviewers had as low standards as Trump.  Geez.  "Do you think you can do this job?"

"I'm actually being paid to do the opposite of what this position requires."

"Welcome aboard!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vjqIJW_Qr3c  Or using mousetraps to model nuclear fission </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Reverse Cargo Cult https://hanshowe.org/2017/02/04/trump-and-the-reverse-cargo-cult/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one was born knowing the word "recalcitrant."  Everyone had to have it explained to them at some point.  Think of it this way: today you learned! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I can imagine I live on Titan, but if I try to fly by flapping wings on Earth, I'm stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuckin' Morlocks keep electing awful presidents on the Eat Eloi platform... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait for Trump to get into a fight with a world leader and ask, "You and whose army?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before someone spends time on this, could you explain, in your own words, what a sanctuary city is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't their lawyer's carefully nuanced argument this time, "It doesn't really do anything so you should let it go?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of the traits generals could get in Rome: Total War.  I really liked that system.  It made them feel a lot more unique, like they had a history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might be the first bit of forward thinking the administration's ever done.  If you can't trust the White House, why trust the next administration when they *claim* 45's wanted for crimes against humanity.  Everyone knows the White House lies! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like people would *think* Pence was joking, just hearing him say sincere stuff.

"Why did you leave the meeting?"

"I can't be alone with a woman who's not my wife."

"Haha, good one, Casanova." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You know what they say about Trump.  He's stupid!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, more like a paper bag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I just spent 15 seconds with Google and got this: http://www.mlive.com/news/jackson/index.ssf/2016/08/woman_sentenced_to_100_days_in.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "My vagina's cold.  Could you keep it warm with your dick?"

"It's okay.  Just wear these blankets, instead." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is, uh, there something about TotalBiscuit I don't know about?  I'm a bit curious about the_donald + games... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way.  Redditors are too smart to be fooled by shill accounts.  It's not like we're Pepsi-drinking idiots.  The refreshing taste of Coca-Cola is what we crave, am I right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, unless he's time-traveled, how does he know whether free will is moot or not?  Is he claiming to know that time-travel is Harry Potter-style? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Satoru Iwata took a 50% paycut when Nintendo was doing poorly.    http://www.polygon.com/2014/1/29/5356812/nintendo-boss-satoru-iwata-will-cut-pay-in-half-after-poor-fiscal  Of course, he's Iwata.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the inherent difference in productivity/contribution between an undocumented and a documented immigrant?  I mean, when someone's visa expires, do they suddenly become shiftless and lazy?  If there had been some error during your immigration paperwork, and you missed a deadline or something, would you have become bad for the country? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://infographic.statista.com/small/7083_b.jpg  ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't he want to seat them in the family members area or something, too, and the debate moderators had to tell him no way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Dark Ages </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Boy, honey, this comic sure has a lot of tentacles and...Asian schoolgirls...  M-maybe you should write a different comic you'd want to read." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This girl I had a crush on came and visited me when I was working on campus once right after we met.  She spent most of my shift playfully hitting and poking me.  Finally, she went in for a kiss.

And I, expecting a hit, dodged.  

Luckily she tried again later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any games that give you a set number of soldiers for the entire game, and every death is irreplaceable like that?  Sort of like XCOM without any new rookies ever showing up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slightly off-topic, but reading out-of-copyright translations of Greek works, you find a lot of English translators decided to render the Doric (Spartan) accent in Scottish brogue.  So goddamn annoying and so unnecessary.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Whitehouse.  His comments during Loretta Lynch's hearing were great.  http://www.mediaite.com/tv/dem-senator-gop-making-lynch-hearing-into-soundbite-factory-for-fox-news/

I regret that this hearing and this solemn occasion has been coopted, to that extent, and turned into what appears to be a soundbite factory for Fox News and conspiracy theorists everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Accurate sign, at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but what percent of Americans won't vote for Republicans over not having a non-partisan committee, because that's the important number. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact, considering Trump's connections.  Putin shoved so many documents into a stove that he *broke* it, while destroying KGB documents in East Germany.  http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2014/11/09/how-the-fall-of-the-berlin-wall-radicalized-putin.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I can't be asked to do my own thinking so here's a thought someone else had."  Although, I admit, I do tend to post Edmund Burke quotes without commentary more than I should...   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Project Highrise?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/67c80y/h_freedom_and_intergalactic_bundle_leftovers/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, it's /r/sexcom, thank you very much. (NSFW)  (Possibly NSFL) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Yorkers were cool with it, hence her winning elections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I didn't know my job after 100 days, I think my employer would be pretty justified in firing me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When will the LIEBERAL media stop asking gotcha questions like, "Do you support NATO?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you classified the employees as models, would it still be illegal?  Can't you restrict employment based on appearance under certain conditions?  I mean, I assume some place like Hooters is able to restrict serving staff employment to females only, and sex is a protected class just like race is.  I'm sure there's some loophole that would make it legal.  It'd still be an awful idea that no investor would ever want to touch, but still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also at the top of the article, but only if you read it upside-down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he should threaten to hold his breath until we give him funding for the wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone should start asking him about made-up organizations and his thoughts.  Like when people test hipsters with fake bands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry.  Nothing I'm interested in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, uh, don't think being more familiar with the game would help in this situation.  I don't think the game's lore covers Pharah's genital coloration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry. Nothing I'm interested in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Freedom and Intergalactic Bundle Leftovers, including Sins of a Solar Empire: Trinity, and Super Hexagon [W] Games/Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [My IGS Rep page](https://www.reddit.com/r/IGSRep/comments/5wjj8v/saintodhrans_igs_rep_page/)

All games I have are Humble gift links.  

**Games I Have**

[A Virus Named Tom](http://store.steampowered.com/app/207650/)

[Dangerous High School Girls in Trouble](http://store.steampowered.com/app/27400/)

[Double Fine Adventure Documentary](http://store.steampowered.com/app/402590/)

[Dusty Revenge%3A Co-Op Edition](http://store.steampowered.com/app/252430/)

[Galactic Civilizations I: Ultimate Edition](http://store.steampowered.com/app/214150/)

[Galactic Civilizations II: Ultimate Edition](http://store.steampowered.com/app/202200/)

[JumpJet Rex](http://store.steampowered.com/app/329460/)

[Monster Loves You](http://store.steampowered.com/app/226740/)

[Potatoman Seeks the Troof](http://store.steampowered.com/app/328500/)

[Sins of a Solar Empire: Trinity](http://store.steampowered.com/app/201290/)

[Space Hulk Ascension](http://store.steampowered.com/app/317620/)

[Streamline](http://store.steampowered.com/app/252850/)

[Super Hexagon](http://store.steampowered.com/app/221640/)

[Thirty Flights of Loving](http://store.steampowered.com/app/214700/)

**Games I Want**

Axiom Verge

Nobunaga's Ambition: Sphere of Influence

Galactic Civilizations III

Urban Empire

The Magic Circle

Wasteland 2

Furi

Inside

Transistor

Orwell

Project Highrise

Feel free to offer anything else and I'll see if I like it, but I'm mostly into strategy and management games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OemqVWi_R0k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love when it shows the top comment, and then it says 27 replies, and then the most recent comment, and it's somehow gone from, "This music makes me happy!" to "How can you be such an idiot?  Hitler did nothing wrong!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear FDR mentioned often with pride as an example of a great Democratic president.  What Democrats *don't* do is rest on those laurels and act like what he did absolves us of any guilt ever like a Lincoln, or act like he was a perfect demigod like Reagan.  He did lots of bad stuff, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hitler's dad died when he was young, though.  So maybe it's all part of a Boys From Brazil plot to create another Hitler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he would.  He'd brag about how he always wanted to be shot at, and of course, if you hadn't gotten in his way, he would have dodged the bullet himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Furthermore, Joe Lieberman fuckenda est. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of curious.  Do you think if you polled Trumpets in Hawaii now, they'd agree they don't deserve statehood and ask Daddy Trump to please forgive them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, for as much as Republicans consider the people living in cities on the coasts "elitist," I've *never* heard a liberal say that a judge from some "fly-over state" shouldn't be able to actually participate in the judicial system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only know that I know nothing, *and* that Trump is incompetent.  That's it.  Just those two things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got banned from /r/conservative for a Futurama quote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, so entirely rational, then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As recently as 1998, the majority of Icelanders believed in elves, so...  https://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2013/10/why-so-many-icelanders-still-believe-in-invisible-elves/280783/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, there are Black Russians.  I don't know of any more similar name, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Whoa, I can see my house on the ICBM GoPro!  ...wait..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dippin' Dots is NOT the ice cream of the future and never will be!  They are liars and charlatans!  Now if you'll excuse me, I have twenty packs of gum to eat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: Hillary Clinton was America's most admired woman 21 times: http://www.gallup.com/poll/200771/obama-bests-trump-admired-man-2016.aspx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that puppy's probably what, eight weeks?  And already flying kamikaze missions?  Crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like Fry!  Like Fry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Trump's just *so* perfect.  However will we find something to criticize?  We might have to wait a whole eight seconds for him to tweet that Obama tried to assassinate him on the campaign trail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How could MC Hammer be in debt?  Have you seen his parachute pants, bud? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the ones with weather control powers who fuck up Republican Conventions for giggles?  Yeah, me too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does 7/11 sell dick pills that are, from what I can tell from the name, made by Chinese apothecaries? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I assure you I had rather be the first man here than the second man in Rome."-Julius Caesar, while passing through a tiny village in the Alps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, I guarantee you *no one* here expects perfection from Trump.  We expect basic competence and we're still disappointed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it makes you feel better, even Rome had some of its best days (the Good Emperors) *after* Caligula and Nero. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Patrician IV, or any of the Tropico or XCOM games (besides Interceptor and UFO Defense)?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/65x5ti/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_w_offers/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just want to recommend this classic book on sea power: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Influence_of_Sea_Power_upon_History </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Imperial_Regalia_of_Japan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do the same, and yet you still disappointed me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, he totally released zero birth certificates and tax records. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confirmed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun way to cheat at chess, if you don't mind a 50% win rate. Start two games, one as white, one as black.  Let the white player in your black game move.  Make his move in your white game, and then what the black player moves, make his move in your black game.  You're now basically a middleman between the other two players, and no matter how good they are, you're guaranteed a win in one of the games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traded Team Indie for Not the Robots with /u/karldreher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It still feels like when you make a save game just to fuck everything up for the achievements.  "Huh, there's an achievement for destroying democracy in 4 years?  Yeah, I can do that." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Engineers are apparently more likely to believe in creationism, too, which is interesting.  http://rationalwiki.org/wiki/Salem_Hypothesis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Open primaries in Texas and he barely won his primary last time.  Vote him out in the primary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Event[0] or Valhalla Hills?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/65x5ti/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_w_offers/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, he *would* be a Trump supporter, wouldn't he?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We predict that at this point, aliens from Tau Ceti notice our flat tax, and, impressed, offer us their advanced alien space-capitalism, dramatically improving GDP growth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cliched? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Thomas Midgley Jr. of US politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A /r/T_D poster who's racist?!  Now I've seen everything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but how often do you go golfing?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I picture him as more of a Goldfinger type, you know, big and orange.  How would Spicey look in an Oddjob outfit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kid had to reach for it, but yeah, it looks like he got it: https://twitter.com/MicahGrimes/status/854009984606228480 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our president is Hugh Laurie's George, Prince of Wales from Blackadder.  Awesome.

https://youtu.be/hEy7xR-eOjg?t=1m32s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the Robots looks good.  If that's good with you, let me know and I'll send the link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His parents were cotton sharecroppers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't fool me.  That's clearly Andy Richter from the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Freedom Bundle Leftovers [W] Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [My IGS Rep page](https://www.reddit.com/r/IGSRep/comments/5wjj8v/saintodhrans_igs_rep_page/)

All games I have are Humble gift links.  I want to get rid of these games.  I'll trade away everything for a good offer.

**Games I Have**

[A Virus Named Tom](http://store.steampowered.com/app/207650/)

[Dangerous High School Girls in Trouble](http://store.steampowered.com/app/27400/)

[Double Fine Adventure Documentary](http://store.steampowered.com/app/402590/)

[Dusty Revenge%3A Co-Op Edition](http://store.steampowered.com/app/252430/)

[Galactic Civilizations I: Ultimate Edition](http://store.steampowered.com/app/214150/)

[Galactic Civilizations II: Ultimate Edition](http://store.steampowered.com/app/202200/)

[JumpJet Rex](http://store.steampowered.com/app/329460/)

[Monster Loves You](http://store.steampowered.com/app/226740/)

[Potatoman Seeks the Troof](http://store.steampowered.com/app/328500/)

[Sins of a Solar Empire: Trinity](http://store.steampowered.com/app/201290/)

[Space Hulk Ascension](http://store.steampowered.com/app/317620/)

[Streamline](http://store.steampowered.com/app/252850/)

[Super Hexagon](http://store.steampowered.com/app/221640/)

[Thirty Flights of Loving](http://store.steampowered.com/app/214700/)

**Games I Want**

Axiom Verge

Nobunaga's Ambition: Sphere of Influence

Galactic Civilizations III

Urban Empire

The Magic Circle

Wasteland 2

Furi

Inside

Transistor

Orwell

Project Highrise

Feel free to offer anything else and I'll see if I like it, but I'm mostly into strategy and management games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For anyone curious about this, Enver Hoxha, dictator of Albania, kidnapped a dentist who looked similar to him and had plastic surgery performed on him to make him look even more similar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that requires that the person paying has a reputation, and if you're known as "the guy who should have been executed but paid his way out of it," you're probably going to get a visit from the executioner soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, you probably worked out your arm a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The day I first had to use the plunger in the women's restroom at the restaurant I worked at was a bad day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shrines really feel like a dungeon was dissected and its individual rooms just spread across the world.  I like that kind of incremental, one-room problem in something like Metroid, where it's more integrated into the world, but it feels less satisfying when it's set off like it is in Breath of the Wild, and the weakness of the Divine Beasts doesn't help that either.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was a good question.  You're asking if a game ever started as an established IP, and then they were like, "This is getting kind of off-track.  Let's rebrand it as an unknown," right?  Just doing some Googling, it looks like Devil May Cry is an example, starting life as Resident Evil 4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember when that tape of Trump bragging about grabbing women by the pussy came out, and Republicans thought the reason people were upset was because he said the word "pussy" and not because he was describing sexual assault?  Context seems to be a big issue with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never heard of that tragedy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teacher, after four minutes of a stripper in his classroom: "Eh, let's see how this plays out..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They just read the story of Onan, where god insta-kills him for pulling out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, but let's say I myself wore a Princess Leia hairstyle, and said it was inspired by Princess Leia.  Would that be false because Hopi women wore it first?  Is it literally impossible to be inspired by anything other than the first instance of a thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.snopes.com/origins-princess-leias-hairstyle/  I mean, this has some pictures of soldaderas with such a hairstyle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, he shouldn't have any stake in his companies anymore because he's the fucking president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's more interesting how recognizable that third one is.  I mean, obviously when people make a Christ depiction, they're drawing off of older ones, but I'm sure most Westerners could guess that's Jesus without any context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/repressedgonewild </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I Can't Believe My President Is So Treasonous!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there anything we can do to address all of the intentional gun deaths?  I mean, that's a lot higher, so it's a problem, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is how the Berlin wall was built.  All nicely on the East German side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying it's terrible that there are flags everywhere and so many ads feel the need to be like, "Hey Texans, this product is big and strong like Texas.  Buy our Texas-like product!"  It's just strange.  

I *am* judging them for having such pride in a state with such a history, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god, Texans love being Texans.  I don't think I had ever seen a state flag that wasn't at a town hall before in my life until I visited Texas.  So many ads have to remind people they're Texans, too.  It's just such weird pandering for a state that left two different countries to keep slaves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, he got corrected on the country, but the reporter didn't know about the cake.  Maybe he forgot the cake, too, and there was just no one around to correct him.  Like, he thought it was chocolate cake and missiles to Iraq, but really it was carrot cake and Syria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna be a massive fucking nerd but if you read Minus, she actually *can* deflect that meteor, and more than that, there's a non-zero chance she's responsible for it in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You little shits, do you know how lucky you are that I voluntarily do this for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Freedom Bundle Leftovers, including A Virus Named Tom, Super Hexagon, Streamline, and others [W] Offers, ideally strategy games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [My IGS Rep page](https://www.reddit.com/r/IGSRep/comments/5wjj8v/saintodhrans_igs_rep_page/)

All games I have are Humble gift links.  I'm really just trying to get rid of them, so I'm not gonna be very cut-throat with these.  I'm willing to trade multiples for anything I want.

**Games I Have**

[A Virus Named Tom](http://store.steampowered.com/app/207650/)

[Dangerous High School Girls in Trouble](http://store.steampowered.com/app/27400/)

[Double Fine Adventure Documentary](http://store.steampowered.com/app/402590/)

[Dusty Revenge%3A Co-Op Edition](http://store.steampowered.com/app/252430/)

[JumpJet Rex](http://store.steampowered.com/app/329460/)

[Monster Loves You](http://store.steampowered.com/app/226740/)

[Potatoman Seeks the Troof](http://store.steampowered.com/app/328500/)

[Streamline](http://store.steampowered.com/app/252850/)

[Super Hexagon](http://store.steampowered.com/app/221640/)

[Team Indie](http://store.steampowered.com/app/302850/)

[Thirty Flights of Loving](http://store.steampowered.com/app/214700/)

**Games I Want**

Axiom Verge

Nobunaga's Ambition: Sphere of Influence

Galactic Civilizations III

Urban Empire

The Magic Circle

Wasteland 2

Furi

Inside

Transistor

Endless Legend

Icey

Europa Universalis 4 DLC

Orwell

Redout

Project Highrise

Feel free to offer anything else and I'll see if I like it, but I'm mostly into strategy and management games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, between the people who are pushing Nazi ideals, and the people calling them Nazis, it's *definitely* the latter who are more disrespectful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds less like a bar and more like a nicer, healthier opium den. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caligula was apparently Trump's role model when it came to filling government positions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idiotic stupid bullshit

EDIT: lol so many downvotes it's worse than I thought </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, communities were working so well that people fucking invented the police force.  Do they not imagine what the world was like before government services were created?  Do they think that life was just so idyllic in 1800s London that Peel was like, "I'm bored.  Let's create modern policing for no reason whatsoever.  I just hate all those smarmy communities coming together and stopping all crime on their own." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
