<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3835</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? Did you reply to the wrong comment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's not a video. But reposting to gain more attention/views/clicks/etc isn't allowed regardless of the type of link. We don't allow reposts within three months, so if your project is still relevant then you can repost then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed - do not submit more than once to gain views. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose it is big, but I meant the giant default-y sort of subs. I wasn't really being specific. Definitely anything with 10m subs though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Requesting /r/holidayHole - lots of spammy submissions which need cleaning up after the only mod deleted their account </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/conspiracy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems fair enough. I've always liked the mods on /r/askReddit. They're the only big subreddit with decent mods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah. What ever happened to that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've removed your post because it's poorly tagged. I didn't want to do this in the past but as every post of yours is poorly tagged, you need to improve your titles. Look at the other posts on the subreddit for reference. Adding every conceivable search term to your title does exactly nothing to gain views and just clutters the text to make it less readable, which explains some of the downvotes you've been getting. Just one [tapping] tag is sufficient to ensure that readers know it has tapping in it. 

As a bit of technical info, the way search works does not rely on exact matches. So if I search for "tapping", it'll show anything with the word "tapping" anywhere in the title. A search for "fast tapping" will return anything with either "fast" or "tapping" in the title. Writing them more than once does not improve your searchability, and adds clutter. The tags are also not special in the search - they're just treated as regular text, the same as the rest of the title. So saying "[tapping] [fast tapping] [agressive tapping] is entirely superfluous; as is saying "[asmr]" etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does a surprising amount of damage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10,000 characters. Some emoji count as two or three chars depending on the emoji, although most are just one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if there are people who have to live in hiding, perhaps literally underground, because they're deaf but they didn't get a permit for it and they're on the run from the law because they're illegally deaf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was 1 month ago; see the link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally love the [Samsung S Voice "listening" sounds](https://youtu.be/axMZ9UqnDN8?t=36s). They're so cheerful :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Haiku] Creative Genius </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 15:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the link. That was fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad it helped you! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had the power to remove one company from existing and give all its assets to charity, which company and charity would it be and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 11:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to know when the servers go down </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep same here - UK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 10:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/UnexpectedReinhardt  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also this is a recent repost. Please search before submitting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the missing leg idea is beside the point; that's not what's being discussed. I assume OP is arguing far more for the termination of incurably diseased and incapacitated babies. A missing leg is a bummer and definitely decreasaes the quality of life, but ultimately they'll be a congniscent human with a full ability to understand the world and develop good relationships. Someone whose disease constricts them to a wheelchair and makes them entirely dependent on 24/7 care for life from their parents is an entirely differnet case. I know someone like that and it's really sad to watch the parents struggle to maintain this teenager who'll never amount to anything, never form proper relationships or understand their surroundings, and will die if left alone for more than a day or two. The extreme effort at maintaining such a life seems wasted in honesty. If it were even remotely possible to cure them down the road then sure, but that's not the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> iOS 3.1 on an iPhone 6S? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, that'll come in really useful!

edit: well ok not *really* useful but it'll save a couple of seconds here and there and I'll appreciate it and think of you 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh I didn't know this one. Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just use F6 :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What keyboard shortcut is incredibly useful but few people know about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stairs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/anticlimax </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Approved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've removed this post because you asked for emails to be left in the comments. Please see the [sticky post](https://www.reddit.com/r/TestFlight/comments/50b6eg/do_not_post_or_ask_for_personal_information/) for details, then edit your post to remove that part, then I'll reapprove your post. Reply to my comment when you're done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the title is completely overkill, not very friendly to read.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 11:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate this idea that they "allow" anyone to do anything! How magnanamous of them. It's not theirs to "allow" and they're being greedy and selfish by consuming so much of the communal space. They're being entitled by taking it back. As others have pointed out they're acting like /r/the_donald. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 11:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask who? The owner of the canvas? Pinging www.reddit.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 11:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well in the rest of the world, invading other people's communities and being selfish and entitled is considered very rude. Don't try to make this about culture when it's really about being dicks. There's no culture you can hide behind to justify being dicks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you *let* it stay do you? That very generous of you. You must feel really good about owning that entire strip of the community's canvas and allowing some poor community the scraps from your table.

You're being the bully in the playground. You're acting like /r/the_donald and ruining the spirit of /place. It's supposed to be fun and inclusive of all communities, not something to be claimed and owned by whoever has the most subscribers. It's everybody's canvas.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a case of being "allies". It's a case of not being a complete arse and selfishly taking up half the fucking canvas with one flag when you should be being inclusive of all communities. 

Your mob behaviour and sense of blind entitlement is reminiscent of like /r/the_donald. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! They really are. 

This is really sad actually. The whole idea of /place is to have a little representation of every corner of the internet on one big canvas showing how great everything is. But destroying other people's communities isn't great. It's selfish and sad. If you want a huge swedish flag which destroys everything else on the image then [here you go](https://www.google.co.uk/search?q=swedish+flag).


Involving everybody and letting every community have their own little corner of the canvas has made me so delighted in the last few days, and watching everybody getting involved and the inclusion and communities has been great fun. But watching the swedes consume everything for their own greed and sense of entitlement is pathetic really. They're spoling a great piece of internet history.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The landlord? How fucking entitled can you get? It's everybody's space, not yours. Especially when you've greedily consumed so much of it already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the swede's canvas. It's everyone's. And the swedes are being very greedy and selfish by consuming so much space. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really sad actually. The whole idea of /place is to have a little representation of every corner of the internet on one big canvas showing how great everything is. But destroying other people's communities isn't great. It's selfish and sad. If you want a huge swedish flag which destroys everything else on the image then [here you go](https://www.google.co.uk/search?q=swedish+flag).

Involving everybody and letting every community have their own little corner of the canvas has made me so delighted in the last few days, and watching everybody getting involved and the inclusion and communities has been great fun. But watching the swedes consume everything for their own greed and sense of entitlement is pathetic really. You're spoling a great piece of internet history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compensation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too greedy? Have you *seen* the size of that swedish flag? It's very selfish to take up so much space. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/place/#x=851 y=74 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sshh it's ok you're safe now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One post per hour, going back for at least 1000 posts (I can't view any further back than that). Probably much longer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Automoderator is being forced to do a slave's work in /r/TheArmory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminder that you can use the bot to link to some popular channels by using double brackets like this:

[[heather feather]]

[[pudding whispers]]

[[massageasmr]]

[[asmr darling]] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meta] This is the end. Say goodbye. To the [Media] and [Article] tags. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a little announcement to say that we're merging two of our required [Flair tags](https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/wiki/index#wiki_tagging_system) into one: the [media] and [article] tags will no longer be used, and the **[journalism]** tag will represent any news, stories, articles etc on the subject of asmr or the community.

The reason for this is that the [media] tag was very frequently mis-used, as people misunderstood its inteded use. In addition, the two previous tags were often confused between each other, and in honesty there was a lot of ambiguity in their definitions. We think [journalism] is much clearer and covers both of the previous definitions.

Hopefully this will clear up any confusion or ambiguity going forwards. The changes are live as of now.

Happy Sunday :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 10:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Junkrat changes? They're already live? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> User on CMV is opposed to sand, has a steep learning curve in the comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed - not a testflight beta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think we should focus on defending. We have limited resources and our corner is being dissolved. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 12:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, we should prioritise pixels that are the closest to the bottom right corner. Mathematically, the priority of each pixel is equal to it's X coordinate plus it's y coordinate.

So, we should focus on re-blueing our corner, starting in the corner and working outwards. So everybody go in and re-blue the closest non-blue pixel to the corner that you see. Summon your alt accounts for extra blue power.

We'll start an organised repair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think we should focus on defending. We have limited resources and our corner is being dissolved. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 12:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, we should prioritise pixels that are the closest to the bottom right corner. Mathematically, the priority of each pixel is equal to it's X coordinate plus it's y coordinate.

So, we should focus on re-blueing our corner, starting in the corner and working outwards. So everybody go in and re-blue the closest non-blue pixel to the corner that you see. Summon your alt accounts for extra blue power.

We'll start an organised repair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 11:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can remove the entire bottom row. It's just entirely black and it'd look fine without it, and you'd save 1,500 pixels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 11:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THAT WAS MY UK FLAG LAST NIGHT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/place/#x=130 y=662

please undo any vandalism you see :)

---

I'm aware that it's not quite right but there's only so much you can do in an 11x9 rectangle

edit: THOSE WHORES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why post the gif at all? Why not just post the whole video?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, well I've removed your post because we can't support plagiarism of content.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you link to videos on YouTube? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Grown ass-man](https://xkcd.com/37/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 11:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [here you go](http://bfy.tw/AxgH) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 10:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D2fSXp6N-vs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The difference between British and American comedy - Stephen Fry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 10:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 10:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Stephen Fry once trying to explain the differences of British and US comedy

[Found this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8k2AbqTBxao), it was interesting. I love Fry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You won't date someone who has good table manners? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they're a smoker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 10:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> scr*wing around 

I hope you mean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 10:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're going to censor the word dick, then rephrase your title so you don't have to write the word dick. But this is the internet, so it's ok to write dick here. I promise I won't tell your mum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't really see - which jpg artifact is his face? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/titlegore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gilfolye's "What do I do" rant from Silicon Valley (spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do I do? System Architecture, Networking and Security. No one in this house can touch me on that. But does anyone appreciate that? While you were busy minoring in gender studies and singing acapella at Sarah Lawrence, I was gaining root access to NSA servers. I was one click away from starting a second Iranian revolution. I prevent cross site scripting. I monitor for DDoS attacks, emergency database rollbacks, and faulty transaction handlings. The internet - heard of it? Transfers half a petabyte of data every minute. Do you have any idea how that happens? All of those Youporn 1's and 0's streaming directly to your shitty little smart phone day after day; every dipshit who shits his pants if he can't get the new dubstep Skrillex remix in under 12 seconds; it's not magic, it's talent and sweat. People like me ensuring your packets get delivered unsniffed. So what do I do? I make sure that one bad config on one key component doesn't bankrupt the entire fucking company. That's what the fuck I do.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. As in either of the two knights that are in a position to take the queen. I don't understand how that could be ambiguous? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone also mentioned this on the forum.

I'm aware that skirmishes and practice range sessions are on a 30-minute timer, but I don't think this is the reason I'm being removed - especially when it says "Not enough players". I'll have to pay more attention to the timer but with the frequency that I'm kicked out of the skirmishes I doubt that the majority of them are cause by the skirmish session expiring. Maybe some are, but not enought to cause this level of frustration with being removed every 1-2 minutes.

You would expect to be removed due to the timer once per 30 minutes of skirmishing (on average), but I'm finding that I'm being removed once per 1-2 minutes on average so the timer doesn't account for all of my removals. I frequently get bounced around to several (2-3+) skirmishes while waiting for one ctf game. I'd much rather just stay in one skirmish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [discussion] Please don't remove me from a skirmish unless I'm joining a game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Queueing for CTF or grouped comp matches can take a while. The skirmish feature is a fantastic way to pass the time, and I love interacting with other players and testing lesser-used heros in a little sandbox like this. It's a great idea and I love the feature.

But there's a problem. Very often I'll be removed from the skirmish and put back in the menu, or removed from the skirmish and placed into a different skirmish. This is infuriating. I'll be happily duelling with another couple of players, or exploring a map's detail, or otherwise passing my time quite happily, when suddenly this free time is interrupted for seemingly no reason and I'm removed from the skirmish without being placed into a match. 

The worst is when it cites "not enough players" as the reason for removing me. I literally don't care in the slightest if I'm the only player there for minutes on end (and this has happened to me!). "Not enough players" should not be a reason to remove me from a skirmish. Firstly, are you telling me that I'm the *only* player in the queue in my region? I seriously doubt that. Secondly, even if I am then so what? Dump me in a skirmish anyway and I'll find something to do on my own. Worst case is I alt-tab out like I would do on the menu anyway so nothing is lost. And thirdly, what about the 4 other players I was just skirmishing with before I was removed? Do they suddenly not count? 

Another reason to be removed from a skirmish is to be placed into a different skirmish. The process of choosing a hero and navigating from the spawn into the map can take a while, and is boring. Interrupting the fun I was having in a skirmish with other players, only to put me on a different map with different other players and have to choose a new hero and walk for maybe a minute across to find the new enemies seems like an excercise in futility to me.

Many times *per day* I've been seconds away from an exciting multikill, or I've just seen an enemy and am about to duel them, when the skirmish ends and I'm removed and suddenly my fun is over. I know it seems like a minor thing but it really is annoying. I can't think of a good reason why I'd have to leave a skirmish to join a different skirmish. Maybe there's a technical reason, but I think this is an issue that should be addressed.

My proposition for a better system would be simple: once I'm in a skirmish, don't remove me unless either I'm inactive or you've found a game for me. I don't care if I'm in with players 2000SR above me. I don't care if I'm in there on my own. It doesn't matter. Just please don't remove me while I'm having fun.

TL;DR: Skirmishes are a fun way to pass time. Stop kicking me out for no reason!

[I cross-posted this at the Blizzard forum here](https://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20753716090#1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for fordmonster (Caution: profile links very NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, that. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ELI5: SEP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, Russ was right. Jared really does fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favourite oddly specific English word is "defenestration". 

To throw someone out of a window

I mean how often can you even use that word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At what point do you change the units you measure his age in? Why say 14 weeks and make me do maths, instead of just saying 4 months? If you want precision you could say 98 days. At how many weeks do you change to months? Or years? Should I be telling people I'm 1,175 weeks old?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh interesting. I just clicked the link you gave and pressed `practise with computer - get hint` and it said Ngxe5.

I just went in again and changed the depth to 25 and Ncxe5 is right. Interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 11:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny, the same website tells me [the best move is Ngxe5](https://i.imgur.com/WxiI7RH.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 10:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or the bishop. Or either knight. She didn't really think this through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 10:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-bqAymxw2_w </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's meant to be a joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About 30 seconds by my count. [Rita at Alton Towers](https://youtu.be/HnhzchMuLzE?t=17s) is even less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And stay down! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sick reference bro
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really think drinks can steal anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/UnexpectedReinhardt  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/UnexpectedReinhardt  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 11:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MWR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 11:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [archive link](https://web.archive.org/web/20170327090229/https://www.reddit.com/r/chicagor4r/comments/60ykkk/18_f4r_looking_to_see_get_out/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed - bad link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll admit it's rather annoying to have like 50% of the videos in my subscription feed being "mouth sounds #274!" when I can't stand them. Hopefully we'll soon pass the mouth sounds meta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand when people say heroes are "slow". All the heroes have the same movement speed except genji and tracer. Am I missing something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do not keep resubmitting your post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed - testflight is for iOS betas using the testflight app only.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 22:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed - last warning. Don't repost the same questions more than once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 22:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed - please don't ask your question more than once. She's very busy and she'll get to you soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 22:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone.

This is a very busy thread and we're doing our best to keep it friendly for everyone so that we can all have fun and enjoy the AMA. 

If you see anything you think should be brought to our attention - spam, distasteful comments etc - please press "report" underneath the comment so that the moderators can review it and take action if necessary. If you're not sure whether something is ok, please err on the side of caution and always report anything you're not sure about - that way we can decide if it shoudl be removed or not.

Have fun! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 22:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> multiple questions are ok but try to keep related questions in one comment. There are hundreds of comments coming in and we don't want to make unnecessary spam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always been surprised that saying "Call an ambulance".. doesn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the announcement is at the top of the subreddit :)

https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/comments/60b19n/meta_announcing_our_next_ama_asmr_darling_will_be/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations. But we have rules in the subreddit and part of those rules is no creepy comments. So if you say something creepy your comment will be removed and you may be banned from participating in future. Giving her a dollar a month doesn't give you immunity from the rules that everybody has to follow in order to make this a nice community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? Why say X:01 if you mean roughly X o'clock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> removed - duplicate submission. I left the other one up as it was tagged more appropriately with [request] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which word? "Cursor"? Firstly, I'm quoting from the github comments, so *I'm* not using anything wrong. Secondly, it's used correctly in the quote.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cursor_(user_interface)

Also, ironically, you're [using that meme wrong](http://knowyourmeme.com/memes/you-keep-using-that-word-i-do-not-think-it-means-what-you-think-it-means) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 11:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully you shouldn't even see anything like that. I'd like to think that there won't be too many creepy comments, but the few that are submitted will hopefully be removed quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recorded a Timeline in the Developer Tools, and a cursory look suggests that the CPU activity comes from rendering the blinking cursor every 500ms.

^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^

and a cursory look suggests 

^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^
a cursory look

^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^^
cursory 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/massage-asmr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed - recent repost. Please search before submitting.

https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/comments/60lyp7/hi_stranger_unintentional/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh is it a meme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand your title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burger *King*? Huh. Sesame seeds.. CICADAS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. Tried restarting client and no difference. Maybe the servers are dying. Might try again in a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean "significant" with its correct definition rather than the casual use. As in, the difference is not negligible. The Air 2 was 6.1mm and the new "iPad" is 7.5mm, which is 23% thicker, which you'll definitely notice holding it in your hands. 

Not that 7.5mm is *bad*, it's just noticably - significantly - thicker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't actually see what's different about it. I [had to check online](http://www.techradar.com/news/new-ipad-97-vs-ipad-air-2) - seems the only difference is the processor bump from the A8X to the A9 (not even the A9X?). And it's now significatnly thicker and slightly heavier. It's cheaper though. Nothing much to talk about really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5k refers to the screen resolution (5120x2880), not the price. Although it's not far off $5k. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition I'd be concerned about the data you're collecting on your users' use of your app. How much of their activity are you monitoring? Are you using secure connections to transfer the data to your servers? How secure is your database storing all of their personal information? 

It looks as if you're trying to take on a lot more than you've given thought to, given your previous answers. You've got good ideas but to execute them properly is going to take years of dedication and work, which doesn't seem plausible for something that you're not making any (visible) money from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the response.

I need to access the methods in the (e.g.) `user` and `file` structs/classes (amongst others) from outside the `Program` class (i.e. from `Main.cs`), so declaring them internally wouldn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. 

I'll definitely look into using the Property as you describe then. Seems like a better solution.

I wasn't entirely sure what a struct was (how it differed from a class) but I read somewhere that it's useful for organising code into sections. However from your explanation it seems that a class might be the better option, so I'll look into updating them to classes too. I do however want to keep the methods organised into groups (whether classes or structs - probably classes going forwards), as they match very closely with the way that the software works and help me organise my code much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of the aim of the project is to create Program as a reusable module so that we can package it up elsewhere, so Program and Main need to be kept separate for future modularity. Thank you for your response though :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your answer. What do you mean by saying I should be using a property for currentSession? Am I not? Maybe I'm confused as to what a "property" is, but I thought it was just a piece of data on the class, which is what currentSession is unless I need to be corrected.

Why would you recommend against using the structs? I initially just had a long list of methods, but I found it much more organised to group them into sections (the sections also directly relate to areas of the software I'm writing the SDK for, so it's much clearer with the methods sectioned off). There are seven such structs, allowing me to group methods into e.g. `myProgram.user` rather than having ~100 very different methods listed under Program.

I noticed that you used _program in your recommendation. That is actually what we used, but I changed it to `myProgram` for what I thought would be clarity in the post as _program and Program may be easily confused. I'll definitely look into the conventions.

Thanks again, what you've said is really helpful.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I was trying to simplify the code as much as posible for the sake of the submission. The if is already in a method exactly as you described, and removing the `static` results in the property being inaccessible from inside the `user` struct.

I've updated my submission to include the login method </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My concern is that this is exactly the same (as far as I can see, unless I've missed something) as creating your own subreddit. For example I use /r/subject3835 (set to private) for my own stuff, but I've seen many content creators who just have their own subreddit, usually set to be the same as their username. How would this be different? They could be the sole moderator or invite friends to be mods, and they could restrict submissions so only they can submit but everyone else can comment. Seems exactly the same to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Program structure help - property in my Class is only accepted as static </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm developing an SDK for work, and I've got a file `Main.cs`, and a file `Program.cs`. `Program.cs` looks something like this:

    namespace SDK_Interface {

        public class Program {

            public user User = new user();
            public file File = new file();

            public static UserSession currentSession = null;

            public struct user {
               //some methods, including accessing currentSession
            }

            public struct file  {
            }
        }
    }

Then `Main.cs` is something like this:

    namespace WPF_SDK{
       public partial class MainWindow : Window {

           Program myProgram = new Program();

           //some methods, including requiring access to myProgram.currentSession 
           //I'm currently accessing Program.currentSession to modify the value in here
           // note that using myProgram isn't allowed. This is the problem.
           // e.g:
           
          private bool login(username, password){
             //some stuff
             if (Program.currentSession != null) { //user isn't already logged in
                  //login stuff
                return true;
             }
       }
    }

I can't seem to find the correct way to be access currentSession. Maybe I'm missing something fundamental here, but I want to be able to access it both from within my user sctruct (e.g. `user.login(username, password){}`) and also from within my `Main.cs` file i.e. by `myProgram.currentSession`. 

It seems that the only way to access it in both places at once is to declare it as static, however my understanding is that this means that if I instantiate my Program class more than once they'll share a value for currentSession, which is not what I want. Currently I'm accessing Program.currentSession  (note that this is not myProgram.currentSession - sorry for the naming), which works with only one instantiation of Program - myProgram - but is not a good solution going forwards.

My question: how do I design this such that currentSession can be accessed both in the user struct and also in Main.cs outside the class?

Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 10:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2nd of April seems like a long way away. Giveaways are usually 24 hours or maybe a couple of days at most.

Anyway, I'd love to win because I accidentally let my 7 update to 10.2 and I've been watching with sad envy as everyone plays with their tweaks on here. I'd gladly swap my device out for an older OS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 09:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not the AMA. Questions will be taken on Friday in the AMA thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is one not enough?

https://www.reddit.com/r/Overwatch/comments/60i9d6/orisa_ptr_visual_bug_shooting_through_cars_and/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 09:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an interesting idea. I quite like the feeling of it being a live event and buzzing with lots of people and activity. I think if we post it the night before people might just ask their question and leave and it'd feel less "live" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do not resubmit things after I've removed them. I watched the video before removing it and as the focus is around music, which we don't allow, it was removed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nano boast

^^^^^I'm ^^^^^really ^^^^^good ^^^^^at ^^^^^Overwatch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  afai've

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll be moderating the thread very closely, as we have with all AMAs so far, and removing any inappropriate comments or questions as they come in. She's not going to be answering very personal questions so we'll remove anything that's creepy, too personal, or otherwise inappropriate. This subreddit is a safe place and we do our best to mitigate trolling and creepiness. As always community reports help greatly with this, but we'll be moderating the AMA thread especially closely and thoroughly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meta] Announcing our next AMA - ASMR Darling will be answering your questions on Friday 24th March at 5PM EST // 2PM Pacific // 9PM GMT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the success of our last few AMAs, we're going to try to arrange around one per month for the rest of this year. 

Please save your questions for the AMA thread, which will be posted at the above time on the 24th. As usual it'll stay up for a few days to allow anyone who can't make the time a chance to review her answers afterwards. She'll be answering questions for a few hours with some breaks, and you can ask her anything at all, be it about ASMR or anything else. 

[ASMR Darling Youtube](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCikebqFWoT3QC9axUbXCPYw)

[Twitter](https://twitter.com/asmrDarling)

[Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/ASMR-Darling...)

[Instagram](https://www.instagram.com/asmrdarling/)

Hope to see you there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can still share the link, just don't ask for "help", "upvotes", or imply anything similar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 10:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another month, another comment lost in the sea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 10:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/missjofai/status/840881913942429696

As per [the sticky on the front page](https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/comments/5zq6g7/meta_a_reminder_about_vote_manipulation_including), do not ask for upvotes externally. This is a friendly reminder but we're going to start issuing bans going forwards as this is a very strict site-wide rule. Please read the sticky for info.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 10:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed and warning issued - do not ask for upvotes on twitter. This is strictly against site-wide rules. [See the sticky.](https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/comments/5zq6g7/meta_a_reminder_about_vote_manipulation_including) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: https://www.reddit.com/r/PrequelMemes/comments/5zyorq/are_ya_ready_younglings/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are you ready younglings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you zoom right in you can see my edit lines. Sorry :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop feeding the troll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT: feeding of the trolliest troll ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I guess it could. I assumed it meant when you're eating one. Maybe we'll never know. ^^^except ^^^your ^^^explanation ^^^seems ^^^more ^^^likely ^^^now ^^^that ^^^I ^^^think ^^^about ^^^it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grammar: the difference between knowing your shit, and knowing you're shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can there be two posts about salad *next to each other* on the front page of a non-salad-related subreddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since nobody else asked: why is the water pink? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not that you're gay

You're trying to make him out to be a homophobe. He's making good points and you're making it all about your sexuality. As people are trying to point out, this has nothing to do with sexuality. Some puppies and babies and girls and boys are cute (amongst other cute things) regardless of whether you're sexually attracted to them. I'm a straight guy but I've thought some guys are cute. It's more of a personality trait than a physical trait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP You have no idea about the can of worms you've just opened. Brace yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a submission a couple of years ago pointing out that Apple and Google disagree on the length of a year, and a few people noticed the battery level and that's all I ever heard about.

https://i.imgur.com/IQt57mm.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well then the F should be capitalised </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See? Was that so hard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, you totally can't convey tone through text. Gotcha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that. But I still think that it's much better to phrase something in a way that's obviously not serious than to have to label it. The label kills any humour it has, so the joke/point just fails straight away. 

To be honest, I think this is an American issue. The yanks have never been great at sarcasm, and the Brits are known for being incredibly sarcastic all the time, and it's sort of true. There's a joke in /r/UnitedKingdom that nobody ever writes /s because it's never needed: nobody has any trouble distinguishing what's sarcasm and what isn't. The less finely-tuned ear of other nations might have more difficulty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but people should recognise that what they're writing could be ambiguous and write it in a clear way to avoid confusion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not standard reddiquette. It's just a symbol of poorly written jokes. If someone can't tell wheteher or not you're being sarcastic without you having to literally label it with "(this is sarcasm by the way don't worry)" then you've written the comment very wrong. If you're too lazy to bother trying to signal that you're being sarcastic  then I'm too lazy to spend hours pondering whether or not you're joking and assume that you're not.

People who use /s are just lazy writers.

(this isn't sarcasm by the way, but I'm sure you could tell that already because I wrote it in such a way to signal that without this unnecessary label) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meta] A reminder about Vote Manipulation, including off-reddit requests for upvotes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've noticed an increasing trend of voting manipulation recently, both on reddit and off. This can involve using alt accounts to upvote your own submissions, asking for upvotes from friends or on social media, or otherwise gaining upvotes by unfair means to cheat the submission ranking system. 

This is strictly against site-wide rules, and is grounds for a reddit-wide ban on both your reddit account and links to your youtube channel. Linking to the reddit post externally for the purpose of the discussion/comments is ok, but asking for - or implying you'd like - votes is not.

From the [reddit site-wide rules](https://reddit.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/articles/205192985):

Vote manipulation is against the Reddit rules, whether it is manual, programmatic, or otherwise. Some common forms of vote cheating are:

 * Using multiple accounts, voting services, or any other software to increase or decrease vote scores.
 * Asking people to vote up or down certain posts, either on Reddit itself or through social networks,  messaging, etc. for personal gain.
 * Forming or joining a group that votes together, either on a specific post, a user's posts, posts from a domain, etc.

Cheating or attempting to manipulate voting will result in your account being banned. Don't do it.

We've given out a few warnings to various content creators who have engaged in such behaviour. After this reminder post we expect this manipulation to stop, so we'll be more firm with subreddit and channel bans following any infringements going forwards, whether or not the user has received a warning before.

As always, community reports help us greatly with this. If you see someone asking for upvotes on a reddit submission please report it immediately. Similarly, if you have good reason to believe a submission is gaining unfair or disingenuous upvotes, please similarly report these. 

We also recognise that there's a sad problem with people being downvoted against our subreddit guidelines, which has been [discussed at length](/r/asmr/wiki/downvotes) and it's a shame we can't do anything about it. However this does not give users the right to attempt to unfairly gain upvotes through their own means.

We don't like having to make posts like this, but it's a shame that a minority feel the need to try to gain an unfair advantage. 

---

There's some lighter and more cheerful news to announce soon, so stay tuned for the announcement post on Sunday afternoon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dad makes a VR ride for his daughter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 - MUM - 1:37.294

2 - DAD - DNF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Try ending your comments with a /s to indicate sarcasm.

Please, don't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you play a creator's video, does it count as a view on YouTube? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a few channels which do things similar to this, so you'd probably have to find some way to make yourself stand out from those otherwise I doubt you'll get many views. And you'll have to consider the cost of buying each game , which could be 100s a month depending on which ones and how many you play. 

I think it could be a great channel, but you'd have to work very hard to distinguish yourself from other similar channels and build an audience based on what makes your channel unique and different from the rest. Gaming ASMR is a niche within a niche so it'll be very difficult to grow quickly. Also expect a lot of haters, as ASMR and gaming communities are known particularly for their trolls etc.

Good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Myke? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [L] request - this dog going down a slide forever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/FwbRKxL.gifv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recognise this removal! I remember writing it ;)

https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/comments/5zk5z8/lascia_andare_desapega_la_prova_che_una_vita_non/deyouo0/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request - this dog going down a slide forever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If everyone's hyping and expecting a fantastic game, they can only be disappointed, even if the game is *good* but not *incredible* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/comments/3q0bl3/meta_rasmr_discord_server_a_howto_introduction/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [19](https://gifsound.com/?gifv=qYuCUGb v=feA64wXhbjo s=19) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> March the 14th be with you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of those stupid ones that could be 1000 different answers. It's not a riddle.

 A man was walking down the street, when suddenly he looked up. Why did he look up?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any chance you could share the file? It's been taken down, as predicted, and I didn't get to see it :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Please do not rapidly submit content from a single channel. This is seen as spam and is grounds for a subreddit ban, and can get your youtube channel blocked from having its content submitted to reddit.

* The three submissions you linked to today are not asmr; they are either music, which is not allowed to avoid confusion with frisson (see /r/frisson), or they are relaxation tracks, which although can be nice are also not asmr. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [See the discussions](https://www.reddit.com/r/Tinder/comments/5z9qrg/saucy_start_to_this_conversation/dex0iec/). They manage to work it out between them. It's actually quite interesting.

And if you zoom right in you can just about make out my edit lines. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See full discussion:

Has a good explanation:

https://www.reddit.com/r/ios/comments/3nmdmh/apple_and_google_disagree_about_the_length_of_a/

Has more comments:
https://www.reddit.com/r/google/comments/3nmdhx/google_and_apple_disagree_about_the_length_of_a/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a submission a couple of years ago pointing out that Apple and Google disagree on the length of a year, and a few people noticed the battery level and that's all I ever heard about.

https://i.imgur.com/IQt57mm.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dat bitrate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got into programming by playing with Warcraft lll's World Editor. I started with teaching myself very simple if's and worked my way up. That was the sole reason I took CS in college, then university. And now I'm a programmer as my job. So, thanks, I suppose. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh the bot can only detect the same video being submitted multiple times. since this was technically two different videos (i.e. two youtube links, even if the content was identical) it wouldn't have detected the repost.

But yeah you're right, I won't remove the duplicate this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it was it would have been automatically removed. The bot detects and removes reposts of content submitted within the last 3 months.

Do you have a link to the previous submission so I can manually review it? The bots do make very rare mistakes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought that the name "BeatsX" is a terrible, terrible, but hilarious name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When was this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
