<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2728</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the hell do you manage? Who are you zac efron </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People of reddit, how many people have you slept with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting over 50 deaths because of hackers in mw2 :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad they go slapped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorote player on the raptors, period. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wow. I thought game one was bad...this is straight fucking embarassing its like the bucks are playing an elementary shool basketball team. I have no words, this is fucking disgusting and embarassing. I hope i get proved wrong, but u doubt it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have made like 2 fg lol... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right, im extremely interested in other peoples experiences and situations. I hope to find something a broke university student such as myself can pursue. Been thinking about creating a website or maybe an app, just waiting for that spark for that original idea. That being said my family has nothing to worry bout money wise, my dad owns a couple successful businesses, one being very successful and has also invested in many solid stocks/companies etc. However, thats him... thats his money and his life, i would never be able to ask for his money to invest nor would he give me the money. Perhaps after i get a degree that will change, but for now im just looking for something. Im hungry for wealth and success, and i am more than open to any mentors or opportunities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im also interested in this, im in my first year of university and things arent going so well, ive never been the best student and i dont think i ever will. I just wanna look for ways to build my income. Not saying im gonna drop out of university, but i think having a steady/increasing flow of income will make me more motivated to graduate allowing me to pursue that venture as soon as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knew a guy from another highshool who was basically passed out drunk, eyes barely open. Girl goes in the room grabs is dick and anals herself with it. People were laughing about and attempting to take videos. Imagine if it was the other way around... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Rich people of reddit, how did you do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn... you beat me to it :( KENNY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Favorite: being able to be so close with someone and really be who your truly are with them and being able to talk about anything

Least favorite: having to change your schedule for them, sometimes you dont feel like being with someone, when you want to go home but they keep begging u to stay like a child, arguments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who do you sing it about though?!?! Itll be like, "happy birthday dear...ummm" bang your dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You have a gun pointed at your head, you must recite a song perfectly without making a mistake or you will be shot dead, what song do you choose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raptors defence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats what i was thinking, why do they always leave derozan out hes one of the the elite scorers in the league deserves at least second or third team </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Derozan already has his own kobes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dats ibakaaaaa hes a no long talkaaaaa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, people are that careless with money in the UK? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 07:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have forced cleveland to game 6 last year is that not enough considering we were starting fucking Scola and jonas was injured/coming off an injury? This year our teams is much stroger dont judge us after one game, you should be fucking supporting a fellow toronto team... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 07:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The raptors dropped one game of the series...they played bad, this is true. But, we are definitely contenders, they could possibly make it to the ECF and even the finals. Dont judge the raptors on the only game you have ever seen them play i  your life because obviously if you have seen them play before u wouldnt say suh a stupid fucking thing. 

Lol, not to come off as condescending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shouldve gone to bed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive been watching since the chris bosh days, im obviously overreacting, but im still fucking pissed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who shoots 17% and scores like 25 in the second half... fuck me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never seen a more embarrassing display of basketball in my life. Worst game ive ever watched. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im sorry you had to see that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> L </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But not like a Kidd before christmas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
