<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3901</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 12:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sehr schn!

Ich selbst lebe in Berlin und habe mich auf https://toot.berlin registriert, aber je mehr lokale Instanzen desto besser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 12:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wunderbar, vielen Dank. Da ich in Berlin lebe, habe ich mich dort angemeldet. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An external 1080 Ti can quadruple a MacBook Pro's graphics power | Are there any similar reliable tests for the XPS 15 9560? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderful! :) Do you intend to keep it Linux/BeLUG-centric or do you plan to use a broader and more inclusive name, like *mastodon.berlin*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Mastodon.social is an open-source Twitter competitor thats growing like crazy](https://www.theverge.com/2017/4/4/15177856/mastodon-social-network-twitter-clone)**

On https://instances.mastodon.xyz I can see a bunch of instances with weird sounding names but if someone were willing and able to host an instance with a clean name like *mastodon.berlin* or something like that, that'd be sweet.

Any Mastodon users here? If so, what's your experience with it? I only just came across it and I'm intrigued. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a Berlin instance/server of the open source social network Mastodon yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deinem Flair nach zu urteilen, wrst Du womglich der richtige **[hierfr](https://www.reddit.com/r/europe/comments/661qbm/anyone_interested_in_hosting_a_european_server/)**? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *[journalists mostly](https://www.reddit.com/r/selfhosted/comments/63g3lb/mastodonsocial_is_an_opensource_twitter/dfugtps/?context=10000)* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Mastodon.social is an open-source Twitter competitor thats growing like crazy](https://www.theverge.com/2017/4/4/15177856/mastodon-social-network-twitter-clone)**

On https://instances.mastodon.xyz I can see a bunch of instances with weird sounding names but if someone were willing and able to host an instance with a clean name like *mastodon.eu* or something like that, that'd be sweet.

Any Mastodon users here? If so, what's your experience with it? I only just came across it and I'm intrigued. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone interested in hosting a European server for the Open Source Social Network Mastodon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Es gibt bergreifende Kommunikation - man muss nur die jeweilige Instanz angeben, wenn man jemanden aus einer anderen Instanz sucht oder kontaktiert.

Also z.B. wenn ich als *subject3901* in der *mastoton.fi* Instanz registriert bin, lautet mein kompletter Handle **subject3901@mastoton.fi**.

Alle anderen user auf der *mastoton.fi* Instanz kann ich direkt ohne Instanzadresse finden - nur wenn Du z.B. als *64738362* auf der Instanz *kinky.business* registriert bist, muss ich **64738362@kinky.business** angeben, um Dich zu finden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 10:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Mastodon.social is an open-source Twitter competitor thats growing like crazy
](https://www.theverge.com/2017/4/4/15177856/mastodon-social-network-twitter-clone)**

Auf https://instances.mastodon.xyz/ sehe ich allerhand Instanzen. Wre cool, einen deutschen Server zu haben.

Nutzt hier irgendjemand Mastodon und wenn ja, was ist Eure Erfahrung damit? Bin gerade erst darauf gestoen und finde den Ansatz interessant. Erinnert mich etwas an das leider gescheiterte Diaspora*-Projekt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gibt es einen deutschen Server fr das Open Source Social Network Mastodon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 10:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 10:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an amazing shot.

What are the chances that the falcon would land right there in the background in the narrow field of view of such a long lens shot?

The cameraman must have felt like winning the lottery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tarifverhandlungen: Elektroautobauer Tesla droht Streik in Deutschland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 06:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kurzgesagt - Is the European Union Worth It Or Should We End It? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an explanation for personal reasons to do something or not to do something (like boycotting a company) even though one's own singular actions of course don't change the big picture all by themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 09:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *"You can resolve to live your life with integrity. Let your credo be this: Let the lie come into the world, let it even triumph. But not through me."*

 Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 11:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich bin kein Programmierer. Meiner Ansicht nach werden in Zukunft mehr und mehr Berufe zumindest grundlegende Programmierkenntnisee erfordern - nicht nur reine *Softwareentwicklung*-Jobs.

Ich selbst arbeite in Film und Animation. Vor ein paar Jahren noch brauchte man dafr keine Programmierkenntnisse - selbst in 3D-Grafik. Inzwischen wird es aber zunehmend schwieriger, ganz ohne zumindest grundlegende Scripting-Kenntnisse auszukommen, um repetitive Aufgaben automatisieren zu knnen.

Ein 3D-Grafiker/*VFX Artist* ohne Scripting-Kenntnisse fllt zunehmend im Wettbewerb mit Kollegen *mit* solchen Kenntnissen zurck.

Mein Bruder ist Biochemiker und auch er hat im Studium Programmieren gelernt, um gewisse Probleme lsen und zeitaufwndige aber repetitive Aufgaben automatisieren zu knnen.  

Genauso wie nicht nur Schriftsteller lesen und schreiben knnen mssen, so werden knftig auch nicht nur Softwareentwickler programmieren knnen mssen.

Ist meine persnliche Einschtzung basierend auf den Entwicklungen, die ich sehe. YMMV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 13:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich glaube, dass der Vergleich nicht ganz verkehrt ist.

Programmieren scheint mir im 21. Jahrhundert durchaus vergleichbar mit Lesen und Schreiben im 19./20. Jahrhundert zu sein.

Man konnte Anfang des 19. und 20. Jahrhunderts durchaus noch einen Beruf ausben und einen Lebensunterhalt verdienen, ohne (gut) lesen und schreiben zu knnen, aber der Druck stieg mit der Zeit mageblich an und im Laufe des Jahrhunderts wurde es praktisch unmglich, als Analphabet in der Gesellschaft zu funktionieren.

Eine hnliche Entwicklung sehe ich im Bereich Coding. Wrde mich nicht wundern, wenn im Laufe des nchsten Jahrzehnte der Druck, Code zu verstehen, genauso zu einem grundstzlichen und als selbstverstndlich erachtetem Allgemeinbildungskriterium wird.

Ich merke schon heute den immensen Druck, programmieren zu knnen, in meinem beruflichen Feld. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 12:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the mental model of *'myself'* and *'who am I'* isn't very helpful. It leads to the same confusions you describe.

The Buddhist **[*no self* or Anatta](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anatta)** model appears much more helpful to me.

A related short essay that I keep recommending to people is this: **[Keep Your Identity Small](http://www.paulgraham.com/identity.html)**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ZEIT | Wer nicht programmieren kann, ist ein Analphabet, heit es. Unser Autor hielt das fr bertrieben. Bis er selbst coden lernte. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 12:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Europas fatale Abhngigkeit von Microsoft </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 10:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 09:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The HDR10 spec is a bit fluid. They basically want to see the ability to hit 10-bit color, DCI-P3 color space, and some degree of higher peak brightness (1,000 nits target, 4,000 nits the maximum currently in the spec).

According to https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/High-dynamic-range_video#HDR10 they specify not only DCI-P3 but **[the larger Rec.2020 space](http://www.heavyoptical.com.hk/images/DMColorRec2020_s.jpg)**.

Since the LG is only 95% DCI-P3 it appears to me that it's quite far from actual HDR10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 09:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Does understanding that emotions are constructed help us control them?**

Its never going to be the case that its effortless and never the case that you can snap your fingers and just change how you feel.

But learning new emotions words is good because you can learn to feel more subtle emotions, and that makes you better at regulating your emotions. For example, you can learn to distinguish between distress and discomfort. This is partly why mindfulness meditation is so useful to people who have chronic pain  it lets you separate out the physical discomfort from the distress.

I think understanding how emotions are constructed widens the horizon of control. You realize that if your brain is using your past to construct your present, you can invest energy in the present to cultivate new experiences that then become the seeds for your future. You can cultivate or curate experiences in the now and then they become, if you practice them, they become automated enough that your brain will automatically construct them in the future.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Its not true that we all feel the same things, that anyone can read other peoples faces, and its not true that emotions are things that happen to us." | Neuroscientist Lisa Feldman Barrett explains how emotions are made </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 09:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got a link to the specifications of HDR10+?

I don't see it listed on https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/High-dynamic-range_video#HDR10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking to buy a good and affordable UHD HDR10 monitor (it's for professional use, so affordable means not significantly over $1000 and preferably under that) but I'd much rather wait than buy some sort of half-arsed *HDR10 compatible* (which seems to be the new *HD ready* if I believe top comments **[here](https://www.reddit.com/r/Monitors/comments/6004oj/lgs_32_4k_hdr_monitor_will_be_available_328_for/df2gfp5/)**) display.

Question: Does this monitor meet the full HDR10 specifications? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LG 32UD99-W 31.5" 16:9 HDR10 FreeSync IPS Monitor 32UD99-W | Can someone tell me if this is "true/full" HDR10 or another half-arsed HDR10 "compatible" thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[All Art Is Propaganda](https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/51tKNaIXsKL._SX323_BO1,204,203,200_.jpg)**

The only question is, for what?

Sense8 is propaganda for empathy, connection and diversity. Doesn't sound too bad in my book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mindfulness is a hot commodity these days. The market around meditation and mental well-being has, in recent years, ballooned to more than $1 billion, with countless websites, YouTube series, mobile apps, and subscription services existing on top of your traditional in-person classes and studio memberships.

This opening paragraph immediately puts me off but I'd rather not be prejudiced. Has anyone used *Sway* and if so, what was your experience?

Thoughts on this technology? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sway embraces the contradiction of meditating with your smartphone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *There is no such thing as bad publicity.*

Pepsis day-over-day social mentions increased by over 7,300% between April 3rd and 4th as social reacted to the ad.

 https://www.brandwatch.com/blog/react-kendall-jenner-pepsi-ad/

21000%+ increase in mentions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is **[Dell Command Update](http://www.dell.com/support/home/us/en/04/Drivers/DriversDetails?driverId=FXD2R fileId=3659167175 osCode=WT64A productCode=xps-15-9560-laptop languageCode=en categoryId=SM)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Die Mehrheit der Bundesbrger (55 Prozent) befrwortet unterdessen nach einer reprsentativen Umfrage die Energiewende. Allerdings halten 63 Prozent der Befragten die Kosten dafr fr zu hoch. Die Hauptkosten sollten nach Meinung von 67 Prozent in erster Linie ber den Energieverbrauch finanziert werden. "Wer viel Energie verbraucht, der soll auch einen hheren Anteil an den Kosten der Energiewende tragen."

Kann mir das jemand erklren? Die Leute beschweren sich, dass die Kosten der Energiewende zu hoch seien - damit nehme ich an, sie meinen die Strompreise?

Aber dann wollen sie, dass die Kosten an den Energeverbrauch gekoppelt wird (was ja auch Sinn macht)... d.h., hhere Stromkosten fr hheren Verbrauch. Passt dann doch so?

Oder verstehe ich da jetzt etwas falsch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Msste man austesten, aber normalerweise kann man auswhlen, ob Photos automatisch auf Google Photos hochgeladen werden oder nicht. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Google PhotoScan](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MEyDt0DNjWU)** sieht wie dafr gemacht aus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, thanks. However, I don't see a difference in the User Preferences after launching Blender with either GPU:

**[It still reads GeForce GTX 1050 (Display)](https://i.imgur.com/2Ca6BdN.jpg)**, suggesting that it renders the UI etc. with the NVIDIA card as well.

What I want is to unburden the NVIDIA card from having to draw the UI and let the Intel card do that, so that the NVIDIA card can be utilised fully during rendering without having to work on refreshing the UI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 16:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on Windows 10 and not seeing an option like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 16:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, right click where? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bing oder Gnther Oettinger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 13:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 13:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2018 wenn Ubuntu offiziell auf GNOME umsteigt. Pass blo auf! ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 13:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Die steigen nicht *wirklich* wieder auf Windows um, oder?

Ist das schon beschlossene Sache? Das ist in etwa so intelligent wie in den USA Umweltschutzauflagen rckgngig zu machen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On a laptop with an Intel GPU and an NVIDIA GPU, how can I make Blender use the Intel for display and the NVIDIA for rendering? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 10:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't seem to find any settings to make Blender use the Intel for display and the NVIDIA for rendering.

Currently my User Preferences  System under *Cycles Compute Device* reads **GeForce GTX 1050 (Display)**.

How can I make it use the Intel GPU for display and reserve the NVIDIA for rendering only? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 10:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shouldn't it go up to 3.8 GHz? I have the i7 version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is it that my XPS 15 9560 maxes out at 1.89 GHz during Intel XTU CPU stress test while on the Ultra Performance profile? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 10:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 09:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's worth it for the 4K display with wider gamut but I turned the touch functionality off. Don't want touch on a laptop.

If there was a matte non-touch 4K option I'd have gone for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 09:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you guys keep your XPS 15 9560 up to date most efficiently and correctly? Is there a fix to this? It's quite annoying and feels amateurish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dell Command Update is such a pain - it keeps finding the exact same update for my XPS 15 9560, installs it, claims the install to be successful, yet finds the same update to install again. Any fix? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 09:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 10:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Habe Deinen Kommentar jetzt **[drei Mal gelesen](http://gph.is/2fBr6vh)** und kann ihn noch immer nicht ganz nachvollziehen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keine Ahnung, was das "NUTS" soll.

Fand die Infographic nur cool.

Bevlkerungsrckgang, v.a. global, ist durchaus wnschenswert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deutschlands Bevlkerungsrckgang </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 11:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed, I haven't had a TV in 13 years either. ;P

(However, I do have a nice projector setup) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a German without a Facebook account and I feel as if *everyone* else is using Facebook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using Ubuntu GNOME.

What I meant is that I'll be returning to main Ubuntu again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this isn't a joke I'm going to start using Ubuntu again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 09:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blender Cloud is definitely worth the subscription. Tons of more resources on there as well, all included. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 09:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apart from the fact that whether or not something is an advert has nothing to do with whether the thing it promotes costs money or not, is there a problem with that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who said it's free? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blender Motion Graphics course - now on cloud.blender.org/training </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blender Motion Graphics course - now on cloud.blender.org/training </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blender Motion Graphics course - now on cloud.blender.org/training </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blender Motion Graphics course - now on cloud.blender.org/training </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wir sind Personalausweisinhaber bei Grokonzernen? Klingt als wren wir schon in **[Snow Crash](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Snow_Crash)**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Da hast Du Recht - ich bin leider *definitiv* nicht Teil dieses reichen "wir". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
