<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6446</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recovery sub reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 14:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 00:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude what the fuck...I feel high lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 23:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I finally feel a little calmer but I think its because iv gone for about 30 something hours or so without sleep I actually feel calmer than I have in quite a while </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 23:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel better now it just stopped randomly...il chalk that one up to hormones lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 12:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thinks mainly because, when I was diagnosed my doctor tested about 4 different medications, in atleast 3 different doses on me, over the course of less than a year. I looked at my medical record and it was actually pretty scary even just reading it. Stuff like not seeming to be myself anymore sleeping constantly and then staying up days at a time and having violent outbursts. I dont remember any of this (I think I have repressed alot of memorys because of things unrelated to this ordeal) So my parents basically watched me get treated like a lab rat. I was really young it probably would not have seemed so scary if I had been older....anyway I think everyone in my family, especially my mom, was pretty traumatised by the whole thing and so they just never talked about it.

My mom always helped me so much that I performed pretty great in school, and so she sort of made up for the lack of medication. I know the whole thing is weird, but I also know that if I had any excuse to fail I would take it and say see look I told you I was a failure!   so I also think she was trying to prevent that too. it actually made me feel good in the end to find out that even with ADHD and dyslexia I made all As. 

I've always felt inadequate and stupid but its all in my head (so they tell me ;) i will use any justification I can to call myself stupid  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 02:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to sound weird, but I went up until my senior year of highschool not knowing I was dyslexic or that I had ADHD. 
The weird part is my mother knew...I was diagnosed in the 4th grade, and she didn't tell me until after highschool, (sounds bad but there was a good reason). So I just kinda thought I was stupid... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
