<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject845</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Rant] The end of my first love: a one sided relationship *Warning: very long ;)* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 07:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been 10 days since the relationship officially ended. We met when I was a high school freshman and he was a sophomore. Me being a complete tomboy and only having friendships with guys never had a real crush before. When I saw him my first thought was, "Wow, he's really cute. "WTF WAS I THINKING? I NEVER THOUGHT ABOUT GUYS THAT WAY." I was the one that made fun of all my friends who obsessed over boys. I wasn't going to be that girl.

I failed. Later that night I friended him on Facebook. He accepted and we constantly chatted for weeks and weeks. I didn't like him at the time. His good friend told me he liked me and that absolutely shocked me. It was the first time I knew of a guy liking me. Naturally, I started liking him back. Once I got the balls to do something about my feelings, it was too late. He stopped liking me and got a girlfriend. She was tall and cute. I fucking hated that bitch.

We stayed good friends, though. I introduced him to a lot of people including my best guy friend (a huge mistake since this friend of mine introduce him to his next girlfriend). He eventually broke up with his girlfriend and I had high hopes for myself, but refused to let anyone know that I still liked him, including he, himself. He jokingly asked me out constantly to which I obviously responded, "no, fuck off" even though I liked him. He continued flirting with me.

The summer of my sophomore year, everything changed. This boy changed me. We went to see Guardians of the Galaxy (I know, super romantic) along with another guy friend. My crush and I ended up cuddling and he ended up feeling me up amongst other things (yes, the other friend was sitting next to us in the theater, BUT HE WAS WATCHING THE MOVIE AND WAS NOT PAYING ATTENTION TO US). This was, again, a first for me. 

Two days later he asked another girl out. **Two fucking days after he took advantage of me.** All of my friends were so happy for the two of them. She was "pretty, nice and all around perfect." I was beyond depressed.

It was hard being in the same friend group as the two of them and **extremely hard** ignoring the boy when he sent me snapchats jokingly flirting with me while in a relationship. A little over a month after they got together, I was asked out by one of my best friends. I accepted. We lasted for 3 months until I ended things due to me still having feelings for this other boy and failing to put in effort into the relationship.

One night my crush and I were messaging and he told me that he was thinking of breaking up with this girl. I was confused. He said she was too immature for him and wanted to fuck around with other girls. I should've ended the conversation there, but I didn't. I was dumb and continued talking to him. After all, he was my good friend.

I invited him to my sister's engagement party. He told me how pretty I looked and complimented me over and over. Later after the party, we all went to my friend's house and watched a movie. During the movie, the boy sat me on his lap, unzipped the back of my dress and gave me a back massage. Yes, he still had a girlfriend. Yes, I'm a fucking idiot and a bitch.

The night they broke up, he came over to my house to tutor me in math. He wasn't really helpful due to his tears smudging the paper and him not concentrating at all. I decided that we should just stop with math and go play some video games. After 20 minutes his ride came. Before walking him to the door, he kissed me. He left.

He messaged me immediately after saying that I can't tell a soul. I told him I wouldn't, which was complete bullshit. He told me he wasn't ready for a girlfriend yet, but wanted to be FWB. I freaked out at him and refused. He kept insisting. I stopped talking to him. 

One night I got stuck at his house with a bunch of my friends. He and I were still fighting. He decided to be funny and had us watch Guardians of the Galaxy. All of my friends knew what happened the night we saw it in theaters and thought it was hilarious that he did this. I was on the verge of tears. I tried avoiding and ignoring him for the rest of the night, but he came under my blanket on the floor and apologized. I forgave him and we started making out under the blanket. Once everyone fell asleep, he took me to his garage, laid me down on his workout bench, and started feeling me up ~~and eventually fingering me~~. Another first. Afterward, he asked me to give him a blowjob. I refused.

The day after, he was pissed at me for not sucking his dick. He complained about his blue balls and how much pain he was in. I felt terrible. He said he regretted doing what we did in his garage and that I can't tell anyone. I was so hurt. I loved him.

I found out that my crush was talking to our guy friends about getting back together with his ex-girlfriend and how he never stopped loving her. I was distraught. I realized I was completely taken advantage of. I spent the next week crying in bed. My friends came to visit me and bought be a stuffed sheep. I named it after this guy, but his name spelled backward. He saw my snapchat story of my stuffed sheep and asked who got it for me. I told him my friends and he was pissed. He explained that he was having a hard time too, "being in love with two girls at the same time."

Eventually, he and his ex got back together. She never really found out the truth and is still with the asshole today. After months of pain and ignoring him, I decided to "forgive him" and be friends with him for the sake of my friends and my current boyfriend.

10 days ago, the day after my 4 month anniversary with my boyfriend, I noticed that this guy unfriended me. I confronted him about it. He said he wanted to end our friendship and cut all contact. I didn't understand why; I still don't really understand. At first I was so hurt but eventually accepted it. Yes, I lost my friend of 4 years, but he wasn't truly my friend. Yes, we had great times together, but he also hurt me so many times.

It's still hard because my current boyfriend is friends with him and hangs out with him all the time despite knowing our history. I'm nervous to visit my boyfriend at his college since he spends so much time with him, but I know my boyfriend loves me, will protect me and will always be on my side. I love him so much and can't believe I ever liked this other asshole.

**Thanks for reading my rant.**

EDIT: Douche and girlfriend officially broke up. She dumped him. 

EDIT EDIT: My boyfriend dumped me and is an asshole

EDIT EDIT EDIT: I'm currently with my new boyfriend and he's the love of my life. Best thing that has ever happened to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a 17 year old that looks 12. Roast me! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 05:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When your legs don't work like they used to before... (My baby, Max) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 06:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 05:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I love you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL it's not fun when your friends find your reddit account. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 06:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does my human put the best food in the "garbage" and get mad when I eat it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 02:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 06:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THEY TOOK MY DREAM JOB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
