<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5127</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 23:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn! You beat me to it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snow+fog+cemetery= gorgeous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 17:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I haven't cut on my legs in a long time. I'm okay now though and plan on trying to go for a few days without cutting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 05:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 01:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I was thinking. Thank you very much for sharing. Gave me some hardcore goosebumps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 01:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will definitely look into it. Sounds kinda like the movie, Sinister. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 01:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm, very creepy. Definitely will probably be contacting you to turn this into a short film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 01:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet! I'll be sure to check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 01:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes me sick to my stomach. Thank you for sharing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 01:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 01:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard stories like this before! It's possible that there could've been an accident of some sort where people died. I like this story though. We're their faces white? Like slender man? Or were they black? Simply flesh toned with no features? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 01:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't blame you at all. Something like that happened to me too, at a beach in South Carolina. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 01:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think sometimes seeing nothing is far scarier than seeing something. Very creepy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 01:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's terrifying! Do you know if there was any sort of death on your property? Other than the animals, I mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 01:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's very freaky. What do you think has caused it. Have you had any sort of, I don't know, problem(?) with a mirror before this happened to cause it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 01:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very eerie! I'd say that's some divine intervention of some sort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 01:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm definitely interested in turning this into a short! Can you share the other encounters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 19:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually intend to pursue special fx makeup and film directing as a career! I'll be sure to send you a link to some of my other stuff:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 19:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will definitely look into it! Thank you:) I've heard a few stories of things like that. Would you happen to know who the author of the book is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 19:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is super creepy! I've had that happen once too! Did anything else end up happening? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 19:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, I will be contacting you for help and input as I shoot and edit it! Thanks again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 19:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) I've done some pretty gory stuff with special fx makeup that makes this look very mild. Stuff like this is my hobby :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 19:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your input, I'll be sure to post it there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 19:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much. As soon as I get my Skype up and running again, I'll shoot you a message. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the scariest thing that's ever happened to you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 19:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the spring I'm going to start making horror film shorts again and I could use some good ideas. The story doesn't have to be true but if it is, even better. If already looked into some creepypastas but I figure true stories will be better. If you submit a story, I promise I will give you credit once the final film is done and published. Thank you in advance! If you have any questions, feel free to message me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 18:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -_- alright dude. We've been over this already. Kindly fuck off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 06:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 06:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's all and we'll but at least in that subreddit I don't have to worry about judge mental pricks telling me not to. Thanks for calling me things too. Appreciate it greatly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Still going and going and going </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 06:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 06:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need to be a dick. It's CREEPY makeup, asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We all have a dark side. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 06:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 04:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this captures the struggle of being a girl gamer when it comes to RPGS perfectly, haha. XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 04:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do some pretty bad alternatives as well. I guess the main one isn't too bad, but I know what you mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 03:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, thanks a lot :) I felt stupid for asking. Anywho, you're a lifesaver. Thanks again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wondering about Daedric armor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 20:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you get it on the Xbox version of elder scrolls? If so, where can I find it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 18:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't been alright in a long time my friend. I appreciate you wanting to help. It means a lot to me 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 18:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scarred up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 21:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 07:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If more people had a morbid sense of humor like we do, it would be more popular. But sadly, that's not the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 05:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shouldn't be laughing as hard as I am, but this is so fucking funny. Probably one of my favorite posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 17:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 08:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd suggest hitting up the local drugstore for some melatonin tablets. They work decently but after awhile you start getting tolerant. Good for short term use though until you can see a doctor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
