<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8986</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-11 20:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriend doesn't seem to understand this concept about his exes, specifically one that is bipolar. He is very caring, but is too caring for his own good sometimes. How would I tell this to him without it sounding cruel, or it seeming like I'm acting jealous? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-11 19:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since you don't have a lot of money, I'm guessing you don't eat many full meals throughout the day. The sugar in the chocolate probably keeps your blood sugar levels up the way a meal would, but the problem is that since it's just sugar, you crash more quickly than a meal full of fiber/protein/whatever. So you eat more chocolate. When I ate less, I thought it would be healthier but I ended up eating lots of sweets for this reasons. Try eating things high in calories. Keep basics around like eggs and bread (maybe make your own).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-10 23:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since you are more susceptible to falling into bulimic tendencies, over-excersize can be a type of "purging". 

In the end, it doesn't matter what you're diagnosed with, only if you're dealing with insurance for inpatient or whatever. If you feel like it's disrupting you to live normally, such as avoiding social situations because of the behavior, you should seek help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-07 08:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's interesting that you want to change the physical aspects of your behavior, since the obsession seems to sound worse which is helped with other meds. Not trying to downplay, but eating 2k calories in a day isn't bad, but is recommended amount to eat in a day. Unless you meant you binged a few times a day? The 600 calorie intake is a little bit low, so the binges are probably your body trying to make up for those days. In my eyes, you seem pretty normal in terms of calorie intake, but it's the obsession that you talked about that is getting to you more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-06 21:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I thought you meant medications about EDs in general. 

If you don't think you are a binge eater and aren't willing to speak about it with your doctor, maybe you shouldn't look to take a medication to lose weight for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-06 10:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He did mention cannabis which can be used for increasing appetite, not only mood-based. I think it helps temporarily, as I wouldn't be able to use it all day. 

Although, eating behaviors are so mood based that it's hard to separate different med uses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-05 06:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gave my boyfriend a blowjob, 69 position, about to come and then my jaw locked open. I couldn't close it and had to go to the ER for them to move it back into place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-04 05:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw your hair. I think you'll have to bleach once or twice. It's okay though, I have black hair and am white right now. I'm thinking of doing a light lavender soon. Just use lots of aftercare treatments and conditioner!

I was thinking about [this girls hair](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xWyOzeiBXgc feature=relmfu) when I saw your pic. Luckily, you have teal hair now so it'll be better than if you had bright red hair right now. 

Use purple shampoo!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-04 00:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on 250mg and have been on Lamictal for a few years. It's been great, with no real side effects. People talk about brain fog but I had that before anyways, so I don't really see a change for me. I'm diagnosed with depression and anxiety, as I've never had a real manic episode, but it runs in my family so I might just be lucky right now. I've been through many SSRIs, SNRIs, whatever, as a combination to Lamictal, but Lamictal seems to be the best for me. 

It's helped specifically with mood swings and getting angry, or becoming out of control during a breakdown type of thing. It doesn't seem to happen to me anymore. Like my brain stops before it gets bad. I also take xanax and klonopin because I have pretty bad anxiety, but lately it's just at night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-04 00:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you end up spending so little on the floor? It looks great, by the way! Did you order it online?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-04 00:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have butcher block as well. We just keep tons of cutting boards around (you don't want to use the counter to cut) and had extra wood to keep vinegar/soy sauce/leaky things/etc on top of. It's been probably a year and a half and so far so good. There was one stain (from a cup maybe) but it was sanded off. 

On the germs thing, the reason why people use wood cutting boards is because wood is antibacterial. They somehow get trapped and the lack of air (or whatever) kills them. I don't know, but I haven't gotten sick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-03 22:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, most likely bleach first, but I would go for a pink+purple combo, with more purple, mixed in with conditioner so it isn't so bright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-03 20:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep laughing about it. The only way I've heard it has been like "omg do you wanna go halfsies on the bill omg lol" type of way. I think if not hapa, then "mixed race" or something might be my second choice in words.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-03 06:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nope! sorry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-03 06:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that as a sex tip too, but whenever I tried I feel like it gets too thin. It's supposed to soak in the skin, so I wouldn't use it for long sessions.

After shaving pubes it's great to use as the area is pretty sensitive and it's a great moisturizer that you don't have to worry about getting in places moisturizers/aftershave/whatever doesn't go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-02 21:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To second (third?) this, my boyfriend has used multiple prescription soaps and things for his skin/scalp and recently found coconut oil has done better than anything else. I believe it has anti-fungal properties.

Coconut oil is great, but I generally don't cook with it. Theres great ways to eat it raw, such as on bread as a replacement of butter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-02 20:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from southern california, but not hawaiian-japanese. Here, it's basically anything that's asian + other. It's a pretty broad term. I've never heard halfsies. It so silly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-02 08:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, is "halfsies" a real thing? I'm japanese/polish, and say hapa.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-31 05:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naomily 3 

Although, I did love "I'm Katie Fucking Fitch, who the fuck are you" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-28 02:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that's the same with all schedule ii drugs, so meds like Adderall as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-25 20:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a moment I honestly thought you meant she was the neighborhood stray that gets fed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-24 23:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's what I had. I would get tingling in my extremities and stuff. It was probably be like 20 seconds for me, but I got so used to it that I just kind of kept going? Not as bad as a few minutes. I had never fainted though. That makes sense, with the lack of blood flow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-24 08:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't vision blackouts pretty... normal? If you mean like orthostatic hypotension, I don't think that comes from becoming severely anorexic. Before my anorexia was "severe", my doctor said I had that and I should "grow out of it". 

My nutritionist told me that the bone density was the most important to bring back as soon as possible. I was taking in lots of calcium. People start to naturally lose bone density in their 30s (I think), so before then it's a prevention of losing calcium for your body for your later years. 

You're right though... the brain is pretty plastic, it'll recover neurological damage much easier than physical.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-24 02:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a general tip, drinking water helps a lot when consuming lots of sodium. It's like the one way you can fix the problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-22 23:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally thought it was a photo of blogger [Gala Darling](http://www.flickr.com/photos/galadarling/2534641926/in/set-72157600055279854), who is in her mid-late 20s I believe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-20 06:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love[ this picture](http://24.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lzr1xrYLsg1qa0xfro1_500.png) of her :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-19 23:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm watching BSG for the first time right now (in season 2)... Oh god she is so amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-14 18:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing it might have been a specific episode that led to being diagnosed. A lot of people aren't depressed for years before getting treatment (I know a lot of us are, though). It only takes a few weeks of depression to be diagnosed, it doesn't have to be chronic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-08 21:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a friend with a similar body shape, and she goes to specialty shops for bras and things. Comfort first, so find a top that is very supportive, and the looks will probably fall into place afterwards since it would fit her nicely. Even without a brand name, it can be pricey. 

But the questions people are asking also need to be taken into consideration. Will she be sunbathing or swimming in the ocean, for instance?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-08 20:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't imagine how you can find a place for 2 for $700! 

My friend found a studio for $700 in Canoga Park, but that barely fits her. On the other hand, my boyfriend lived in a $1200+ studio in Venice about the same size. 

I'm surprised OP said "doesn't matter how many beds" because it's definitely the cost of a 0 bed apartment (studio, not saying they can't find a place). 

Maybe because I've lived here my whole life... I'm surprised they were considering a 2 bed for a $700 budget.

Still want to look at this thread for any job opportunity ideas though, but no one seems to have any!

I don't know how long OP is planning to stay, but maybe they can find a place to housesit for a few months or something. I'm sure theres lots of travel homes around here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-06 06:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Odd, I'm right by where they found her / suspected her. Why is internet in my real world? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-06 01:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the wine racks sturdy that way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-05 21:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a house from the 70s with a mini bar installed that we're planning to decorate soon. This is great inspiration :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-05 02:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in a large, liberal city so all of this coming out business isn't really a big deal for me. I saw a 30 Days episode on atheists and they had this graph basically explaining atheists are the most hated group of people in America, or at least christians. This was past gays, muslims, all those things that can be stereotypes. I had no idea this was true until that episode about a year ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-04 00:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't know from experience but i do know leather itself only gets better with time. i would definitely guess it's much more stable. the downside of it is cleaning since you can't throw it in the wash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-03 18:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tell us how it is! i'm on the search and have been eyeing this one, but i think i'm going to go leather from many people telling me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-02 06:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can ask your therapist what your "treatment plan" is... How long they think it should take, and what methods they use. You can also look it up online. I live in a large city so it's rather easy for me, but I'm not sure about you. My therapist specializes in a bunch of things but mostly eating disorders, which is good for me. Definitely don't be afraid to switch if you feel like you need something else. I went to 2 before I see the one I'm seeing now. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-02 04:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! I just saw them live last week! Love them so hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-01 21:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never had a therapist diagnose me, my psychiatrist usually does. 

The first therapist you see may not be the one for you, so be open to see other doctors. The treatment that works the best is CBT based, very much so for anxiety. It would be great if you found a therapist that was based on that system instead of just "talk therapy" which has been proven to not do much, especially compared to other methods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-01 19:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [her own videos on youtube :\)](http://www.youtube.com/user/katdennings/videos) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-29 22:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd go to /r/sex rather than /r/actuallesbians since you're a guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-29 08:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [gif!](http://24.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lovukvWOLq1qex8keo1_500.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-29 03:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> West coaster here and use the term all the time, since I get things as simple as other people's ring tones stuck in my head. I've heard other people use the term and also know what I'm talking about too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-29 02:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, my head is stuffy from a cold so sorry if I don't make sense! I'll try though.

It might be better if I gave an example. I think I was just adding that it might be less to do with being straight/male/female/gay/whatever and more with personal tastes/group of friends (for me). 

People I surround myself with won't flirt with the obvious "Hey sexy baby" as a greeting, but they are love to flirt. In the gay community at least, I know people are pretty aware of who is dominating in that situation, even if it's just for the night. So in situations like radicaljane was in with her coworker, girls might be uneducated in what it means to be submissive and give it up easily. But if you have enough confidence in knowing when you are submitting, you obviously aren't going to give it up to just anyone (unless that's your fetish or whatever). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-29 01:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely understand this. I think I hang out in a pretty sex positive crowd, whether straight or queer, so everyone is very aware of power. It has to be used wisely, whether holding power or giving it to someone. So when I see flirting outside of my usual groups of people, there is no subtlety. Maybe because I just see people flirt more cerebrally as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-24 19:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always loved the term "chapstick lesbian" but I agree with everyone else. Labels are probably a thing of the past, as the lesbians I know aren't extremely one way or the other. I'm wondering if in the past it was easier to have those labels as part of someone's identity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-24 08:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you'll mostly get A as an answer since people who self injure will most likely want to click a link with "self injury" in the title (as I did).

On the topic... I've used cutting to cope with overwhelming situations, but at one point it did become compulsive. It was almost like "I don't know what to do" so I cut. I had a few months in my life where I would cut several times a day. Now its 1-2 times a year :) Anxiety doesn't trigger it now, it's usually some sort of depersonalization type of thing, but it used to be caused by anxiety. Something about the endorphins + the ritual of it all, it's addicting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-24 03:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really liked *Best Of*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-24 02:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To add: this is also the kind of thing that can lead to obsessive compulsive behavior. That's what it's like for me, at least. It's probably why all of this is related. You feel like you need to do something, so you make up a behavior that gives you some dopamine boost, rinse, repeat. It's like making up your own addiction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-24 01:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went on to read about monks' alms bowl and their spiritual meanings behind it and suddenly I see OP talk so offensively about people using soap. Your minimalistic editing of his wording seemed relevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-22 22:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand the memory thing, but I think for me it's related to my depression (I'm not bipolar). I'd drive to school, but even though I've been going to class for a few months, I have had times where I had to sit down and look in my notebook to look at the room number. I also have ADHD and anxiety, I don't know if it's related. But it might be from so many things, so I just kind of accept it and try to work my way around it. I take notes a lot, write down where I've parked, whatever. I think I've always been like this, but I've also been on Lamictal for a couple years which can cause... memory loss? I know a few people who take it and we joke about forgetting something and call it having Lamictal Brain. I don't know. 

I haven't read a full book in probably 5 years. I don't know why. It definitely hurts academically. It pisses me off because I'm not dumb, I just can't read.

Why don't you think it's depression? There's lots of "brain fog" in depression for me. Kind of like walking around with tunnel vision. I've had times where depression was much more just... feeling numb more than anything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-21 03:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I probably put too much effort into this, but I freeze my chicken myself. I get chicken breasts cheap, I'm guessing no more than $4, I don't know how many pounds. I wipe them down, wrap them in threes in saran wrap (so it's not all one big chunk of meat once frozen), toss them in a bag and freeze.

edit: I went shopping today and chicken breasts were on sale for $1.89 per pound. This is where the freezing comes in handy... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-20 04:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Her body is similar too](http://www.flickr.com/photos/ilureu/6235198165/). :) Anyways jesus I feel like I am turning into a crazy cat lady. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-20 04:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks a lot like my old neighbors cat (which is half mine because she lives in my parent's yard blahblah I wish I had a cat :(... ) I love [this picture of her](http://www.flickr.com/photos/ilureu/6235577486) but her color is more similar to your picture, shown [here](http://www.flickr.com/photos/ilureu/424375350/). She had kittens when my neighbor first rescued her, but their colors were either full grey, orange, or black. No white. Funny, really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-17 07:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've believed that for a while now, but I'm too cat obsessed to give up. I have multiple rooms in my home and it would be an indoor/outdoor cat. I'd put up shelves everywhere to help my cat escape. I don't know what else to do. It depresses me to think I won't get a cat. Of course, it depresses me more to see it be my fault that a cat got hurt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-17 05:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In any disorder, you should seek help if it's bothering you in your every day life... Like, you can't work or go to school or have a healthy relationship or whatever because of it. 

I have generalized anxiety disorder and panic disorder so I agree that it doesn't have to be severe, but you don't necessarily have to see a psychiatrist if it doesn't affect you. It's just another way to look for solutions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best type of cat for a (possibly) aggressive dog?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-17 04:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea where to put this question, but I'm guessing you guys might have some input on this. 

My boyfriend and I adopted a 7 year old english bull terrier. We've had him for a little over a year. In the beginning, he was hard to hold on a leash, would bark at every dog passing by, jump on kids. That seems all normal-ish, but there have been two instances where he was on a leash and chihuahuas that were not leashed got into a fight. The small dogs weren't hurt but their heads had actually gotten inside my dog's mouth (I wasn't there so I can't explain better than that). When my dog sees cats outside, he growls at them. He's gotten to the point of barking when dogs bark, for example when dogs bark back at him, when the doorbell rings, etc. On walks he can get aggressive sometimes though.

The thing is, I really want a cat. I am a cat person. I subscribed to Cat Fancy when I was little. That sort of thing. I'm looking into different (no-kill) shelters and can't decide what kind of cat would make the easiest transition into our home. I'm not sure if I should get a kitten so this can be a new relationship, or an older cat that is already dog-friendly. I don't know if I should get a cat that is active (in case s/he gets chased), or a lazy one. I'm guessing an old lazy cat, since my dog seems to be okay with the snakes we have who don't move much. 

Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-16 08:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a lot of tofu recipes are good as well. i just got my wisdom teeth pulled and i had some korean tofu soup and it was exactly what i needed. i don't know about your grandpa liking korean food though. grits were good eventually but they got stuck in the sockets. solid things, not hard, are good... for instance, pizza (basically soaked in butter) was easier to eat than grits. apple sauce is good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-12 21:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you should try going to therapy. it helped for me. and not just like talk therapy. I don't know, you said you feel like you have BDD and i have anorexia and getting help from professionals has definitely helped me. It gets better.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-12 13:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you should get help for it.

i have a boyfriend and i'm doing generally well. you really have to push yourself. i have social anxiety so things like grocery shopping or filling up gas or whatever is challenging for me, but i do it. think of the things that are hardest for you and think of why. 

i've met all my close friends now from the internet (okcupid). it's nothing to be ashamed about really. i dont know what else to say.

are you in therapy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-11 23:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What medications were you on that made you feel numb? That's a side effect, not with all meds... I just hate politics and "big pharma" bullshit running into threads like this. I hope that's not your stance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-11 23:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you've found your right medicines. It's terrible that you must have felt that you traumatized yourself :/ What are you taking now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-11 23:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know someone that is schizoaffective... isn't that what it's similar to? From what I know its bipolar with severe delusions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-11 14:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks. i see my journals too. i remember writing long letters to exes and i knew they never read them (who would). i never had to fill out forms i guess when i saw my (mental) doctors... but i remember they would ask things that i knew which disorders they linked to. so i didn't say i had rambling thoughts but i do. i never hear what my diagnoses are anyways. just things like "well your social anxiety..." but this is the first time i realized i don't know what mania is. well i'm up at 5:49am and this has been too regular. i like who i'm being treated by but it just takes so long... 1-2 months per medication is a long time in regards to seeming normal while taking college classes. i hated my first psychiatrist. ive seen 2 other therapists so i'm good with that. thanks for listening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-11 13:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you aren't trying to sound rude but I do have mental illness but I've been trying my best to live sane. I can't work without panic and I leave in the middle of class because I can't do it. I dropped to 88 pounds and see a nutritionist, psychiatrist, therapist... I don't think you've read what I or other people have written but clearly just because you "lived life" doesn't mean mental illness isn't true. People like you just make me feel more shame about my actions. Im finally driving on my own, I had a job last year, I'm in a long term relationship and i exercise. It's real bullshit to say its just life and to get off meds. I would be dead without them, not from suicide but anorexia. Wrong forum but whatever. I've never been suicidal but I'd be in the hospital from trying to kill myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-11 02:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that analogy makes a lot of sense. that's terrifying. 

i'm glad you're feeling better.

i have stuff to talk about with my drs but they'll probably say it has to do with anxiety. i'm just in the middle of a med change and important life events or whatever so i don't think i'll be taken too seriously right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-11 01:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm in the same place. i am going off paxil because it makes me sleep 14 hours a day and my boyfriend was upset because i don't want to have sex (upsets him more than me). i stopped lexapro because of money too. i'm also on lamictal right now. try to get some benzodiazepines (xanax, klonopin) to help you through. that's what i'm trying to do. i don't know the next time i can see my pdoc but the last time i stopped i hurt myself. ssri withdrawal is terrible for me, with the nausea, dizziness, besides the whole suicidal ideation... the physical stuff sucks too. hopefully you don't have to go through that. good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-11 01:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> one of the first things i realized recently was when i thought i shouldn't consider all irritability and all those sorts of things as just anxiety. that's what i tell my doctors. but when i tried to explain it to myself, its definitely how you described how you can hear tiny detail. i wrote an analogy about how how cows have 4 stomachs to digest food and i need 4 brains to digest everything but instead its squished into 1. every sensation "hurt"... my boyfriend tried to touch me and it hurt... sounds that were almost mute were too much for me to handle... are you're sure that was part of your mania? is there more information on it? is it just called "sensitivity" or "irritability" or something?

if ive ever been anywhere near manic i always assumed it was because of my borderline personality or just being a teenager and not dealing with it... like cutting, starving, promiscuity, general not caring myself... now it's gotten to taking too many drugs to shut my brain off. but none of it is me being happy doing it. i'm actually very quiet about it. thats what makes me think its depression. i depersonalize if anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-08 13:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of people that need emotional help don't have learning disabilities. I don't mean for this to sound mean at all or anything. Just a common myth :) I've learned, for instance, a lot of schizophrenics become high functioning by having jobs that are less stressful (working at a drug store for instance) but are actually much more intelligent than what their jobs seem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-07 23:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing the same thing right now. I'm on lamictal (helps with mood swings) and will increase, but I just went off of Paxil completely. I haven't been without an antidepressant ever but the klonopin helps. I used to only take it at bedtime thinking 1mg would make me so tired (in the beginning it did) but taking it in the morning helps me. I do still get irritable in the evening so I try to take it more hours before sleep (I can't say what time of day because I've been waking up at around 3pm). I'm still feeling agitation but it's just the beginning. Of course, going off of the effexor should make you agitated at least for a while (the withdrawal). 

Just writing that I'm going through the same thing, and am currently reading what other people are writing... It helps a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-07 23:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do this with every day life (I have generalized anxiety too) and my therapist basically says "Whats the worst that can happen?". It's funny to say but thinking about the worst possible solution helps. But I can't imagine doing this while having a panic attack while driving... it keeps happening and it's so dangerous because car accidents are actually frequent! But anyways so I'll be driving and start crying out of no where that I'm going to die... and I keep thinking of the worst (not on purpose) and it makes it worse. In retrospect I know it's irrational but during it I can't do this. I wonder if it only works with certain situations... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-05 12:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cutest boobies ever! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-05 08:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I know Japanese manga but not how the english ones are... Don't bother me, I don't know anything :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-05 08:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't it still be the opposite? Even reading right to left... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-04 00:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also agreeing on OkCupid. I'm still 19 so I can't actually go clubbing... it's hard to find a place where it's easy for people to approach you / you approach them without it being weird i think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-31 00:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The absolute cutest! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-31 00:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [t rex hates push ups!](http://imgur.com/gallery/BjNYo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-30 00:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually probably Poladroid. Not a phone app, but the worst of them all. I like instagram, though. I think they were good inventions, it just sucks because exactly this-- all you want to do is guess the filter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-28 19:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know exactly what you don't like about it, but kefir is a liquified version (if you don't like the thickness). Of course theres milk and it's various creamy siblings. If not, whey powder, and if not that, you can make a smoothie without yogurt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-27 02:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, don't use much. I use probably 1/4 tsp for a pot of miso soup (making maybe 4 bowls). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-26 03:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe this photoshoot is for this [final photo](http://4.bp.blogspot.com/_zvT2g6U42BM/SlPoAfP9EMI/AAAAAAAAAWU/O3PpnHAi4Ns/s400/shanehugo2l.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kate Moennig... Also she's shirtless. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-26 00:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-26 00:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You're welcome. :)](http://26.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lycfbm2vJd1qz9qooo1_500.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-25 08:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I just didn't want to be misunderstood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-25 04:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ha! i didn't mean it like that. i meant a lot of girls are afraid of sex because it's dirty. i didn't say all straight girls are like that. i meant, especially girls who aren't used to porn. [this is an example of what i meant.](http://www.tube8.com/lesbian/francesca-and-leila/1282471/) by dirty sex, i mean sex with sweat, tears, etc. not necessarily s m. things that aren't in that video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-25 03:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a bisexual, I can't stand straight porn and am very picky about lesbian porn. I think too much about it... I heard that a lot of lesbian porn has 1 lesbian and 1 straight girl. The lesbian gives the chemistry, and the straight girl reminds them their on camera. I don't know if this is true, but I'm always trying to find the lesbian. I can't stand lesbian porn made my straight men (or so it seems). Once I heard a man in the background of a video that they forgot to edit out and I was so turned off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-24 23:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I would eat them. Yummy. They look like nails made of cotton candy. Then I'd spit them out because ew.

I'm a grinding type of masturbator so HEH irrelevant post to me ;D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-24 23:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a similar manner, I think many (if not most) girls are into girl-girl even when they're straight. 

There was this study, and I might be generalizing or getting small things wrong, but the gist of it was that women can become more easily turned on than males when it comes to different subject matters. The study used straight porn, gay porn, lesbian porn, as well as animals (apes?) having sex. The men were turned on (physically) with the porn of their preferred orientation (or it could have been like straight + girl/girl) whereas women were sexually aroused by all of them, including the animals (not related to bestiality).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-24 22:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, that soft stuff bores me so much. I jokingly call it straight girl porn, where people are afraid of dirty sex. The stuff thats slow and mostly kissing. It's beautiful in a cinematic way though. 

I mentioned this in a comment here just now, but I love the Crash Pad series. It's not sm (although Kink.com is great for that) but it's more queer than people might be comfortable with, such as very androgynous women or people with curves... I'm guessing TwoX doesn't have much of a problem with that, though. There's real chemistry between them all, and very often repeating couples that I assume might even be people in romantic relationships outside of porn. At least, thats what I like to fantasize about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-24 21:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Crash Pad Series fan forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-24 12:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please read Miranda July. This reminds me of the goldfish scene in Me You and Everyone We know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-24 11:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you go to Sallys or any specialty shop? Where I went, they had loads. They're in tiny tiny bottles that you can mix with developer, and there's also ones in the dye cups that look purple (like virgin snow). Your hair looks good nonetheless! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-24 09:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woohoo! I'm in the process of going white right now. I'm naturally dark brown to black haired. I've done two bleachings so far (since Christmas eve) and went pink in between to give my hair a break and I hated having orangey hair. Going to bleach again. 

Which toner did you use? Last time I went white I used silver lady and it seemed to go pretty well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-24 08:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay I've seen you around with your smiles and boobs on happygirls :) Yipeee! Lovely lovely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-24 05:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have those too. I think my GAD / panic episodes led me to have depersonalization episodes. What specifically happened (if i may ask?). I had no idea what it was but I don't think the doctors cared much. It didn't happen every day so it didn't affect my life enough to matter much, as mental disorders should be categorized. I could see why a doctor might think that... you know, not medicating you for something that didn't happen often (not trying to make it sound like nothing). Klonopin helped when I dissociated. My doctors always said the thing they wanted to treat first was the mood disorders, such as Depression / Bipolar, then the anxiety, etc. Maybe visual disturbances was just low on the list at that point. I do hate when psychiatrists chuckle though. My first psychiatrist sucked so bad. She's the one that diagnosed me as Borderline so I think she wanted to make me rage because she expected it. I wanted to break her table but I didn't because I'm not Borderline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-24 05:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought my ADHD/impulsivity was part of Borderline Personality Disorder (I was diagnosed but I don't think I have it). It's all very strange. You should definitely try Adderall. It was the best few months of my life (okay, not really, I'm exaggerating). I'm going to try to get really healthy and my heart strong enough so I can take it. It was a really good one for me, not in an addicting way. I was where I should have been. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
