<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5711</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 03:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thing is she was with a man in her teens but she says it doesn't  count because he was also gay  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 01:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i hope the coverage of this story makes them change there minds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 01:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is that slender mans cousin bent man? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 01:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i 100% agree its just a selfie that will be deleted at some point its just stupid but who am i to tell them what to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 00:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we need to protect children from FA and HAES people they are slowly killing there children and these kids cant stop them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 00:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so what losing 5 pounds makes you think OMG i could lose 6 NO thats way to far i don't want to relapse in my anorexia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doesn't believe I'm a lesbian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 00:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My partner who i am married too for the past year and been together for 2 still doesn't believe i am a lesbian like seriously.
She states i cant be a lesbian because she never got the vibe off of me and she is very good at picking out who is gay and who isn't. 
Her second reason is that before i came out when i was 16 i dated men 
and had sex with men then i started dating woman and have ever since.
also says that if we get devorced i will go back to dating guys ( I won't)

so to summarize i am not a lesbian because i dated guys when i was a teen before i came out even thou i am married to a woman and have been dating girls since i was 16.

WTF like fkjfdupifnwipfbreupigne </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 06:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think farting is nasty so yes get back at him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 06:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because he's a butcher doesn't mean that he won't support you being a vegetarian  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 06:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if its your ONLY one then treat it like it is your only one.
Think about kids who only have 1 doll do they trash it 
NO they treat it like its the most amazing thing in the world and take care of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 01:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how dare you think that i would find a fat man attractive. 

how dare you not find MY fat attractive you shallow whore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 00:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just made my day:)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TITP contradictions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 23:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what TITP contradictions can you think of my fave is * everyone should love there bodies, everyone is worth something* 20 Minutes later....... * your thin you know nothing about oppression you should cover you body its ugly and makes me feel bad*
you cant have it both ways
oh also: they post a selfie and people think they are amazing a thin person posts a selfie they are bullied and shamed till they take it down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 22:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes always challenge them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 22:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why is it bad to want a perfect genetic specimen i am trying to have a baby and i am getting donated sperm i want the sperm i buy to be the top of the top i don't want some fat man with below average intelligence with health problems.
and thats just how it works  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 06:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> send this pic to them they might give you free shit 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 06:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats just what i was thinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 06:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHERE IS THE WARNING assface </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 06:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> someone tell me?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 06:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> those arnt boobs that is fat rolls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 06:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have seen it like 15 times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 06:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do NOT think it should be legal at all and i am being told I'm an moron and that i don't understand. But what i do understand is that smoking pot is just like smoking cigarettes and almost all pot is laced i hope it never becomes legal.
also i don't care what you say pot DOES lead to harder drugs because eventually weed doesn't work anymore  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 06:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name : Cotie
Reddit age : this account only about a month BUT old account was about 3 years 
Why I want to MOD : because i want to give something back to my have site and they are really funny 
 How much can I be Active (include your GMT): I can be active about 15 hours a day every day ( EST ) time zone
 How fluent I am with css: Not really  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 06:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mind if i ask what CSS Mod is  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 02:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i was going to say something educational but fuck it 

your retarded  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 02:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> really everything is ok until its not ok 
sounds weird but its ok.
i think people are hard wired to stress out more then is really necessary you WILL be ok and in a few weeks you will think " i stress out WAY to much".
have a great holiday and remember every time there was hard ship your still OK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 02:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really sorry 
i have gone through this and i know that nothing i say will make you feel better 
i bet you don't want to hear "if its meant to be then it will be" or "you will find someone better" because that really doesn't help at all 
but with time you do feel better i promise. 

i cant make you feel better but i can let you know that your not alone and there are people to help you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 02:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i know this might not help but what friends family does is pushes christmas back a few days and goes to the sales.
they just say that a family member is sick and they don't feel right opening presents on a sad day.
and really anything is good to kids go to the dollar store and buy a bunch of little things then she has LOTS for a little bit of money 

I'm sure your friend and the baby shower can survive with out a gift just this one time.

Bills are just bills as long as you have a roof over your head and food to eat i think you will be ok  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 02:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely agree HAES and FA are just the same as PRO-ANA they are promoting that people not listen to doctors and basically kill them selves 
FA AND HAES are telling people to listen to them and not there doctors who are trying to save there lives 
i do believe that even with freedom of speech they should be banned from tumblr just like pro anas are  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 02:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i know its corny but have you tried like an adult friend finder  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 23:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't have a single friend not since i was 15. When i was younger i had 1 or 2 friends but nothing else 
i am now 20 and i haven't talked to anyone that wasn't my family or my partner in years. Other then the friendly hello goodbye on the street , casher at the store or the doctor never more then a few words.

I LOVE it  i never felt the need to have other people in my life 
why don't you just try to not talk to anyone just sit with your self and your own thought. Or you can join an online forum or gaming community and try to get people with the same interest if all else fails go to a bar and get trashed you never know what can happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 23:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i get this to i wanted some crappy old made for tv movie for my partner and it was like $3000.00 . i think theres a glitch somewhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 23:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "He knows when your awake........" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 23:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pooh Bear needs to get over robin and pull his life together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 23:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank god I'm allergic to bananas and I'm a lesbian see how that worked out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 23:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> beat me to it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 23:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is there a health department there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 23:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did you taste them? Do they taste good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 22:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because all those starving people in africa are so fucking fat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 22:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wtf my sister is fairly thin and she is having a high risk pregnancy because last  pregnancy she had preaclampsia and a very large baby  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 21:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOUTUBE is not a doctor stop getting your info from there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 21:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> at least some people are taking action TITP is just as bad as people who promote anorexia  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 21:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anorexia can only be diagnosed when the person has a bmi under 18.0 but anorexics start out average size NOT fat your right  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 06:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im a lesbian and i can tell you i don't think its just men because my partner is very manly and she does this. It pisses me off to no end i think it has something to do with being around other males growing up for my partner it was a lot of male friends that made this behaviour. I can tell you from my point of view woman love men that will show emotions we don't want robots my partner won't even hug me because it makes her feel weak. 
just try to cry by your self at first see how it feels i like people with emotions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 06:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> really your were offend by a fucking puppet 

in other news TITP was offend by a sock that mimicked her body shape in a shaming fashion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
