<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6210</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 03:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure vodka is the lowest cal alcohol. So you can just get that with your favourite low-cal drink! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 03:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything came back normal, so I didn't have to get hospitalized. I just wasted all day in the ER </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 01:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything is normal now and I'm getting sent home after I have an EKG.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 01:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was 78/64 with a heart rate of 120bpm. I don't feel dehydrated. I drink lots of water </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Urg, I hate the hospital </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 01:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to the doctor's this morning for my weekly check up/weigh in (lost 3lbs!!). And my blood pressure was incredibly low and my heart rate was really high. He told me and my parents to go to the emergency room to get IV fluids and that I might have to stay overnight. I've been sitting in the ER for 5 hours already, I still haven't seen a doctor or gotten my IV fluids. I really want a cigarette, but they won't let me leave. Urg, I don't need this right now, I have finals to study for.

Edit: I did not get hospitalized, I just wasted all day in the ER. My heart went back to normal and all of my blood work is perfect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 21:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am super stressed out because I should be studying for finals, but instead I have to spend the afternoon in the ER because my blood pressure is really low and my heart rate is really high. I might have to stay overnight and defer my exam in the morning. Urg, I really want a cigarette, but I can't leave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 04:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is awesome! I like the quotes "The girl of my nightmares, sultry and corpse-like" and "Diet coke and cigarettes is what skinny girls are made of" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 04:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have IBS, I take probiotics to help the symptoms and it works for me. 

What most people with IBS try is the low FODMAP diet and a lot of people say it helps. I personally never tried it though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 01:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8) and 2 egg whites (34)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0)

Total: 361 calories
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 01:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 5'8 and I wish I was taller! I wish I was 6 feet tall and had nice long legs, but that will never happen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 22:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8) and 5 almonds (35)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0)

Total: 362 calories
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 19:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know her stats? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 02:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8) and 2 egg whites (34)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0)

Total: 361 calories
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 16:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Height: 5'8

CW: 92 lbs

HW: 115 lbs

LW: 92 lbs

GW: 90 lbs

UGW: 84 lbs, but I'm thinking of lowering it.

WL: -12 lbs

BMI: 13.84

Age: 19

Gender expression: female

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 04:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope to do well on my finals, and study lots. I hope I lost weight at my next weigh-in. And I hope to stick to my meal plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 00:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8) and 2 egg whites (34)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0)

Total: 361 calories
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 00:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We were just both in such bad places mentally, we both started manipulating each other and talking shit about the other. But we actually reconciled a few years later </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 23:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's nice to have someone to talk to, but it usually gets pretty competitive when you do it with friends. It kind of ruined one of my friendships  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 23:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, I am always in my giant bathrobe wrapped in a blanket! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 22:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a few "friends" at university, but they're just my lab partners and once the class is done we probably won't ever talk again. 

I'd love to have an ED meetup, but I doubt anyone on here lives near me. It's nice to have irl friends who know what you're going through. I had a few friends in high school who had EDs too, but they all recovered </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 22:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's alright, but it's probably the most boring part of Canada, and our winters are usually horrible (not this year though, thank god!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 22:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope :(
I'd love to kik though, add me my username is labellemort! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 22:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate clubs, the only time I can stand them is if I do M, but because of anti-depressants I don't get high from it. 

Haha, I've been joking that I'm an 80 year old man in a 19 year old girls body (idk why I am an old man though) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 19:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally understand what you mean. It's a lonely disease, and it does force you to isolate yourself. Thankfully I have 2 people to talk to about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 19:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, we are far from each other. I'm right in the middle. I wish I was put west, it's much nicer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 16:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I have a dog and she's great! I wish I could have a cat though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 16:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so excited to get weed. I try to only smoke it when I'm on holidays and I'm on holidays in less than 2 weeks. I can't wait to get high and not feel horrible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 16:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am from Canada! But it's so big we are probably far from each other </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 06:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She'll grow out if it! She's just a kitten.
It's always nice to have an excuse to get out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 06:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not real weight. It's from the food and drinks you had today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 05:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I had a cat, I love them, but my mom is super allergic. I wish I had friends who invited me out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 05:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, my mom is great! But sometimes you just need a friend who isn't your mom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 05:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, pretty much every Saturday night is me alone in my bed on reddit. It really sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 03:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I am super introverted and the ed doesn't help. All of my friends from school are hardcore partiers and go to raves, so when high school ended, I had nothing in common with them anymore and we just stopped talking. I wish I had someone who just wants to hang out and talk or watch movies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The loneliness is killing me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 02:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been so lonely these days. I have no friends, the only person I ever really talk to is my mom. I just wish I had someone to talk to, that's probably why I post so much on this sub, haha. 
I don't know how to get over the loneliness. I just want friends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 01:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same as everyday. I'm such a creature of habit
Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8) and 2 egg whites (34)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0)

Total: 361 calories
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 20:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have a thinspo journal. I think I know where it is, I should pull it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 20:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey fellow lesbian! It's nice to see that there are other LGBT* people here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 20:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the sub! Glad to have you hear and hope we can help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 20:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've noticed that all I see is fat when I binge. But thankfully I've only binge twice in the past month </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People making comments about your body </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 18:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Urg, my dad just told me that I need to put some meat on my bones. He knows about my eating disorder. I just snapped at him and told him he was never allowed to make comments about my body or what I eat. Urg, he just pissed me off soo much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 16:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! You'll get there! I believe in you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 16:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 06:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only really compare my body to really thin girls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 06:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how it is for most people with eating disorders and I was like that too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 05:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! Welcome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 03:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cinnamon (147)

Lunch: 1/2 red bell pepper (11) celery (6) cucumber (8) and 2 egg whites (34)

Dinner: Rice cake with 1 and 1/2 tbsp of light peanut butter (155)

Snacks: Diet coke (0)

Total: 361 calories
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eating disorder without dismorphia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 03:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually people who have eating disorders have body dismorphia and see themselves as larger than they really are. I used to be really dismorphic, but not this time. I can see that I'm thin, I probably don't see myself as thin as other people see me, but I still see someone who is thin. But I want to get even thinner, pretty much a skeleton. Is anyone else like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 03:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 03:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can do it! I believe in you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 03:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I've been liking my hip bones a lot lately </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 02:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of hope that my eating disorder kills me, but I doubt it will, especially since I'm getting monitored weekly by my doctor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 23:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love /r/fatlogic. Such a great sub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 22:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 2 accounts. My main one and this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
