<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1637</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As part of her presidential campaign, Hillary Clinton should buy the $10 bill. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 19:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 06:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Order of the New Templars?" Man why did Nazis take all the cool names... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 20:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's kind of dickish. I mean, if you disagree with him then ignore him or engage him in honest debate. Fucking with him like this is petty and childish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really worried that her publisher is taking advantage of her old age and forcing her to publish the prequel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 00:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. As a comeback, it was snappy and very effective, but as an argument it's useless. Citing fiction doesn't support a real-world argument. 

What it DOES do is force the other person to denounce a well-respected work of art in order to maintain their argument. They have to say "To Kill a Mockingbird is unrealistic," which might be contrary to what they actually believe. It's sort of a petty, personal victory, and would be a waste of time in an actual debate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 22:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That prince has such thick, perfectly coifed hair. He's his father's child, indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 21:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When they aren't getting angry or offended, tumblr users are generally pretty fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 20:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally raise all my kids, so I know the one. It's either a) the kid likes to party and I encourage him/her to host big parties, or b) the kid has his/her first kiss and I teach him/her about the birds and the bees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CK2 converter not working with the new patch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 19:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The new patch made my previous conversion game incompatible, which is only to be expected, but now it doesn't recognize any games I export as mods for eu4. Help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 18:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this inspired by the cover story in Science today? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 10:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say "abolished" necessarily, but if they are going to be incorporated they need to make some major changes, administrative and doctrinal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 10:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our church is the church of all people, whether or not they have accepted its truth. I'm all for placing the well-being of our flock above others, but the needs of refugees are greater than our own. Economic migrants, yes, have no inherent right to the riches of Europe and the church must look out for Catholics first and foremost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 10:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canon is very important to many people, so I agree that she shouldn't try to write any more Discworld novels. However, I do hope that the fan fiction community thrives for a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 10:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope that fans of the series will continue to expand the disc by writing quality fan fiction. I wouldn't want to risk the series being tarnished by poor canon, but I really hope the fan fic scene for Discworld thrives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 10:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Pirates of the Caribbean soundtrack is such an underrated masterpiece. The melody line just screams "adventure." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 01:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brawler main here, looking to start using swordfighter more often. What moveset do you recommend?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 05:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Dolly, but Pico is annoying af. I wish she wasn't always there, it's kind of uncomfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does Story of Seasons compare to RF4? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 05:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking to get a new title for my 3ds, I've already got Rune Factory 4 and I'm wondering how SoS compares. 

I found the farming features a bit too complex in RF4. The different soil nutrient levels were nice in theory, but they took away my favorite part of HM: Seeing a uniform, fully grown field of crops. Is it the same way in SoS, or is it the standard, simple farming system?

And how do you like the marriage candidates, bachelorettes specifically? Don't name any names, I'd like to go in blind, just say if you liked them or not, variety, depth, maturity, etc.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 05:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RF4 was the first Harvest Moon game where I (heterosexual man) liked the bachelors more than the bachelorettes. In my girl playthrough, I married Arthur because he's serious and competent on the job, but also has a sense of humor. You know, like a normal person. The glasses obsession was adorable too. Didn't like Doug or Dylas, they acted like dicks to compensate for being self-conscious. I hate that. Vishnal's cool, never really thought about him much.

As a boy, I married Dolce first, her snark and puns were very charming. Then Xaio Pai, because everything about her is just really cute. I wasn't a fan of the rest of the girls. Margaret seemed so bland, Amber and Clorica were TOO ditzy. I became good friends with Forte, I like her a lot but I never felt inclined to date her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 05:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Pop Island title. I ADORED those games, I wish they had been more popular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 15:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Nepalese can't leave. And they often don't get paid. Leaving is what the illegal aliens in the US are afraid of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 05:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Story of my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 00:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably because my comment didn't actually contribute anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 22:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was so deliciously campy, I loved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 22:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this was a video about the growth rate of Shia Islam... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 20:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the best comment in the thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 20:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm obligated to point out that individuals don't evolve, populations do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 13:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude what if the twist is that the player was an android all along. Calling it now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 23:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm not sure either, it takes a lot of the customization out of the character. Also Boston accents would get annoying after a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 22:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a link that I'll try to find,  the male and female voice actors said that the player starts the game in a cryo chamber. Coupled with the fact that they have memories of pre-war times, and of entering the vault, it looks pretty certain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 22:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the player character really is cryogenically frozen in Vault 111, then character creation will probably include choosing a past for them. Career, skills, hobbies, quirks, etc. in addition to the standard traits/perks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 22:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those flashback sequences would mean that the player was alive during the great war. Either Vault 111 is a cryogenic preservation experiment or the player is a ghoul, and his skin looks pretty smooth to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 02:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Punchline in the title, but good story! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 21:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Standard topics: ISIS, Ukraine

Relevant but not as common: South China Sea, unrest in Mexico

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 09:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok I like Korrasami as much as anyone but it annoys me how that's all people focus on. I mean the last season dealt with some powerful themes involving personal growth, and touched on the relationships between people who feel differently towards each other in a very mature way. But all anyone sees is one scene at the end which concluded a rather petty romance. Not to say it was particularly immature, it just didn't stand out among all the other great parts of the last season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 09:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dead men can't steal. If people start getting disruptive, it's really in his best interest to keep serving them until they pass out, or worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 02:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What comic? Link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] The voices know they're not real, and it agonizes them. They decide to visit a therapist to help cope. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 20:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 17:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean look at what she was *wearing!* Come on, Nanking was asking for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 03:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THE SECRETS OF !!FUN!! HAVE BEEN PASSED DOWN THE ARMSTRONG LINE FOR GENERATIONS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 00:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. I guess I shouldn't take facts from /r/TIL without reading the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 00:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then proceeded to insist that people call him "His Mightiness the President of the United States." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary should pick Bill as her running mate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 20:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 19:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why playing Orthodox is so awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 06:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, lets count the votes. 270 needed to win the presidency. Which states will vote Republican regardless of who wins the primaries? 

We can confidently assume that the South will go red, so that's Texas, Alaska, Arkansas, Louisiana, Missouri, Alabama, Georgia, Tennessee, South Carolina, Kentucky, West Virginia. 

The Plains states are pretty Republican too, so lets throw in Montana, North/South Dakota, Wyoming, Nebraska, Idaho, Utah, Arizona, Oklahoma and Kansas. 

All told that's 180 votes that we can be fairly certain will go to Jeb, should he be the Republican nominee. As a Floridian, he'll also probably win Florida, so that's another 29. He would need to win 61 more votes to win the general. Say he takes North Carolina, Virginia and Ohio, the three closest states in 2012. Now he needs 15 more. Throw in New Mexico, for the high Spanish-speaking population (Jeb is fluent in Spanish, and surprisingly popular with Hispanic voters). 4 votes away now. At that point it's anybody's game. New Hampshire sometimes votes Republican, Minnesota, Wisconsin, Colorodo and Michigan were all close in 2012. Any one would give Jeb the win.

Tl;dr: you don't like him, but it's within the realm of possibility that he wins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 06:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was being sarcastic. I should probably stop doing that, it never seems to get through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 00:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, fuck England! Murica! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 04:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Approximately 100 billion people have been born

2. Of those, all but 7 billion have died

Conclusion: I have about a 93% chance of dying. Therefore, I have about a 7% chance of never dying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 05:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because America has no peers #WestIsTheBest #Murica </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 04:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bush "brand" helped George Jr. and Jeb get a jump-start in politics, but it didn't win them the presidency. Look, when there'a an election for your representative in the state legislature, you probably aren't going to know a lot about the candidates. State races don't get much press. But if one of those candidates is an immediate family member of a President? Why, you already know his positions on political issues, you heard all about them in the last Presidential election. By identifying with a well-known figure, it's easy for candidates to get their start. 

Elections for higher offices (Senator, Governor, President, etc.) are more competitive, and the name association doesn't help nearly as much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 06:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drinking is a social activity. Alcoholism is a disease.

Also, that saying Native Americans are more likely to be alcoholic isn't racist, it is a commentary on the trend of a genetically-linked disease in a population. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 06:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to call it Galloway's Razor: If you can interpret both a fact and its hypothetical opposite as support for your argument, then neither is valid supporting evidence.

example: If someone interprets "Democrats have higher incomes than republicans" to mean "Democrats are obviously more educated and productive," and then interprets "Republicans have higher incomes than democrats" as "The GOP is the corporate party of the rich," then it's hypocritical and illogical to accept either argument as evidence that Democrats are better than Republicans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 06:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well when you're speaking philosophically or emotionally, or if it's an interpersonal issue that there is no consensus on, then personally experience is more valuable than anything. It's also not unreasonable to say "I will hold this belief based on personal experience until a credible source proves me wrong, because this is something I don't really care about." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 12:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if everyone felt the same you did?

Well, then Id be a fool to feel any differently!

Catch-22 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 12:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the requirement for the college of engineering. So the surface pro 3 is more like a traditional laptop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 00:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'll take a look at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [USA] [$1,000-$2,500] [Touchscreen with active stylus] What computer should I get for college? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 23:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm graduating in a few weeks so I'm looking at my university's computer requirements. They require a touchscreen device with an active stylus, in addition to the minimum i5 processor, 8GB ram and 256GB SSD. They had a few suggestions on the website (Fujitsu T935, T725, and Lenovo Thinkpad Yoga 12), but the range of prices was huge. One of their suggestions cost upwards of $3000, while another was like $1500.

What should I expect to pay for a device with those specs? Is the range really that large? What am I paying for if another device has identical specs but costs $500 less?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 04:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a bunch of other people have already said it, but your style is great! It looks like the comic took a lot of work, and it came out really well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 19:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rhodoks:

UA: Horses are for pussies - All hills tiles produce +1 food. All melee units start with "drill 1", all ranged units start with "barrage 1". Cannot build Cavalry units, and horses provide no extra production. 

UU: Rhodok Sharpshooter - Replaces crossbowman. Has the same ranged combat strength, and has the ability to melee attack.

UU: Rhodok Sergeant - Replaces pikeman. Slightly higher combat strength, and upgrades to musketman instead of lancer.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] War is obsolete. Militaries aren't. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 19:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 19:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 18:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oceania: Big Brother

UA: We have always been at war with Eastasia/Eurasia (name changes every time you play) - 20% less unhappiness when at war. no unhappiness from ideological pressure.

UU: Thought Police (replaces spy) - double espionage efficiency. Reduces unhappiness when in one of your own cities.

UB: Ministry of Truth - replaces library. +1 science for every 3 citizens in a city, +3 happiness

Edit: I have always known the name of the Ministry of Truth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 18:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not only hilarious, but actually a pretty balanced domination civ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 12:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pop Island is one of my favorite DSiWare titles, it's simple and loads of fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 05:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much singleplayer content is there for Smash Bros? I don't have any friends to play with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 05:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like the Professor Layton games. I enjoy the Ace Attorney games, but I like Layton better. Out of *Professor Layton vs Ace Attorney* and *Professor Layton and the Last Spectre*, which is the best bang for my buck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 02:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fajita. I have to eat every so often, and preparing food is a chore. I don't have any requirement to get off, and preparing to fap is exciting.

Basically, I can always eat the fajita then masturbate, but if I randomly orgasm there's no guaranteed fajita. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 03:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manhattan Project. Use nuke once, everyone fears you for the rest of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 20:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe they didn't use the word "gentile." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 15:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UKIP was right though; the Poles can't be trusted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 23:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 23:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] A simple, classic fairy tale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 19:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prospective student here: Is it possible to transfer from the College of Science to the College of Engineering after the first year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 23:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got accepted into my second choice (Physics at Science) but rejected from my first choice (CompSci at Engineering). I want to know if it's possible to enroll in the College of Science, get through all the first-year weed-out classes, and transfer to Engineering for my desired major. I looked at the VT website for transfer students, and I'm not sure if those requirements apply since I'm not transferring from another university. So is it possible? Is it particularly difficult?

Thanks for the help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any information about Virginia Tech MUN? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 16:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm deciding on what college I want to go to and I was wondering what VT's MUN program is like. Do they even have an active one? Any contact info? Have others in their circuit ever seen them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best Mesoamerican religion in the game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://www.reddit.com/r/eu4/comments/316hw9/best_religion_in_game/) post asked what religion was best, excluding the new Mesoamerican religions. What I want to know is, which of the three Mesoamerican religions provides the best bonuses? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've got good friends that like me, but they never invite me to anything... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 06:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Senior in high school. They don't seem to think it annoys me, because they talk about their parties right in front of me all the time. It's not like I've indicated that I'm uninterested in their social gatherings, I've just never been invited. Anybody know how to get people to invite me to things? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: there's no such thing as "gender" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 15:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think Howard wanted to hire Jimmy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 05:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howard was impressed by Jimmy's drive, still wary about hiring him as a fully-fledged attorney but willing to give him a shot. I think it was Chuck that *really* didn't want Jimmy working as a lawyer at HHM, and he asked Howard to break the news. That's why Jimmy has such an irrational hatred of Howard, he thinks that the man stopped him from getting a job working for the brother he always looked up to. I mean, Jimmy couldn't have imagined that his big brother would turn him down like that, so he blames Howard instead.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody going to Georgetown Model Arab League? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 17:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are alternate titles written in the form "*Title*; or, *Alternate*"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 16:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Moby-Dick*; or, *The Whale*

*Dr. Strangelove*; or, *How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love the Bomb*

There are a couple other examples that aren't coming to mind right now, but why that particular punctuation for the title and subtitle? The semicolon seems like it could easily be a comma, and the comma after "or" seems completely unnecessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did the German Democratic Party (DDP) lose so many Reichstag seats in the 1920 election? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 19:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The DDP was one of the most powerful parties in the Weimar government, but in 1920 they lost almost half of their seats (75-39). The 1920 elections were the first under the new constitution, which the DDP had a large part in creating. Were the German people dissatisfied with the constitution written by the Weimar coalition? Was there a significant shift in political ideology? Or did the 1919 constitution change the way seats were apportioned? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My best friend's mom died today and I have no idea what to do about it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 05:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read an email this morning about it and texted him right away, he called back and we talked about it. It was... awkward. I had no idea what to say. How do I console a friend who lost a parent? All I could say was, "I'm so sorry." He knows I'm here for him, I'm his best friend too, but I think he also knows that I don't have the slightest idea of how to react to this. 

My mother suggested I go over his house. School is cancelled tomorrow, so I could do that. But what would I do? Just show up, give him a hug, and then...? What is there to say, or do? I don't know if I should try to get his mind off it, or face the reality with him. I just don't know, and I feel like such a shitty friend for not being able to help.

Any advice for what I can do for him would be greatly appreciated, especially if you've dealt with this sort of thing in the past. We're both Seniors in High School, and he's an only child. Also we're both religious, there's a mass for his mother on Monday and I've told him I'm praying for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] A 19th-century rationalist discovers a tribe with curiously accurate myths and rituals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 22:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just found this great Youtube channel, TestTube. All about geopolitics and global economics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 03:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I didn't get into U.Va. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 00:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a personal policy of not telling any of my friends about college decisions, because it either makes me look stupid or arrogant. I've been accepted into two other colleges so far, Purdue and Case Western Reserve. U.Va. wasn't my dream school per se, but it was my top choice. I'm disappointed that I was denied. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [VA, US] Is a Computer Science degree applicable in IP law? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 15:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a High School senior, thinking about my major in college. I'm interested in getting a J.D. So I'm trying to find a major that has some application both within and outside the law. 

My father is a patent attorney specializing in chemical patents, and he tells me that Computer Science is very useful in IP law. I just want to get a second opinion, to be certain. So is comp sci a useful major if I intend to go into law? 

EDIT: Thanks for all the advice! The main reason I'm looking at Comp Sci instead of some other field is because I really love computer science, and my secondary career choice is working as a software developer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I compliment people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 03:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I read "How to Win Friends and Influence People" and I found it very helpful. One part of the book involved having a "new mindset" about how I approach people. It basically suggested I be more appreciative and positive towards everyone.

Now I've always been a pretty negative person. That is, most of my conversations and jokes are complaints about things I don't like. I hate this, I hate that, you're shoes look funny, haha this girl put on way too much makeup. 

I want to change that. I want to be a more positive person, but... no matter how hard I try, I can't seem to escape my negative mindset. I see the bad in everyone and everything, when I encounter someone or something new my first thought is always "how can I criticize this?" And for the life of me I cannot compliment people.

I'll stand in front of someone and just have absolutely no idea what is good about them. I draw a blank, completely. I tried to write down, just now, all the things I like about my best friend. All I got was "he agrees with me on a lot of topics" "we share an interest in geopolitics" "he's in a lot of my classes" and "he's diligent". That's 4 things I like about my BEST FRIEND. And 3 of them aren't even character traits, they're just circumstantial similarities.

The post title is "how do I compliment people?" and I went off on something of a tangent there, sorry about that. But how can I find the good in people rather than the bad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've never exercised before, but I want to start </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 04:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an absolute, complete beginner. The closest I ever got to "exercise" was playing basketball in middle school. I'm now a high school senior. 

I'm super skinny (120 lbs at 5"8') and I want to get in shape. Problem is, I don't have access to a car, which means no gym. 

I thought /r/bodyweightfitness would be the right place to go, so I came here and looked at the recommended routine. I barely understand a word of it. The only exercises on there that I've heard of are the pull ups and push-ups. And I'm still in the process of finding an adequate place to do pull ups.


I'm really at a loss here. I need to get in shape, but the learning barrier is so great that every time I try, I end up giving up without even getting to the exercise. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE Always feel sick after eating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 01:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It strikes me that this might not be normal. Anytime I eat a significant amount of any kind of food, I feel nauseous afterwards. I've never thrown up from eating too much, and I really never feel *that* kind of nausea, but for a good 30 minutes after every meal I'm just miserable. 

EDIT: Also, I'm a really skinny guy, 115 lbs at 17. I work out very little, but enough to keep me in some semblance of shape, and regularly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel like I've pissed away my high school years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 16:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We just had a wind ensemble concert, which made me realize how much everyone else has done, and how little I have. Sebi got the award and scholarship for musicianship, and he's in the play, and he does crew. Joseph is also a devoted musician, he's the lead in the play, and he's in a band with some other kids. Daniel is Model U.N. Secretary-General, and in Cappies, and NHS. Josh and Wendell are undersecretaries-general, and in charge of Honor Council, and they each play a sport. 

Me? I'm undersecretary-general of MUN. That's it. I tried out for the play, as I have for the past three years, but I didn't get cast. I'm not even very good at Model U.N., and it certainly isn't a time - consuming hobby. So now I'm sitting on a fat lot of nothing, nothing to show for three and a half years of high school. Every day, I went home and messed around on the internet. Most of it was video games. Some was reddit. Some, I am proud of, learning from videos and classes and Wikipedia. But most of my high school years have been useless filler.

And now I want to change all that, but... what am I supposed to do? I'm halfway through Senior year. It's too late to start anything; most clubs are full and not accepting new members. 

So here I stand, alone and bored to misery. Seven nights a week I have nothing to do. I've wasted high school, the years that are supposed to be some of the best years in my life. And I'll never get the chance to live them right. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My mother is the noisiest fucking person in the whole goddamn world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 02:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't work. I can't sleep. I can't study. I can't focus. SHE WON'T SHUT UP! As soon as she gets home it's nothing but chatty chatty bitch. "Guess what I did today." "How was your day?" "What do you have planned for the week?" 

And then the complaints, dear god, the complaints. "You don't spend enough time with us." "You have to stop being so irritable." "Hey, I'm just concerned for you."

If you were concerned for me, maybe you would listen to what I'm saying and GIVE ME ONE. FUCKING. SECOND. OF. SILENCE.

I'm falling apart here. I want to get better, I've got plans, and every once in a while I get in the right mindset to put myself on track. But if I want to swim, I first have to be able to float. And I can't keep my head above water if this noisy woman keeps following me around. 

I'm never alone. I want to be. I want just a few hours where nobody can bother me, nobody knows or cares where I am. I want to sit in the middle of siberia and cry my eyes out and shout at the world and release all these pent-up emotions without worry of others reacting. I wouldn't mind being around people so much if I didn't have one of them constantly present and needing my attention. She's like a goddamn dog. I have to constantly devote my attention to her or she'll whine and complain. Even if she has someone else's attention, and doesn't need mine, she's always talking. She makes me think of the Nile; a constant flow of words, and at regular intervals, a flood.

/rant 

That kind of came out more angry than depressed. I promise, I have depression, these are just the feelings that came out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Survivalocke </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 18:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am finding Alpha Sapphire too easy, so I'm imposing a few restrictions on my play. It's something of a stretch to call it a Nuzlocke variant, but I'm calling it survivalocke nonetheless. 

**Rules**

1. You may never use a Pokemon center to heal. 

2. If a Pokemon faints, you can keep it in your party and bring it back with revive.

3. You are not allowed to withdraw any pokemon from the PC. Ever. That means that any Pokemon you deposit is dead, and you must have an empty spot in your team if you want to catch any new Pokemon.

4. You are forbidden from buying anything except decorations, TM's and repels.

**Optional**

1. You must nickname all Pokemon. 

2. You can use the daycare for breeding, but any Pokemon who enter the daycare must be deposited in the box as soon as you take them out. 

3. After each mandatory healing spot, you must deposit any Pokemon that were fainted when you came to it. 

**Tips**

Catch a Zigzagoon for Pickup. Maybe catch several. 

Plant tons of berries. The challenge becomes much better once you've got some leppa berries. 

So, that's my challenge. I'm about halfway through and it's very fun and very difficult. What do you think?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Race=/=Culture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 05:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I see a discussion of racism come up, nobody seems to think it proper to bring up this distinction. 

Race it's something genetic, something you're born with and cannot change. It's physical; a certain shape of eyes, a certain color of skin, a certain shape of face.

Culture is something completely different. It it's a set of values, a mindset, a way of thinking. A person's culture can change (we call that assimilation). Culture is a totally mental and internal thing.

Sometimes, cultures are bad. It's not just that certain people of that culture are bad, the culture itself has values that are (from a Western, American standpoint) simply wrong. Korean culture, for example, prizes the Korean race as inherently superior to all other people. Arabian culture holds women as lesser than men. Etc, etc.

Well, I guess what I'm trying to say is that discrimination based on culture is not racism. It is almost never justified, but still it cannot be called racism. Race=/=Culture. It's generally bad to be prejudiced against either, but they aren't one and the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Evolution is unique to Earth. All other life-bearing planets contain only one species. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 19:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just want to be alone. Is that so much to ask? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 00:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm the Holy See in a committee about Cybersecurity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 18:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Combat is the Most Common Game Mechanic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 22:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all know the basis of narrative design: conflict. Conflict is the way a story progresses, it's how things change. Games have a difficult time with conflict. 

In literature, you can read the characters mind, know exactly what they're thinking. This makes is simple, trivial, to give the characters *internal* conflict **(Man vs Self)**. It comes with a drawback, though, in that a writer cannot convey any senses with the work. The writing is absorbed through the eyes, but the reader does not *see* what is happening. Any description of sensation, visual, auditory, olfactory, emotional, or otherwise, must be imagined by the reader because it is not provided by the work. 

In film, or theatre, sensation is different. The viewer can *see* and *hear* what is happening. While this allows more clarity in those sensations, it comes at the cost of other senses. It is more difficult to imagine the smell and feel of something if you are outright given it's look and sound. So while you know what the characters are doing and saying, other feelings must be conveyed through those senses. Internal conflict is still very much present, but it must be mirrored by *external* conflict. 

Still, this has an advantage over games. Film and theatre are simply stories being told. Audience participation is rare, and only ever present as an extremely simple gimmick of the art. So while they can only convey visuals and sounds, they can use those to convey other sensations. Take the film *127 Hours*. It's a work that relies on emotion and physical sensation imagined by the viewer. Without it, the film would be an extremely dull tale of a kid sitting still for a long time. So, film and theatre are unable to use purely internal conflict, but they can very easily use non-violent external conflict and internal conflict together **(Man vs World)**.

Games are restricted more than any other narrative medium by the need for *meaningful interaction*. Games have to portray and resolve conflict by having the player complete tasks using mechanics. 

*Mechanics.* These are the heart of the problem. Games must give players a mechanic, a set of tools with which they can solve *all* the problems they encounter. For simplicity's sake, most games have a single central mechanic. What does this mechanic have to be? Well, it has to be capable of resolving conflict in the game. It has to be broad enough to cover the diverse array of conflicts that games must have in order to not be repetitive. It also has to be broad enough to include a wide array of tools that games need for the same reason. Those tools have to all be able to manipulate some aspect of the game that the various conflicts all share in common.

So, a broad mechanic capable of resolving many different instances of conflict through the same ends but many different means. What is the first thing you can think of that fits all those criteria? That's right: combat. You can fight lots of different enemies, you can use lots of different weapons, and everyone shares the health bar in common. It's simple, it's easy, it's flexible. Combat can be changed up with a bunch of different gimmicks but remain fundamentally the same, recognizable pattern of conflict: make the bad guy's health hit zero. 

But what other mechanics can accomplish all this? Lets take a look at some excellent non-combat games. 

First, Portal. The central mechanic in Portal is movement, or more specifically, portals. Portal presents conflict as **Man vs World**, Chell against the facility. The facility gives her a wide array of problems which can all be solved by the central mechanic.  Check, check and check. Portal is the best example of the puzzle genre done right. The player is in conflict with the world, and has all the agency they need to find out how to overcome the conflict.

Second, Minecraft. Yes, Minecraft does have combat, but that's not the point of it. Minecraft is interesting in that it's conflict is not really obvious. At first glance, it appears to have no conflict at all. Really, though, it is just a struggle between the realities of nature (there are no trees here) and the desires of the player (I want to build a treehouse!). The central mechanic of Minecraft is building. It is used to manipulate the world around the player to create what the player wants. You can build with any of the blocks/materials, overcoming the inertia of the world to accomplish the goals. Check, check, check. Minecraft is definitely a game, yes, but it lacks a strong narrative structure. This is common in games where building is the primary mechanic.

Third, I'm going to go with Monaco: What's Yours is Mine. I wanted to pick a stealth game that isn't about assassination. In Monaco, you and up to 3 others have to stealthily break into places and steal things. I'm identifying stealth as the central mechanic here, which is a very broad and difficult to define concept. It includes movement and timing. Basically, the conflict is between the player who wants to not get caught and the "world" which wants to catch any thieves. The mechanic includes a variety of characters with different tools, used not to resolve conflicts but to avoid them. While avoiding conflict is a conflict in and of itself, this makes stealth games very interesting to contemplate. They are usually also combat games, but rather than trying to engage in combat the player is to try to avoid them. But, anyway, the variety of conflicts in the game are all solvable with the central mechanic. Check, check, check. The stealth mechanic struggles with its identity, usually ending up as a hybrid stealth-combat game. This is mostly because stealth is not inherently entertaining. Extra Credits put it best: Stealth is about making waiting engaging.

Fourth, racing games. I don't have any specific examples other than Mario Kart, which isn't really a good one. Sorry, it's not really my genre. Anyways, racing games are both Man vs Man and Man vs World. The player is racing to compete against other racers, but the ability to actually impact the other competitors directly is very, very limited. The central mechanic is obvious, movement, and it relies on reflex speed to be competent. Clearly, movement is the primary way by which each race, each conflict, is resolved. Check and check. Racing games are sort of like real-time highscore games: you're competing mostly indirectly, like trying to get a highscore that beats your friend, but you can also see them progress simultaneously with you.

And I'm having difficulty finding any others. This post is already very long, and a bit rambling. I'm going to post it as is and continue with edits. I'm really interested in getting a discussion going about the prevalence of combat in games, so please comment with your opinions on the subject. I'll leave you with this final thought: Puzzle games include a wide variety of mechanics, and are so different in scope that they do not deserve to be lumped together into the "puzzle" category. 

**TL;DR: Combat is the easiest form of engaging conflict in a game, but is it the best?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Magneto vs Amon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 21:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Amon, the villain from Avatar: Legend of Korra)

1-on-1, in a major city that neither are familiar with. Amon's bloodbending/chi-blocking is fully functional, and he is able to take away Magneto's "metalbending". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm Crisis Director for a small, 1-topic committee about ISIS. What are some fun, interesting crises I can use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 18:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to be alone. But nobody understands what alone means. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 23:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care if there are people around me, talking, crowding, making noise and taking space. I would be more alone in central Shanghai than in my own home. Because in Shanghai, nobody knows me. Nobody cares about me. If I broke down crying no one would give a damn. But in my house, I always have to be conscious of what I say and do. I'm playing a role, and I'm tired of being on stage all the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should Mercenaries be outlawed under the Geneva Conventions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 20:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The definition of a mercenary under international law was clarified in The Protocol Additional Geneva Conventions 1977, article 47, which reads: 

    Art 47. Mercenaries

        1. A mercenary shall not have the right to be a combatant or a prisoner of war.
        2. A mercenary is any person who:

            (a) is especially recruited locally or abroad in order to fight in an armed conflict;
            (b) does, in fact, take a direct part in the hostilities;
            (c) is motivated to take part in the hostilities essentially by the desire for private gain and, in fact, is promised, by or on behalf of a Party to the conflict, material compensation substantially in excess of that promised or paid to combatants of similar ranks and functions in the armed forces of that Party;
            (d) is neither a national of a Party to the conflict nor a resident of territory controlled by a Party to the conflict;
            (e) is not a member of the armed forces of a Party to the conflict; and
            (f) has not been sent by a State which is not a Party to the conflict on official duty as a member of its armed forces.

More information can be found [here](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mercenary#Laws_of_war).

What should the legal status of mercenaries be? Are the foreign fighters for ISIS technically mercenaries? Should they be? Speaking of ISIS, notice how all nations are extremely hesitant to put "boots on the ground" in Iraq and Syria, because they fear public opinion backlash against an unpopular war. Were mercenaries legal, states could employ them to fight in such a war, and it would be much easier for wealthy countries to intervene in foreign conflicts.

There are two clearly prominent issues with legalizing mercenaries. First, they are answerable to no law for the crimes they commit while fighting. Second, large, organized modern armies without a country may decide to intervene in conflict independently, intent on profiting from assets captured or even overthrowing the government and installing themselves as rulers.

On the other hand, legal mercenary companies could give citizens to fight for causes that the military leadership of their nation does not want to be a part of; people can decide their level of involvement in foreign conflicts. They also reduce the need for some governments to maintain expensive standing armies, and could provide training if necessary.

Discuss! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] Canadian-style flag of Ireland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 01:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Ray Bradbury's "The Long Rain," men land on a planet on which it is always raining. How possible is it for that to happen to Earth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 22:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drop thousands of Honduran teenagers infected with Ebola on ISIS from a Malaysian Airlines plane. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 17:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: Students should not be punished by their schools for actions committed outside of school. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 03:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a pretty straightforward issue, as far as I see it. I'm a student who attends a high school, and I think it's ridiculous to punish students for breaking rules that are not those of the school. If somebody sees a teacher that they hate outside of school, why shouldn't they insult them? Other than the fact that it is a mean and irresponsible thing to do. If they break the law, they should be tried by a court, before a jury of their peers. Not by a school official. 

The main counter-argument I see is the issue of cyber-bullying. Frankly, I don't see the problem. If it's rude, alert the perpetrator's parents. If it's harassment, report it to the police. If neither of those are the case, well, suck it up. I don't like to say that, but adults don't get an all-powerful school administration to which to cry when they are being picked on. 

Now, if the student is on a school trip, or wearing school merchandise, then yes, the school can enforce their rules in the interests of protecting their reputation. Otherwise, students shouldn't be punished in school for infractions committed out of school.

CMV

_____

 *Hello, users of CMV! This is a footnote from your moderators. We'd just like to remind you of a couple of things. Firstly, please remember to* ***[read through our rules](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/rules)***. *If you see a comment that has broken one, it is more effective to report it than downvote it. Speaking of which,* ***[downvotes don't change views](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/guidelines#wiki_upvoting.2Fdownvoting)****! If you are thinking about submitting a CMV yourself, please have a look through our* ***[popular topics wiki](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/populartopics)*** *first. Any questions or concerns? Feel free to* ***[message us](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=/r/changemyview)***. *Happy CMVing!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Incorrect Serial Key" Bug is apparently happening to Napoleonic Wars servers right now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 02:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a thread on the forums about it, seems like all the NW servers aren't working tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How might I set the level cap lower than 100? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 00:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking to make a small hack focused on fighting with low-level pokemon, probably maximum lvl 5 or 10. How might I implement this?

EDIT: Preferably in RSE, but I'm alright with FRLG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [CW] In less than 250 words, tell me why having a minimum of 250 words as a writing constraint is ridiculous. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 14:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: Public corporations are inherently evil, and immoral business practices are caused primarily by the existence of shareholders. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 00:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets assume that a man is the sole proprietor of a company. That company is owned by one person. He can do whatever he pleases with it. He can use it solely to make profit, or he can direct its energy and resources to other endeavors. The company is an extension of the man. If the man is moral, the company will be moral in its practices to the extent that the man can control it. And being the sole owner, he can exercise quite a bit of control. So, as there are moral and immoral men, there are moral and immoral sole proprietorships. 

But look at a public corporation. There might be 10,000 people who all own a part of the company. A company acts on the behalf of its owner, but when there are so many, how does one decide how to act? Almost any goal available to that company will please some, but anger many of the shareholders. 

So how does the company act on behalf of the collective shareholders? It orients itself towards the goal that everyone can agree on, the common ground for the shareholders: profit. It is the only aim that a public corporation can select that will please all of its owners. 

And when the aim is ambiguous as "make money," there will be moral issues. The CEO has the job of "make money for the company." Without any details other than that, it is his duty to choose the most profitable course of action, without regards to morality. After all, he works for the shareholders, and they can't all agree on morality. While some may be upset that he chooses "immoral" business practices, they can take comfort in the fact that morality does not factor into his decision. 

As a corporation, the company is no longer an expression of a person. It is the expression of the one common goal of a large group of people. With nothing more to guide the decisions, it will take the most profitable courses of action and ignore any harm they cause to others.

CMV

_____

 *Hello, users of CMV! This is a footnote from your moderators. We'd just like to remind you of a couple of things. Firstly, please remember to* ***[read through our rules](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/rules)***. *If you see a comment that has broken one, it is more effective to report it than downvote it. Speaking of which,* ***[downvotes don't change views](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/guidelines#wiki_upvoting.2Fdownvoting)****! If you are thinking about submitting a CMV yourself, please have a look through our* ***[popular topics wiki](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/populartopics)*** *first. Any questions or concerns? Feel free to* ***[message us](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=/r/changemyview)***. *Happy CMVing!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pictures from tonight's photoshoot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 05:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm experiencing a bug that is preventing me from arranging any marriages. Is anyone else having this issue? Is there a fix? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 22:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, literally any marriages. It happened in the middle of the game, I was emperor and I decided to arrange a marriage for one of my daughters. I clicked the arrange marriage button, and I got the little popup with the list of candidates. Only there were none. At all. Then I assassinated my wife to try to marry another woman. Tried to arrange marriage for myself and, again, no candidates. I was a 50-year-old christian emperor, and there were definitely characters in my court that I should have been able to marry. AI characters are getting married just fine, but I am unable to arrange ANY marriages. I tried restarting, ran the morehumans and marry_anyone commands, inviting characters to court, etc. Nothing. I even killed my character to see if my heir would have the same problem. Sure enough, he did.

I've never experienced anything like this bug, and I've searched everywhere for a fix, but I can't find anything. Has anybody else experienced this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As the King of Ireland, I accidentally inherited the Byzantine Empire. How can I lose that title without losing Ireland? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 04:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title says all. They have different succession laws, so if I wait for my character to die the titles will go to different heirs. But then my primary heir will be the Emperor instead of the king. Is there any way to ditch the Byzantine crown, preferably to a dynasty member, and remain an independent Ireland?

EDIT: Just to clarify here, if I die then I play as the heir to my primary title, the Byzantine Empire. I can't make Ireland primary, because it is lower ranking than an empire, and I can't grant my primary title to someone unless I have another title of equal rank i.e. an empire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What countries without unique national ideas deserve them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 19:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Explain Macbeth like IAmA hardcore Crusader Kings 2 player </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 18:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When creating the government of America, was it ever considered to model the new country after the Holy Roman Empire? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 23:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The former colonies, as I understand, were very much against a strong, centralized American government. The Holy Roman Empire was still around at the time of the revolution, and it seems to me that that sort of government would have appealed to the founders. Was it ever suggested that the new American nation have a government similar to the HRE? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened to teamspeak? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 02:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck France... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 21:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> France attacked my 72,000 man army in Lombardia with a stack of 32,000 and won. The worst part about it isn't just that they won, but they ATTACKED. I don't care how good their armies were, no goddamn general is going to attack an army twice his size across a river in a fortified mountain unless he's out of his fucking mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to balance the Espionage idea group </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 21:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Espionage idea group has a lot of potential. But right now, it is lackluster and underpowered. With a few changes, they could be an interesting and viable group without being too overpowered.

**Problem: Sabotage Reputation**

 This action could be a tool to weaken the diplomatic standing of an enemy, attack their relationships with allies and make them more vulnerable. Instead, it damages their relationship with their *neighbors, enemies and rivals*. Why in God's name would I send a diplomat to make Burgundy hate France? Burgundy already hates France! It's only use right now is to make some electors dislike Austria in the HRE. 

**Solution: Make it targeted**

Instead of a penalty for all neighbors and enemies, make it a penalty for a specific nation. I could use 1 diplomat to make Venice hate France, and if used at a tense moment in their relations, break their alliance. The ability to target weak alliances and break them with Espionage would make Sabotage Reputation more useful, more fun, and more strategic.

**Problem: Sow Discontent**

Sow Discontent curently gives the targeted nation +1 revolt risk and +50% stability cost. While the revolt risk is nice, the Stab cost is useless. In my experience, a country with low stability that I am sowing discontent in will just wait for my agent to be discovered, and when he is, boost stability before I can send another diplomat. It's impossible to maintain long-term instability in a rival.

**Solution: Add Potential Rebels**

Sow Discontent could be used as a supplement to Rebel Support. I often encounter a situation where there are no rebels to support in a country, which is frustrating. If Sow Discontent added a small, low-risk group of potential rebels for me to support, I could spend a bunch of cash to increase their revolt risk and, for quite a fortune in diplomatic upkeep, weaken the target's military and prestige. 

The benefits of Sowing Discontent would be to incite potential rebellions, and maybe even to choose the type of rebels (though that would probably be too powerful). The costs would be high discovery chance, maybe with a prestige penalty if discovered.

This would ideally be instead of all the current effects, to prevent it from being to OP.

**Problem: Assassination**

This is the most widely wanted feature in the Espionage group. The ability to attempt assassinations on rival monarchs. It's a popular idea, but also a very powerful one. To keep the balance, it has to be difficult to assassinate a leader, but to keep it strategy/skill based, it shouldn't be just a random die roll.

**Solution: Assassination Plots**

Rather than taking a single action to kill a monarch, make assassination plots a thing you can fund, the same way as supporting rebels. Their chance of attempting an assassination would be taken from several other factors, like legitimacy/republican tradition, stability, base revolt risk, etc.

There is also the question of which idea this should replace. My vote is for getting rid of Sow Discontent altogether.

**Problem: Spy Offense**

What the hell does it even do? Reduce discovery chance? Big whoop, I can just send a new diplomat as soon as the old one is expelled. It is an absolutely worthless stat to invest in. The most annoying thing about it is that it doesn't actually improve your covert actions. The only real benefit of high Spy Offense is that you are *slightly* less likely to get AE from fabricating a claim. And hell, you don't even need Espionage ideas to do that.

**Solution: Have it impact your covert actions**

It's a pretty simple fix. (Your spy offense - their spy defense) * base effect of covert action = Spy offense/defense modifier 

So say I Sabotage Reputation against France. Sabotage Reputation gives a base -50 penalty. I have 35% Spy Offense, thanks to Espionage Ideas and my Spymaster advisor. France has +5% Spy Defense from having 1 stability, and +15% for Ile-de-France's base tax. (25%-5%-15%) * (-50) = -7.5

So that would give France a penalty of -57.5 relations.

I love Espionage ideas, I think it's a lot of fun to use your diplomats to manipulate and infulence the political landscape without getting your hands dirty. Right now, they're underwhelming, but with a few tweaks and buffs, Espionage ideas can be one of the most popular and strategic groups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any negative effects for bacteria in developing a resistance to an antibiotic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 04:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the growing success of the LGBT rights movement, is it really worth it to segregate by sex/gender anymore? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 15:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is somewhat more of a cultural topic than a political one, so if there's a better sub for this let me know.

I got into a discussion about "don't ask don't tell" earlier, with my friend defending the policy. He argued that if we completely accepted homosexuality as an official sexuality, we would have to not discriminate between heterosexuals and homosexuals. If we don't differentiate, then we cannot allow 2 gay men to share a public restroom, since a heterosexual man has a different restroom than a heterosexual women. He said that if homosexuality is fully accepted, we would have to either make all public restrooms private, or shatter our cultural norms and make all public restrooms unisex.

The way I phrased it was somewhat poor, but my friend is not homophobic. He said that we should pretty much just ignore the logical issues that arise from accepting LGBT rights by pretending that they don't exist sometimes. 

I do not support "don't ask don't tell," but I think he had some interesting points. Is it really worth it to maintain sex-segregated restrooms and showers? Would it perhaps be better to integrate, and trust people to be mature about it? 

The side in favour of sex-segregated facilities would argue that restrooms, of all places, should be based on a person's physical sex rather than sexuality or gender. Women's restrooms can contain things like tampon dispensers, which is something that has no need to be in a men's restroom.

The most popular argument on this side is the issue of sexual harassment. Fear of rape would possibly make women afraid to use public restrooms or showers, because of their vulnerability in the presence of unknown men. However, to tie this back to the LGBT movement, men might be afraid of rape at the hands of other men. Or women, by other women.

Should sex-integrated restrooms be considered? If so, how could the problems involved be averted? If not, how should we reconcile the differences between the sexes with the accepted differences between sexualities?


Sources:

In [The Apartheid of Sex](http://www.abebooks.com/9780044409588/Apartheid-Sex-Manifesto-Freedom-Gender-0044409583/plp) Martine Rothblatt compared sex segregation with racial discrimination in the Jim Crow era, and referenced the Supreme Court's ruling on Separate but Equal as a reason sex-segregated restrooms are unconstitutional. 

[Coming Out of the Water Closet](http://law-journals-books.vlex.com/vid/coming-closet-segregated-bathrooms-65019823) argues that sex-segregation marginalises sexual minorities, and forces a binary societal view of gender. 

The *Harvard Crimson* expressed support for sex-segregation on modesty, privacy and safety grounds in [this](http://www.thecrimson.com/article/2011/2/11/bathrooms-genderneutral-harvard-harassment/) editorial. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favorite card games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 18:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Specifically deck of 52 cards. What are the best games you've played? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody know how to hack the berry/clock system in Emerald? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 00:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to make a farming-themed hack, but I don't know how to make the berry system work properly. I intend to have a faster in game clock (~1 minute real time = 1 hour in game), and make certain events trigger a jump forward. Resting in bed would jump forward 8 hours, Pokemon Contests jump forward 4 hours, so on. 

Does anybody know how this could be made possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need help. But I can't go to my parents. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 04:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a rising Senior in High School. I've finally recognised my depression after years of denial, and I want to get treatment. But for that, I have to talk to my parents, and they are not going to support me. My older brother told our parents that he was depressed, and they attacked him for it. They thought it was just sloth, and they refused to "waste" money on a therapist when he could just "snap out of it." 

I'm so frustrated right now. I have finally accepted my problem, and I admit that I need help. Actually getting the help is supposed to be the easy part. But I see no outcome that involves the treatment I need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the first time in 5 years, I cried last night. Thank you /r/depression </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 04:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've though I was depressed for a long time, 1 or 2 years. Never felt any reason to figure it out. Last night, though, I was feeling extra down. So, out of curiosity, I typed "Reddit.com/r/depression" into the search bar. I read some of the posts on this subreddit, first the recent ones, then sorted by top of all time.

I cried. It was great. All the dullness I've felt was actually expressed. I felt an emotion, for the first time in God knows how long. A real emotion, not an instinctive, reactionary feeling. It was a sad emotion, but it was something. I was alive.

I've never considered suicide. I don't want to die, but I do want to stop. Just stop everything and be still for a while. I feel tired constantly, and everything just feels dull. My brain is muddled, and I'm terrified that I'm becoming less alert, less smart. I can't remember details well. I'm really just moving through life because it's there. I lie awake every night wishing I wasn't sleeping alone. 

I've felt all of that for years now. And all of those thoughts have been expressed in /r/depression posts by other people. It's an incredible relief to know that there are people here who understand. Not just sympathy, but empathy. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I convert a CK2 save with the Holy Roman Empire that I changed the name of, will it revert to being called "Holy Roman Empire?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 23:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, I play CK2, take the Holy Roman Empire and rename it "European Union." Then I convert the save to EU4. Will the HRE be called "European Union" or "Holy Roman Empire?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
