<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3094</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 05:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That part of it is definitely what keeps me going. I love lifting, and I have seen a change in my numbers, which is something I honestly didn't expect at all. 
  
As far as food, I have been watching my macros like a hawk and I've read just about everything I can find on the proper kinds of food. I have spoken to many professionals as I received treatment for anorexia, but they typically advise against getting too deep into any type of fitness program because of how obsessive people with eating disorders tend to be. Kind of like a "gateway drug" to falling back into old habits. I feel like I've made enough progress to handle it, but it's tough. Thank you for your advice. It really helps to know people care.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 05:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typically it is, but in special cases (such as anorexia) your body does all kinds of things to fight what you are doing. For example, it will even begin to produce a very thin, fine layer of hair called lanugo. More or less what the guy above me said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 05:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do understand the medication part; was it a lithium based med? Anything lithium based causes unbelievably rapid weight gain.  
  
Thank you for sharing your experience. It is rare to see a male speak about living with anorexia, and I'm sure it's difficult. I want so badly to have a healthy relationship with food. I just want to FEEL healthy. And I have been feeling so much better, it's just those thoughts that creep in telling me that I'm doing something wrong because I'm not hungry. The fear is a major part.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 22/f: From an ED to serious lifting, and I need your help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 01:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, Fittit. I've lurked for a while and I guess it's time to suck it up and ask for help. Also, apologies in advance if my formatting sucks as I'm on mobile, and for how long this will surely end up being. 
  
I have struggled with weight issues my entire life. I was always just a little bigger than my friends, and it secretly tore me up. My food issues got pretty serious around the time I turned 17. I started eating less, losing weight, and getting compliments. It felt good, so I kept doing it. I was very athletic all my life; I played softball from ages 4-18, and played on multiple competitive traveling teams almost year round from about 12-18. I played catcher exclusively, so I stayed toned and rather muscular without much extra work. However, my body issues and eating issues really got in the way by the time I was supposed to start college, and lost me a softball scholarship. This is where it turned dangerous.   
  
I started to heavily restrict my diet, and it continued to get worse and worse as time went by. My goal intake was 500 calories a day. I became anemic, I was losing my hair, I was dizzy, couldn't sleep, etc. I know it sounds crazy, but I truly was convinced that I wasn't hurting myself. It made me feel strong to lose weight and buy smaller clothes. It was an obsession, but it was so, so hard to keep up.  At some point I sort of lost motivation and  started slowly gaining weight, though I wasn't happy about it. In this time (right before my 20th birthday) I became pregnant. Eating during pregnancy was a no brainer, even for me. Aside from a few short bouts of restricting days, I had a perfectly healthy pregnancy and a perfectly healthy baby girl. However, as soon as she was born, the disordered eating came back twofold.  
  
Fast forward another year of severe restricting, health issues, struggling, weight loss, weight gain, and being 100% reckless with my health and future. It was worse than it was before, and it was ruining my life and my relationship with my boyfriend. One day, I was staring at my daughter running back and forth. She was asking me to get up and play with her, and it hit me.  
  
"I will not be alive to enjoy her life if I don't fix this."   
  
I bought "Thinner, Leaner, Stronger" by Mike Matthews and decided right then and there that I was going to change my life for the better, and then I binged on any and every food I could get my hands on for a whole month. I finally got to the point where my (rapid) weight gain tapered off and I figured I had more or less reset my metabolism, and I prepared to start some serious weightlifting and macro planning. 
  
I've been at it for about five weeks now and I truly LOVE lifting! My intake is about 1530 calories a day and I pay extremely close attention to macros. But here is my problem. Compared to just not eating, seeing results seems to take FOREVER. I have spent many years programming myself to think that feeling hungry is strong and being full means I fucked up and I should be ashamed. Moderation was never something I practiced; it was either eat every single thing I can find, or eat barely anything at all. Losing weight and seeing a difference in your body doesn't take long when you're starving yourself. My question is, how do I push through the disordered thoughts and stay patient? How long does it normally take to really see a difference in your body? I find it really hard to stay motivated sometimes, and I have bouts where I binge like crazy and get really down because I don't feel like I'm accomplishing anything. How do I keep my focus on the prize?  
  
I don't want to be sickeningly thin anymore. I want to be STRONG. I want it so, so badly. I just need some advice.  
  
TL;DR: went from anorexic to a skinnyfat physique, and now trying to lift seriously. How do I stay motivated and patient in regard to seeing results?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 07:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stand it up in the cup holder on the next hot day! It'll re-melt flat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 20:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was about 6:30 am, I had just got back from the gym, and I was starving. I wasn't being especially attentive to my banana separating technique.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
