<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6681</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 17:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello there!

I know that gaining sucks, and with an eating disorder it can make you feel like the world is ending, but I just thought I would leave a comment to say it's not all that bad! In reality, half a pound is hardly anything. 3500 calories is one pound of fat. Therefore 1750 calories is 0.5 pounds of fat. A 1750 calorie deficit isn't too big, and can be easily lost within a couple of days. It can even be lost that quickly at a healthy, non "eating disordered" rate! And that's not even taking into consideration water/sodium weight. 

Sometimes our illness can make larger numbers seem scary. It sucks, but your not alone here3 . I hope you're having a great day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 18:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slightly hungover from last night, with no idea how many calories I ate. Oh well.

I finished lunch at 12:15pm and I think I am done for the day. I might fast for 24 hours, but we'll see if I can get away with it.   

**Breakfast**: Skipped

**Lunch** : Tofu and Spinach (315 calories)

**Dinner**: Skipped

**Snacks**: Skipped

**Total**: 315 calories.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, thanks for the "advice". I think my friend was mainly worried because she knew I had an eating disorder to begin with. So she already had raised suspicion.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 22:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went on vacation recently with some friends and I walked 20K+ steps for two days in a row! It's doable but my legs hurt pretty bad haha. Shows just how out of shape I am. Good luck with your goal!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 22:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aweh Thanks, you're so sweet. But yeah it can be scary almost having your secret revealed. I never thought of the cavity thing, I guess I'll have to add that to my growing list of excuses. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 22:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! Your stats look great. If I were you I wouldn't worry too much, (although I know that is easier said than done!). The people "talking behind your back" might just be the ED part of your head talking for you. Chances are he was just concerned, as rapid weight loss is easier to observe.  Based on his previous comments, it seems he is just looking out for you!
Hope you are having a great day!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost caught purging on vacation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 21:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everyone!

Sorry that I haven't posted much, or did any food diaries the last couple days. I actually have been on vacation in the city with my friends. Turns out, I came back with a story to tell. 

 While I was on vacation, I was very worried that I might have to eat "normally" around my friends in order to avoid raising suspicion. I figured 3 meals a day couldn't be /too/ bad... especially since I was walking alot too, I thought I would burn some extra calories. But I forgot about how anxious I feel when it comes to eating around others and eating out at a restaurant. Since we were on vacation, we ate out three times each day with snacks in between aswell. I really wanted to avoid purging, but I will admit that i did purge a couple times. It was just too much to handle. I thought no one noticed at the time (I always said I was just going to the bathroom, no one came with me ever). 

It wasn't until the last meal, when another guy who was on vacation came into the washrooms and asked me what I was doing.. Apparently one of the girls on the trip (most of my friends are female) sent him into the washroom to check in on me and make sure I was okay. He mentioned how she (the girl who sent him in here) thought it was odd that I went to the washroom after every meal. I told him I was fine, and no one ever brought anything up after that. Although I technically wasn't caught purging, I totally thought that I blew my cover right then are there.

 This was way too close of a call. It's August 5th...For those of you who don't know, I am moving 6-8 hours away come September. I will be alone with no one who knows about past history with ana. 

I've made it this far being low-key about my ED...tricking friends... family... and therapists. 

I cannot screw up now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 14:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey and welcome to the sub! I'm so glad I was able to inspire you to participate!(: I Hope you enjoy your stay~  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 20:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry! Everything will be fine. 

I have had days like this in the past too. It is always reassuring (for me atleast) to remind myself that "A calorie is a calorie". In terms of weight loss, it doesn't really matter if that calorie came from brownies or spinach (although nutrition is a different story). 

As long as you are eating under your TDEE, or maintenance value , it's impossible for you to gain any real weight. If the scale goes up a bit after a binge, it's most likely water weight.  There is no need to worry(:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I almost gave myself away. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 19:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello friends - Today I have a little mini story/rant for you. 

So I was at a friend's place yesterday and we were playing a version of family feud. If you don't know what family feud is, it's a game show where you have to guess the most popular responses to survey questions. In the game, you usually have to answer as fast as you can in order to go first.


So we were all having a wonderful time. Then, it was my turn again. The thing with this game, is that it's primarily about responding fast, so it can reveal a lot of your subconscious thoughts. The question was "I love the feeling of being ___" . Without even thinking, I hit the button and said "hungry". I was NOT thinking of the social context I was in. As soon as I said it, I wished that I could take it back. I got a lot of weird stares. Fortunately for me, it was actually the 4th most common response. A couple people started laughing and said things like "who in their right mind enjoys being hungry? lolol". I laughed along with them and tried to play it off as a joke. 


There was only one girl in the room who knew that I had an eating disorder. She knew that I went to inpatient not too long ago because of it too. Luckily for me, her mind seemed to be somewhere else because I don't think she picked up on the little exchange that just happened. Or maybe she did, but she just didn't say anything - who knows?


Anyways, that is my story of the day. 


TLDR:  I almost exposed myself and my eating disorder in a game of family feud, but I don't think anyone really picked up on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
