<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8657</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: When should one be concerned for a friend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 02:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend of mine been losing weight pretty rapidly. She had been advised to lose some weight by a doctor. She is down many pounds over 3 to 4 months.

Currently she says she is happy with meals that are like snacks and lots of water.

As far as I know she has not shown any symptoms like fainting, being dizzy, or the like, but she is quite constipated.

Should I be worried? She has always eaten a lot while I have known her, but not recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Suggested Websites or Books for dealing with BED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 12:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to spare you an extremely long story because if you've dealt with anorexia/ bulimia I'm sure you know exactly what I'm going to say around that time in my life. This is the third time I've typed up a post for this sub and I'm sick of not actually posting it out of fear.

I tried to "defeat" my ED by drinking. That lasted around a year and I've been bulimia free for over two years. Predictably, I developed a binge eating disorder. 

I have two therapists that cover my PTSD. Asking them to focus on my ED alone would keep me from more immediate issues being managed. I have never sought professional ED help. 

A week ago I decided it was a safe time to start restricting my diet in a healthy manor- as the binging has left me morbidly obese at this point and I'm as unhappy as I was when I had my AN. I'm working on a low cal diet around a safe amount of calories per day to get to a healthy weight, but I've been keeping my intake at a barely anorexic level because fucking ED doesn't just disappear and tricks me I guess. I thought it was clear thinking then I realized it was that dusty bitch pretending to be me. I hope that makes sense. After I decided to stop throwing up, I began to see my ED as someone inside of me that i needed to work with. I hope really that makes sense... It's way too easy for me to restrict my calories to an unhealthy level and that has me concerned.

I want to do this right.

I can't work out very much because I have disabling vertigo so my weight loss will revolve around changing my relationship with food.

Are there any videos or books I can read that made a difference for you? Any websites where the focus is on people like me? 

Thank you so very much in advance for any responses.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 14:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts and articles:

[Wrestlers and EDs](http://www.eatingdisordershelpguide.com/eating-disorders/dying-to-gain-a-competitive-edge-wrestlers-at-risk-for-disordered-eating-habits.htm)

[Wrestling and Eating Disorders](http://wrestlingeatingdisorders.blogspot.com/)

[Weight lifting and ED](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2onxf7/request_is_it_unlikely_that_my_fiancee_anorexia/)

[Recovery and exercise](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2bunjx/request_cant_be_recovered_and_exercisediet/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 14:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Girlfriend with bulimia](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1pl03w/sharing_girlfriend_is_recovering_from_bulimia/)

[Helping girlfriend with anorexia](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2ajwpb/sharing_some_of_my_personal_experince_on_how_to/) --restricting and purging can, and many times do, go together.

[Wife with bulimia](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2qvje9/request_please_help_my_wife_used_to_struggle_with/)

[Model with ED](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/14ewvw/post_request_struggling_with_bulimia_and_feeling/)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Athlete, wrestler, with Bulimia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 13:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently a HS wrestler with bulimia because of my fear of "not making weight" for matches. 

i dont have anywhere to go or anybody to talk to and i found this subreddit and i just wanted to share and ask for advice from this community. 

i had this problem last year during wrestling season and it subsided afterwards but now it's coming up again and i'm beginning to purge about once a day. thank you so much!

How can I avoid bulimia this season? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Worried About Girlfriend With BN, Need Advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 13:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Hi all,

My girlfriend has bulimia and I am her (often overly) worried boyfriend. She's had it for a couple years and doesn't quite have it under control. 
We've been great friends for longer than that but only became romantic recently. 

I do my best to be loving and supportive without trying to be Mr. Fix-it. We don't talk much about her disorder, but every time it comes up it hasn't improved.

Recently, she got approved to design and model an outfit for a competition, and I'm worried about her bulimia flaring up. She's done modeling in the past and it didn't do her any favors in the BN department. 

I'm afraid to ask her if it's going to affect her in any way. I realize there's almost nothing I can do, but I just needed to vent about how powerless I feel and accept any advice you all can give me. 

I just want the woman I love to be happy and healthy.

Thanks /r/eatingdisorders. You guys do good work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 14:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Decide to recover](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2gafly/request_how_do_you_decide_to_recover/)

[What is recovery like](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2d7g1l/request_what_is_recovery_like/)

[Not wanting to recover, then wanting to live more than the ED](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2mrtxy/the_truth_about_eating_disorders_one_persons/)

[Depression and recovery](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2303mc/request_battling_depression_with_recovery/)

[Substance abuse and EDs](https://www.nationaleatingdisorders.org/substance-abuse-and-eating-disorders). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: help, how do i decide to recover, bulimia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 14:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please help me... i know it says to keep it short so i will try. 

i have been bulimic for the past three years. unfortunately in the country where i live there is no ED treatment center and our mental hospitals aren't really functioning very well. i have been to one about a month ago because on top of my purging i've started drinking a lot. that is about all i do - i drink at night and if i do eat something during the day i will purge it.

i am of normal weight and i am EXTREMELY EXTREMELY scared to even try recovery.

what do i say? who do i even call? what if they make me eat and i start gaining a lot? like really a lot? will they give me a lot of meds?

i feel like everyone is going to say just go home and don't be a huge pussy. you're fine, just eat. but i can't. and i can't live like this anymore. i've already had a kidney infection that i am almost 100% sure came from my extreme laxative abuse. i will get extreme burning sensations in my stomach and sometimes a feeling like a cramp (not hunger pangs...those used to happen when i was restricting).

my entire family has no clue or knows very little (i am married, with two kids) and they keep telling me to "snap out of it".

i am so very very scared and i feel lost because i have no idea how and where to start and i feel like such a failure.

i have no idea what my question even was. im sorry.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Survey on Mental Health Disorders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 00:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I I am with Drexel University and I am doing my senior thesis on living with mental health disorders. The project will be an educational resource for the general public to attempt to lessen the misconceptions about these disorders. I want to provide primarily first hand information so I am trying to get this survey out. I have already posted it on a few other subs and people seem to respond well.

[Link here](https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1lc70FgP3w1uYNhc8vmQSKyzX0fXHwHl-4tnmr3b9X_Q/viewform).

Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I think my Mom has an eating disorder, I can't seem to get through </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 16:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's been doing this for a few years now (67 yrs old). I believe she is starving herself. I calculated she needs a recommended amount of a day. I have been counting her calories behind her back (she is visiting us for 4 weeks), she is clearly undereating.

 Any time I try to get her to eat something she says she's not hungry. For breakfast she'll have a very small portion. For lunch she'll have, again, a very small portion, for dinner it is hard for her to escape and I try to make her eat but can't ever get more a very small portion in her then it's "i'm full, really, mmm that was good". 

She has no snacks or anything. She doesn't look healthy, looks bony and somewhat pale. When I say things like "I am worried about you, you do not eat enough", it's always "I'm fine, I feel great". 

She is yawning all day and nervous/jittery. I think she's surely malnourished and likely to kill herself soon by doing this to her body. 

My father is an instigator in all this telling her she's fat and when she starves tells her she looks good. She's very skinny at this stage and gaunt. I can't see any way to change this. 

Is there a name for what she is doing? 

Is this common in some women her age? 

How can I best help her? Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to deal with a friend, male, with AN. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 15:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Reddit, my best friend of three years has had an ED far before I've known them. I was so oblivious until I joked about it one day, saw their extremely off-put reaction and began noticing all the typical signs: excuses for not being hungry despite them spending entire days on urbanspoon looking at pictures, googling pictures of food, more time fiddling with food than eating it, being particular about food not touching and then refusing to eat it because it wasn't the way "they liked it", CONSTANT comments about their weight, and thinking any comment about their appearance was a direct comment to how fat they've become.


About a month after noticing all the direct signs, I confronted them and of course, was greeted with lots of attitude and denial despite my very calm and understanding demeanor. For a while, I felt that it was important to bring it up about once a month in order to remind them that despite my knowing, I was caring to them, still cherished the friendship, and that I was still willing to be there for them in case they ever wanted to do anything about it. I began a hobby of ours to try new restaurants every week to encourage them to find the passions and joy that can come from eating, and we have been going strong. This has been happening for two years.


Fast forward to today. Right now we are roommates, and I try my hardest to never allow their ED to become how I identify them, because despite it all, I know they are human and my dear friend. It's come to the point where even after strongly suggesting alternatives to the starvation, with things like therapy, group support, they still refuse strongly, still continue starving themselves, and has continued to watch their own health deteriorate before their eyes - cessation of the menstrual cycle, hypothyroidism, severe nutrient deficiency, thinning of the blood, thinning of the hair, hair falling out, dry and crackled skin, extreme sensitivity to changes in temperature, "greying" of the skin, and only then to say it's because of their "genetics", despite the other five members of their family having perfect health. I've brought it up to their parents only to be responded with a very high level of respect, but still extreme denial from both parents.


Reddit, I'm a 20 year old male college student with a lot more on my plate than my friends ED - engineering school, an internship, and a part time music job that demands lots of my time for practice in order to pay bills. At this point today, I feel so ready to just draw the line and call it quits, because I feel that I've done everything I can do, and that if they aren't willing to open up their ears to anybody's help, even from their best friend, then there's nothing I could do to change their ways. It's become so severe to the point that my friends whom I have around the house have begun to notice and will make unintentional comments, leaving my best friend to feel more insecure and defensive (accusing me of sharing it with everyone) even though I've kept the ED to extreme discretion and have only told my mother who is in the medical field to ask for her guidance. I care so much for them, but in the end, feel that I need to look out for myself now that I feel like it's beginning to take an effect on my emotional health, but don't know if that's even the right thing to do. I don't feel that it's fair that they want to just use me for my friendship, but never address the real problems that true friends have the ability to discuss like adults.


I reach out today because I have no experience with this, and need the perspective of someone who has dealt with this before. 

I'm desperate, I'm confused, and more importantly, I feel so defeated that even with my extreme patience (it may sound cocky, but I know that I've been abundantly patient), I haven't been able to get them to even take the first step to treating this, let alone even have them acknowledge it. 

I'm still treated with adamant denial, extreme close-mindedness, and I need help other than my own. 

Am I bad friend for wanting to move on? What should I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My daughter, 13, has just been diagnosed with an ED, but I am uncertain and want her to get the right help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 15:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My daughter has just been diagnosed with an ED. She is 13, undereating and underweight. I am not sure it is an ED and want to get her the right help. 

6 months ago she started with stomach pains whenever she ate. Numerous trips to the gp and eventually to a pediatrician by Sept she was diagnosed with stomach inflammation. However she has not responded to medication and in fact limited her diet even more, both in variety of foods she can eat and quantity. Scans and blood tests have all come back completely normal, they can't find any reason to explain the worsening pain. We saw the consultant again this week who basically said she can't find anything physically wrong with her now, and believes she has developed an ED and the original inflammation has healed. She is booked to go to hospital next week.

However i don't see evidence that she wants to lose weight, although I do see that she has many inconsistencies regarding what is good or bad food and when she feels stressed it directly affects her stomach.

 Can it be an ED without the weight issues? 

I guess I don't know a lot about ED and am worried that if it isn't, the Drs will miss what it is and my girl will hate me for not believing her. 

On the other hand if it is an ED I want her to get the help she needs to be well again. 

My heart is breaking for her either way. Can any of you relate? 

How can I support her if it is an ED?

Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm on a panel discussion for eating disorders and I need help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 15:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A week from today, I'm involved in an event for teenagers. Within that, there's panel discussion where we talk and people ask questions. 

I'm on one for mental health and my focus is eating disorders. I used to have one when I was ~13 and I'm 18 now. I'm recovered but I still have to check myself when I start new diets or exercise regimens. I have to be completely honest about myself on whether or not something is healthy for me and it can get pretty difficult. 

But back to the topic, I definitely have experience and can talk freely. 

My question to you is if there's something that I definitely need to say during the event? My bigger concern however is making sure that I'll be okay. I'm a strong person but I want to make sure that I won't get triggered or that I will know how to handle it.

Should I talk about my experiences if it is going to trigger me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Stressful week next week- worried about judgements, evaluating my recovery progress. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 15:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Hi,
So next week, I have four job interviews. Probably more to come. Which is great, right? Wrong. I've just started recovery a few months ago and my BDB and Mia are still flaring up. 

I'm terrified of how I will look in the interviews and that my clothes won't fit (I'm scared to even try them on). I can't focus on my interview answers, the skills or knowledge I'm bringing in, any of it. All I can think about is how little progress I've made in recovery. I don't want to admit it, but it's led to some serious restricting ever since the phone calls started. Started purging again today and God help me I don't want to go down this path again.

The worst part? I'm a psychotherapist. I should know better. They're psychotherapists, and I'm convinced they'll know and think I'm incompetent because of my inability to cure myself.

Help? Please?

How can I get the courage to try on my interview clothes?

How can I let go of evaluating my recovery progress?

How can I be comfortable with how I look?

How can I not worry about judgements?

How can I get out of this cycle?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Has anyone else with a purging problem experienced this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 03:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: [Support] Friend in Recovery asked me on a Group Lunch outing! [Advice?] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 03:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend has had BN and Exercise Bulimia for longer than I've known her. The unspoken rule between our group of friends was that we wouldn't talk about weight, exercise, counting calories, nutrition, or even good food places we found because it would trigger her to purge shortly after. (I'm not sure if this was a healthy approach, but we were young and had no idea how to handle this.)

Now, we are in our mid 20's and she's finally opened up to me about this part of her life. I want to do anything I can to help her, but I have no idea how to act. I LOVE food. My insta is all #foodporn and I'm one of those avid Yelp girls. I know that normally, I would be all over lunch and hyper-excited to eat. I'd take tons of pictures and act like it was Christmas Day over a cup of froyo. Every bite is "Ohhh GOOODD that's good."

My question: Is my normal self appropriate for this situation? If not, how should I act? The last thing I want to do is to trigger her or make herself feel badly about herself. We are going with other girls in her recovery program and the friends they invited as well. Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I am completely worn out from binging and purging and don't know what to do. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 03:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 23 year old female who has been binging and purging for 8 years now. I am tired, my body doesn't work the way it should, and I hate it so much. I am so scared of myself, but have no idea how to get myself to stop.

I want to get help - I need to get help - but this is something I can just not afford. Living in Nebraska, I have not been able to find a low income or free support group or therapist to help me out. I feel so stuck.

I don't know what to do. I feel completely helpless. I'm tired of being a slave to binging and purging, it's really ruined my life. I've already lost the love of my life and friends because I could not stop. I'm extremely afraid I'm going to lose my own if I am unable to.

What should I do, reddit? I just want to be better.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Anorexia and Personality Changes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 04:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Please excuse my ignorance. I assume that anorexic periods must be associated with personality changes of some kind, but I have no idea whether that's what's going on with my best friend. Any advice appreciated!

I have been close friends with Rochelle (not her real name) for 15 years. I met her after she had already recovered from a previous anorexic period in her life (I believe she was diagnosed, she told me it was definitely anorexia). In the time I've known her she's tended to struggle with tending to be overweight, but overall she had a pretty healthy relationship with food and exercise (something she's always been proud of).

In the past six months she's rapidly lost a great deal of weight (I'm sorry, I'm really bad at guessing others' weight, but maybe 70 lbs?) and is now underweight, similar to the photos she showed me of her previous anorexic period. She tells me she lost this in a healthy way, and I haven't pushed the topic (especially because she makes remarks about others where it seems that any comments on her weight changes by anyone seem to be interpreted as hostility) but it seems visually like an extreme change to me. 

I would not like to "stick my nose in where it doesn't belong," but her personality has changed, as well. Some of this has been good, for example, while she has dated on and off before, she would often withdraw from the dating world because she felt unattractive at her weight. Now she feels confident to really jump into the dating pool. 

She has also started socializing much more heavily with acquaintances, but on the down side, she has been treating me, her closest friend for all these years...frankly, like chopped liver. I feel that she has become inconsiderate, cold, and even maybe more shallow (she was always very philosophical, considerate and warm-hearted, and now I don't see much of any of that anymore). 

I did confront her about her changed behavior to me and it did not go well (she apologized and then continued the behavior with no change, and when I pointed that out, she got upset at me that I expected her to "change all at once" - actually, the sudden change WAS the problem!) 

Now our friendship is hanging by the thinnest thread. I feel very insulted by the way she's started treating me, I wouldn't tolerate it from someone without our shared history. I can't figure out if this is temporary (like maybe even literally caused by not eating?) and I should stick it out, or the "new her" (maybe since she said she feels that her weight loss is healthy and good, she associates me with "the past"?) and I should remove her from my life.

Is this personality change likely related to her dramatic weight loss or probably not related? If it is related, is there anything I can do or say, or is this all out of my hands?

Thank you!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Should I tell my boyfriend about my ED? Would it be rude? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 10:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've been dating for almost a year now and we love each other a lot. I've been hiding an ED I've had for years. While I'm mostly recovered it's still a central aspect to each day and I really want to tell him about it.

However, he's overweight (while I'm on the smaller side) and I don't want him to think that I care about his weight, by extension, because I don't. I know he's really self conscious about his weight but he never directly brings it up, and I don't want to make him feel worse.

TLDR; Is it insensitive to tell a person who is much larger than you that you think you're fat and have issues with food?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Can an ED lead to Thyroid issues later on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 02:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I managed to overcome bulimia a few years back, still get the urge to purge every once in a while but I don't give in. However, I still have some physical symptoms that never went away such as cold hands, dry skin, fatigue, baggy eyes, sensitivity to cold, low libido (I think I even made a post here about cold hands a long time ago). A lot of the symptoms line up with hypothyroidism, so I was wondering if permanent thyroid damage can be caused by ED (google is fuzzy on this). Does anyone have a similar experience?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I don't know if I have an eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 07:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a heavy kid, never truly fat, but always right at the cusp of being overweight, and I was very, very aware of it, thanks in large part to my parents. I have always had anxiety and and ADHD-PI and have struggled on and off with depression. My biggest fear was people being aware of my awareness of it, if that makes any sort of sense.

I went a day without eating at age nine, but I was afraid of anyone finding out, so I suppressed that part of me. I pretended for years that nothing was wrong. I stopped eating meat at age twelve, started obsessing over fruits and vegetables, and became fairly thin. I got heavy again from age 13-15, largely through weird hypnotic binges after school. From 15-17 I half-deliberately lost a not-insignificant amount of weight, slowly so that no one would catch on. But they did, and they started making comments. Even though they're flattering, they make me extremely uncomfortable and they cause me to obsess over my appearance and my weight. I'm 18 now, and for the last six months I've been restricting calories for no particular reason and weighing myself multiple times a week (a big change from when I was a child and hid illnesses for months on end so I wouldn't have to see a doctor). Some days I eat almost nothing, little more than some snacks.

When I'm around people I can shut it off and eat normally so that they won't suspect anything, but it stresses me out and makes me feel guilty when I have no choice but to eat 3 real meals a day. Since this summer, I've lost the same amount of weight as I did in 2 years before. When people ask me about it I deny everything and look at them like they're crazy. I don't like to talk about it, and I don't like it when other people talk about their own weight loss. I'm still nowhere near underweight (very average for an 18 year old girl) and I've never made myself throw up (because I tried it once years ago and couldn't do it), but I often have the urge to. I don't think I fit the clinical parameters for any officially recognized eating disorders, but I know I have a problem because I want my habits to be a secret. I know this sub isn't a doctor, but I don't know what to think. Everything I said is true, but the label "eating disorder" seems like an exaggeration. I know I don't obsess as much as other people do and that my behaviors aren't as extreme. Do I need help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How does one distinguish between feeling and hunger? To me, everything is hunger. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 02:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 31 year old woman with an eating disorder. I recently developed bulimia as result of many stressors in my life, including whether or not to leave my alcoholic husband and coming to terms with an abusive, narcissistic mother. Couple that with unhappiness at work and Bulimia ensued.

I want help. I do not want to live life this way. The question I want to ask the sub is that, I've been doing some online reading which tells me to listen to my emotions when I feel hungry or to take a walk or take my mind off of things. None of that works. I just get even hungrier and hungrier until I cant stop thinking about food and then I go on a bingeing tirade. Only to feel guilty and disgusted by myself. To then throw it all up. TO finally feel satisfied and empty and in control. To then feeling guilty and like pure shit because of what my life has become.

My question is: how does one distinguish between feeling and hunger? How can I work on that skill. To me, everything is hunger. I'm "hungry" an hour after I eat, I feel hungry all the time and when I am not eating I feel like I am starving myself all the time.

Anyway, I am on this sub because I need help. I want to end this vicious cycle and I need resources, books to read, and support from other women (especially older women) who have overcome this terrible disorder.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm really worried. Is this an eating disorder? Can't eat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 01:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Over the last few months I've been getting progressively less and less hungry. I noticed it during Christmas dinner when I got a plate and put hardly any food on it, and then hardly touched the food. I ended up going from that to undereating because I forced myself to. 

I decided I should try to regulate my eating patterns so I got a meal today. I ate a few bites before feeling like I was going to puke. I had to throw it away because I couldn't eat anymore. 

This isn't an eating disorder is it?? I'm really scared that it is, because I didn't even realize how bad it was getting. 

Someone please help me :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post: Possible Binge Eating Disorder  In remission? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 06:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I have been pre-occupied with my weight since I was 13. I just turned 54. I have gained and lost the same 20-30 pounds countless times. I have never made myself vomit, but I have wanted to do so many, many times and I attempted it in my teens and 20s, but was never able to succeed, so I quit trying. I dont have a history of going on fad diets, but I did have a few episodes in those early years of doing some really unhealthy things in my attempts to lose weight.

In the last 20 years, I have attempted to control my weight in a healthy way by counting calories and setting a reasonable goal while eating a well-rounded diet of lean meats, fresh fruits and vegetables, and nuts. Im not overly rigid and I allow myself to have treats on occasion. If its someones birthday, I have cake. If its a holiday, I enjoy the meal. Sometimes I can succeed at my goal, but more often than not, I lose control (at some point) and begin a cycle of daily binge-eating.

The binge eating usually takes one of two forms. Sometimes, I know its emotional and I am seeking comfort, so I drown my sorrows in food and I just snack mindlessly. Sometimes, I feel genuinely HUNGRY, so I eat an apple or a healthy snack and I waitbut I am STILL HUNGRY. When this happens, I try to have some protein or a high fat snack like cheese, nuts, or almond butter. After thisI wait to see if the hunger subsides. If it doesnt then Im heading for a full blown binge and I will eat anything I can find until I am stuffed and miserable. Just one of these episodes can kick off a cycle that will last for weeks or months. My binge eating always takes place in private. I hide the evidence and I lie about food that has disappeared.

I never thought I had an eating disorder because I dont fit the profile for bulimia (I dont purge) or anorexia. I recently learned a bit about Binge Eating Disorder and I seem to fit that profile rather closely. When Im in a binge eating cycle, I am full of guilt and self-hatred. My weight balloons rapidly and I may gain 20 pounds in 3 months or less. I realize that my happiness and self-esteem is inextricably tied to my current weight.

I feel silly coming to this realization at my advanced age. I am currently at a normal BMI, but Im also counting calories in hopes of losing about 10 pounds, because THEN Ill be happy. (HA! Thats how its always been!)

I havent had a binge eating episode in about 5 months. What does this mean? Am I in remission? Does remission exist for BED? I dont think Im cured because I know I could relapse at any time.

Where do I go from here, now that I'm 99% sure that I have BED? I haven't seen a professional and I wonder if I will be taken seriously since I am currently at a normal weight and I'm not currently engaged in binge eating. If I make an appointment to see someone, what should I look for to find a qualified professional?

Thanks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Not sure if my diet is bad? 16 and worried it could be an eating disorder. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 06:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was 10ish, I was overweight. I saw an unflattering picture of myself, was horrified with my weight, and tried to change that. Looking back, part of me thinks that what could be seen as anorexia was really just me wanting to loose weight and having absolutely no proper information about how to do it. Eventually, I was in the "healthy" weight range. Anyways, I saw a psychologist, and within about a month I was doing better (thus my hesitation to say I was anorexic).

Now, I'm 16. When I had blood tests done I had pre-diabetes, high cholesterol, etc. I started eating healthier and some of these numbers went down. I was still in the overweight range then. The numbers went down but still weren't healthy. Then I started to lose weight. I'm still losing weight in the "healthy" way, IE eating healthy foods   enough calories to be healthy and not excessive exercise. I use a calorie tracker and worry that I might be getting in an unhealthy way. For example, if I go over the calorie limit, I "roll over" those calories into the next day so that I eat less on that day because I don't want the numbers to say that I'm not meeting the calorie goal. I never go under the lowest recommended amount, yet. I need to lose weight because of my heart health, but I'm worried if I have an eating disorder again?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Question about managing binge eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 00:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit. I was diagnosed with BED last year, which was somewhat of a relief, because I didn't know what was wrong with me. My weight has increased a lot in the past two years, and the time has come to do something about it.

Many of my family members think I should go to slimming world as it means I can eat as much as I want of their approved foods. I've been to slimming world and weight watchers,and I've always failed after a few weeks/months. I'm anxious about going back, because I don't want to fail again, but it always happens, even when I want to lose weight.

I also considered trying to change my eating habits by making small changes. I wonder if maybe slimming world or weight watchers doesn't work because it's overwhelming having to change so much. I'm aware I might also be kidding myself and that changing my whole eating pattern is inevitable.

I guess I just want some advice. Has anyone else with BED got advice on losing weight? Or does anyone have any advice on what I should do?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My girlfriend needs help and I don't know what to do.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 00:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my girlfriend posted a disturbing message to her tumblr a few days ago and I'm not sure what to do or where to turn, or if this is the right place to send this to. I love her like crazy.. I'm so worried and scared for her. I knew something was wrong but I didn't know it was this bad. For example she drinks tons of water so she fills up and doesn't eat as much..

Mod Note: The post request had the full tumblr post. The message is probably not so safe to post here in its entirety, but it would sound familiar to those of you who are familiar with AN. It describes in detail her negative self-image, particularly body image, strictly enforced limits on the amount of calories she allows herself, the amount she exercises, and the fact that she sees food as an enemy and something to be avoided. She specifically points out the pressure she feels to be thin when she sees images of models in magazines. She is a High School senior. 

She addresses her relationship with her boyfriend (the OP) thus:

*" Speaking of which, i do have a wonderful boyfriend who is helping me through it all, and it irritates me that no matter how many times he tells me im beautiful and that he loves me the way i am and that i should basically fuck society, i cant get the gnawing thoughts out of my head. The voices that keep telling me that im fat, theyre also the ones that tell me im not good enough for him. I wish i was good enough. I feel like i have to be a certain size to be good enough for him, even though i know its not true."*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: i need help. Is there a doctor that can diagnose me at a time that isn't Monday-Friday 8-5 ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 15:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really dont know where to turn. It seems like I wont let myself go to the doctor because of my schedule.

I feel insane; I dont know where to start without jumbling it all up. I am 27 years old but i believe i have had an eating disorder for over 10 years. I guess it comes and goes except i really notice it this time.

I dont always feel comfortable preparing food around people so this prevents me from eating sometimes.

I know i would be eating very healthy and on my way to weight gain if i was allowed to prepare food in my room but i have forbidden from doing that ever since my EX broke up with me and I moved in with my widowed grandma.

I think everyone in my family believes i am still 13 and when i say i dont feel comfortable preparing food in the kitchen they think i am being a spoiled, manipulative brat and a picky eater.

Anyway; I know it would go A LONG WAY in convincing my family that i am not a piece of shit brat trying to get my way if i had a doctor give me a note saying i have an eating disorder.

My living situation really sucks which is one of the reasons why i stay in my room. I get no light in my room at all, so it is really hard to wake up... I would LOVE to go to the doctor like a normal person but i am Late everyday day for the past year which makes me feel very uncomfortable and guilty asking for any time off. In addition to that I always avoid my lunch so i can seem like i am working harder.

By the time i get off work most doctors offices are closed as far as i know. I call around but i can only call when driving because my room gets no reception neither does my office.

Everywhere i have managed to get ahold of tells me they arent the right doctor for that. Or they cannot diagnose the disorder. I've been to eating disorder treatment places but they cannot diagnose either.

I dont know what to do. I am too depressed to drive miles away from my house to call doctors.. All the doctors i can go to are all closed when i am free.

I literally own my weight in food, right next to me. But it is uncooked and unprepared. I wish i could eat it but i am forbidden from doing anything with it in my room. It has been like this for months and i just sit in my room and starve and cry.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What should I ask for from a recovery mentor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 16:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I have an opportunity to reach out to a few mentors for recovery. 

What specifically do you think I could ask for in terms of assistance?

What do you look for in terms of support? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Recovering from an ED and thinking about pregnancy. How can I handle it? Attitude towards body changes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 02:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi!

Ive struggled with an ED for the past 17 years. I am now recovering and am a healthy weight. I have come a long way but am still in the recovery stage. 

I am 28 years years old and my husband and I are thinking about having a baby. I know I'm getting older and don't want to wait too much longer, but am so fearful about what pregnancy will do to me mentally and physically. I do not want to be triggered and relapse and I want to be able to "enjoy" the pregnancy.

I am so scared of what pregnancy will do to me and my recovery. I fear the changes to my body both before and after pregnancy. I am struggling to accept myself now where I'm at, so how will I be able to handle a lot that comes with pregnancy and having a baby? I really want to say I can do it and will be able to handle it, and I hate to think this ED will rob me of something else in my life! 

Any advice from others on how they handled pregnancy and their attitude toward body changes during and after? Any advice or thoughts would be so helpful!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Should I be concerned about this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 11:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the past few weeks at least, I have heard my sister often talk to my mum about her almost-seven-year-old being fussy about food- for example, she won't even eat [certain food] or we got her to eat [certain food] the other night. Today we visited my sister, and this is what I gathered from the conversation:

* that she hasn't even been eating jelly over Christmas, even though she usually loves jelly

* that one day she did eat 3/4 of a Weet-Bix- after my sister didn't watch and said she would like to "be surprised" every time she checked back, and bribed her with dying her hair (like her older sister) and that if she ate the Weet-Bix, she could choose what the whole family had for dinner (she chose McDonalds).

* My niece had been complaining and crying of a stomach-ache one day, and seemed to think it was caused by food (though it was most likely caused by no food). My sister used reverse psychology and said "okay, I'm not going to make you eat anything today" and suddenly my niece seemed happy as Larry.

I know that many kids are picky about what they eat for various reasons and that they will often go through phases like this.. but the reason I'm writing here is that I heard her say "I love being a skinny bitch!" twice, and after hearing about her food issues, I made a link. I don't know too much about what is actually going on with her eating, only little snippets here and there when my sister talks to my mum, and it could be that she's just repeating something she heard on TV. And I'm not sure exactly how common EDs are in young children. But do you think I have cause to be concerned about this/say something to my sister?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 19:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts

[Advice](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2a6v9j/request_advice_on_what_to_saydo_when_my_gf/)

[Body distortion](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/26s10k/request_body_distortion_does_it_ever_go_away/)

[Girlfriend unhealthy view](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2594ya/request_girlfriend_has_unhealthy_view_of_her_body/)

[Unhealthy body image](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/22kcw7/request_how_to_stop_overwhelming_my_husband_with/)

There are others. Consider links in the sidebar, too.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Can anyone recommend any books or other media (podcasts, movies, blogs, etc.) about recovery from eating disorders? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 18:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone recommend any books or other media (podcasts, movies, blogs, etc.) about recovery from eating disorders?

Specifically any that focus on the "control" aspect of it.
I actually have a different illness (OCD), but i am finding eating disorder stories sound very familiar, so maybe eating disorder recovery stories could be helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I have no idea what's happening to me. Graves Thyroid Disease, hypothyroid, hormone replacement therapy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 15:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

I don't know where to start. I was overweight for a decade. It never bothered me. Not even a little. Suddenly, I lost a very large amount of weight. To the point that I was underweight. I was diagnosed with Graves Thyroid Disease, which for me, the onset was extreme. Also, with the disease, you're always extremely hungry, and can eat whatever you want around the clock, and you're still losing weight. So for four months, I ate nothing but junk and in huge amounts. Everyone smothered me with compliments.  And then I got diagnosed, and went on medication to slow down my thyroid. I should also mention that while people were showering me with praise, I was really sick. My hair was falling out, I was having panic attacks every night, extreme palpitations, the whole nine. I was at high risk for cardiac arrest the whole time I was undiagnosed. That's Graves, and it's horrible.

Anyways, my thyroid slowed down. I gained a little weight back, but I was still a healthy weight for my height. It didn't bother me. Fast forward about six months. Suddenly, it was like a light bulb lit up. I decided I wanted to lose the weight I'd gained. I set a goal weight for myself and started exercising, and counting calories with one of those stupid phone apps. So I did that for awhile, and approached my goal weight. For some reason, that wasn't good enough. I set a new goal weight. When I got to that one, that wasn't good enough either. I was weighing myself obsessively. I stopped exercising, lost all energy. I saw where this might be going, so I stopped calorie restricting. I started eating whatever I wanted.

I went to the Endocrinologist, and found out to my surprise, that the Graves disease, which is autoimmune, successfully destroyed my thyroid. Which means, I am hypothyroid, and my metabolism is way slower than a healthy person's. That thought makes me panic. I'd only gained back a tiny amount of weight, I'm still slightly underweight. I started on thyroid hormone replacement therapy two weeks ago. All I think about is food, and my weight, but I still eat junk when I feel like it...only to feel deep regret afterward. It's like there's something wrong, and I know it, but I'm refusing to let it stop me from eating what I want. Yet, it's always on my mind.

My question is...what's happening to me? What did happen? I was overweight for years and it didn't bother me one bit. Even when my mother was pointing it out and telling me how unattractive I looked. I knew she was just being horrible, and I felt perfectly comfortable in my own skin. I was a healthy weight up until I graduated high school, and then I started taking a certain medication that caused me to become overweight, and I wasn't bothered by that, either. I feel like most girls would have been horrified, but not me. I was okay. 
So...can I get some feedback about this? And how to stop myself from going down this road? I feel like when this hypothyroid thing got thrown into the mix, it made everything so much worse. 

I'm always thinking about eating and not eating. I better go back to restricting my intake because I could be paving the road to being overweight again. Which, to me, seems like a nightmare if it were to happen. I don't get it. I really want to stop thinking about food so much, I really want to stop constantly examining my legs to see if they've gotten any bigger, and checking to see if I can still feel my hip bones...I've successfully stopped weighing myself every day, but that's about it. 

My husband, who is wonderful and loves me very much, keeps telling me that I could be three times my size and he'd still love me to pieces. It's not that I want to impress anyone by being so small, I don't need to. It's just me, something going on with me. 

What do I do? What is this?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Submission request: Going vegan while in recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 03:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been vegetarian since before my ED, but now I'm considering becoming vegan or at least cut out raw dairy and eggs. My boyfriend doesn't think it's healthy for someone in recovery to cut out whole food groups like that. Advice?

A note from the mods: Please remember when replying that there are no "bad" foods. Keep it positive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Significant other has an unhealthy relationship with body and food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 03:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone. My girlfriend is the subject of this post.

In high school, she struggled greatly with an eating disorder. She's overcome the physical parts of the disorder (no longer at an alarmingly low weight) but she still suffers greatly from the mental aspects.

While she doesn't purge nearly as often (about once every three months), she is obsessed with her body image and eating the "right" food. If she eats something she doesn't deem as okay (chips, candy, carbs, etc), she feels extreme guilt. She is often very depressed despite taking Prozac. Most importantly, she thinks she is fat and wants to be "10 pounds" thinner. She is at a very healthy weight and does not need to lose any weight. That's not me wearing rose-tinted glasses, either. Her body is healthy.

I would really love to guide her to a healthier path. I wish she didn't need to experience the guilt or have the constant struggle of becoming an unhealthy weight. I'm very grateful that she doesn't purge as often but I'm convinced that there must be some resources for her. She currently sees a therapist once a week. She was going to see a nutritionist but it conflicted with her work schedule.

Is there anyone out there who has overcome something similar? I would love to hear from you. She has such a good life in front of her and I really want her to be able to experience it to the fullest.

How can I help her be comfortable with herself as she is? How can I help her recognize that she is a healthy weight and that's great?

Thank you so, so much for taking the time to read this.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Please Help! My Wife used to struggle with bulimia and I think she still does </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 02:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm new to reddit but I'm interacting with /r/EatingDisorders/ because Im near my wit's end. Im in my early 30s, and my wife of nearly two years is in her late twenties. Shes the most important person in my life, and the only reason I bring this up is two-fold: Im concerned she might be jeopardizing her health If she really does have an ED, I want her to seek treatment before we start having kids.

I knew before we got married that she struggled with anorexia when she was in college, however, I rationalized it because she was an academic overachiever, so the idea that she would skip a meal to continue working on homework wouldnt seem out of character. She saw a shrink, and that was that. Also, by the time we started dating, her eating habits seemed relatively normal. Her body weight was petite but not skinny.

That said, during the time we dated, she did lose some weight, which I chalked up to the fact that she and I were both eating healthily, exercising, etc. Her BMI eventually leveled out.

I noticed that she used the bathroom several more times than me per day. She also uses the bathroom with the faucet running, which she explained is due to the fact that she cant use the toilet without such sounds (Ive heard this is a fairly common problem in young kids). When Ive asked her about her frequency or duration the answers are usually GI-tract related (i.e. constipation or diarrhea).

One time she took a long time with the shower turned on (in the middle of the day). I basically intimated that I was concerned she was vomiting. She said, no, she was showering. At this point, I lost it because her hair was dry. She said she was shaving her legs which was true.

Another time we ate ethnic food, which she liked at the time, but afterwards she started feeling very nauseous. We went home and she definitely pulled the trigger (the noises were obvious and she admitted as much). I ate the same food, no problems.

It seems like any very heavy dish gives her nausea.

About 6 months ago, she admitted that yes, she was bulimic in college but that she hadnt been for the last several years.

Everything seemed fairly normal until last weekend. She ate like a bird for several days. Then we go to a restaurant and we eat a heavy meal. Afterwards, about 4 hours and one layover later, she starts complaining of nausea on our 2nd flight, because of the aircraft's motion, and wants to go to the bathroom. Mind you weve flown tens of thousands of miles together with nary a problem. I say, here, drink some Ginger Ale, itll help settle your stomach. She refuses to drink any. After a while, I ask her if shes okay, and she says yes.

When we get home, she almost immediately goes to the bathroom, closes the door, turns the water on. I ask, are you still nauseous? she says, Im taking care of it.

When she gets out, Im pretty despondent. I waited too long to write this, so I dont remember either of our exact words, but I made it pretty clear that her behavior was pretty indicative of bulimia, she was livid, if I was bulimic, wouldnt my breath smell? If youd kept it on the downlow for two years, wouldnt you have developed a pretty good method of masking the smell. Nothing good came from our exchange.

Basically, Im at the point where there are one of only a few possibilities: 1) shes bulimic, but unwilling to let me know (possible) 2) shes got a health problem, but is unwilling to get treated (possible, she hates doctors) 3) shes got a paranoid husband who thinks her wife is bulimic (possible, but unlikely)

Do I: a) Try to bring up the subject again, likely provoking another fight with profuse denials? b) Pretend that everything is fine, until she decides to seek out help (which would create a serious rift in our relationship)? c) Do I show her irrefutable proof that shes got an ED, and work from there?

Im basically ruling out any suggestions involving my mother-in-law. We get along very, very well, but my wife takes great offense at any suggestions or concerns her mother raises.

None of the evidence alone is a smoking gun, but you add it all up, and I dont think my concerns are irrational: History of ED Frequent restroom usage Always loud, running water complaints of nausea after big and/or fatty meals refusal to see doc for symptoms cavities perfectionist when it comes to physical appearance

What things dont fit: No negative self-talk (Im fat, I should lose weight, etc) No obvious enamel loss (I asked our family dentist if he noticed anything unusual about her teeth, he said no) Dont hear vomiting (is it possible to puke quietly?)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 00:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Making healthy decisions](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2ivccs/request_pregnant_and_disordered_how_can_i_make/)

[Coping](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2jvv8g/request_has_anyone_gotten_pregnant_while_coping/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Navigating that Frightening Time of Pregnancy after an Eating Disorder. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 00:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Boosting calories not having any effect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 14:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have always been small-built, ever since I could remember. I was able to get to a slightly higher weight when I was on the pill.  Due to medical reasons, the last two years I have been off the pill I have gone back to what I see as my 'usual' weight. 

Over the last six months, my Dr has put I am anorexic on my file and I have upped my eating by double. I snack a lot during the day, drink high calorie drinks and of course, there was Christmas. However, nothing is having any effect. I have been to counselling for the last six months as well and through a lot of discussions, I hold no need to be 'skinny' and desperately want to put on weight.

So despite upping my calories by a lot, I am seeing no physical improvements. Have you got any suggestions on how to progress? I feel like I am at a dead end.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Pregnancy and BN </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 14:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone.

Big news! I found out I was pregnant about a month and a half ago. Along with all the normal nervousness surrounding a first pregnancy, I realize that I'm going to start struggling tremendously with body image issues, mood swings, and the diet changes that are normal among pregnant women, but could easily lead to disordered eating.

I'd really like some advice from people who have gone through this before. I have some specific things that are concerning me right now, which I'll list below.

1. Despite being fairly early along, I'm starting to get that uncomfortably-full feeling despite eating a normal amount of food. This sensation is usually what triggers purging, and it ends up floating in the back of my mind until the feeling passes. This is only going to get worse the further along I get. Does anyone have any coping mechanisms for this that have worked for them?

2.  I often find myself hyper-focusing on "pregnancy superfoods" and the "right" things to eat. Restricting or eliminating certain foods has always been the hardest thing for me to get past, and having this constant barrage of "You should eat this, you shouldn't eat that" from pregnancy websites is typically what we need to avoid. Should I simply ignore this advice and go back to my normal eating patterns(which have helped me avoid disordered eating in the past)?

3. Food cravings are hitting me like a freight train, and they seem to occur at the same time as serious mood swings. Several times now I've bought foods that I know are triggering for me, with the rationalization that, "Oh, I'm pregnant, it's okay. And I'll only eat a little to get over the craving." Obviously it is not working out that way. Is there a middle ground that works for you? I want to get to a point where I can indulge some cravings without losing control and spiraling into the desire to purge.

Thank you in advance and all your advice. Anecdotes are very welcome.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Late-twenties male, is this an eating disorder? Is there treatment for this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 23:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! I am a late-twenties male, and underweight for my height and sex. I have a history of anxiety and panic. Symptoms of these disorders are for the most part extinguished (I occasionally experience symptoms of high anxiety -- nausea in particular is my panic trigger), but one thing that has stuck around is my tendency to limit food intake/lose my appetite during stressful periods as a way to regulate my fear and anxiety (especially of nausea). I have been fairly thin all my life, but lately I've been experiencing a lot of work-related stress and my schedule has not been conducive to the longer periods of eating I sometimes need to get enough calories, thus the weight loss.

I know I am underweight right now, and I very much want to gain the weight back (and then some), but I'm having a lot of difficulty figuring out how to do this. I suspect my anxiety-sensitivity, and fear of panic/nausea are related to the difficulty I'm having gaining weight, but aside from the weight loss these are for the most part non-issues in my life.

Is there a treatment for this? I'd love to have some professional help and support with this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: 23 (M) - Losing interest in food and worried about it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 23:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To start things off, I've always been a fairly underweight individual. About 9 months ago I started looking into options to gain weight as I was going through some personal issues that wanted me to change up my life. However, around mid-August I ended up getting sick (food poisoning is the suspect) and ended up not eating for nearly 2 days. I recovered and moved on but my appetite did not; before I would have to remind myself to eat but it would get done. Now I can barely stomach a meal and eating itself is a chore. I can go a while without food and not even realize it, if I don't set alarms then it sometimes happens. 

The past three days have been the worst, I haven't consumed much and have lost weight, as someone who doesn't weigh enough to afford to having that happen. 

What should I do? This is appearing more and more like an onset of anorexia and I'm worried. Meals will get started and not finished, I'll go a while without eating and my stomach aches yet I can't bring myself to eat. The thought and actions of it make me nauseous. 

Any advice welcome, I'll be the first to admit I have no idea what to do here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: ADVICE PLEASE: getting prof help when you've tried before   it hasn't worked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 12:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I am a female in my mid 20s who is struggling with binge eating. I recently thought I had it under control, but I have been slowly slipping and I have dropped to a new low this week. I am considering reaching out for help from a dietician/counselor specializing in binge eating, but I have some reservations that keep me from seeking help:

-I have gotten help before from therapists and from a support group. I have no trauma i need to work out, and the group I did not like because of the large age difference and the fact that they have been there for decades and have not changed. I know my eating is due to stress situations, incidents where i feel intense emotions (anger, shame, loneliness) or I am avoiding things, or I find myself surrounded by food and erroneously thinking I will be ok eating a triggering thing (and then things go down hill from there).
I have difficulty implementing strategies to help me be proactive ( and I do sometimes make the choice to be self destructive because in that moment i wont care about my future). I'm not sure if help from others can help me anymore.

-I notice that a lot of binge eaters do have past trauma they have not dealt with, or have chronic anxiety/depression/anxiety attacks, and that is not me. So I am unsure if I do actually have 'bad enough' disordered eating to seek help, or if I just need to pull myself up and cut the bull. That being said, I do know my binging hurts others (when I take out my anger on them) and I do tend to isolate myself when my appearance is not meeting my expectations

-I do know for a fact I have trouble being completely truthful about how I feel, and about my actions (i have been told this by family, whose opinion i trust). I have had difficulty telling my parents about what I have been eating when I have been asked point blank, and I couldn't tell my sponsor either when i was in a support group, out of shame. I do want to be truthful, I try but then...I'm not. I'm aware of me having a tendency to be manipulative to protect myself , and of sabotaging my efforts to change (at least I'm aware of it).

I just want to know if there are others that may have similar issues being completely truthful to themselves and others about their condition, of being manipulative ( in the sense of having a part of you that is keeping you from changing your habits completely), and what they have done to be more honest and hold themselves more accountable for their actions (accountability i also struggle with). Also, do you find dieticians/nutritionists as/more/less helpful than counselors, psychologists and social workers (LCSW's)?

How do you guys get out a rut? I know I have it in me to change since I've done it before, but never for longer than a month and a half, and that was due to an ultimatum made by my family. I don't want to hurt them anymore (I take out the pain I feel after binges on them), and that is why i want prof. help, but I'm not sure if it can help me anymore, due to my past experiences.

Thank you for listening
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: When you were ready to recover on your own, who did you go to for help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 03:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now, I've halfway escaped my eating disorder. 50% of my body wants to gain, while the other 50% enjoys the feeling brought when I count calories and make sure I don't "splurge" over what's necessary. I'm not at a deathly weight, I'm barely underweight, and I haven't lost any weight in the last 4 months, so I have plenty of time to think about whether or not I should seek outside help.

The issue is this: I understand that the root of my anxiety isn't found in food, but rather a deeper issue altogether. Controlling my food intake has simply been a coping mechanism for a greater ordeal. I don't know what exactly this ordeal is yet, but I know it has something to do with my social health, which has plummeted since I graduated from high-school.

I've never had any issues with food until I grew semi-depressed after my graduation, so I believe that if I attack the issue at the source, my eating disorder should just go away.

I've gone 6 months now without discussing my troubles with anyone but the members of this subreddit. Venting through anonymous posts has been pretty therapeutic, but I'm starting to wonder if I need to seek a professional, a friend, or a relative for help. No one would have imagined that I've gone through so much stress every day, and I don't want to make my family worry, so I'm hoping that I can just solve my problems without having to drag anyone else into my mess. 

Is there a safe, anonymous way to seek therapeutic help? If my issue lies in social health, should I simply try to meet new people and see if things return to normal?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Deaths in recent months and years. Can't stomach food. What should I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 17:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need help... I've never really talked about this but recently I realized how bad It's getting.. I have always struggled with weight, in 2010 I was overweight due to stress at college and ended up dropping out.. Fast forward a few years, I always told myself that I would never allow myself to get to that weight so I always watched myself and if I noticed weight gain I would watch how much I ate and often underate. I know It's not healthy but my body was managing it and I felt good so I didn't worry. I'm smart and in tune with myself so I figured I wouldn't let myself get sick. 

Anyway, over the summer I took about internship that was incredibly intense. I was working 10.5 hours days almost everyday so my lunch and breaks were limited (I didn't notice the weight loss until recently) when the internship was over I went home for a few weeks before college resumed and everyone I saw commented on how thin I was looking (not in a bad way, just different) I was Happy so I kept doing what I was doing, only really eating when I felt hungry ..which started to become less and less... 

When i was home i saw that things had gotten bad with my parents, and i was unfortunate enough to see my big brother in a heroin comatose. It haunted me.   I went back to college (5000 miles from my family) and then my friend died in September I hit insanity and didn't know what to do. Then a month a bit later I received a phone call from by parents with the horrific news my brother had died...I was broken. 

By this time I had lost a crazy amount of weight and food became disgusting to me. Every time I tried to eat something I felt sick, nothing could go down. The only time i stomached food was when I was smoking weed. Fast forward to yesterday, (Chrismas Eve) I was puking all day due to a bug and have lost even more weight. My parents have noticed and are consistently asking me if I've eating yet and things like that..I lie because I don't want them to worry. They just lost their son in the worst of ways and don't need to be worrying about their daughter but now they are worried.

I really need advice on what to do... I really few that no one is going to take me seriously and tell me I'm just being stupid but I just can't stomach eating and I am fading.

What should I do? 

Could there be a medical reason I'm not able to stomach eating?

Would therapy help me with the recent deaths I've experienced?

Should I be concerned I'm lying?

Why is it I don't want to fade?

Why is it I want someone to notice and help me? What does help from family and friends look like? 

Also side note: I'm the strong one, I've lost nine loved ones in the past few years, I live far from my parents, I'm very intune with my surroundings and help my friends with life everyday.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: As an employee in residential treatment facility, I am supposed to interact and eat with clients. What are some good meal time topics of conversation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 17:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a new employee in a resident eating disorder treatment facility. I am going to eat dinner on nights I am working with the clients. As employees, we must try to interact with clients during meal times and also try to make them feel comfortable (the idea is so they won't be thinking too much about food or distraction). 

I am wondering what are some good conversation starters or topics for clients, so they will feel comfortable and be willing to conversation? 

Also, anything I should know or watch out for?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Developing? Considering? I don't know, I just feel lost. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 16:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is currently 2:27am on Christmas Day. I've been shuffling through my private tumblr (I keep it password protected) to see how I have recently been doing. I use it to vent and somewhat catalog myself for reference/monitoring.

I should prefix this with the fact that I have never done anything like starving myself, purging, etc. I have always been a chubby girl, but I never truly considered it. Unfortunately I struggle with medical problems that prevent me from doing a lot of physical activities. I have tried to maintain a balanced diet, which I do most of the time, with the exception of the holidays.

Now, I'm writing this because I am scared. There is no other way to describe it. I was ill last winter/spring and put on roughly twenty pounds. It has destroyed my confidence even more, but what is scaring me is my reaction to it. Initially I told myself I'd just go on a diet and lose it - even attending weight watchers with my grandmother for a short time, but I fell off that wagon due to a busy schedule and simply shit food supplies in my home.

I keep telling myself that perhaps if I just don't eat for a while and drop the weight I can go from there and maintain what I've lost. As if starving myself for "just a short while" is reasonable and I recognize the absurdity within that idea, but the weak and confused part of me keeps screaming that it may work. I know EDs are not something you can switch off, but the illogical part of me keeps whispering that little idea to me.

What I want to know is: is this a warning sign? Am I practically on the trail to developing? How do I save myself from myself when it comes to this?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I stop stressing out whenever someone close to me starts losing weight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 04:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm not sure if this is the right place for this but I didn't know where else to go for advice.

When I was a teenager I struggled with disordered eating. I'm now trying to channel this into eating healthily and exercising which is going well and I feel great, but I'm finding it hard to cope with some things. One of the main ones being how I feel when someone close to me loses weight/wants to lose weight. It sounds stupid but I start to panic thinking they're going to end up with an eating disorder even if they only want to lose a few pounds and it really gets to me.

For example, my little brother has always been a bit overweight and has been dieting on and off for the past few years (he's 18 now) but I live away from home and don't see him often. In the past 2 months, he's lost a LOT of weight, and it's instantly sent me into panic mode. Instead of being proud of him I'm worried that he's going to develop an ED. I'm obsessing over what he's eating, if I feel like he hasn't eaten enough I feel like I have to remind him and I can tell I'm being really annoying but I can't help it. I'm constantly reminding him about proper nutrition and if he skips a meal, or eats less than me I start to get really anxious. It happens every time a person close to me loses some weight.

How can I stop this from happening? Its affecting me quite badly, whenever I find out someones been losing weight I start worrying about it and won't stop comparing myself to them. It's even gotten to the point where if someone says they're going to start exercising, I secretly want them to stop because I'm worried they'll become obsessed. I'm such a hypocrite because I promote healthy eating and exercising but I worry whenever someone else starts to do it too! I hate feeling this way because I know it's pathetic and I want to have healthy feelings towards weight loss, is there anything I can do to stop having these feelings?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twelve Ideas to Help People with Eating Disorders Negotiate the Holidays, from NEDA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 15:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 16:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Coping with guilt](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2inur2/request_how_do_i_get_rid_of_or_cope_with_the_guilt/)

[Don't know what to do](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/25whqz/request_im_freaking_out_and_dont_know_what_to_do/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I don't have an eating disorder but... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 11:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have an eating disorder, but I have some really unhealthy coping mechanisms involving food. I have anxiety, I selfharm, I have mental issues up the wazoo basically. I am a healthy weight, but I tend to severely undereat during bad periods, feeling like it gives me control. I have never seen this as a big issue, and have downplayed it a lot.

Last night while visiting my parents I had an AHA-moment, realizing how bad it has gotten. I think I might be endangering my health.

So last night I decided to try and fix it, and ended up nearly with a panic attack while trying to eat dinner. I realized I have been lying to myself, and that maybe just 'cos my medical records don't say I have an ED on them, maybe I still do. At least a little.

I am not trying to self diagnose here, what I am looking for is helpful advice; does anyone have some methods they can share for when they want to not eat, that makes them able to eat anyway?

I want to beat this before it becomes a thing, and I am scared to death it might already be a thing. I don't weigh myself during bad periods 'cos I am scared of obsessing over the number, having an "ideal" number in my head that far below what I should be, and in the same vein I have been trying to not log my food intake, in case I should look at the empty page and feel good that it's empty.

I downloaded a mealtracker app so that I would maybe a have calorie goal to reach each day, but that seems insurmountable today.

So, does anyone have any suggestions that help me eat "normally"? I am willing to try nearly everything.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My Dad got my Mom a Fitbit for Christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 06:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 23 and stuck living at home while I'm in between jobs (I left my job to recover because I was a mess). I've struggled with BN with restriction for nearly 5 years. I'm in therapy and am doing very well--haven't purged in about 6 months, I'm eating balanced and regularly, and no longer have most of my food fears and rituals. At this point my biggest hurdle is my weight, which is still on the low side.

My mom has this really triggering habit of basically self-lecturing ("I should really walk more during the day" "I should stop eating this candy right now, I've had enough") and her solution to this is that she thinks it would be super great (read: enabling her horrible self-lecturing tendencies) to have a Fitbit.

I have a hard time explaining to her that when she talks that way that it's triggering to me, because it's hard to pinpoint exactly why, and also it's her life so I can't exactly tell her what to think and do.

But I am really REALLY upset that my dad got this stupid thing for my mom.

I'm terrified for Christmas morning, I am terrified of having this damn gift ruin one of my favorite holidays--I don't want everyone "ooh"-ing and "ahh"-ing over this ridiculously obsessive device. I don't want my mom constantly talking about it every day after as she uses it and tries to figure it out. I DON'T WANT TO HEAR ABOUT IT LET ALONE BE AWARE THAT IT EXISTS AND IS BEING USED IN MY HOUSE.

I am having a really hard time coping with this, and it's making me dread Christmas now, which is doubly upsetting for me. Does anyone have any advice on how I can deal with this? I wish I could just ask my dad to return the thing, or give it to her in private and not advertise it around me but I don't think either of them would even understand why this thing bothers me so much if I tried to talk to them.

I had told my mom a few months ago that I thought the Fitbit was a bad idea and kind of triggering and her response was "Well I am not obsessive like you so it wouldn't be a problem for me" - literal words out of my (psychologist!) mother's mouth.

Is there anything I can do about this? 

Or ways I can look at this so that it doesn't make me want to cry and feel like relapsing to spite my ignorant dad and insensitive mother?


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Dr. recommending weight loss after journey from AN/athletica to BED. I can't seem to let myself do it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 15:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the last 7 years, I went from being extremely underweight to obese. I am currently overweight and my physician wants me to lose weight. He knows of my prior anorexia and BED, but insists that I drop the weight to avoid complications with an autoimmune condition I have. 

The thing is, there is some type of mental block preventing me from really losing the weight. I exercise, but don't over do it. I eat healthy, but don't restrict. I almost feel like my recovery practices are now interfering with my health. Has anyone else dealt with something like this before?

Should I listen to my doctor? Should I look for another? Advice? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Body image starting to deteriorate, advice for body acceptance and not relapsing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 17:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I have recently left an inpatient facility after going from a very low weight to a weight within the healthy range. I have been maintaining at this new, healthy weight for about a month now. 

At first my body image was 'okay', some days I even felt that I looked pretty good, but over the past week or so my body image has plumeted to the point where I can't look at myself in the mirror without seeing chubbiness and desperately wanting to restrict again. 

Has anyone advice for this? Feeling good at their setpoint / healthy weight at first but then falling into feelings of intense dissatisfaction later? I've only heard of it going the other way. 

Any advice would be much appreciated. I'm terrified of this sending me back into a relapse.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I think I'm in the middle of a relapse, but I didn't even know it? Is that possible? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 04:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some background: I've been dealing with EDNOS (or OSFED now, I guess) for 6 years. My family didn't know until I came clean and asked for support in recovery about 3 years into it. With the exception of some "hiccups," I've been pretty stable since 2012... except now I think I'm in the middle of a relapse that I wasn't even aware was happening.

This past year was absolutely horrible. I moved 2 hours away for a job that turned out to be absolutely horrible and I can't seem to advance to a different branch. It's a high-stress job and some of my co-workers seem to get a sick pleasure in making my job harder for me. I tried to do everything I could to keep busy and keep my depression at bay - I joined a roller derby team (which is so much fun and filled with wonderful, supportive, kick-ass people). I wrote. I spent time with loved ones. I adventured around the city   surrounding areas. I thought I was ok.

I moved to a new apartment recently and found my journal while unpacking. As I was reading journal entries, I realized I might be in the middle of a relapse that started this past August. I had gained a lot of weight since moving to my new city (before you say it: I only gained a little bit of muscle from roller derby), but looking back at these journal entries, I realized I had lost a significant amount of weight in a short amount of time and the stuff I've been writing for the past couple months are very similar to journal entries from 2008-2011. I write my calorie count in my daily planner... and I've been restricting since August. I'm at a healthy weight now, so everyone think I just lost the weight I gained when I moved here.

I'm terrified because I've been able to realize old behaviors and squash them before they manifested. So how the hell did I realize NOW that I'm 4 months into a full-blown relapse? I feel ridiculous that this snuck up on me. And this time, I'm on my own insurance, which is complete garbage compared to my parents' insurance (which I was on back in 2012) and I can't afford any kind of treatment.

Any advice on how to get out of this rut? Am I really that crazy to not notice this?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Being lectured by Dr when I finally feel comfortable in my own skin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 12:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has this happened to anyone else? I wont talk numbers, but I had a check up yesterday and was lectured about my BMI being too low, as well as my weight. I told my doc that I am not at my lowest weight, feel like I look bangin' (for once in my life!) and am eating in a way that is not restrictive (which is what I used to do). I also go to the gym in the week (I take a couple different classes, with breaks and snacks in between). I am strong, I am gaining muscle. I like my body now.

Sure, every now and then the thoughts pop in. But I can fight them more often than not.

But now I am feeling a bit paranoid that I am delusional or something? How seriously do I need to take this doctors lecture?

(submitted by /u/we_will_be_fine) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 18:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other possibly helpful posts:

[Residency program nurse](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2glmyt/request_residency_programs_what_did_you_like_and/)

[Nurse](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1m1080/post_request_advice_for_how_to_be_a_good_nurse/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Has anyone tried the Centre for Clinical Interventions' Workbook? Can I overcome Binge Eating and remain vegan since my being vegan isn't for weight loss? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 17:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

http://www.cci.health.wa.gov.au/resources/infopax.cfm?Info_ID=48

I have been following this workbook for a little over a week. Since beginning, I have actually been able to overcome a binge twice (a feet I have never before accomplished in my 6 or so years of having the disorder).

I also have a question. The workbook demands that the goal of the program cannot be weightloss, which discourages dieting obviously. However, I am a vegan for both health and ethical reasons. I know the veganism does not likely help my overcoming the disorder, but it feels so wrong to give it up. Do you think I must give up veganism to overcome the disorder? Or may I continue granted my goals are absolutely not weightloss?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Nurse looking for advice on how to make hospital admissions more comfortable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 13:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Nurse looking for advice on how to make hospital admissions more comfortable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 13:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I work on a paediatric ward where we get a lot of patients with eating disorders (predominantly teenage girls). I guess I was wondering if anyone who has had a hospital admission with an eating disorder would let me know what made their admission better or worse and what I can do to make my patients' lives easier in a really difficult time.

Please notify the original submitter, /u/bon_jover , when you reply to this post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 17:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might share with your roommate some of these posts:

[What not to say](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/search?q=what+to+say sort=relevance restrict_sr=on t=year)

[Helping gf with recovery](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1pl03w/sharing_girlfriend_is_recovering_from_bulimia/)

[How to help a loved one](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2ajwpb/sharing_some_of_my_personal_experince_on_how_to/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 16:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Battling depression with recovery](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2303mc/request_battling_depression_with_recovery/)



[Depression leading to ED](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2h76jt/request_depression_leading_to_eating_disorder_any/)

[How to recover](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2ig5dl/request_how_to_recover_from_eating_disorderdual/)

[How to manage depression](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/25z0tx/request_how_to_manage_depression_during_recovery/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Dealing with depression after ED? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 16:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in inpatient treatment about a year and a half ago. Left at a healthy weight, maintained for a while, still seeing a therapist and a psychiatrist. Now I feel like I am back at square one; engaging in the old behaviors and feeling very, very depressed. 

But as of now, I'm not underweight. I feel like I NEED to be underweight to seek help. 

My ED started as somewhat a manifestation of my depression. And now that I am at a healthy weight, i feel like no one cares that I want to die. Because I am physically healthy, no one seems all too concerned with the fact that I am severely depressed and suicidal. 

My therapist keeps suggesting that i try to remain mindful and appreciative, but I truly feel like I have nothing to live for. How do you disassociate depression from an eating disorder?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is it unlikely that my fiancee (anorexia) can join me in fitness related activities (weightlifting in particular) and does body composition matter when it comes to recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 18:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi r/eatingdisorders, I need your help understanding how to best support my fiance on her road to recovery. Last year she was diagnosed with bipolar depression. She was emotionally abused and bullied as a child and has low self-worth and body-image issues that developed into a full blown ED a couple months ago. Shes now in a partial hospitalization program with a mixed diagnosis (mainly anorexia though) and has a good treatment team, but there are a couple of areas where I could use some enlightenment.

I've got 2 questions: I was a college athlete (recent grad) and I do a lot of weightlifting/fitness things. Basically, exercise is an important part of my life, so I was naturally happy and excited when my fiance began coming to the gym with me and learning how to lift, etc. I thought it was something that could help her with the depression. At first it was enjoyable and fun for both of us, but as her ED got worse it became something that she started to obsess over and part of the problem. 

Given how central exercise can be to an ED, is it unlikely that my fiance will be able to join me in fitness-related activities in the future? Can we exercise and stay fit together once she gets her ED under control, or will this always be an ED-related behavior for her and something that will inevitably lead to relapse? I imagine that this varies from person to person, but whats the range?

Second, I dont really understand how the threshold for being underweight is calculated. I know BMI is one big measure and I took a look at the chart on the sidebar here, but it still seems a little... fuzzy. Now, I have been keeping a close eye on her and it was only in the month before she was admitted to the hospital that I became concerned about her actual weight (before that I was mainly worried about the behaviors: the restricting and obsession with exercise, and eventually purging). However, I know that her BMI has always put her at underweight, even though her BF% has been pretty normal. Her body type is tall and slender - its genetic and everyone in her family is as well.

Shes gained back a significant amount in the hospital, but her dietitian says shes still underweight even though its apparent to me that her BF% is now solidly back in a healthy range for someone her age. (It never did drop anywhere near a dangerous level, but it was lower than most and I was concerned it was starting to head in that direction just before she was admitted.) Her dietician seems to want to get her into the average range, where shes never been before. 

So, what am I missing here? Is it not so much about the weight, and more about her eating habits and mental attitude? Does body composition matter, or is that irrelevant from an ED perspective or when recovering from an ED? If someone could point me to some reliable resources on this, Id really appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Libido and After Effects of ED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 14:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello All,

I need some advice. I am twenty-eight and I have struggled with ED on and off since age twelve. My major relapse was at age twenty-seven and I finished treatment in May 2014. I was struggling for a while, but now I am eating healthfully, working with a nutritionist, haven't used a symptom in a long time, and finding normal again. I have noticed that my libido is still very low however. I am in a great relationship with a partner who has been nothing but wonderful and patient...and looks like a young Edward Norton to boot. ;) I wonder if it has anything to do with amenorrhea. During treatment, I had a cycle for the first time in three months. I had one more normal cycle in mid-May 2014 and then had a light bit of spotting during June 2014. I feel as if I have PMS from time to time, but still haven't had a real cycle since May. I have trouble...um...getting in the mood, so to speak even alone. Any ideas or suggestions? Has anyone else struggled even after recovery?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Need advice for roommate whose sibling is struggling with anorexia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 22:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My roommate has recently been very stressed and upset with the revelation that her brother has been starving himself. 

She knows that I have been in recovery for an eating disorder (bulimia) for over two years now, and is looking for affirmation/advice. 

I really cannot think of any positive, sunny "It's all going to turn out great!!!!" advice to give her, because as many as you know, an eating disorder is pretty awful and soul-sucking for everyone involved- the one suffering from it, and those who love them, and even though many like me enter and stay in recovery, it is a long and hard road to get there. I'm not sure what to say as to how she should deal with this as an ally/loved one, because I was very, very secretive about my bulimia, and my friends and parents did not have a clue about the fact that I had been bulimic for almost five years until I went into therapy. 

Can anyone who has been in her position give me some advice on what to say to her, particularly something that will give her comfort or hope?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Parent needs Treatment options for Reluctant teen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 17:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My teenager has a binge-purge ED and depression. She has been on antidepressants and sees a counselor and a dietitian. She took herself off meds and refuses to go back on antidepressants. Therapy has made no difference in her ED. She doesn't want to get better. 

As her parent, what is the next step in treatment of a teen who does not want help? 

How can I determine which residential treatment centers in my area are a good fit for her? 

How does a parent get a reluctant teen to go into residential treatment?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is this what's causing my binging? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 03:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not much backstory is needed, but I should include a little bit I think. I've actually been binge eating for a couple of years now but didn't know I was. I was usually in front of the TV or my phone so I wasn't aware that I didn't want to be eating. I had no idea I couldn't control my eating. It wasn't until a few of months ago, after I began restricting, when I realized I had a problem.

For the last few weeks, I've been practicing demand eating. I don't measure food or count calories anymore (if I do count, it's usually a really loose estimate), so I don't actually know how much I'm eating. I'm trying to focus more on getting in tune with my hunger signals, and learning to trust myself to feed myself, than I am with body image. It feels great, but the problem I've faced with this is that it never sticks for more than a few days before I binge.

My question is, do binges stem from too little calories or not responding to your hunger? I'm not really hungry often because when I eat, I'm satisfied for a long time afterwards. I just don't understand why the binges keep coming if I rarely feel hunger and always try to respond to it when I do. Why do I binge if I always try to give myself what I want to eat?

I'm really scared when I don't feel hungry. I start to think I truly am hungry but I'm in denial about it. And I'm scared if that's the truth that I will inevitably binge.

Does anyone else who has gone through something similar have any insight to give? Thanks a lot!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Trans girl trying to eat enough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 03:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone,

I was hoping to get some perspective from other members here. I'm a trans woman in my early 30s and am trying to become OK with the idea of reaching a healthy weight by no longer engaging in restricting eating behaviors. Unsurprisingly, the trans aspect of this whole thing complicates matters.

I'm underweight right now, and the problem is that, despite my objections as a feminist to the notion that the one way to be attractive is to be unhealthily thin, I like the comments from friends and coworkers about how skinny I am, even while I understand rationally that being this thin isn't healthy.

Now, one way being trans affects this is that, ironically, I know I'd look more feminine if I got up to a healthy weight--my face would look a little softer and more rounded, my body would take on a more feminine shape, etc. That's probably my primary motivation for recovery (and I'll leave aside for now the fact that conformity with hegemonic standards of femininity is kind of a sketchy motivation from a feminist standpoint).

However, that motivation gets a little muted by the fact that I already get "read" as a girl pretty much all the time anyway, as far as I can tell. If people were calling me "sir" and "dude" and stuff, I'd probably feel a stronger push. Still, wanting to feel happier with what I see in the mirror--i.e., seeing less boy and more girl in my appearance--does feel like a good motivator.

What's sparked a recent change in my thinking was when my friends stopped unexpectedly for ice cream and brought me peppermint bark ice cream, which they know I really like. I didn't eat it (they know about my eating behaviors and understood), but dude, it's the holidays, and peppermint bark rules. I think that just kind of made me think, "Wow, these restricting behaviors really, really suck, and I'm exhausted from dealing with them day in and day out."

For the past couple of days, I've been experimenting with being less restricting in my eating habits, with the goal of "I'll just try this out, get to X weight [only a small change], and see how that feels." I've made progress toward that, and it turns out that it feels terrifying. I kind of want to curl up into a ball and cry.

I'm scared of changes in my body from gaining weight, or comments from my co-workers (even though they're nice people who I doubt would really do that).

I think I also am upset because, even though strangers look at me and see a girl, and even though I'm not that tall, I still think I've internalized the idea that women are supposed to be small and delicate (which, of course, is a harmful, anti-feminist notion that my conscious self objects to). I'm also shy and don't like being the focus of people's attention, and I think being thin helps me feel a little less likely to attract anyone's notice.

Anyway, thanks so much for reading. Does anyone have any thoughts, perspectives, etc. you might have on dealing with this?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Bulimia turning into Anorexia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 03:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a 25 year old male who has been struggling with bulimia for the past 2 years. Recently, 2 months ago, the binging and purging stopped. But then immediately turned to the opposite extreme, restricting. Is this common? I have lost a lot of weight and now I am on the fast track to inpatient (I have been there before for bulimia) and am very worried. The problem is when I try to eat I literally start to feel sick to my stomach. Also after I eat I am overcome with a huge sense of guilt, a "oh god what have I done" kind of feeling," and it lasts for days. Is there a way to overcome that?

Also where can I find guys my age that deal with the same issue's? I feel very alone being a young male with an ED. I tried opening up to my friends about it once and it got extremely awkward and they said things I wont repeat here.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 14:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Before I Eat* for binge eating problems has been suggested as an addition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 14:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Helping gf](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1pl03w/sharing_girlfriend_is_recovering_from_bulimia/)

[What not to say](http://www.anad.org/wp-content/uploads/2010/11/What-Not-To-Say.pdf)

[Helping gf #2](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2ajwpb/sharing_some_of_my_personal_experince_on_how_to/)

[Help gf](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1y5gup/request_how_to_help_my_gf/)




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Feelings of Inadequacy Perpetuating Binges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 12:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) I find someone who I may be interested in. 

2) My appearance in comparison to their beauty pretty firmly cements the idea that it would be ridiculous to imagine they would ever reciprocate, and if by some miracle they did, I would always feel inadequate and want to improve/diet/etc until I felt deserving. 

3) I dwell on this. 

4) Feelings of supreme worthlessness. 

5) I overeat at the lower end of the spectrum or completely lose it and binge. 

6) By doing so I have made no progress towards ever feeling good enough and end up self sabotaging my ultimate desires. 

7) I am still attracted to that person or people and yet now I am post-binge, and worse off.

This seems to be happening over and over. I want to improve. I want to feel good enough, deserving, and not have to worry about my appearance all the time.

I am just having trouble breaking the cycle that seems to be an almost daily thing now.

I would be grateful for any insight/advice.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Help my friend: body dysmorphia, bulimia, eating disorder. Suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 05:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

Hello, my friend isn't doing well. She sees herself as fat, which she is far from. She eats very little and she throws up most of what she does eat. She is happy that people are noticing that she has slimmed down but it doesn't seem like she has any intention of slowing down or stopping. I've tried to get her to go to the doctors but she doesn't want to. What would you suggest?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 21:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can edit out the "mia" please as per the guidelines.  Some consider that it trivializes the illness. This reply will be removed when it's changed. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Permanent Damage from Bulimia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 16:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I am a former bulimic/binge eater who has been facing a lot of digestion problems since my bulimia episodes. Doctors have yet to find anything delectably wrong with any aspect of my digestive system (recent ultrasound, gastroscopy 2 years ago). 

I am curious if anyone has any knowledge about damage that can be done to one's insides through bingeing + purging, in hopes that I can get some direction for a diagnosis. 

Symptoms include: bloating, pulsing headaches, fatigue, brain fog, and abdominal tightness, acid reflux, all which are exacerbated from eating.

Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Should I be drinking coffee? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 03:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should people with binge-eating disorders be drinking coffee? Is it just me or does coffee/caffeine really disconnect you from your true hunger signals? Thanks a lot
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanksgiving </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 21:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To everyone suffering from or recovering from an ED, please know that you're not alone this Thanksgiving. Remember to take things in moderation. It's probably the hardest day of the year for everyone with an ED, but we can all get through this! I'm thankful for what a supportive community this is, and all of you guys! Happy Thanksgiving :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 15:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Binge Eating Recovery](http://np.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2i4ja3/post_request_binge_eating_disorderhelp_needed/).

[Portioning meals](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2dc4rb/recovery_sharing_ziploc_bags_and_other_things/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm worried my eating habits are unhealthy but don't know how to fix it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 00:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Hi /r/eatingdisoders, how goes it?

I'm a female in my 20s, currently in a stressful point in my graduate school career. I also recently went through a painful breakup which has not helped my emotional state. On top of that, I have ADHD - I take Adderall XR every day in order to focus on my coursework, but it kills my appetite.

Between the stress, the depression from the breakup, and the lack of hunger from the adderall, I just don't feel like grocery shopping or cooking or eating anything. This isn't so much restriction as simply not eating or undereating. Some days it just doesn't occur to me to eat. This has been going on for about 3 months now. I've lost  weight but I'm not clinically sick at this point - I'm hovering around the line between a normal weight and underweight.

I've dealt with borderline-ED before. I was unhappy with my slight college weight gain, so I restricted, occasionally binging and purging, and exercised. Although I counted calories obsessively, I generally got enough to eat and I never felt sick. Eventually I graduated and didn't have time to work out anymore - all the bad (and good) habits I had developed went away.

Right now I don't know how to fix my problem. I've been on anti-depressants for over 5 years. I don't think my dose needs to be messed with - everyone has good and bad days and I think these issues are fixable with behavior adjustments. My internal chemistry isn't the issue right now.

I recently started seeing a new therapist. I didn't know when I started seeing her she is actually an ED specialist so that's good. However, my last few sessions with her have focused on my breakup and stress over upcoming exams (which will make or break my graduate career - no pressure!). I plan to discuss my eating with her more next time I see her, but that's not for 2 weeks. At the same time, I will confess that at times I feel good when I see myself looking very thin. I weight myself often and I freak out if the number goes up even a tiny bit. These sorts of behaviors are scaring me.

Even when I try to eat, I don't have any appetite. This morning for breakfast, It was not very much food, but I couldn't finish it. I felt full, to the point of feeling sick and nauseous like I had overeaten.

I don't know what to do. I want to feel better, and eat healthy, but when I try I just can't do it. 

I want to feel emotionally better, but I don't think it is safe to do the things that (in my experience with depression) will make me feel better, like exercising. If I stopped taking my adderall I could probably eat, but I can't afford to mess with my concentration at this point. I feel trapped at every turn.

Please, any advise is helpful! What should I do? 

How can I do well on my exams if I am not eating much?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 16:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are:

 * Recovery Record

 * OneHealth Meeting Finder

 * Body Beautiful

 * Optimism

 * Positive Thinking

 * Self Help Classics

 * Mindfulness Bell

 * Cognitive Diary

 * Eating Disorder Assessment

 * RecoveryBox

 * The Kissy Project

 * Rise Up + Recover

 * What's my M3

Please tell us of any others apps, and what works for you. Be sensitive to others if something doesn't work for you, please, but do let us know.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 13 Best Eating Disorder iPhone   Android Apps of 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 16:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 16:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ideally, your treatment team gave you dietary guidelines and you are still working with a therapist and/or nutritionist who can help you set ups meal plans.

Hopefully helpful links:

[How to eat](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2imluw/request_how_to_eat_3_meals_a_day_at_specific_times/).

[Recovery meal plan](http://healingforeatingdisorders.com/sample-meal-plans-for-eating-disorders/)

[Food to eat](http://www.amazon.com/Food-Eat-hopeful-disorder-recovery/dp/1480083461/ref=pd_sim_b_1?ie=UTF8 refRID=1V4PDYE0B2CZH8M188R3) --just double recipes, and [Drop the diet](http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/1496188713/ref=pd_lpo_sbs_dp_ss_3?pf_rd_p=1944687782 pf_rd_s=lpo-top-stripe-1 pf_rd_t=201 pf_rd_i=1480083461 pf_rd_m=ATVPDKIKX0DER pf_rd_r=0XFE7RFC65YQWJ6Y8S9Z) by the same people.

[Process of recovery](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1t0qto/request_recovery_from_anorexia_can_someone/).

[Adding more calories](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/20d3fx/request_struggling_with_adding_more_calories/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Need help with binge eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 12:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earlier this year I was diagnosed with binge eating disorder, which was a relief, because at least I knew what it was.

However, I'm struggling with ways to manage this disorder. My weight is alarmingly high, and I just can't seem to stick to diets. I did weight watchers for a while, but fell off the wagon, and I joined slimming world because it actually helps change your eating habits and lets you eat more, but again I fell off the wagon.

I've been to therapy over the years, because I also have depression/anxiety, but nothing can make me stop eating. I feel like the comfort eating started when I was 13 and I don't know how to stop.

My family are all very concerned, and so am I. I know I just need to find the willpower, but it's all so overwhelming. I'm just looking for some guidance and advice to help me make a change, and also how to explain it to my parents, who are very practical, and don't know how to deal with it. Thanks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Continuing Recovery Out of Inpatient </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 12:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have recently left a 25 week stay in an inpatient facility for my anorexia. It was a long, hard process involving significant weight restoration and challenging all the 'rules' I had made for myself. I was discharged very shortly after reaching the minimum healthy BMI that the program requires, and am now largely without dietary support. I want to continue to gain a bit of weight to give myself more of a 'buffer' above the minimum BMI but am unsure of how to go about it on my own. I worry that I won't be able to keep challenging myself to my fear foods the way I did when I had support 24/7. Any help or advice would be very much appreciated.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Do I need to get a doctor involved? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 11:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been struggling with anorexic tendencies for a few months now, eating extremely few calories in a day. However, I've recently begun to recover with the help of a few close friends. No one else knows what's been going on. At this point, I don't feel physically bad or even all that weak. But I'm worried about the damage I may have caused my body. I was never more than a tiny bit "underweight" on the BMI scale, but could my muscles or bones be in trouble even if I feel fine and am eating a normal amount now? Should I see a doctor?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Minnie Maud? How did it work for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 23:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

Hey guys. I'm a 19 year old female who's been struggling with Anorexia for about 2 years now. I've finally reached rock bottom, which is what it's taken for me to genuinely want to change my ways and realize enough is enough. I'm seeing a doctor this week, and starting to see a counsellor. Unfortunately in my area there isn't anyone specializing in eating disorders.

I was wondering what you guys think of the Minnie Maud recovery guidelines? How did it work for you? Have you heard of anyone who's recovered this way? Or, if you used another method of recovery, what was it? I'm just looking to go into my appointment prepared with some ideas. I can't live like this anymore. Thanks guys:) .

Edit: Please only respond if you have experience with Minnie Maud. If you respond please be sensitive to all readers. So far, there is not one remedy that works for everyone, so if you respond, please remember the guidelines and be sensitive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Dealing with "sick" clothes, gifts that are too small for me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 23:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For my birthday I've been receiving some clothes that are in my old size and it is unbelievably triggering. I've gotten two pairs of pants that won't button up and fit comfortably and I don't know what to do about it. As of now, I've torn off the tags and promised myself to get fit and stick to my vegan diet to try to fit into them in a healthy way.

 I just can't bring myself to admit to my family that I can't fit into the size that I wore for years, but I'm afraid of a relapse. I feel like such a failure. 

These are gifts from family members who don't know (as far as I know) about my time in treatment, so I don't feel comfortable outright telling them that a pair of pants is so upsetting to me. On the other hand, I feel terrible about them wasting money on me. I'm just not sure what to do about this.

Do I say anything to anyone or not? How do I deal with this in the future? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I make healthy, "normal" people understand? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 16:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a couple incidents lately that have really set me back in my recovery. 

1. I was trying on dresses for a special event I have coming up. I found one I actually really liked, which was a big step for me because it was more form-fitting and showed off my arms and legs. When I wore it out, my mom's best friend immediately went, "Oh no, promise me you'll never wear that again! You look anorexic!!!" Fortunately my mom stepped in and changed the subject, but my self-confidence was shattered. 

2. My SO has started to become very agitated about my weight. I believe he is trying to help, but when he says, "It's easy - just eat more!" or makes me eat while he watches, it's frustrating and anxiety-provoking. When I tried to explain that it wasn't that easy because I'm scared of food, he thought it was a joke ("It's just FOOD! What's scary about that?").

With Thanksgiving and all coming up, I'm worried about how to deal with people making comments about my body. I don't want to be rude and shout out "Hey, I'm in recovery from AN so shut-up!", and confrontation/making requests of other people has never been easy for me.

Is there some trick for explaining myself or asking people to respect my privacy? I'm trying to get better but every day is a struggle, and hearing people take liberties with talking about my body or giving me unhelpful advice makes me feel like I'd rather disappear.

Has anyone been through anything similar? 3

edit: please pm /u/NewOrcCity when you reply here.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is this considered a problem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 16:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never considered my eating habits particularly unhealthy until recently. I've always been underweight and now from stress I've started losing weight more than I'd expected. It's not because I want to, and I'm scared.

These past few days I've had horrible eating habits, eating only one meal per day plus a small amount of snack food. None of them have given me much energy. Then tonight, I realized that I haven't been sleeping regularly at all (went to bed at 5 am yesterday and woke up 2pm).

I know it's because of university stress, but I am freaking out. I can't bring myself to eat much because I'm stressed and tired, but I know I'm tired because I'm not eating. I'm not particularly depressed, just feeling at a total loss. (I don't know if this is TMI, but I also have been having horrific diarrhea these past few days)

It should also be mentioned that my only food source is from my university's cafeteria, but my plan only allows me to eat there once a day. I'm so poor from paying for room, board and classes that it's really the only meal I do get when I force myself to go there.

Do I even have an eating disorder or is it just stress?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: 14 y/o diagnosed with BN and I don't know what I am doing. Why change? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 18:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am 14 years old and was recently diagnosed with BN. I am attending an outpatient program but I don't know what to do. 

I am still consistently purging but I'm not losing enough weight. I want to be thinner and I feel weird. I don't know I just want to be thinner.

What's wrong with wanting to be thinner?

What are the side effects of purging constantly?

I can stop any time, right?

Why change? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Disordered eating kicks my ass every holiday season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 09:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do my worst eating of the year from November to December. I think part of it is instinctually wanting to eat more because it's cold. Part of it is because I hate my family and love eating my emotions, and the other part, who knows.

Last night for example I know I shouldn't have binged but still did. I felt so sluggish when I woke up, and then I didn't feel like working out. Like, this is not who I've worked to become. I've thought I was beyond binging so many times, but at certain times of the year it seems impossible not to avoid.

It feels like I'm two people: the shallow self who says "no, don't order the pizza, it's not healthy, this is why you're not losing weight you dumbass", and the deeper self that says "fuck you, I was deprived for a long time and now I'll do whatever I want, because I don't feel guilty anymore."

Not as guilty, at least. How can I make it through this holiday period? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 01:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully [helpful post](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2hmq78/request_selective_eating_disorder_what_can_i/).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Has anyone got any experience with overcoming "picky eating"? Selective eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 01:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
For as long as I can remember, I've been labeled a "picky eater" by my parents and family. My diet's mostly limited to potatoes (in most any state), chicken, pasta, toast, cereal, bananas and random snack foods. There's the odd other bit of food I'll eat, like sausages, apples and carrots, but I can only stomach these in small quantities, and I can force most varieties of vegetables down with a lot of effort.

Basically everything else, I'm repulsed by. Anything with a glopy texture especially, like sauces and dips. The moment I start moving the food towards my face, the mental block sets in and I seriously can't get past it. It makes eating in public exceptionally difficult. I never ate lunch in school once because of this, and I'm always worried about going out to restaurants or going over to friends' houses for dinner because whatever they're serving might not be part of my extremely limited diet. I can't even eat sandwiches, because the fillings often have a texture that just repulses me, and makes me want to gag.

I'm not even sure if this is a real eating disorder, so I'm sorry if these problems are petty in comparison to the effects of real eating disorders, but it's seriously impacting my life and I can't find any advice regarding it. So, can you offer me any? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm not sure how my recovery is going. Confused if I'm "recovered" even though thoughts about food/health still consume me. I feel alone. (bulimia) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 18:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eight months ago I finished an outpatient program for my BN.  It was kind of stressful. My fiance has been more than supportive to me. Since I had already been in serious therapy, fighting urges was a little easier. It took me about two months of constant attention to my body's cues and the food I was consuming to be able to keep myself from throwing up. **However, I feel like I've only fixed one aspect of my ED.** 

**I'm confused about my body.** I feel hungry half the time and I feel full the other half, but still want to eat a lot. My digestive tract is still all wonky. Sometimes I can't use the bathroom regularly for almost a week at a time, and sometimes I get so full I'm nauseous from eating a small snack. I'm confused about if I can even claim that I've recovered? 

**It was really hard for me to accept what my healthy weight is**, and sometimes I still need to fight the urge to do something to change it. I still almost always have eating or food or nutrition on my mind. Sometimes I even daydream about back when I was ill and I almost miss those times (Is that normal???). 

I eat several small meals throughout the day because it helps me fight binges, and I can even enjoy it, but I feel guilty about it. Sometimes I feel like I have to force myself to eat, sometimes I feel like I have to control how much I consume. I still identify myself as having an eating disorder and being depressed (I realized that I was only having a depressive episode for about nine months, I qualify more for dysthymia), even though I'm doing much better than I was this time last year.

I'm so frustrated because I'm now in college studying to be an RD so I can help other people in (hopefully) other out patient clinics. But I can't apply it to myself. I can recite why fats are good for you, why protein is important, how not all calories are the same, but I feel like none of that applies to me. I got a chance to attend college near other relatives so I moved in with them, but they are crazy religious and still ask me if I'm 'cured' like, I'm piece of ham. I'm moving out in three weeks when the semester is over because I can't stand it. 

I talk to my fiance about all of this and it helps, but **I miss talking about it with people who genuinely understand.** Sometimes I feel totally misunderstood and misread. I'm bone-deep lonely. Not just because I'm not near people. I feel hollow.

I feel like BN became part of me, is still a part of me. It's almost like I don't want to get better. I get upset when people make fun of ED victims. **I have conflicting thoughts:** I think "okay, do this and I will get better" which is logical, but I also think "Well...if I do this then I'm dirty and gross." I feel like I'm in this weird in-between land where I'm not exactly recovered, but I'm not exactly showing enough symptoms to have an ED anymore.

 * Am I getting better? How can I tell? I think I am, but why am I still obsessed with food and my body? 

 * What do I have? How do I let go of these thoughts and feelings? 

 * I'm afraid but reassured at the same time that I still identify as someone with an ED. Does anyone feel the same way? Can anyone relate? 


 * On a side note, does anyone else feel ashamed for saying 'depressed'? I was always lead to believe that people who said that were faking it because truly 'depressed' people kept it a secret from people. I promise I do know that I depression is real! I know it's scary and a serious problem, however, I grew up being told that it was made up and now I feel like I'm faking it, but other people aren't. Does that make sense? I have conflicting feelings about admitting I have these feelings, I can't tell if I'm genuinely feeling this way or if I'm being dramatic.

 * Please share your thoughts (if you're comfortable doing so). It would be nice hearing from people that are going through recovery, want to recover, or who have already recovered. I need help from you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Personal responses to being diagnosed with EDNOS. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 03:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing a dissertation on disordered eating in literature, and I'm very interested in learning about people's experiences in being diagnosed with EDNOS. 

That is, 

 * what their experiences were with doctors

 * how it made them feel about their themselves 

 * how it might have changed their perspective on their behaviour, 

 * and how it might have impacted the progression of their illness. 

I know from my own experience that being diagnosed with EDNOS gave me more questions than answers, and I'm curious to learn if others felt the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Binge eating is ruining my post-bulimia life. First steps to help myself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 16:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I used to be sort of between anorexia and bulimia and terrified of most foods. I'm past that, and I was even happy with my new size, but for the last 18 months I've been spending 100+ per week on binge food. I've put on enough weight to make me seriously uncomfortable.

My bedroom has currently got SIX bin bags of food waste in it. Our trash doesn't get collected all that often and I live in a house with a bunch of other people. I'm pretty antisocial anyway but I can never let anybody in my room.

I'm not interested in food unless I'm bingeing. I wander around the supermarket for 20 minutes trying to find healthy food I want to eat but I can't find anything, so I go home and later come back out to buy binge food.

I'm trapped by my obsessive bingeing and by my disgusting living arrangement. What are the very first steps I can take to help myself? Even things like "don't eat between meals" are too advanced for me right now because meals aren't happening, even though I'm constantly making meal plans.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What should I have done? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 02:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a woman come into panera's today. She looked sickly, abnormally thin, and wore baggy clothing, 40-ish. She looked like how I would expect someone that has an eating disorder would look.

She came in and just sat down, didn't order. I thought perhaps I should invite her to sit down with my daughter and I to eat. But maybe she was waiting for someone? I didn't know. After about an hour, she left. Didn't meet anyone, didn't order, didn't eat. Just watched people.

Is this common behavior for someone with an eating disorder?

Did I miss out on a chance to help? I don't underestimate the kindness of strangers and have been on the receiving end in the past. Could I have done something? Would inviting her to sit with us be appropriate? Am I way off base in thinking she had an eating disorder?

I'd like to learn if/when I'm in a similar situation.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Bone Density Scan after Anorexia, nervous! :( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 02:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my ED has not been too much of an issue these past 2 years (I was receiving help and not opposed to recovery) but anyway, lately a few things have been wrong with my back and now I'm getting a bone density scan. I didn't have my period for about 8 years and it's still not regular, so the osteopath ordered a test and was surprised I'd never had it done before. I'm really nervous!

I find myself both wanting the bone density to show something - to validate my ED - but also not wanting it to show anything. I can't imagine that 2 years is enough to reverse any damage. I will be embarrassed if there is nothing to show on the scan. I was always told I was faking it. Regardless of how bad it got, my parents never acknowledged it...

I don't know why I'm posting really, or what I'm looking for. Maybe anyone's experiences and what happens afterward, if there is Osteoporosis or Osteopenia? or did anyone have a similar experience where it showed no bone density issue?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Recovering but constant anxiety. Is there a helpful way to overcome this anxiety? (bulimia) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 16:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I'm currently recovering from bulimia (binge/purge through vomiting). I haven't purged in a few weeks so I'm very new to recovery but very strong in my resolve. I haven't yet told my Doctor that I was purging. It was occurring every few weeks for a few days at a time for two years.

Now that I'm recovering, I can't help but fear that I've permanently damaged my body. I don't have any symptoms to go by but I do think I start to imagine symptoms of heart failure and kidney failure. 

Is there a helpful way to overcome this anxiety? Sometimes I just feel need someone to tell me I'm not going to die as I've stopped the addiction.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Broken the bulimia cycle, but need help with anxiety! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 12:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have ended the cycle after 8-9 years of trying! Binge-purge free for the last few months! Finally told someone about my disorder when I saw a therapist and it turns out I have extreme anxiety. She suggested exercise and mindfulness as coping methods. Since pointing out my anxiety I have realised that I DO feel extra anxious around the times I crave food.

I already exercise a lot and Im trying the mindfulness thing, but does anyone have any additional strategies? I never found yoga very helpful...

Breaking the cycle: I broke the extreme binge purge cycle by using the healthy, structured, pre-packaged food from Jenny Craig for 5 months: - I had no involvement in the food prep - Knew it was already calorie controlled (so I got to stay away from nutrition labels) - "Binges" were limited to the weekly food allowance; even eating tomorrows food meant I didn't gain weight after it all averaged out over the week. And it sucked having a little less food each day so more motivation to stay on track! - AND, even after a binge, because I knew it was calorie controlled I didn't feel as much guilt and managed to end the purge cycle.

After a bumpy first couple of weeks, I got into a pattern, eating small meals regularly and had nothing bad around to tempt me. I still messed up occasionally, but it got easier and easier.

Sticking to a limited daily menu is helping me. Minimal foods to obsess over, repetitive food choices mean I am less enthusiastic about eating them and eating has become something I do to live instead of enjoy or comfort myself with. Including a lot of healthy but high fat foods in my diet now means I feel REALLY full or REALLY hungry, never in between (~2 hrs after a main meal was when my binges happened more often). Longer feeling full (not just "not hungry") = less cravings for food.

Any additional tips for staying on track would also be very welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Online support for ENDOS? How to cope with being in a foreign country and needing help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 15:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, I've been struggling with EDNOS for about 3 years (since diagnosis). I am currently on exchange in Japan, and inexplicably my bingeing/purging behaviour has gone into overdrive, despite me actually feeling very comfortable and happy here - not feeling homesick at all.

If I were at home, I think I would start to see a therapist about it again, but as I'm here I don't feel able to. If the university here knew I had mental health issues, it is possible they would send me home and I really don't want that. I have considered speaking to some of my new friends here about it, but although I get along with them all really well, it seems like too much pressure to put on a new friendship. Likewise, I don't feel that I can speak to people back home about it, as they will simply worry about me and they each have their own problems which I don't want to add to.

So basically, I'm feeling a little stranded. Does anyone know where I could find support online (in English)?

Additionally, has anyone had a similar experience, and if so how did they cope with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Truth about Eating Disorders: one person's experience with not wanting to recover, then wanting to enjoy life more than have an ED. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 15:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I know if it's a problem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 11:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been throwing up since I was about 17 years old; I'm 21 now. Used to be overweight/obese as a child and young teen, got down to a normal BMI in high school through purging and restricting. I lost enough weight in a short enough period of time that a tearful intervention by my friends mostly curbed my behaviours. I stopped for maybe 6 months, then did it very infrequently as a means to deal with anxiety after starting university. I've never really quit the habit, so to speak, but it's been at decidedly non-problematic levels for the better part of the last three years.

I'm fairly overweight right now, and have been purging at every available opportunity for the last few weeks. Which is not as often as I would perhaps like, as my roommate is home a lot. While part of me can see, logically, that this might be a problem...I don't know. I can't take myself seriously about a potential ED when I'm so overweight already. I don't want to trivialize other people's struggles with genuine mental illness. And the last time it was this bad, I mostly stopped when I was called out on it. I've never been clinically underweight. I'm also about to finish a psychology degree, which makes me feel stupid about seeking help, since I have a fairly thorough understanding of the inner workings of ED, and have successfully counselled friends with anorexia before.

I have never seen a doctor or psychologist about this; nor have I told my parents or anyone in my family. Part of me wants to seek guidance with this before I graduate and don't have free and easy access to a therapist anymore; part of me thinks I'll be laughed out of the office because I don't exactly look like I'm suffering with my eating. I don't want them to think I'm being dramatic. And I kind of think I might be being dramatic. Part of me feels like I won't want to follow their advice anyway. Part of me wants to stop, and part of me really doesn't.

I don't know if I have an eating disorder or not. I don't know what to do.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 16:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully helpful posts:

[Relapse](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2j7kf8/request_crazy_bingepurge_relapse_after_8_years_of/)

[Bulimia recovery sharing](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2dc4rb/recovery_sharing_ziploc_bags_and_other_things/)

[AMA on bulimia recovery](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/1uob3k/ama_on_recovery_2_years_ago_i_recovered_from/)

[Addressing Bulimia](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/24g5vt/request_how_to_begin_addressing_bulimia/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 15:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully [helpful post](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2lg37c/request_think_girl_i_am_dating_has_an_ed_if_so_ow/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to deal with a friend (long distance) who has bulimia/an eating disorder? How can I best relate to her difficulties? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 18:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking around for ways to help a friend of mine who has bulimia. However, most of the help is about spotting and getting them to realize that there is a problem type thing. That is not my problem. She already knows she has a problem and is getting outpatient treatment for it.

I've got a friend of mine [Let's call her Karen] who has an bulimia [and some other issues.]. We live roughly five hundred miles apart and so we mostly communicate by Facebook. We talk about mutual interests mostly, but from time to time, she will either post on facebook about having a hard day or our conversation will wander in that direction. When it does, I really want to help her. I want to be encouraging and be in her corner. However, I feel somewhat helpless to actually help.

I don't understand what it's like to be in her head. I've never had an eating disorder of any sort. I feel like I don't know how to talk to her. I do try to encourage her and try to be a good friend, but it's completely uncharted territory and I'm honestly afraid of accidentally hurting rather then helping.

I often analogize it to being like someone has a broken leg. Getting frustrated with them because they can't run across the field with you is not going to help anything. I feel like as a friend, it's my job to lock arms with you and help hold you up as we cross the field together. However, what I'm afraid of is not locking arms right and so because of that you break your leg again. I don't know if that makes sense, so let me try to put it a different way.

I really want to be in her corner, but rather then being Micky, I feel like some random person from off the street. How do I deal with this?

What is a good way to relate to her difficulties?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 18:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consider [this post, here](http://www.reddit.com/r/EatingDisorders/comments/2lgrru/request_request_for_advice_on_how_to_talk_to/).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
