<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject758</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 13:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SMASH AND BURN PLS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 11:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> grow your hair a bit more and you can be Tintin. :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 07:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize masturbation feels like pizza tastes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 13:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've eaten at this place and let me tell you, I never liked it. And I am certainly not coming back after seeing this, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 10:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can relate and I hope one day I'll reach contentment and a sober-free lifestyle and manage my ED. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 10:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to get my ass back to an NA/AA/OA/whatever 12 step meeting and I'm ashamed that my old sponsor will know if I relapsed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 10:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 19 year old female.

I was addicted to Vicodin/OxyContin/Oxycodone for a good year and then I had to go to rehab, the worst part was also dealing with an eating disorder at the same time and losing all my friends, dropping out of school, being hospitalized several times. It was shit. 

Life was about using, feeling numb, feeling in control, going to sleep, and doing the same shit over again+ having to pretend that you're okay and you're sober.

Absolute fucking shit it is, and I just relapsed and I struggle as I'm currently typing this. The worst part is how badly I want to stop but I don't know how I'd live or manage without drugs, my eating disorder, or anything addictive that's bad for me. I'm struggling and I desperately need help and I fucking hate ambivalence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 13:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [someasiankid](http://25.media.tumblr.com/902cdf2169c433fd98fd5f261cdc30a1/tumblr_mulur6dmXH1shzdc1o1_500.jpg)

also I have a mole that's like, oddly placed.. and braces..oh yes, the teenage years are delightful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 06:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm gonna come down super soon like couple minutes."

wat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 03:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> kittens will wander up your butt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 03:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh okay! No prob. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 02:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you everyone for their support. 

I read everything.

I just hope I can persevere. Honestly, I don't know if I can. Wish me luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
