<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3259</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which word's spelling and pronunciation bothers you the most? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 07:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking to transfer for next fall...what should I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 07:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys so currently I'm a part time student at a university in Ontario. I don't like my school or my program and am thinking of transferring universities. At the end of May I'll only have two courses done. 

 I was looking at OCAD and was wondering how hard it is to get in? I would say I'm pretty good at drawing/painting and am very creative and want to pursue something in art. I also saw their BA degree but it says you have to submit an essay?

If anyone could give me some insight as to what OCAD looks for and what the whole campus feel is like, that'd be much appreciated! 

Or if anyone has any other program or school suggestions that are art-based and in Toronto, that would be great :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 06:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DO NOT EAT RAW COOKIE DOUGH
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What strange childhood habit have you carried on into adulthood? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 06:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some hobbies that are good for the soul? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 06:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So recently all I've been doing is baking. Every. Single. Day. I find its a great stress reliever however I always end up eating too much of what I make. The problem is I have an ED which when combined with my baking, isn't good for my health. 

What are some hobbies you guys have that help your mental health and your physical health?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 06:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The high school I attended was super religious and had stupid rules about almost everything. Kids who went there were mean af and just ruined the whole HS experience for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 06:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I don't see myself living past 30. Maybe I'll reach 25 if I'm lucky. I'm so alone in this world, always have been and always will be. I'm stubborn and unhappy. Can't see myself successful, married or having kids. Either my ED is going to kill me, or my depression will cause me to either kill myself or just stop takin care of my health.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 06:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally just ate an apple a day and did lots of strenuous work. Lost tons of weight which of course I gained back but I learned that if you just eat less and move more weight will be lost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 06:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My birth. I finally was in the flesh instead of a pruney blob floating in a sac of amniotic fluid :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your weird food habit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 20:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just realized that maybe eating tomato sauce straight from the jar isn't all that normal...

So what are some of your odd food habits? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 20:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delicious waxy regrets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 08:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who don't use their signals (bonus if they cut in front of you) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 08:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caffeine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 08:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make dildo moulds and sell dick shaped ice pops:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 08:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your parents having sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have an "all or nothing" food? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 08:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about the food you can't have in the house because you'll literally eat it all in one sitting. 

Mine is peanut butter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 08:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man I dont even want to think about that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something you will never tell your kids about yourself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 07:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 01:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have good connections. Dress smart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 01:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine was 'Cheese lips'

I used to lick my lips so much that under my nose got so red I guess it looked like nacho cheese </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your nickname when you were a kid and what did you do to earn it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 01:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 01:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Melatonin. That shit will knock you out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 01:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took a trip to the east coast when I was younger. A hurricane came along(I think it was Bill) and we were stuck in an inn right in front of the ocean. Literally right in front of it. 

So the night before it hit I thought we were going to die so I hit up the lobster buffet and then gorged myself on seafood chowder. Workers then came to board us up inside our rooms so there was no way we could leave or see out the window. 

Morning hits and the power is out so no tv but we listened to the radio. Spent the day eating froot loops with no milk and crying with every gust of forceful wind I heard. Took a nap and when I woke up the storm was dying down. Wasn't even that bad to be honest. I was young so of course I thought the worse. It made for a cool story though. 

Tl;dr: went to New Brunswick,  got stuck in hurricane, ate a bunch of froot loops and didn't die.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something you do that you thought was normal until someone pointed out that it was creepy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 01:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 00:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I'm sad I tend to spend money on stuff I wouldn't rationally buy when I'm happy so I would say that I waste more money when I'm sad; not necessarily spend more b </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 00:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OH MY GOD haha! I did this once! The guy was so pissed off at me but it was such a good laugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your best response when a guy asked you for nudes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 00:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh...let me start out by saying I'm totally fine with people sending nudes and you do you etc etc. BUT I am so tired of guys that ask for nudes and when I say 'no', they start with the guilt trip and the classic "it'll only be seen by me."

What are some ways you've trolled guys who do this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 23:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recipe I used was allrecipes.com/recipe/6749/ciabatta/?internalSource=search%20result referringContentType=search%20results

Let the starter sit for 24+ hrs and it was delicious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 06:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went to go ride the roller coaster when I was younger but I didn't meet the height requirements  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 06:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bagging items </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When is the worst time a case of the serial shits could hit you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 06:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's something everyone should learn before they move out on their own? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 10:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's one thing parents are expected to teach their kids that you taught yourself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 08:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 08:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents always work(ed) late so around dinner time I started to cook the basics (like eggs) and then discovered that cooking was pretty cool. Read some cooking books and played around with recipes. Taught myself most of what I know. Mostly now I just bake but I find both cooking and baking to be very relaxing hobbies...minus the cleanup.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE find that those who drive luxury vehicles use their signals less than those who drive other cars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 08:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 07:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When there's that silence when you're alone together and you know you both want to kiss...just go for it. Lean in and if she reciprocates the feelings she will let you kiss her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 07:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exiting the womb 

0/10 would not recommend  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 07:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put a cucumber behind them when they're drinking out of their water bowl  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 07:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anything by Ray LaMontagne, Damien Rice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 20:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's one thing you should do before stepping into your car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 05:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 05:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being behind a slow walker with bad b.o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 05:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elaine from Seinfeld .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 05:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It may be time to sit down with your dryer and talk to it about the dangers of drugs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 00:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know how hard it is to fold cardboard into a circle?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 07:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please don't apologize! 

I may not be the best for  advice like this seeing as how I handled my situation but I think you should just let him know the truth and don't get too caught up in it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 06:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's awkward as hell.  I was pretty upset with them because they basically ruined something that could've made me happy. 

Does he like you though? Because if he does then it'll still be awkward but you can still work with that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 06:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robot Dick  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 06:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd guess that the Nigerian Prince came through on his word.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 06:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dick shaped lollipop that was made in China. Put it in my closet where my mom ended up finding it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 06:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of us actually enjoy wearing makeup and it's kind of fun to put on TBH  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's one thing the opposite sex spends money on that baffles you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 06:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 06:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friends told him. I ran away and avoided all contact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 06:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed that "Santa's" handwriting was suspiciously similar to my fathers...upon further investigation and a side-by-side comparison, I came to the conclusion that Santa and my parents were one in the same. This is why I have trust issues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 06:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoiler alert </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did you find out Santa wasn't real? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 06:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 06:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do they not make this mandatory to learn in high school... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 06:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My coping skill? Locking myself inside my house distracting myself with cooking, cleaning, baking, exercise and painting. Does it work? Yes but only for a short bit of time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 06:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would not want them to find the password to my phone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
