<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1637</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 16:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be crossing the line. Going after lawyers for doing their jobs makes me uneasy, but I suppose if she was unprofessional about it then that's a valid criticism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 15:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Folks, I hate Hillary as much as the next guy but this is something we can't go after her for. She was a defense attorney, she defended her client. That's her job. Even scumbag rapist child molesters have the right to a lawyer, and the justice system doesn't work unless defense attorneys represent their clients' interests to the best of their ability.

MAGA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 14:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Derevi's ability doesn't cast her then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 00:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two-weapon fighting seems WAY undercosted. I could see that being on-curve at 3, and *very* playable at 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 00:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Songbird's Champion would be interesting as a commander. A perpetually available 3 mana "gain 8 life". 

EDIT: Just saw that it was a theme, not a single creature. Leviathan's would be a crazy good commander, 3 mana draw 2 always available?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 19:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy I play Magic with is an obnoxious asshole. He's a judge, so he acts like he's always right about the rules and most of us believe him. But I've caught him lying about the rules twice now. Not just mistakes, no, he *made up rules* that didn't exist specifically to give himself an advantage in the game.

He's constantly belittling and insulting me and my friends (it seems like half of what comes out of his mouth is the word "stupid"). He argues about everything, insisting that we play the way that is most advantageous to him. He argues for penalties when others make mistakes, and argues for leniency when he makes them.

And he's extremely selfish. Last night he sold me a 2015 Commander deck for 25$, which is 15$ off the sticker price. I counted the cards and, lo and behold, there were 7 cards missing. He said he just took out a few of the cheap ones. I haven't checked the value of the missing cards but I'm positive that one of them cost 3$, not cheap by any stretch. I'm not sure why I trusted him in the first place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 18:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rune Factory! Both 1 and 2  are great games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 19:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please correct me if I'm wrong, but I believe that bail money is put down as "collateral". Rather than a bribe to get you out of jail, it's a way for the state to ensure that you stick around for your trial. You get it back after the decision is made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 17:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is number 3? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 06:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red Rocket Factory. I turned the gas station into a scrap producing workhouse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 03:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this on /r/all and although I'm not a Trump supporter I'm disgusted. This is the sort of behavior that is gradually convincing me that Trump is a better alternative to the fascist left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 06:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the morning after pill is explicitly abortive, and has no alternative uses, then yes. If a gun manufacturer was advertising their product as a great way to shoot up a high school, then yeah I'd hold them accountable. But there's no reason that a gun maker who advertises guns for deer hunting should be held responsible for any murder committed with their weapons. I don't think you would hold Cutco responsible if one of their knives was used as a murder weapon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 06:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SAVAGE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 17:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been thinking about this ever since clues were announced. I'm toying with the idea of going Jeskai or even Boros, since [[Thraben Inspector]] helps round out the curve and [[Bygone Bishop]] makes them relevant mid/late-game.

Green gets a lot of mileage out of clues, but doesn't do well at creating them. The best you get is [[Tireless Tracker]] giving you 1 clue per turn, or [[Ulvenwald Mysteries]]. 

Blue has good clue creation only if you have the support for it. [[Ongoing Investigations]] and [[Trail of Evidence]] are too inconsistent if we're building around Aether Grid. [Erdwal Illuminator]] is excellent for any clue deck.

In the end, I decided to throw caution to the wind and build Jeskai Clues. I'd like to hear what you've come up with! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 23:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In modern you're better off with archive trap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 19:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This explanation doesn't make sense to me... in English adjectives come before the word they describe. Why is it dehumanizing to use an adjective to describe a person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 18:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is the difference between an initialism and the full term important? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is the PC term for black "person of color" but "colored" is super racist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 18:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 17:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Played last night, my pulls were pretty bad. Promo Tireless Tracker, got a Graf mole and ended up building GW. I had a grand total of 3 removal spells, 1 Puncturing Light and 2 Humble the Brute. I went 1/3. Takeaways:

That 1/3 Skulk Lifelink as a 3-drop is way better than it looks. Functionally a "drain 1 life per turn".

Ethereal Guidance is a sleeper hit. A good white deck is going to have TONS of 1/1 flyers, I had 5 on the board at one point and my main color was green. Pumping all of them is great value.

Delirium is hard af to get online. Don't count on it.

Surgical Extraction is underrated. Takes up a card slot, yeah, but if it means countering Devil's Playground it's worth it.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to kill something </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 22:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 20:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. 3/3 for 2 is great value if you have cheap madness. You won't want it on turn 2, but dropping it turn 3 with fiery temper is game-changeingly good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 20:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're overlooking the versatility of Sanitarium Skeleton. It's not just 2B to save you a discard, it's also 3B to save you a sacrifice. It can be returned at instant speed, so if you have untapped mana saved for combat tricks you can still tap it for value if your opponent doesn't swing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 19:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. It has a huge advantage of being both recursively discard-able and sacrifice-able. Late in the game, when you're topdecking, you'll have a lot of free mana during the opponent's turn. As we saw in the LRR event, you can use that to return Sanitarium Skeleton after you block with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 06:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Build a dike and make *the ocean* pay for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 18:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've actually been building this character on-and-off for a few months now. He's an expert mechanic who fights with a pipe wrench and a robot butler. I originally started playing him so I could max out Robotics Expert, hack every robot I found, and use them to defend my settlements.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 17:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Newb here, can I tap a land for mana and *then* sac it for the upkeep? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 15:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's *thir* to you, Codsworth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Automatron] Do you have to complete the Silver Shroud questline to get special speech options? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 15:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does "abusing" adderall actually mean? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 00:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read articles about how college students are abusing adderall to help them focus, as a "study drug." But isn't that what adderall is for? Helping people focus? I don't see how that's considered abusing the drug. And I've even seen the term used in the context of people prescribed adderall using it to study, so it isn't just illegal use. So what does "abusing" a drug actually mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't transfer into the major I want, and all my other options suck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 09:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to transfer into cs, but I need a 3.2 gpa and I only have a 3.0. I go to a tech school, so majoring outside of STEM is a waste of time and money. So my options are basically chemistry, physics, biology and math. I hate the first three, and though I love math I cannot stand taking more than 1 math class per semester. 

I'm so lost. I really feel like I fucked up irreversibly, and I'm honestly considering killing myself. When I planned my college life, I kept my depression in mind. I made sure I always had a backup plan, so I would never feel like life was hopeless if I fucked up. Well, I ran out of backup plans. If I can't transfer into a major I'm ok with, I'm just a waste of time and money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 23:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly? Too many variables, not enough letters. If I see a v in an equation I don't know if it means volume, voltage, velocity, etc.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 05:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Explosive pipe rifle. Plentiful ammo, and with the demolition expert perks it does tons of damage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm changing my major at the end of this semester, should I switch to CS or IT? (X-post /r/CSCareerQuestions) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 22:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My current major is Physics, and I've struggled with it all year. I don't really like it, and it's tough to understand. I really enjoyed the two programming classes that I took in HS, but I'm terrified of the possibility that I will be sitting in a desk all day doing nothing but typing code on a computer.

IT on the other hand looks promising. I figure it involves a lot of hands-on, physical work with computers, which appeals to me. My worry is the job market. Programmers are well-paid and in high demand. And a CS major is versatile, it could lead to a job in almost any computer-based field. Does IT offer that same kind of flexibility?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm changing my major at the end of this semester, should I switch to CS or IT? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 20:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My current major is Physics, and I've struggled with it all year. I don't really like it, and it's tough to understand. I really enjoyed the two programming classes that I took in HS, but I'm terrified of the possibility that I will be sitting in a desk all day doing nothing but typing code on a computer.

IT on the other hand looks promising. I figure it involves a lot of hands-on, physical work with computers, which appeals to me. My worry is the job market. Programmers are well-paid and in high demand. And a CS major is versatile, it could lead to a job in almost any computer-based field. Does IT offer that same kind of flexibility? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 20:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not nearly as bad as I was expecting. There's good reason to oppose him, so if that's the way the leadership wants to go I don't expect them to have too much trouble. But it wouldn't be a tragedy if this guy ends up on the SCOTUS. 

That said, I can't find any info about his abortion stance, and I would be MUCH more comfortable with a justice who I know is pro-life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 20:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything about that would have been hysterical.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 15:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Trump isn't wrong when he calls Cruz "Lyin' Ted." I can think of several instances where he has told out and out lies on tv.

That, *that* is a good reason to fear a candidate. Constantly telling blatant lies to advance their own ambitions. But still, on that front he isn't nearly as bad as Trump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 13:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The President has been overstepping the bounds of executive authority for decades. Our ideal president should be one who *can't* get anything done, even if he tried. That administration would see the power of governance returned to its rightful place in Congress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 13:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See? This is what I'm hearing:

1. He's unwilling to compromise

2. The GOP don't like him

3. He's generally unlikable

4. He has an annoying face

These are all really bad reasons to dislike a candidate. If you agreed with him, you wouldn't want him to compromise his views. If you don't like the Republican establishment, then point 2 is actually a plus. And personal likability is *totally* irrelevant to effective administration. 

I know there are good reasons to oppose Cruz. His tax plan is madness, he's wrong about climate change, his immigration policy would hurt the country, etc. But these aren't reasons to *hate* him, just to *disagree* with him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 13:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I'm real confused about this. Why does everyone hate Cruz so much? Like, I don't *like* him, I don't even *agree* with him, but why are people treating him like he's an absolute tyrant? He's probably the most small-government guy left in the running. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 10:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will vote for the Libertarian nominee. As the largest third party in America, they have the best chance at gaining a spot at the table with the big two. And this year both major candidates will be hugely unpopular, so there's a decent chance the Libertarian will participate in the debates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 10:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  My main complaint this season was that it was too predictable/the foreshadowing was too easy. I saw a handful of things coming ahead of time (assassination, VP, Seth v Doug, Doug and the widow...) and I don't think I have an overly keen sense of storytelling. I felt the past seasons caught us by surprise more often.

Yeah, the foreshadowing was pretty obvious. When Frank traced Meechum's hand on the wall I literally said out loud, "Meechum's going to die, and someone's going to paint over the handprint, and Frank's going to be pissed." It was very predictable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 10:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok to be fair the original House of Cards was heavily based upon Richard III and Macbeth. If you've seen both of them, these parallels are easy to see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 03:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Politifact leans left. If you read a few of the articles that were labeled "mostly false," "half-true" or "mostly true," you can see that they are more inclined to apply negative labels to conservatives after reaching essentially the same conclusions about the facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 21:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it happens. The GOP has a TON of debates, and this cycle they've been hosted by CNN, NBC, and MSNBC at some point. Fox News, particularly Fox Business, tends to run good, policy-oriented debates, and I don't think that would change too much if it was a Democratic debate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Donald Trump is the Republican nominee, what would be his best choice for a running mate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 09:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 03:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, but he deliberately ran to the center in this primary campaign, so the perception is that he is moderate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 01:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   he's not a conservative

  he's running without specific policies

  possible abuse of power

 This describes every nearly establishment Republican.

Not really though. The last two "establishment" candidates in the running, Rubio and Kasich, are both very conservative (though Kasich has deliberately tried to run as a moderate). They're running with very clear policies that have been mostly consistent throughout their political careers, the only notable exception being Rubio on immigration. And nobody but Trump has proposed such abuses of power as war crimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 21:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with Kasich is that he is perceived as too moderate. More conservative voters might not bother coming out to vote if Kasich is the nominee. 

Rubio is the establishment choice because he's electable enough to sway independents but conservative enough to bring hard-line Republicans out to vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 19:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be an excellent card to manifest cheat in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 21:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Romania's anthem sounds deliciously fascist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 18:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit,

1. Lucas gets arrested and openly speaks about a conspiracy against him by Frank Underwood,

2. Lucas meets Dunbar,

3. Lucas shoots Underwood.

That's going to look mighty suspicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 18:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the contrary, the only honest way to present an opinion is as fact. If I said "I think Nixon is a great president" my statement would be factually true. But in saying "Nixon is a great president" I am stating only an opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 18:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH Nixon was a damn good president. Watergate soured his legacy, for good reason, but if it wasn't for that he'd definitely be in my top 10.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 18:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 17:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does she count as red when flipped? The card doesn't say Avacyn is red, and there's no red mana in her cost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 01:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is bonesaw ready?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has Nate Silver become much more famous recently? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 13:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never heard of him until I started following the 538 about a year ago. Now I feel like he's becoming a meme. Was he always this popular, or is his fame a new thing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 07:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah Shapiro is a huge fan of Ted Cruz. My original comment was based on the assumption that Trump and Hillary will each be their party's nominee. And the assumption that Ben would even bother voting in that election lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 02:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shapiro wrote an article about how he would never vote for Trump, and that he's worse than Clinton.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 23:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked Rubio before this. I still like him, because I think his immature jokes are just as repulsive to him as to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 23:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jim Webb voting Republican and Ben Shapiro voting Democrat. This election is weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 16:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of this evidence is anecdotal, so it's difficult to cite reliably in a debate. Any sources for an argument that abortion is *never* medically necessary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 16:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He mentioned in passing that "... the vast, vast majority of medical concerns occur at 24, 25, 26 weeks of pregnancy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 05:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "We are not defined by sexual attraction. We are not defined by sexual behavior," he continued. "We are sons and daughters of God, and all of us have different challenges in the flesh." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 05:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you actually read the article, it's really not homophobic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 05:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cruz is no more selfish than any other candidate running. I'd argue that Rubio is more self-serving, because if he dropped out and endorsed Cruz then Ted would get most of that support. But if Cruz drops out, there's no guarantee that his supporters would back Rubio any more than Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 23:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is honestly the best settlement I've ever seen. It looks amazing. Did you use mods, or is it vanilla? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 21:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  buying college

This is such a concise way of putting it, I'm surprised I haven't heard it until now. You don't "go" to college, it's not a vacation from life, it's a product you buy. If you buy it as an investment, don't expect it to always be fun. If you buy it as a luxury, don't expect it to advance your career. 

EDIT: Yes I realize the post's grammar is shite overall but this is a good way to frame the reasons people attend college. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 19:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would have been ridiculous to rule any other way. If the court tried to force a Priest to violate the sanctity of confession, he'd probably just take the contempt of court charge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 16:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, woops. My bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 06:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Virginia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 06:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so this article is mostly bullshit, but Cromwell was still terrible. He was personally responsible for the attempted Irish genocide during his campaigns, and he was overall an intolerant, tyrannical sectarian dictator, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm currently in my home state, but not my home county. Can I vote in the Super Tuesday primary today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 06:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, my state is a super Tuesday state. I made the mistake of confusing my absentee ballot application form with an actual absentee ballot, so I didn't make the absentee deadline. Can I still show up with a state driver's license and vote at my local polling place tomorrow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 21:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anger and relief are not mutually exclusive. Of course I'm upset that my fellow Christians are being persecuted for their faith. I pity those Muslims who respond to the Word with such hate, and who do not know the love of God. But yeah, I'm relieved that they aren't being beheaded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 20:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ol' Aarfy's never paid for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 18:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We aren't talking about barring them from anything.

I used a poor example for my point here. Back before the SCOTUS decision on gay marriage, one could make the argument that gay people are so small a fraction of the population that even considering the issue is a waste of federal resources.

 The fact is that a gender neutral system drastically increases the percentage of bathroom interactions with people who are sexually attracted to you. This also increases the number of people who might act on that.

If we can agree that the amount of sexual assaults from a group is proportional to the population of that group, then the number of victims of homosexual sexual assault is proportional to the number of homosexuals. If the former is a small enough proportion to dismiss, surely so is the latter? Surely we shouldn't have to consider homosexuals when making policy decisions, right? If the complaint about a certain policy is that it discriminates against homosexuals, then under this argument a valid response would be "there aren't enough homosexuals for that to matter."

Again, I'm not necessarily opposed to these arguments. We dismiss small constituencies all the time in the democratic process, often purely for the convenience of the majority. But you have to be willing to accept that if you're going to make the argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 17:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a dangerous argument to apply, though. I could easily say, then, that gays are such a small part of the population that barring them from military service (so they don't make straight people uncomfortable) is a minor injustice outweighed by the benefits. I could say that trans people are such a small part of the population that gender neutral bathrooms aren't worth the cost.

I'm not saying these are bad arguments, but you have to be comfortable making them if you're going to make the "negligible proportion" claim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 15:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we're going to treat gay people equally, we have to either disregard the "sexual predation" argument or conclude that all bathrooms should be single-occupant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 17:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Romney* shots fired? I'd say calling Catholics not Christian is much more savage than applying the same label to Mormons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 17:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it! I do think the white field with stars on the whole hoist is a bit much though. It's similar enough in length to the fly that the flag might look symmetrical "in the wild," so to speak. Have you considered just using the white field for the canton? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good things to pay attention to that most people don't notice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 17:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilary probably. Most of the president's actual job is foreign affairs, and Bernie had no fucking clue what he's doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 22:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> College. I'm usually good with being reasonable and understanding the other side, and in hindsight I've concluded that her real problem was that she treated me like a child. She didn't trust a word I said, ignored me when I told her that I was no danger to anyone, and at one point even said "nothing you say will convince me [not to call the director]." 

I have no patience for this bullshit. If I need to talk to someone, I'll find a friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 20:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? That's what I said. I told them "this contract guarantees confidentiality except if I threaten someone or there's a court order. I haven't threatened anyone, so unless you have a warrant you can't reveal anything." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My school's counseling center is awful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 18:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I go in for my initial appointment. I'm feeling pretty good about myself, finally took action to solve my problems. They have me fill out a ~15 minute survey, then I go into a counselor's office. We talk for a bit about a bunch of topics (family, friends, school, etc).

Then she starts asking about anger. See, I responded on the survey that I "considered physically harming others" and "felt anger often." I told her that I answered truthfully, that I, like every other human being, often experience the basic emotion of anger, and that the instinctive reaction to anger is violence. I made a point of saying that although I often feel anger, and fantasize about violence, I am a rational human being with self-control and I have never acted on it and never planned to.

But she just would not leave this topic alone. I kept telling her that I didn't want to hurt anybody. I'm probably physically incapable of it. In fact, I broke up with my girlfriend last week because she got angry and pushed me over, and I don't tolerate people using violence to solve their problems. But no matter what I said, she just kept putting on this faux-worried face and saying "I'm concerned."

Well, after an hour I had had enough of that. I told her that I wouldn't be scheduling another appointment, and that I would be leaving now. So she *threatened to break confidentiality* and alert the police on the grounds that she thought I was a danger to others. She told me I couldn't leave! Had me wait in her office while she got the director. While I was waiting, I reread the contract and saw that she had NO FUCKING GROUNDS to break confidentiality. Her "concern" is not enough, I would have had to make a *threat of serious harm* to others. 

I talked to the director for like 5 minutes, told him I wasn't coming back, and that if the counselor violated confidentiality they would both be hearing from my attorney. 

I came in to be treated for depression, and they tried to call the fucking police.

Mind you, I'm not a delicate eggshell here. I was cool and rational the entire way, I didn't feel like I was making myself uncomfortably vulnerable. It isn't like I was timid and a small mistake could drive me away. It took a real serious fuck-up to make me give up on them.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 18:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend of mine actually wrote a novel-length Richard III fanfic with this concept. Everyone used modern technology except they were still fighting with swords and horses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 15:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which way is it this time, Germany or Russia?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 00:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminder of rule #2 people. Don't make claims, positive or negative, about the efficacy of any treatment or self-help strategy, including religion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 21:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't agree with everything he says, and I don't like the way he says it, but I have massive respect for the man. He's the most philosophically consistent politician I've ever seen. Rand Paul truly believes in what he says, and he has the balls to say a lot of unpopular, uncomfortable truths. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone else had a bad experience with delegates from Northeastern University? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 05:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not here to complain about any specific delegates, or their school, or their program. In our last conference we saw the Northeastern delegates behaving unprofessionally. The issues were specific to the delegates from that school, and my concerns were shared by several other delegations attending the conference. The head delegate for Northeastern, when responding to the concerns at the head delegate meeting, seemed to imply that these were recurring problems.

I don't want to paint the whole team with a broad brush, or get into a fight about their behavior. We will probably be seeing them at future conferences, and I'm just trying to find the extent of the  issues with their delegate behavior. Has anyone else experienced working with Northeastern delegates before? Was your experience similar?

Also, if anyone reading is from Northeastern University's MUN team, PLEASE RESPOND. The last thing I want is to wrongfully malign another team, so I would appreciate your perspective on the matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 04:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had an incredible New Years! From 18:00 on December 31 to 02:00 January 2 we played a metric shit-ton of board games. Started with **Battlestar Galactica**, then **Twilight Imperium**, both of which I've played before. Then we started **Virgin Queen**, a first for all but one of us, but we only got through 2 turns. After that, we did a group favorite **Game of Thrones**. After a nap we played **Middle Earth Quest**, and I finally got to play Sauron. I lost, but it was a blast anyways. We rounded out the marathon with 3 missions of **Star Wars: Imperial Assault**, which I LOVED. I made the mistake of picking Mak Eshka'rey, so I wasn't terribly successful, but it was good fun nonetheless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 06:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unanimously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 06:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Won WWII and forced France to accept war guilt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 22:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also a few months ago I was in a Turkish Cabinet crisis, and we got an update about Syrian refugees. So I wrote a directive that read:

1. Build a wall across the southern border

2. Make the Syrian government pay for it

3. Make Turkey great again

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 22:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in a Weimar Republic committee and managed to become Chairman of the Nazi Party and Chancellor of Germany, despite the fact that I was

a) Not a member of the Nazi Party, and 

b) Devoutly Jewish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 20:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Cultural libertarians expose the hypocrisy in these codes and rules, using social media theatre, satire, and **the dankest of memes** to point out that these chefs do not eat their own cooking

My time has come. Our memes will block out the sun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 09:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Old Man and the D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 23:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I just reread your post and I can see where you're coming from. Really the only biologically significant events in a human life are conception, sexual maturity, menopause and death.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 22:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After birth, the baby is still completely dependent on its parents.  Would you argue that there is no conceptual difference between a haircut and total neglect of a child after birth?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 17:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's in the game, his stats are mad good, and he's got enough land to snowball early on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 11:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fear I may have been unclear. I did accept the gift, and promised to get him something in return, only on Christmas day I followed through and he seems to have forgotten his promise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I politely remind my cousin about a gift he promised me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 07:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Dec 23 I was playing Magic TCG with my cousins. I don't own a magic deck, and I liked the one my cousin lent me. He basically said, "well, I'm never going to use it, so keep it. Merry Christmas." I was hesitant to accept because I didn't get him anything, but I told him that I would accept it because I was going shopping later and I could get him something.

Christmas day, I give him his gift. He doesn't mention the deck. So when we play Magic with our other cousins, I ask to use that deck. He gives it to me, and at the end of the night, takes it back. He didn't mention any intent to gift it to me. I didn't get any gifts for any of my other cousins, and I very clearly and overtly signaled to him that I would like the deck.

Another thing to mention is that my cousin has mild Asperger's. I fear he may have forgotten, and not picked up on any of my signals. Not to sound like a dick, but how do I get him to give me the deck without insulting him?

If there's a better sub for this, please redirect me to it. Thanks!

EDIT: To clarify, I didn't turn the gift down, I just said that I'd get him something in return.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 00:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate him because he ruined a cool name, and a cool outfit, and a bunch of cool imagery...

Holy shit, I hate Kylo the exact same way I hate Hitler. Bravo, Driver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 00:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also liked it for worldbuilding purposes. I was very upset that bowcasters in KOTOR were just weaker versions of blaster rifles. Now it has been firmly established that bowcasters are extremely powerful, but difficult to wield.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 21:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it was Butch #TunnelSnakesRule </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 17:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As usual, the Swiss Guard's primary weapon is *fabulous*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 12:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Protestants amirite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 13:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are part of a group like atheists, maligned by an obnoxious vocal minority, then you have a responsibility to deconstruct the stereotypes. You have to tell people you are an atheist and show them that atheists are really just people. Don't let atheists change someone's opinion about you, *you* will change *their* opinion about atheists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 00:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an optimistic way of looking at it, I guess. I usually see it from the angle of "I feel nothing when a normal person would be ashamed because I am incapable of true emotion" but you know what I like your perspective better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 00:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually don't feel bad about it at all, which is paradoxically *why* I feel so bad about it. It wasn't like I could do anything about it. But I felt the need to act like I was super embarrassed because that's supposed to be the natural reaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 21:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Savage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 02:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's absolutely necessary. I usually try to have at least one "vanilla" play-through before any mods, but this mod doesn't add content, it *restores* content. The stuff in the mod was intended for the original release, but was cut due to budget/time constraints. It's all canon AFAIK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 18:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The General Atomics Galleria! I would love the opportunity to turn it into a proper town after clearing out the homicidal robots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 07:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twilight Imperium, Game of Thrones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 10:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lost 60 pounds? Shave your beard, I think I found them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 15:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an excellent idea (and very well written to boot). The player ought to have the option to unite certain factions and work together with them, at the cost of one or both factions losing an important advantage. Like, have the Railroad join the Institute, and the Institute stops Gen 3. 

Or, during Blind Betrayal [you can try to bring Danse back to the Brotherhood, convince Maxon that Synths are victims of the Institute, and unite the Brotherhood and the Railroad. Or convince him that Synths are useful tools and incredible scientific advancements, and petition for the Brotherhood to annex the Institute.](/spoiler)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 00:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ryukyu controlling Japan. THREE MOUNTAINS BANZAI!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 00:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean it certainly made the most important planet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Free Friday] Who are your favorite protestants? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 00:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just for fun, lets try to keep it lighthearted. Mine are the Methodists because I've seen the Methodist church on my campus do some awesome things for the poor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 23:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hear, hear. Some people are willing to have a civilized debate, but at places like Oxy they will only argue against their opponents rather than their opponent's positions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 23:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too actually, I just thought it was funny that part of their demands to the university was that the Governor take action. All in all, UVa's demands were probably the most reasonable and articulate. Still pretty ridiculous though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 23:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am actually in the student legislature at vt, actively fighting against legislation that is anything like this. I'm really proud of our no-nonsense campus culture with respect to stupid crap like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 22:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UC Berkeley is on the list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 21:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The FiveThirtyEight did a piece on the most common demands (that's where I got the link from). You should check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All the demands of BLM campus movements. Highlights include firing Yale professors who disagree with the movement, abolition of the Virginia ABC, and Yale demanding dental coverage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 20:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
