<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject758</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 12:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't drink much soda or eat much candies/junk but I think I really don't drink enough water. That may be my problem.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been 1 week without cigarettes.. my skin is breaking out like crazy? help me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 12:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so I'm a 19 year old female and my skin has always had acne here and there, or occasional breakouts but my skin is seriously looking like a pepperoni pizza now. 

Can anyone relate? 
when does it end? 
should I just go to the gym and eat healthily? 

WHEN DOES THIS END

(I've been smoking for 2 years.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 21:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had this before, it's super good. 
Thanks for the recipe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 09:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ex boyfriend was being molested by his mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 02:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh thanks haha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 02:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is it amazing?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 22:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a TV, haha so I do know what you mean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 22:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to purge so much that the brackets in my braces would always end up falling out or the metal would leave a terrible taste in my mouth. I forgot to add that I was a RECOVERING bulimic and I haven't purged in 2 months. The urges are there every single day though. It's not easy to stop, but it's possible. Over half of my thoughts are usually filled with guilt of how I need to purge and get food out of my body, but I know if I relapse I'd lose my job and drop out of the culinary program that I'm in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 22:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am feeling slightly better. 
It is raining hard outside and I hear thunder.
I'm just in bed, I don't know if I'm well enough to go to the gym today..I haven't gone in awhile.
Thanks. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 21:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have braces. My teeth aren't so white, they're more clear and I really lack calcium. Sigh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 21:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My BMI is 20.5 and I don't really want to discuss height and weight cause it can be triggering to some individuals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 21:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had pizza at a nightclub.

Never again. It's been a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
