<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6210</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 21:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I picked my goal weight because it was the weight I was at before I got horribly depressed. I have this idea that it will make me happy again. Except I know that it won't make me happy because I will be really sick at that point.

I have had the same goal weight since my ed has started. I never reached it, and I probably never will </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 02:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only started having problems when my bmi was around 14. I'm always cold, I have chest pains, light headedness, low electrolytes, rapid heart rate, low blood pressure. I have a whole swath of problems because of my low weight. But it never got bad until I got down down to around 14 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 02:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal (150)

Lunch: Oatmeal (150)

Dinner: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cocoa (147)

Total: 447 calories

I decided to do an oatmeal mono today and tomorrow. I decided to do this for 2 reasons, first because apparently mono diets are good way to lose weight fast and secondly because I have diarrhea (sorry tmi) because of new medication and oatmeal always helps when I have diarrhea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 02:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I watch a lot of Netflix and I'm reading Harry Potter right now! Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 23:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's my first time.
They said it would probably be in 3 to 6 weeks, but that it could be more or less time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 18:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea. I could get the call in a few days or in a few weeks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 17:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm alright, pretty tired and bored though. I'm feeling pretty sick because of some new medication. I have a few doctors appointments today.

I'm just so tired of everything. I just want to get admitted to my treatment program, but I have no idea when that will be. I'm tired of waiting and doing nothing all day. 

I'm also doing an oatmeal mono today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 14:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a bunch of apps that help to learn new languages. You should check it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 05:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put a heating pad or a hot water bottle on your stomach, it'll help with the bloating and pain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone ever done a mono? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 03:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking of doing a mono diet and I was wondering if anyone had any experience with them? 

I'm thinking of doing either a chocolate, peanut butter, oatmeal or egg mono. 

If anyone has any insight, I'd love to hear it

Edit: I've decided that I will do an oatmeal mono tomorrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 02:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a pretty face, people always tell me I should be a model </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 01:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cocoa (147)

Lunch: Egg whites with partially skim mozzarella and sriracha (120), celery, red bell pepper and cucumber (25)

Dinner: Peanut sesame shirataki noodles (144)

Snacks: Rice cake with 1 1/2 tbsp light peanut butter (155), diet coke (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 591 calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 21:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That it's about food and weight, when really the obsession with food and weight is just a symptom of a bigger problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 18:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely think that bulimia is much harder on the body than anorexia. When I was bulimic I felt much worse physically than I do now with my anorexia.

I used to purge everything that I ate. There were times when I couldn't even stand up or do anything. I remember having to crawl around my house because I couldn't stand up. I couldn't open doors or do anything really.

Now with my restriction, I am much thinner than I was when I was bulimic, but I feel better physically. I don't have to crawl around and I can do more things than when I was bulimic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 02:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cocoa (147)

Lunch: Simply egg whites with partially skim mozzarella and sriracha (120), celery, red bell pepper and cucumbers (25)

Dinner: Tortilla, pizza sauce, partially skim mozzarella and red onion (144)

Snacks: Peanut butter with 1 1/2 tbsp peanut butter (155), diet coke (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 591 calories

So I seem to be stuck in a binge/restrict cycle, so I decided to increase my intake to around 600 calories a day. I might lower it in a while, I don't know yet. Hopefully I can stop this binging.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 00:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You will most likely still get a period when you lose weight. It might be lighter though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 00:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It definitely sounds like you have disordered eating, but we aren't doctors and can't diagnose you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 03:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cocoa (147)

Lunch: Simply egg whites with partially skim mozzarella and sriracha (60), red bell pepper and cucumber (19)

Dinner: Vegetable bouillon, soya sauce, shirataki noodles and green onions (41)

Snacks: Rice cake with 2 tbsp light peanut butter (195), diet coke (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 462 calories

I feel like I'm going to binge tonight because I binged last night. I really hope I'll be able to resist, but I somehow doubt it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 02:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've had about 550 cals today. But I still want to binge, I honestly hate this binge/restrict cycle that I'm in. Plus I'm pretty sure I'm gaining weight, which upsets me and triggers me to binge more.

Sorry for ranting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 02:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm having a hard time resisting. I'm worried I'll binge when my mom goes to bed because that's usually when I binge. I've been wanting to binge all day since I binged last night </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 02:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was planning to binge today too, but I've resisted the urges up to now, but I don't know if I'll be able to resist for the rest of the day

Good job on resisting, hopefully I'll be as strong as you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 21:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Protein is good, if you're restricting you should try to get as much protein as possible. I eat egg whites and peanut butter for my protein. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 17:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I binged on peanut butter last night. I ate wayyyyy more than 800 cals worth of the stuff, plus cheese and bread. I kind of want to keep binging today, but I know I shouldn't. 

Good luck on your final, you'll do great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 03:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm feeling pretty depressed too. And I'm super bloated these days and I don't know why.

Sorry you feel this way. Hope you feel better soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 03:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had pretty much the same question today! I got invited to a friend's birthday at a pub tomorrow night. I have no idea what to order.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 02:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, nice. I love pb and rice cakes.

I buy cracker barrel partially skim mozzarella </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 01:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cocoa (147)

Lunch: Simply egg whites with mozzarella and sriracha (60), celery, red bell pepper and cucumber (25)

Dinner: Peanut sesame shirataki noodles (161)

Snacks: Rice cake with 2tbsp light peanut butter (195), diet coke (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 588 calories

I want another rice cake with peanut butter, but it would bring me over my calorie limit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 20:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They said probably 3 weeks, but that there is no guarantee. It could be any time. 

I should leave the house more often, it's just so cold out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 16:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been really depressed lately. I don't know why. The fact that I stay at home alone everyday doesn't help. I just don't know what to do with myself anymore.

Edit: I'm also waiting for a bed to open up at the ed clinic. I could get the call today or in many weeks. I hate waiting and not knowing when I'll be admitted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 05:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot about cinnamon rolls!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 02:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pizza, grilled cheese sandwiches and peanut butter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 01:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cocoa (147)

Lunch: Egg whites with partially skim mozzarella and sriracha, celery, red bell pepper and cucumber (145)

Dinner: Shirataki noodles with curry sauce (182)

Snacks: Rice cake with 1.5tbps light peanut butter (155), 2 rice cakes (70), diet coke (0) and mio sport (0)

Total: 699 calories

Today was the second day of weening down my calorie intake. Tomorrow I will have 600 cals. 

I was feeling depressed today and I don't know why. It kind of sucks, I don't know what to do with myself these days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 17:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks! This is great because I don't have access to a scale, so measurements are my way of tracking my progress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 17:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only take them if I haven't had a bm in over a week. Laxatives don't help you lose weight. Your food and calories are absorbed in your small intestines, while laxatives act on your large intestine. So by the time it gets to your large intestine it's completely absorbed already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 05:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great! I will definitely use it everyday. It would be really cool if we could enter other measurements, such as waist, hips, bust, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 02:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar, cinnamon and butter (301)

Lunch: Simply egg whites with partially skim mozzarella and sriracha, celery, red bell pepper and cucumber (145)

Dinner: Whole wheat tortilla, 1 tbsp pizza sauce, 1/4 cup partially skim mozzarella, 1 onion slice and 2 slices of spicy salami (190)

Snacks: Tortilla with mozzarella and 1/4 cup salsa (150), diet coke (0) and mio sport (0)

So I've been in a binge-restrict cycle, so I decided to start at 800 cals and reduce by 100 each day until I reach 400 cals. I hope this helps me to stop binging

It was hard to figure out what to eat to get to 800 calories for the day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 22:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between relapses I maintained a weight of around 105lbs at a height of 5'8. I was eating pretty healthy, but I also ate junk food </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 20:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! Welcome, and don't worrfry about your English, it's great. English isn't my first language either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 18:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is a great idea!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 17:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a tip for next time you are on antibiotics, take acidophilus. It helps keep your vaginal microbiome healthy so you don't get a yeast infection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 15:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is awesome! I wish I was as talented as you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 04:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Urg, today I've been binging a lot. I had starbucks with a cookie and croissant! Then I had some calamari, a grilled cheese, peanut butter, cheese, yam fries, just sooo much food. I'm pretty angry at myself.

I decided that I will have 800 cals tomorrow and I will decrease by 100 cals each day until I reach 400. Then I will stay at 400 for a while. I'm also planning to have a few fasts after I get this under control.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 04:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your comments are on point today!!! I think I will listen to you and start at 800 tomorrow and go down by 100 cals each day. 

I wish it was nice here. We had a super mild winter up to now, but this weekend winter came and it is -40C with the wind these days. So going to the park won't be a great idea, haha. 

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 04:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is! I just have so many cravings all day long, I used to never have that. Hopefully we both find our will power soon!

Thanks, I'm excited and nervous to go into treatment, but I need to do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 04:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! It's something I know it's something I need to do so I can live the life I truly want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 04:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I think I'm going to start at 800 cals tommorrow and go down by 100 each day.

I'm going to miss you guys too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I keep binging and I don't know why </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 23:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since Christmas I've been able to restrict for about 5 days then I go and binge. I don't know why I keep binging, I'm not upset about anything, I'm not forced to eat, I'm not hungry, but I binge after about 5 days of restricting. It's making me so angry. Before Christmas I went over 3 weeks binge-free but now I can't even go 1 week.

I'm debating between starting at 800 cals tomorrow and go down by 100 cals each day until I reach zero and fast for a day or two or if I should just stick to 400 cals a day for a while with a few fast days in there. What do you guys think?

Also, thought I'd give a treatment update. I had my assessment last week and my meeting with my nurse-therapist today. I will be going into inpatient treatment soon for weight restoration then continue in their day program. They said I'll probably be admitted in about 3 weeks, maybe more, maybe less. So we'll see, I'll be sad to be leaving this great community, but I need to do this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 21:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love smoking! It keeps me sane and I love how it suppresses my appetite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 21:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to be 84lbs by then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 00:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cocoa (147)

Lunch: Simply egg whites with 2 tbsp partially skim mozzarella and sriracha (60), celery (6), red bell pepper (11) and cucumber (8)

Dinner: Whole wheat tortilla, 1 tbsp pizza sauce, 1/4 cup partially skim mozzarella, 1 onion slice and 1 slice of spicy salami (168)

Snacks: Diet coke (0), mio sport (0)

Total: 400 cals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 16:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought them at an Asian food store. You can buy them online too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 02:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I'm really proud of myself and it's making me feel better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 01:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Oatmeal with brown sugar and cocoa (147)

Lunch: Simply egg whites with 2 tbsp partially skim mozzarella and sriracha (60), celery (6), red bell pepper (11) and cucumber (8)

Dinner: Peanut sesame shirataki noodles (162)

Snacks: Diet coke (0), mio sport (0)

Total: 393 cals

I was nervous to try the shirataki noodles because of some of the things I read online about them. But they are great! I love them, only 6 calories for a whole serving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 19:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never shoplifted but when I restrict I get an impulse to do it, but I never do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
