<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3094</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Supplements on a budget: What are you bottom line must-haves? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 18:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello ladies!  
  
As a mother of a two year old with a boyfriend and a mortgage, we are currently attempting to overhaul our budget and start saving a lot more than we do right now. My boyfriend doesn't exercise or go to the gym whatsoever and has no plans to, which is fine. I however do, and being rather new to supplements, I just sort of bought a little of everything that I see people using. I currently use protein powder, a BCAA powder (I do fasted training in the AM), fish oil, creatine, green tea extract, a fat burner, and a daily multivitamin. I feel like I need to cut back, but I have no idea which supplements I should do without.  
  
What do you guys use, and what have you gotten rid of? I know some supplementing is important but I just can't continue to spend what I do on everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My boyfriend (26M) and I (23F) have a toddler, a mortgage, and student loans for days. Not entirely sure on how to proceed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 23:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For starters, here's our current budget:
**Monthly income: $3420 (lowballed; he works on commission)**  
  
**Monthly Expenses**  
Daycare: $516  
Groceries: $500  
Household Extras: $100  
Electricity: $160  
Mortgage: $490  
Water/Trash: $70  
Credit Card 1 (mine): $25  
Credit Card 2 (mine): $30  
Credit Card 3 (his): $55  
Credit Card 4 (his): $45  
Student Loan Payments: $178  
Truck Payment: $100  
Cable/Internet: $190  
Cell Phone: $70  
Gas: $150  
Netflix/Hulu: $18  
Gym: $33  
Car Insurance: $75  
Clothing: $50  
Entertainment: $75  
Lawn: $25-50  

**Total Monthly Expenses: $3010**  
**Monthly Leftover Cash: $410-ish**  
    
This looks to put us at about $410 leftover at the end of each month. I have no idea how good or bad this is.  
  
As of right now, we do not have an emergency fund of any kind. I guess I didn't realize how important this was until I started following this subreddit. We've been very fortunate to not have any real emergencies, so I guess I've just sort of looked the other way. If I understand right, our emergency fund should have at minimum $8652, and by reading the FAQ I saw that the first thing we should focus on is building that up. However, I guess my question is this: If our budget is exactly precise which I know it won't be, we would have to focus on building only that for the next 21 months. Am I right that we shouldn't focus on paying down debts until we have built this fund? Or is there some way we should be doing both?  
  
He has about $1300 of credit card debt and I have about $1200. My interest rates on my two cards are at about 18.5%, and I'm not currently sure about his. I was always under the impression that paying the minimum only each month lowers your credit score. Is that incorrect? I know carrying a high percentage of balance on the card does. I've been doing so much reading here lately that I'm really overwhelmed.  
  
As far as 401k, he is already contributing the highest amount that his company matches, so we're good there. My job doesn't offer a 401k, but I have one left over from my last job. What should I do with that?  
  
I'm really motivated to turn our financial situation around; I'm tired of constantly living paycheck to paycheck with zero future plans financially. I really don't know how bad of shape we're in because all of our friends are still in school and without children or mortgages or responsibilities whatsoever, so there's little for me to compare to. Any input you guys might have would be greatly appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 04:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Front tooth gap in females. I am a female. Hnnngghh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 17:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could vary my meals more, but I just simply don't have time to cook myself something different every night on top of cooking for my two year old and boyfriend.  
  
Thinking about it the opposite way is a great idea! That totally makes sense. I'm recovering from an ED and I went from being about 15 pounds underweight to about 20 pounds overweight, so I have hit every spot on the spectrum as far as crazy binges and restriction. Moderation is the main thing I'm trying to get the hang of right now, and it's proving difficult. Thank you for the helpful advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 17:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm definitely seeing an increase in my strength; all my lifts have gone up and that's really exciting! I am recovered from anorexia so I definitely struggle with seeing changes in my body, but I have noticed some definition in my arms that I like. I try not to weigh myself too much.  
  
I guess my main issue is that I'm impatient: when you just don't eat, you tend to lose weight quickly and that's what I'm used to. (NOT AT ALL promoting it as a solution -- anorexia is a sure way to destroy your mind and your body). While I'm LOVING finally feeling healthy and strong instead of shaky and close to death, waiting to see any real results is torture. I love lifting, hate cardio. But that seems to be the norm for most people, haha. The macro planning is a little stressful for me -- moderation has never really been my strong suit. However I ultimately enjoy the foods I'm eating. I get a little tired of the repetition of eating the same foods, but with a two year old and a full time job I don't really have time to plan out different meals for myself every day on top of cooking for the fam.  
  
I wish I would have taken measurements, but I've been told that with the ED recovery, it's better not to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 17:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I look forward to mine all week too! And I always feel super motivated until AFTER. That's when I feel like I screwed everything up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
