<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9229</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only play Sombra, so this might not apply to every hero since her weapon spread is so large, but I use low sensitivity combined with a very large mouse pad. I believe I use 600 DPI with a sniper button on my mouse (G502) that further lowers it to 400 if I need to track something farther away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I stopped playing competitive. I main Sombra and am actually really good with her, but I was sick of hearing everyone complaining and bitching to me every round in comp, so now I only do quickplay. Overwatch competitive has become toxic just like CS:GO or LoL and it ruined the fun. Bottom line is that I play to have fun, and that's all that matters to me. Other people might have different opinions, and that's fine. I'll stick to quickplay and they can play competitive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you want Omnics? 'Cause that's how you get Omnics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 00:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why we need double POTGs. For those poor souls who play Zarya or Sombra and never get POTG.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the same issue with 7.62x39. Not a huge deal though since Tula Ammo is pretty cheap,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always loved how utilitarian these looked. Definitely one of my favorite Cold War era rifles. How does it shoot compared to say, an AR-15? I've always wanted one, but have never even seen one, let alone shoot one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 03:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Training+poor ideas+budget restrictions= this monstrosity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 03:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like a 
K20/K5 frame, so likely a 350.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 03:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always hear "Welcome aboard captive" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Borg have arrived I see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The new gen TTs are actually designed to look like a mini R8 so I see no problem doing this to a first gen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely not true. A former friend of mine has a lifted powerstroke F-350 similar to this and has a gooseneck he tows all the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's some well done body work actually. I'd be interested to see it when it's complete. Then again, this is coming from someone who wanted to put a fox body front end on a 1985 Ford Ranger  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely love this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah definitely. One of my favorite tactics is hacking a health pack and making my enemies chase me to it. (Or putting a translocator on it) I can then just sit on it and wreck their shit. 

Another thing about Sombra, is I often play with a friend who is a Mercy main, so he gives me damage boost and heals me when I need it. The damage boost really helps Sombra. It turns her into a mini Bastion (well not quite, but you get the point). It's great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Jeep actually, for completely different reasons than most people are listing here. It's very hard to explain, but driving a pre-Chrysler designed Jeep is very different from driving any other car. It's surprisingly "springy" when you press the accelerator, yet is one of the slowest vehicles I have ever driven (0-60 of maybe) Having all around leaf springs gives ride quality somewhere between shit and rubbish on the road, the steering has almost no feedback (AMC and early Chrysler Jeeps have way too much power in their power steering), not to me tion it's pretty sensitive, and the transmission feels like driving a truck. The body roll is horrendous, and anything over 70 makes it feel like the Jeep is about to shake itself apart, since none of the door fit correctly and the top isn't sealed with the windshield. This is in a unmodified 1995 YJ, mind you with pretty low miles and made up of parts from about 5 different jeeps. . This is how they drove stock too and I absolutely love it. It's absurdly fun and horribly dangerous (no airbags, no abs, no crumple zones, high chance of rollover, etc) , but that's what makes it great. 

TL;DR: sorry for the clique, but It's a Jeep thing. Driving a death trap has its benefits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your translocator is your best friend. Stick it right on top of a hacked health pack and wreck the enemy team from behind. As soon as you take significant damage, teleport back to the health pack. Rinse and repeat, while hacking as many enemies and health packs as possible. You also want to turn your mouse sensitivity wayyy down. It helps combat the absurd SMG spread and helps you keep on target. Since you also can see enemies that are critically injured, always go after them first. If you get into a 1v1 situation, turn it into a running battle so you can either escape or slowly wear down your opponent and kill them. Avoid Symettra/Zarya/Winston at all costs since they dont really have to aim and you can't escape once you start taking damage.You can also take damage while translocating at both the starting position and at the translocator for a short period of time while the animation is playing (which is really unfair, and why you can't escape Symettras beam) Doing all this, I can usually get gold or silver in eliminations, albeit in quickplay. I don't play comp though because I'm sick of getting screamed at for maining Sombra.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> too much Overwatch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I main her. She's fun as hell to play as. Fucking with the enemy team is great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a libertarian subgroup. Libertarianism isn't one set group. The term libertarian describes a pretty wide range of ideologies, from Anarcho-capitalists to Libertarian Socialists. Most libertarians fall somewhere in the middle, though lean towards the Minarchist/AnCap side (mind you, most libertarians still believe in a state, just a minimal one).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet it's coarse and rough and gets everywhere too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeep of Theseus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me that I need to paint my full doors for my (black and chrome) YJ. They're red and have mild surface rust spots but I got them with a OEM hardtop from another YJ for like $500 so I can't complain though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see this on my way to go ski all the time too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More likely than Maul was though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly this. Every single US military personnel swear an oath to defend the country and uphold the Constitution. Nowhere in the oath is allegiance to the government sworn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the Asus VG248QE as well and can testify that it is a phenomenal monitor if anyone was curious. Good luck with your sale!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally dozens. I don't care that she's underpowered. She's very fun to play.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I main Sombra and that's exactly how I feel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another Sombra main here. And I agree completely. I'm just going to keep playing as her until the fixes occur (if ever). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 2.8 V6 in those trucks is probably o e of the worst engines Ford has ever put into any of their vehicles. They blew head gaskets all the time. I was driving around on a hot day and it overheated and blew.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the point! Sometimes I miss being a dumb teenager for this reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had cops approach me. Just stay calm and they will just tell you to stop. I don't know anyone who's ever gotten into any real trouble doing this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss both my old Rangers for this very reason. You can't really do this in a Jeep Wrangler. You will roll yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've actually found that ads with one photo and very little to no information actually tend to work out pretty well if the car is cheap. They are usually cars that have just been sitting in someone's driveway that they never use. I bought a 1985 Ford Ranger XLT 4x4 that way for $800 and it was flawless other than being a little dusty (and being an auto, but I needed a car at the time and love first gen Rangers). I eventually blew the head gasket and killed the engine, but that thing was great. It had no rust either, which was rare for being in Ohio.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't. These are the people that wind up in mental institutions, at least if they don't eventually realize how dumb they sound.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so hard for me to not do this on recovery runs. I always accidentally speed up to race pace until I pass them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. When I play Sombra (almost always) I have a personal vendetta against Pharah. I can't help it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does this happen? Lol. Do you not schedule your own classes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a dish washer. Our dish washer had no soap or hot water. I used it anyway because I was getting paid shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Semi-relevant flair? I know what it's actually for, but still somewhat relevant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just Rams. My Dakota and almost every Dakota I've seen does too! They rust away and just fall off or start hanging really low for some reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still hate that bar in the middle of the headlights. I love the truck other than that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why and how? We need pics of this thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is typical when a new president comes into power. It's meant to give them time to discuss new policies and practices, instead of confusing the public with different promises or viewpoints. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But we are? Lol. The US makes up the majority of NATOs forces.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure that's the problem. My lifepod is tilted at a 45 angle because of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeep YJ!  I've had more fun in my Jeep than as any Miata. It's a different type of fun, but it's still fun. You can get them for really cheap too (I bought mine for $4500 and it's (almost) rust free and is now mechanically perfect after replacing the leaky valve cover gasket. They are starting to increase in price though as pre-95 ones start to rust out and die.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's almost like more complicated and desirable options make a car more expensive. Who woulda thunk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not unreliable, just very expensive to fix if something goes wrong, assuming you don't do the work yourself and have a shop do it instead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 12:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've driven my parents 2011 Murano and it's suprisingly not terrible. It's comfortable and drives nice, and actually has some decent pickup.  

My grandmother has a 2012 Altima and it on the other hand is absolutely horrible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's a little unfair to the developers. They've been doing a phenomenal job with updates. They have to finish the base game first before they go out and start fixing every little bug or problem, hence why the game  is still in Alpha. This game is still one of the best, if not best alpha/pre-alpha games out there right now. Bugs are going to be there, especially if you are playing experimental.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks. The warning were just freaking me out and I didn't want to have my Seamoth explode within my Cyclops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'lll throw my build in since it seems to be the weakest listed so far and I consistently get 144fps with minor stuttering and drops to around 60. 

i7 4790k

R9 290

16GB Ram

128GB SSD

I recently switched my install directory from my HDD to my SSD and it made more difference than anything. Almost no stutters or FPS drops. I get excellent performance and can run the game around 144fps consistently, which is also the refresh rate of my monitor if that makes any difference. I also deleted the corresponding batch file that is responsible for the lag when loading new areas. Mind you, this is playing on experimental as well. It seems to be a crapshoot from system to system though. I know that the Youtuber Jacksepticeye runs twin GTX Titans in SLI and gets pretty poor performance and stuttering, so it doesnt seem to really be based on the power of your system.

Switching to an SSD made a huge difference for me, it used to take a couple of minutes to load up the game after selecting the save file while I had it installed on my HDD (Western Digital Blue 7200rpm) but now it only takes a few seconds. I attribute the lack of lag when entering a new biome to my SSD as well since that ceased once I made the switch. 

At this point in the game since it is early access still, its not well optimized so we should see performance increase in the future as bugs and glitches get fleshed out and taken care of. The devs have been doing an amazing job pumping out updates and I have no doubt they are capable of making the game ,more optimized once all the content is there. 

All in all, this is the best early access game I have ever played and I am looking forward to the future, so thank you devs for making such a phenomenal game. 

Sorry for the long wall of text and I got off topic a bit, but I think I answered your question pretty well. 

**TL;DR; Get an SSD**

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about vehicle depth when docked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 14:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If my Seamoth is docked in my Cyclops, can I still only go down to 300m? I don't want to test it to find out since I keep getting the crush warning for my Seamoth.Also curious because I was watching Jacksepticeyes play through and he undocks his Seamoth from his Cyclops whenever he goes below crush depth for the Seamoth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously an SSD is better, but if your sole purpose of buying one is to improve loading times/performance in this game, it won't make a difference. I've had Subnautica installed on both my HDD and SSD at different points TS recently and there is very little difference other than how fast the game launches and gets past the loading screen. Still, go for the SSD if you can. It's so much better in every way for he general computer tasks and may actually be of greater help once the game is more optimized. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 12:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a problem with your storage device. The game isn't optimized yet, so whenever a new area needs to load, the game gets laggy and it only gets worse over time. If I recall correctly, there is a specific batch file you can delete in your Subnautica directory that should cut down the lag quite a bit. You may have to delete it every once in awhile (as in delete it again) if your game gets too laggy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 15:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard the new JL may only have removable panels rather than a fully removable hard top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 14:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would kill for a modern t-top muscle car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  My Jeep is already just bare metal under the bed liner in the floorplans since it had new pans welded in. The weld are shitty but it works. I did try MEK and it didn't work before, but I didn't let it sit, so I will try that and maybe that will work. Or maybe I was using a diluted form or something. Either way, thanks a bunch. That's really helpful  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto with my '95.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is the el-cheapo spray on crap. I can pick it off with my fingernail if i try. I will look into citi-strip. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Removing Bedliner from yj floor pans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 13:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been using a wire brush attached to an electric drill and a chisel to remove the crappy bedliner that the previous owner of my Jeep decided to use to rust proof the floor pans but it's kinda taking forever. Do any of you know a better/quicker way of doing this? I'm trying to strip pretty much the entire interior of the body tub of paint/liner so I can have the rocker rust cut out and replaced as well have it professionally line-x'd. Any thoughts? Is there even a quicker way, or am I doomed to freeze my ass off for another 12 hours to get it done. So far all I have done is the driver side floor pan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 12:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also I think you can hear someome calling General Syndulla over the intercom when Jyn, Cassiun, K2SO, etc are going to the transport shuttle to get to Scarif. I'm also pretty sure I saw Chopper in the back during that scene too, but I'm not sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 11:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he would freak out more about it being Anakin/Darth Vader's former lightsaber  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 05:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From best to worst in my opinion is:

R1

ROTJ

TFA 

ESB

ROTS

ANH

TCW

TPM

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 05:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just went and saw it for the second time just so I could see the Ghost in the Battle of Scarif.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cuba is nowhere near being a successful communist country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 14:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno. I play Sombra almost exclusively lately and I find that if I can surprise hack them from behind and them charge in, I can usually take them out (with the exception of most tanks). Either that or hack them and bait them into chasing me and I can wear them down (and hack any health packs along the way) and eliminate them that way. The second way is how most of my 1v1s turn out and I think it works brilliantly, since either I win or can quickly translocate away if I'm about to lose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 14:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I think people just have a problem with the pretty big learning curve she has. I sucked with her at first but eventually got good enough with her that she is my main now. (My previous main was Soldier76, so it was a pretty big change) She still probably needs a reduction to her weapon spread, but she is pretty viable, at least in quickplay and low-mid level comp. (I won't speak to high level stuff since I have no experience playing at that level). In the end she is a blast to play as, and that's really all that matters to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 13:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha. Nothing about the healthcare industry is a free market. Government price controls and regulation is why healthcare costs are so high. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 02:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *ding* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 20:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a step in the right direction though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Jeep does this! But only because the only two ducts are pointed directly at the floorplans  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 23:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sombra is my main, and she is definitely a bit underpowered and what she can/can't hack is kind of messed up. I think her weapon spread needs to be reduced at the very least. Despite her flaws, she is very fun to play.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 23:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? That's disappointing. I wasn't aware  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 22:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's one of the reasons I started playing as Sombra more. Hack D.Va and laugh as she gets stuck with no mech </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 21:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. I love wierd cars. A Yugo and an AMC Pacer are dream cars of mine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 21:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im also NE Ohio. There are two Yugos on Akron-Canton Craigslist. $1000 each. I've actually been debating buying one as a beater. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ow :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much much better at pretty much everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 22:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And quite possible one of the most uncomfortable vehicles to ever exist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 15:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm. Was using remanufactured ammo and I had a round get stuck in the barrel of my Ruger P90 and without knowing, I shot another round. Gun got fucked, but thankfully I was fine.  I actually sent the pistol to Ruger and they fixed it though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 14:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely believe he is one of the best actors who are currently alive. He absolutely nails every role.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 14:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. Ohio's great. At least in the area I live in, you will never get pulled over for anything other than speeding or reckless driving. I drove a 1985 Ranger with no plates for a year and didn't get pulled over once.You can get away with everything as long as it passes smog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 23:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I know. I daily a '95 YJ, I'd just be concerned because of age combined with those shoddy mods.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 23:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus. Those are the stock leafs too it looks like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No thanks. And I didn't realize that. I'll lower the price </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not at max settings for some games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [USA-OH][H] LG34UM95-P Ultrawide Monitor [W]Local Cash, Paypal, GTX1080 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Local pickup only, I will not ship. I am local to 44236. 

[Timestamp](http://i.imgur.com/DECrLGK.jpg)

I got this monitor last spring and have loved it. Ultrawide really is amazing. Unfortunately my R9 290 is not up to the task of running most games on this monitor. The screen has no scratches and no light bleed to my knowledge (meaning I never noticed any), which is a common issue with this monitor. 

The resolution is 3440x1440p and the refresh rate is 60hz. 

I had the monitor on a desk mounted VESA mount, which is why the stand is not currently attached. I am missing the screws to reattach the stand, but other than that, the monitor is perfect. 

Right now its just taking up space in my closet so I may as well sell it.

I'm asking $500 or possible trade for a GTX1080. I may be interested in other GPUs as well + cash.  

Edit: Lowered the price </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 14:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeep YJs are absolute tanks, even with the 2.5l. Although I guess it's closer to being an AMC than a Chrysler since it's based off the CJ7 which was of course an AMC vehicle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 14:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not normal. I can (could) put both my Jeep and my old Ranger into 4-Low on pavement and be fine as long as you don't try turning and go very slow. Obviously it's not recommended, and can cause premature wear, but it won't be immediate catastrophic failure unless something else is wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 00:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Jeep only starts after I disconnect and reconnect the battery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 18:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks. I had installed my mods rather quickly and had chosen some textures and such that I didn't want so I want to go through and do it correctly this time. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 18:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I uninstall all my mods using NMM (so they are greyed out, rather than just disabled) and then do a clean install of skyrim, when I go to install and re enable the mods, it should be like I just downloaded all of them from the nexus, correct? They shouldn't remember anything from past installs, correct? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 14:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It works....kinda. I can't actually manage the mods, but it recognizes they are installed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like something from the Vox server. Nice  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 18:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! That worked  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 12:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a way to copy my mod list over from NMM? I'm not gonna bother switching if there isn't since my game is running perfect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 03:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6'4" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 20:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try 25x36. It just flat out doesn't exist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 15:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC, this functionality is built into Sneak Tools as well, which has been released for SSE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 14:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mods don't usually add value to a car so it doesn't even matter. Especially if you can't prove that they were done by a reputable shop (I.e with receipts), then they may even lower the value of the car. That's why KBB doesn't appraise mods. There's too much leeway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 14:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it a Chevy/Geo Tracker? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 04:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Got a 1995 YJ. I'm in Hudson  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 15:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I'm in Ohio! Im north Akron area  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 03:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go with Nobel like the other commenter said. I use it on my PC and it actually increased performance over vanilla SSE graphics and looks great  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 18:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I regret not buying one when I had a chance a few months ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got this playing vanilla SSE. Its a bug in the game, not a mod related issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 23:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh! A Singer! My dream car </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pinzgauer 712k 6x6! So much awesome. Or maybe a Volvo Sugga </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 14:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any texture packs/mods for SSE that will improve performance or at the very least not impact it negatively?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 14:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need display port to run 144hz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 14:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think YJs came leaky from the factory. I own two (both 1995) and have a friend who owns 2 1/2(one '95, an '89 and one is a drive able parts car) and they all leak no matter what. I am constantly bailing out my floor pans before I drive to school in the morning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 04:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Food </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 18:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the car. You can do it very easily with Jeeps older than 1995 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. I've owned a 1985 Ford Ranger and loved it. I've also driven a bunch and one of my practical dream cars is an AMC Eagle and an AMC Pacer. I would trade my Jeep for a Pacer honestly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hard top compatibility between a CJ7 and 1995 YJ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that fiberglass hardtops canswitch between them easily, but what about ones like [This](https://cleveland.craigslist.org/pts/5869830096.html)?
It is apparently a hardtop for a CJ7 and not a CJ5 like I originally thought and wanted to know if anyone ever tried putting one on a YJ, or if it will even fit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 14:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'm the only person who's favorite cars are 80's American made ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
