<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5711</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 07:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no i don't.

i just think that they feel entitled to stuff because there relatives were slaves.

it happened over 200 years ago and the first salves were white and you don't see us complaining about it.

they have every right that white people have so they can STFU about not getting what they want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a racist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 07:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 06:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that Justin Bieber? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 06:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't get it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 06:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you will feel something eventually my wife lost her dad a month ago and she's just now starting to feel it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 21:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sadly they actually think this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 05:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anorexia is an actual condition in the head.

but they just get eat everything ever wonder why there are very very few places for fatties to "get help with there BED" no because it all comes down to STOP EATING.

EDIT: thats right delete your message </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 05:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you it seems i cant function today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Mail? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 04:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i know this is not fat logic but why is daily mail not really supposed to posted? 

or an i wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 04:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes i know i am 

I'm getting help  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 04:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the amount of fat that dress is holding in shit watch your door frames  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 04:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well its still illegal in most places and he's fucking 13 years old why fuck up his brain before its don't growing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 03:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> family bonding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 03:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you really think the 
OP wants to take that chance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 03:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pot always leads to harder drugs stop this fast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 03:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha this sounds like my EX  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 03:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is fucking retarded  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 03:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking like 50+ pounds overweight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate fat people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 03:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 01:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think Eva is 100X hotter i happen to like them that skinny deal with it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 01:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never go full tard  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 01:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i only gained 4 pounds fatties always say its like 250+ wtf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 06:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i cant even....

im so sorry i know nothing i can say will make you feel better but know that you have a whole support system here.

i cant even imagine what your feeling or thinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 03:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sadly i wish more then anything this was a joke.

but there was a guy who talked to them about his sleep apnea. due to being overweight it was killing him 

they told him that its not because he was fat that the doctors are wrong. 

its been a year he lost weight and his sleep apnea went away they could have killed him.

HAES and FA will KILL people they are giving out advice that could harm people. Its proven fact that being overweight makes you dumb ( drops IQ points ) so these woman following them are most likely not very intelligent. so they might just listen to them 

and they obviously are not the best at looking after there health in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 03:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no i think she is doing a AMA about having an only child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 03:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its from tumblr there This is thin privilege 

were fatties try to change the whole world to avoid having to change themselves  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 02:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thin shaming is no a thing

hahahahaha everyone loves thin bodies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 02:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no no your completely right i want just more making a general point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 21:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> send this to r/childfree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 21:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sometimes i don't think TITP knows how the internet works .

or for that matter how freedom of speech works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 08:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if they are worst then usual then go call your doctor when you can or just go to a free clinic I'm no doctor but i know that its always better to sit around for a few hours and be safe then sorry  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 08:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i mean your about the same age as me I'm 20 and i get them all the time as long as you don't have REALLY bad cramps and you don't feel sick you should be ok  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 08:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have you seen a dermatologist or had a biopsy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 08:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i really hope thats the cops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 08:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats just looks like a regular blood cot how old are you?

if you have lots of those go to your doctor or even a free clinic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 07:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banana for scale? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 06:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF happened here 

and i fucking hope those dogs don't live like this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 06:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i mean as long as you were safe and happy i don't see why you need to label your self or hell even stop. have fun enjoy yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 04:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i know this might not help but i had the same problem 

i was 16 and admitted to the hospital in the mental health floor (brought there by my teachers)

mother told the doctor i was faking it for attention ( i was cutting so bad that i needed stitches) 

then got yelled at for making her look bad 

she's the main reason for ALL my depression i moved out a few weeks later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i dont hate my siblings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 04:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have chosen with my partner to only have ONE child because there is all sorts of proof and studies that show only children are superior to children with siblings.

but my family is under some sort of delusion that because i only want one child i hate my siblings.

not true at all i love them but i feel that i didn't get the attention and affection i needed. 

i want my child to have 100% of my time and love 

so NO family i don't hate my siblings i just know that i would have preferred to be an only child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 03:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i would never be able to trust her again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> family is really trying to kill me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 01:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have a sever allergy to coconut my mom keeps trying to feed me coconut.

rubs coconut oil all over her hands then touches things rubs it in my brothers hair who is 6 and climbs all over me.

plus we live 2 hours from a hospital. so if anything happeneds to me I'm fucked 

i don't know what to do i keep yelling at them begging them to stop all they say is well its my house i will do what i want.

i cant move out my apartment burned down in july and I'm waiting for my insurance so i can move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 01:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she cant wipe her ass if its like that 


the smell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 01:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why is finding extremely thin woman attractive a bad thing i am who i am i like what i like. DEAL WITH IT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 01:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tumblr are such ED/fitblr/weight loss haters that this probably got that person banned  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
