<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8986</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might already know this but consider changing your medication. I got into some bad depression by being prescribed too much daily klonopin, I think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FS] Freya Deco Moulded Plunge Bra, Charcoal Grey, [28E] UK or [28DDD] US $35 including shipping, Brand new. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 23:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freya Deco Moulded Plunge bra in Charcoal Grey. I bought the wrong size and returning internationally is too expensive for me. Listed on amazon at $48.50. Selling for $35 including shipping.

[Pictures](http://imgur.com/8l1YZA4)

[Amazon link](http://www.amazon.com/Freya-Womens-Moulded-Plunge-Black/dp/B002RVB9A0/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 qid=1429306099 sr=8-1 keywords=Freya+Deco+Moulded+Plunge), the color is a bit better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 09:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes sense. My card is doing it at equal value at all places so that's why I was confused. Good tip on only getting it where I would spend it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For cash back rewards on my credit card, why would I choose gift cards instead? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 08:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just wondering if there were any advantages to choosing gift cards as an option for getting cash back.  I never use gift cards nor give them as gifts so I probably would just do a direct deposit back into my account anyway, but I have just always been curious why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 01:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could always just try it out and stop if you see it negatively affecting you. Your dosage is really small. 

I was prescribed daily with a higher dose (I forgot) and I ended up sleeping too much, which made me miss meals and eat too little, which all compounded my depression. It was a bad doctor that prescribed this. I now take it as needed. Another thing that works for me is to take .5 to 1mg at night and it lasts a little during the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 01:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lettuce wraps! Add some protein like diced chicken breast. Mmm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 07:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's just me but after they mention YD, doesn't the water kind of make Onion/Sour Cream hair?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 04:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want it on my wall and I don't even know if I'd do that ironically or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 10:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom I think would be in the 15%. She's an atheist/non-religious but when I talked to her about gay marriage (I'm not out, engaged in a hetero relationship right now) she said they shouldn't be married because they can't have kids. I then said if straight couples who were infertile shouldn't get married, and she simply said that was a good point. She didn't disagree with it because of religion or hatred, but I think she just never thought about it and was ignorant. She doesn't have any gay friends that she knows of, and grew up in Japan where being gay was kind of ignored by society.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 06:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's embarrassing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 20:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not [always the case](http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2014/09/02/jose-joe-job-discrimination_n_5753880.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 20:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the bowls they used in the first two! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 08:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another way I think of it similarly is thinking about how much it costs in rent to store the objects. I never come up with a price really but to think that I'm actually spending money on storing a box is silly to me. And yeah, rent is expensive where I live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 07:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/TrollaBot subject8986 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 04:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have any good online resources especially since I'm not vegan so the recipes often have unnecessarily expensive ingredients (pine nuts, etc). It's paired really great with salt. Since I'm experimenting, I really don't measure. 

Popcorn + salt + olive oil + NY. 

Roasted garbanzo beans + olive oil + salt + NY + sriracha. 

Veggies + rice + protein + NY + annie's goddess dressing (tonight's dinner). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 01:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an omnivore but use tons of nutritional yeast. It's sooo good. I'm just being super experimental with it at the moment. I prefer to use it as a topping more than in cooking though. Although I made a miso broth with just miso + nutritional yeast and it was really great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 18:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What softness of pencil is the background? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 18:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you just let people use whatever they want to use without putting them down for it? I use the cup, but you're being kind of dickish about it. It's their body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 20:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once heard a study that the first stall is the cleanest. Now it's my go-to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 20:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sooo wish eating bugs was less controversial in America. It'd be such cheap protein! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 20:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just stick an ice cube or two in. I have a super thermos that keeps heat in really well so I have to do this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 19:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theres lots of sodium, which would be important if you have high blood pressure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 20:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also take some medications under your tongue. I think you can with Xanax.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 08:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on the severity, it could be related to bipolar ii, too. The big difference between adhd and hypomania is that hypomania is episodic, whereas adhd is consistent throughout time. Definitely something to ask a doctor about. From what I understand, depression often follows manic and hypomania episodes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 08:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many thrift stores get an excess of donations so they do have to throw away a lot. You didn't say where you were donating, but if it's to thrift stores, consider other outlets like donating to homeless shelters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 10:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly got me going for a second. Forgot about the thread and I was thinking this was some bizarre proposal by some socially awkward person. I need some sleep. Well written, good job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 08:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I named a neighbor's tuxedo Penguin. Also named my bearded dragon Moose (shortened from Mustache). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 04:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really helpful, but I ordered on the 26th and received it on the 28th but I live in northern california. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 02:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously... we got a $500 fine for having our bikes in our backyard (that was technically "shared space" but is fenced in). Fuck HOAs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 07:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can try jogging early in the morning (6AM or earlier), or even look at /r/bodyweightfitness for things you can do inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 23:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's really bothering you, you can call and see if they say anything about it. I think Wellbutrin takes a couple weeks to work fully, but dr's usually will recommend to stop if you're having a lot of negative side effects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 23:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't citrus (orange) an acid? And I think SBR's has some vinegar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 06:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did this a few days back too, and used shredded parmesan cheese on top for another 10 minutes which worked out well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 07:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took a similar camera, a Superheadz Wide and Slim (not old, but film). It was a gift but about $30, got some dollar store film, and have used it for 2 years. Dont think it can make another year but I loved that it was light and could fit in my camelbak, unlike a (D)SLR. It was also something that if I lost it, it wouldn't be a major heartbreak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 05:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try a [kit](http://humade.nl/products/new-kintsugi-1)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 11:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might be even better if its a main protein source, as tuna has a high Mercury content that needs to be looked out for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 20:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, I wonder if it has changed. I did see that they carry 0000. That's definitely super different than the US. Another thing is that shoes are generally narrower (great for me).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 19:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After watching this for years, I finally realize what pickle surprise means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 00:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant to say that they carry larger sizes than myself. I think thrift stores carry lots of Mediums (obviously...!). Being an outlier sucks sometimes. My size is usually "as smallest as I can find" and a lot of stores (Old Navy, for example) won't carry that because of a larger bodied clientele. My family lives in Japan and their sizes are great and I can usually wear their mediums.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 23:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone on the skinnier side (00/0), I often find thrift store jeans to carry larger sizes. I have to admit I don't browse thrift stores too often (I try not to buy a lot of clothes), and I never shop at Hollister but I appreciate this and was able to find my and my SO's sizes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 23:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to add that they have sales very often in case you aren't sure what to buy. I used to have a Gap credit card and I rarely saw the site not have a sale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 20:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same experience when I went to Japan. The busier parts had great McCafes, and for cheap, which is hard to come by in Tokyo. The one I went to was in Harajuku, and it was multi story I think? It was a small menu. Got the cappuccino and it was great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 06:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The painting studio is on the third floor of Kroeber. You need a code to access the room, and if you want 24/7 access, you need to rent a key to the building ($50 deposit). Not sure but you probably need to be in a class to use the studio, and maybe need to take an art class to rent the key.

The back lot of Wurster 178 is generally open has a silent agreement with graffiti artists to not take down their work, so you can paint back there probably but it would be outside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 09:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanna join, too! ForLife for life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 08:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooh okay. Very cool. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 07:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't been tattood myself, but I always assumed there was plastic wrapped over tattoos (on humans)? Or is this only very early on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 03:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not trying to defend tattooing pets, but it would be relatively easy to stop the dog from itching it. It can be covered/wrapped, and you could also treat it like how a surgery wound would be treated (cone, etc).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 00:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was this, and [Rebecca Sugar's response](http://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/2e4gmx/i_am_rebecca_sugar_creator_of_steven_universe_and/cjw189y) that solidified it to me. My guess is that they are making it subtle so it doesn't piss off conservative families/countries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 04:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also can help when people have been injured. More commonly referred to as box squats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 20:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember hearing he freaked out on stage, and was diagnosed with Aspergers being one of the causes for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Vines - Ride [2:43] 2004 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 08:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 02:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess I'm used to LA weather.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 05:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Violence is wrong and it seems to have discredited the opinions of these protesters. But you can't say civil disobedience won't do shit.

Since people don't seem to be looking at historic protests when looking at this situation, an example you might've seen are worker strikes.  Their opinion does get heard, and unions are formed, and people are a little less marginalized, a little more paid, and a little more insured.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 19:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The discomfort of someone being late to work is incomparable to what the cause actually is about? Police brutality is more important than that, I think we can both agree. 

If you look at successful protests/marches throughout history, they did not get there by being subtle and uninterruptive. 

I totally don't agree with causing violence and damage to property but something like shutting down a freeway does make sense to me a bit. They got their message heard on the news and told the police that they do have power in their actions. If all that they caused in return was a few people being late, which would be pretty few since this was like at midnight, I think the bigger message is more important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 11:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because for a protest to be successful, there should be a disruption to an every day thing like the use of freeways (or taking over golden bear cafe last week). That way, their voice can be heard because they can't be heard from traditional methods. In this case, they were silenced because the police and court system havent been listening. That's what my understanding of it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 08:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a friend explain to me that it was due to a possible future career. Not ashamed of protesting, but doing things like going on the freeway is illegal and it can affect them in the future. Getting filmed for doing so can also cause an arrest in the future. He was in no way intending to cause violence, though.

edit: Loving the downvotes on this and my other responding comments. It really shows maturity on a topic that needs to be talked about. Remember that downvotes are not for disagreeing with someone's comments, but for spam, etc.  Seriously disappointing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 22:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always just pull out a hunk for the first bit, like gutting a chicken. The beginning feels too tight and I'd rather have it a bit looser. The guts end up like a mini-skein. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 03:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It started around 5:00 which is technically during daylight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 02:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an art major that just finished a class on porn studies... this isn't that far from what I experience in an academic setting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 06:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would try for different classes. A lot of them are filled even for art majors. Crashing can be an option. At some point, an email is sent out with what classes still have openings, since there are some that are less popular and don't get the required amount of students.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 06:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a children's illustration DeCal. Also, she should email Dee Levister if she needs a code to a specific class. I would look at the DeCals once they're up, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 21:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's unhealthier to be 15lbs underweight than to be 15lbs overweight, especially in terms of heart conditions. The less you eat, the more likely your blood pressure will lower (in a bad way) and you won't be pumping enough oxygen through your body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a quick rant about the irony of a test question I got wrong in college. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 00:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm taking a Developmental Psychopathology course at my college and on the test, it asks for what the treatment options are for substance abuse problems in adolescents. This test also covers questions about ADHD (among other things) and the great person I am, misread the question and answered it to a T, but thinking it asked about the treatment options for ADHD instead of substance abuse. So I got 0/15 on that. Because my ADHD brain skimmed over the question and made a careless error. And I can't take Adderall anymore because my heart rate is too high. So my lack of ADHD treatment answered it as ADHD treatment options...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 00:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought about it recently, and someone was saying how it really doesn't matter because who cares if someone knows I'm wearing underwear. Like... big deal, I'm wearing underwear.

I don't go commando because I don't wash my pants every time I work out. Going commando leaves residue, if you know what I'm saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 08:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They usually say take 2 classes from your major, 1 required class (prereq or whatever you need), and 1 fun class. I did 2 of my major, 1 of my minor, and a DeCal for my first semester, which added up to be 13 units. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 09:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't diagnose pcos with biopsies (that I know of). An ultrasound is one of the three ways that they detect pcos-- the others being a blood test and just having the physical symptoms. 2 out of the 3 have to show pcos irregularities to be diagnosed.

I had a doctor explain to me that the reason having no periods is so bad is because basically what tissues (egg? maybe?) should be expelled during a period isn't being expelled, so it's kept in the uterus. This builds up and can cause cancerous cells to develop. I might be wrong with the details... But basically my doctor said that having a few periods is much better than none, just so it won't build up.

I know you were saying that you don't want to change your lifestyle, but not choosing a hormonal treatment might do more harm than good. IIRC, you only have to induce the period once or a few times for the cancer risk to lower. So you might not have to be on a medication for a long time or anything. Just something to think about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 18:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got this unsweetened version, [Jarrow Formulas whey protein](http://www.amazon.com/Jarrow-Formulas-Protein-Natural-Pound/dp/B0013OVWHM/ref=sr_1_2?ie=UTF8 qid=1415985475 sr=8-2 keywords=jarrows). It's only $20 and ships to me free using Amazon Prime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 19:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great to know... when I used baking soda, it just reminded me of when I bleached my hair. Same slippery-ness during and same cleanliness after. 

I've just gone with a shampoo bar now, though.

When I wasn't, though, an egg mask in my hair felt like it helped get rid of grease. I've read that doing that too much isn't the best, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 06:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started reading the book and one of the things it talks about is how the goals are on the aesthetic side, focusing on the commons goals women want (booty). It looks like it starts off with pretty easy bodyweight exercises. I agree that she should probably just do them when you're doing your thing but if you're fit enough, you could probably do a lot of the exercises as support for her without tiring out on your own routine in the first month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 19:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is a couple days too late, but in case this is for anyone else: they usually won't give you stitches after 6-8 hours.  Especially if there's already a scab. It'll be fine. Use bacitracin to avoid infection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 20:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you do those three after the main? So 3x a week? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 19:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll look into that now, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 19:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I have been looking at these images and I noticed there isn't a lot of core, especially as primary muscles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Is SL 5x5 a full body workout? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 19:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm starting SL 5x5 and am used to doing lots of dumbbell exercises per workout (pullovers, biceps curls, db bench press, isolated tricep things, wrist curls and reverse, etc etc) and I feel like the three exercises won't be working out my full body.

For those that have used the program, do you do accessory exercises? Which ones? Before or after the major lifts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 21:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has a rack for regular barbells, just not one for fixed barbells, which I think is common. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 20:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right... I forgot I had help with that part, too. I'm going to stick to dumbbell squats for now.

Also, I think /u/mikelieman posted it but it seems to be called the Steinborn Lift.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 20:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, that helps :) I haven't been doing goblet squats for that long, and assumed they were similar to dumbbell squats. 

I love this subreddit!! It's answers like this thread that focus on learning how to start correctly that make me feel better about not being able to squat an empty bar. My fiance is athletic so it's hard for him to give me pointers on this sort of thing. So I appreciate the novel! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 05:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love my DOMS too. I have a multitude of reasons to not push myself before getting my form down (hyperflexible, shoulder injury, herniated disc in my spine, and possible slight muscle atrophy from a past with anorexia). A year ago, a 3lb dumbbell to do pullovers was intense so I'm weaker than a lot of people's starting out points. Anyways, it's just boring excuses, but I'm just trying to say that 10lbs does make a big difference for my body, and everyone starts off at different points. I'm a pain slut when it comes to DOMS, I just don't want to injure myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 04:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's interesting because when I used the bar, I was leaning too forward and felt a lot of weight on my shoulders/back, even with a 35 fixed barbell but didn't feel that much discomfort doing goblet squats. It feels like if I'm too vertical, the barbell will just roll off my back. I think my bodyweight squats are pretty good, though. It's all just a new movement for me. Need to learn how to trust my body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 04:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was doing goblet squats (I think I did 30lb last week, relatively easily).  I also haven't been doing overhead presses, so maybe I should work on that too... More reps it is. 

I hope you heal quickly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 04:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant to say that there wasn't a rack for the preloaded ones. They're too short to fit on the regular squat rack. [They're like these](http://www.gymdirect.com.au/media/pics/site/imagecache/4/E/4E0915147E1760364D113A08B8AFC6FB.jpg). 

That video looks so scary to me. I'm really not used to using my muscles so I'm prone to injuring myself!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 04:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll do that next time. Thanks! 

Today I took it off the rack and was waiting a little bit so I had one end on the ground, making it really hard for me to bring it back horizontally again.

I'm hyperflexible so that kind of movement still feels a little scary (afraid of partially dislocating my shoulder) but I'll definitely do the overhead press way first. If not, I'll do the front squats. Totally forgot about that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I get a pre-loaded barbell on my shoulders to squat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 03:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried using barbells today for the first time. The 45lb bar was OKAY but I really think I need to focus on form before that. So, I went down to the preloaded barbells (I think that's what they're called according to the internet?) and used 35lb, but I can't figure out how to get it on to my shoulders. I had some help today (thanks, strangers!) but since there isn't a rack, I'm kind of confused. Also, I bench press using dumbbells but I guess I could use these too. How would I get into and out of position without hurting myself? 

Does this even make sense? I'm wondering if theres a video out there that would show this... maybe showing someone doing squats but the 30 seconds before and after doing a set. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 04:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never heard of this. Added some cubed chicken breast, some peas and corn. Really great for my hangover today. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 06:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or the white part is the cover of a book of black pages? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 08:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you like it with worcestershire sauce, I'd recommend picking up a bottle of tonkatsu sauce if you can find it. The recipe is close to a japanese okonomiyaki, and with your noodles it would be hiroshima-style okonomiyaki.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 03:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the video! I hurt my shoulder a few days ago, I think because I hadn't warmed up well enough, and I did this before I started exercising today and it was great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 00:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was kind of a BuzzFeed-esque title. "You won't believe your eyes when you see what this one woman did!" Not saying OP meant it that way. I think it's why /r/HumanPorn decided to use more descriptive titles in posts, for instance.

Nice photo, nonetheless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 23:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just said that we rescued a 7 year old dog. That means it was not our fault, and we're doing our best to train him. One way to really fuck up a dog is to leave your dog at home. 

The last time he got to a dog (didn't hurt the chihuahua, but it was in his mouth), we picked him up and pryed his mouth open, cutting up our hands. The owner was kicking our dog, which didn't help. If you think that putting your dog on its back while in a fight helps, you've never experienced a dog fight. Why are you so against putting dogs on leashes?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 23:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A leash won't stop an unleashed dog running up to a leashed dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 23:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has happened on normal dog walks. We walk around our neighborhood since it would be much less responsible to not give him walks. We've had a dog trainer, different types of muzzles, harnesses, and sprays. All you have to do is use a leash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 22:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another opinion, but for me I absolutely hate when the pressure is on the front. The sides where my arteries are feel the best to me. My SO is familiar with choking people out (boxing, bdsm), so I go to the point of almost being choked out but not all the way. Although, I'm comfortable enough where I wouldn't freak out if I was choked out. I hate the feeling of lacking air through my throat and would rather there be no pressure on my actual trachea. And agreed with tapping out to make sure it's all okay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 21:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because your dog is friendly with other dogs, doesn't mean mine is. We got a rescue who was 7 yrs old, and is unfriendly with dogs. We've been doing our best to help him with it, but he isn't perfect. Every time there's been a problem, it's been with dogs off of their leash running up to our dog. And honestly, retractable leashes are horrible too. Leash your dog for the safety of your own dog, not just what you think is irrational fears of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 21:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went twice and didn't go to the temple burn by choice. Exodus ended up being super fast the first year (almost no stopping). Unless you have someone special who passed and something is in the temple, I'd say it would be fine to skip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 20:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info. I've already signed up for the meal plan, but I also will be living a block away from Crossroads so it was the best option for me. Do you know if I can opt out of the meal plan at this point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 08:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! That makes sense. I have insurance so I spend $10 a month in medication, but I know most people aren't as fortunate. It's low enough that I hadn't considered it, since it's covered for me. The large expenses makes a lot of sense too. The rest of it I can't imagine would be more than $100 a month, but I have pretty frugal habits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
