<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8720</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I needed to share this with someone! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 18:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted last week asking how to keep motivated with treatments, and this lovely CF community gave me some great bits of advice, and words of encouragement. As my partner (ex? still not sure) is currently abroad, there aren't many people in my life I feel I can share this with, so I wanted to tell you all. 

I have been 100% compliant with all of my treatments for nearly two weeks now. This is possibly the first time ever. I realise that, where other people have responsibilities to their job, or to their family etc, I have a responsibility to my health. When my relationship fell apart, I had a sudden realisation that I did not like myself - this lazy, irresponsible person. And if I didn't like that, why should he? I never want to be that person again.

I got up yesterday, and I wanted to do my treatments. I wanted to make my bed. I wanted to shower and brush my hair. I cried because it felt so freeing to actually *want* to do something. I saw a friend for dinner, and then I made plans to see her again next week. A month ago, I would have cancelled that dinner. Or I wouldn't have taken my enzymes, in case she saw them. But yesterday I took them and had them on the table so she could see. I've decided not to hate my CF anymore, I think.

I know it's early days, and I know there are going to be days when I get up, and I won't want to do treatments, because everyone has days like that. But I think that when that happens, I can push past that, and realise that I have to, there's no choice, really.

I'm not sure what the point of this post is, and I'm sorry for rambling, or if anyone felt like this was gloating - it isn't at all. For the first time in 22 years, I think I want to be in control of my CF, and not let my CF control me, and I really needed to share that with someone today.

I hope you're all well, and thank you for reading this. 
xx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
