<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8657</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Bulimic for 2 years and continuing and I don't know how to get help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 17:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, in the beginning, I started to get guilty about any kind of food I was eating in high school . Then it eventually came to purging. 

I started purging in senior year, which has continued into half way through my sophomore year of college. Whenever I do eat something, I then feel guilty about it and I just want to purge. No matter what it is. 

I can't talk to anyone about this issue since they'd get mad at me. I don't know what to do or who to talk to without sounding crazy or where to go for help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Worried that my sister who struggles with bipolar disorder is purging. How do I proceed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 22:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know where to start with this... My sister is currently 21 and lives with our parents (I'm 23 and live 4 hours away by myself). When she was 16 she attended a boarding school and during this time began self-harming and had a short period of time where she didn't eat enough, because she wanted to lose weight. Since then she has gained weight, was diagnosed with bipolar disorder and has been through a couple of bouts of heavy depression that she is getting treatment for. About 10 months ago she started losing weight again, seemingly in a healthy way. Recently, while I was overseas for a study-program, she was hospitalized for around three weeks due to prolonged severe insomnia - with which she still struggles. 

Before I left for my study program, I visited home and noticed she sometimes went to the bathroom right after eating. I am now back and this behavior is now happening after every meal. She will stay in the bathroom for a while, flush several times and afterwards there is cleaning product in the toilet. She does not appear to be binging however, and eats normal portions (however less than she used to). She is slightly above normal weight.

My sister and I have never been very close. We never disliked eachother, we just never seemed to speak the same 'language' in the sense of interests, humour or affection. We haven't bonded over or shared anything in a long time and we have had no previous discussion of her (or mine) thoughts/feelings towards her mental health. I do love and worry for her though, and I'm scared of what to do about these new symptoms as she can be very hard to approach. 

I am unsure of when/if to involve our parents, as they seem to not be aware of this behavior yet (I think it may be a matter of time). They are very supportive and truly doing their best to help her with her depression, but I think she is ashamed about her problems and often clash or react coldly/aversively to talking or sharing with them. She sometimes does confide in me about things, mostly about issues with other people, that she does not want our parents to know about. I'm scared about placing even more strain on her relationship with them, if I alert them to her abnormal behaviour around food.

I want to let her know that I've noticed and encourage her to talk to her psychiatrist about this, but at a complete loss of how to broach this topic with her without making her feel threatened or lessen the likelyhood of her seeking help. Keeping my parents out of the loop doesn't feel right either, as they are the ones who are most around her. To make matters worse, I have limited time at home, and even less time available to get alone time with her due to family visiting and her high need for defending her privacy and personal bubble while in our home. Please, any kind of advice or even just reponses would be highly appreciated. Thank you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Information and advice for folks with NSRED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 19:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been diagnosed with Nocturnal Sleep Related Eating Disorder...I sleep-eat. I binge while completely unconscious, and feel so sick in the mornings that I can't function. Are there any approved treatments besides prescriptions for this (sedatives have only exacerbated the condition)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: ED Center is pushing for inpatient </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 17:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I've been struggling with undereating for over a year now and was looking into getting into an outpatient program. However, after going through the initial interviews and etc. the center I was planning on going to said that since I am medically unstable they cannot allow me to do anything other than inpatient. 

With the spring semester starting soon I really cannot do that. My medical results were not THAT alarming (though I am underweight and had irregularities in my workup) 

I was wondering if I really started pushing myself to eat more could I stabilize myself and possibly do outpatient or should I look into other options?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Request for help with BED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 04:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering if you could post my beacon for help-I have BED and am probably going through my worst period of it ever. I've never felt so out of control and helpless (although I'm in therapy and on Vyvanse)

Does anyone have any insight as to how I can feel more in control and ways to kick the urges to the curb? I'm at the point where I'm so ashamed and self conscious, that I barely leave my apartment.

edit: Please PM the OP, /u/SheWeeHerman, when you've posted.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to handle medical leave gracefully? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 04:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My question is about handling medical leave for eating disorder treatment in a professional career.

I've made the decision to go back to treatment for the first time in over 5 years, and have suffered with anorexia nervosa since I was 13 years old. This time, instead of being a high school student, I work full time as an IT systems engineer. My employer offers generous insurance/medical leave (3 months, paid).

My treatment will most likely be partial hospitalization 5 days/week. The only person at work who knows anything about this is my manager, because I had to decline taking over a customer account and said I may need to go on a leave of absence to receive medical treatment and couldn't commit to the account yet, didn't mention anything specific.

Obviously, I don't want anyone at work to know why I'm gone, and ideally not even notice I'm gone(huge corporation, huge office). I have to set an "out of office" notification for anyone sending me emails since there are things people rely on me for and don't know how to word it so coworkers don't worry about me or gossip.

Could anyone provide tips/personal experiences for handling treatment while in a professional career? Also, how to word the "out of office" email to not raise any flags for nosy people(could I just say I'm on PTO, because it technically is paid time off)? Usually, the advice I read is aimed at students leaving school/university for treatment.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Requst: Is there a support group? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 04:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My fiancee has bulemia, and it caused a seizure that put her in a coma for 4 days this summer. We worked hard to get her into an inpatient facility, and then she refused to go last minute. All the outpatient facilities in our area then turned her down because of the coma... they said her disorder was too severe. Now it's Christmas and she's stopped going to therapy entirely. All this time, I've been seeing a therapist specializing in eating disorders so I can get advice on how to help her. But now I'm the only one still trying, and her bulimia is worse than before. I know our relationship is ending, but I can't leave for fear that something will happen to her and no one will be around to help - the only reason she lived last time is because I was working from home that week and was able to call an ambulance immediately. I'm at the end of my rope, and I feel like I have no one I can talk to without humiliating her. Help?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I suspect my elderly mother's live-in care-giver has an ED and I'm worried about my mom's health/safety </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 22:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Help! I'm pretty sure my elderly Mom's Live-in care-giver has an ED. She's in her 60's and has been leaving shockingly-messy vomit   diarrhea in   around her guest room / toilet (the other caregivers use this en-suite bathroom too, during their shifts) and in another toilet in the utility room. Other caregivers have noticed the messes as well. 

We are all terribly worried. I think she's had an ED for decades: among other signs, she's extremely thin   her teeth are so bad she wears a tray. 

Equally concerining: I'm very worried about hygiene as she cares for my Mom and prepares food. She also works in food service. We are all extremely fond of her plus, she's very talented. But her ED and its effects on her personality and decision making have often been an problematic. She's FIERCELY independent and defensive so I don't think she will be easy to approach. We've danced around the issue for years (she breezily claims it's merely trouble gaining weight) but it now seems like she is getting way worse. 

I can explain more of my observations if needed. I can't understand why she would not flush   clean up her toilet? I can't find anything about this type of situation (Care-giver who has restricting with purging ED) 

Advice???  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Supporting SO with ED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 12:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello all, I could use some advice. My girlfriend has been wrestling with her ED for about 7 years. When we started seeing each other about four months ago, she was in therapy, seeing a GP and a nutritionist. She seemed very happy, she was putting some weight back on (which was very necessary) and I made sure to be supportive and positive. In the past month, she's ceased seeing her therapist and nutritionist, her GP is concerned based on tests, and she's slowly and surely pushing me away. No visits, hardly any contact at all. In her defense, it's a rough month for her; holidays always bring family problems to light, but this month also marks the anniversary of her friend's passing. I offer to be there is she needs me, but I try to respect her space. It's at the point now where several days will go by, and if I try to talk to her or see her just for the sake of seeing her, I'm attacked. She'll say something like, "I sent you articles about [bumilia and relationships] and told you I needed space." That's fair, I can't argue that, and don't push the issue. She says she wants this relationship, but really, it's not much of one at all these days. I'm virtually non-existent. Call me selfish, but I'm trying to protect myself from getting hurt (I can't stop wondering if I should stay or go at this point, which I obviously don't want) while trying to be supportive of her, hoping there's something I can do to help her find her way back to her recovery path. 

Is there anything I can say or do that won't set this powderkeg off? What's the line, and how do I walk it? Any help is sincerely appreciated.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Managing a career in geology with an ED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 22:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geology is an unstable career where you often have to work in remote or isolated areas away from your home town. I'm looking for advice on how to manage an ED relapse when I am in a small town with zero resources. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to help my girlfriend recover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 17:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend is anorexic. Its not as extreme as things I've read about. however its been going on for some time now. she used to starve herself, work out before school, and then again after school. now she's slowly recovering. when we go on dates she eats just like normal, but when she's on her own or pretty much whenever she isn't with me she doesn't eat. she knows that she needs to gain and she's been trying but I just want to support her as much as possible. she attends therapy 3 days a week, but she's getting sick of it because she wants to travel. 

any help or advice would be greatly appreciated. I love her to death and want her to be healthy
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Christmas gift ideas for teenager currently hospitalized </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 23:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 16 year old sister-in-law has been in the hospital for AN since collapsing in September. She was sent to a program that specializes in AN in late October but was sent back because she refused to not leave the facility unsupervised. This has made me feel like she isn't sincere about recovery because that was the one rule at the facility and she consistently broke it despite numerous warnings because she "wanted to be alone to think." She has no problem following the rules and not leaving the hospital unsupervised at home.

While I fully believe that her AN is real and serious and not a choice. I think that she hasn't made the choice to get better yet. As a former teenage girl I remember the desire to perpetuate teenage angst and I feel like, at least for right now, she is stuck in that mode. Not wanting to get better because she is not ready to move on from the "poor me" stage. She has also told me numerous times that she can't get better because she doesn't have a good support system. I've told her multiple times that whether or not that is true doesn't matter, you can't rely on others to make you better. You have to do the work yourself and part of recovery is learning to find the strength within to overcome your illness.

Anyway, I mention all these things because I am torn about what to do for Christmas. I don't want to reward her hospital stay and enable her to not choose recovery. With that in mind, I was thinking of offering her a girls day when she's back home. Something we could do to bond that she could look forward to coming home to while she's at her next program. But I don't want to do anything that would be a detriment to her recovery. Would it be bad to take her to get her hair done and a makeover or is that counterintuitive to recovery? Am I off base with offering a gift for after she completes her program?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Girlfriend has an eating disorder but wants to work as a gym trainer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 10:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend has an eating disorder and body image issues. She applied to work as a personal trainer. I feel like this would make her eating disorder worse. How do i tell her she shouldn't apply to these jobs without being controlling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ED Article] How to do Christmas better </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 10:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: 50 days binge/purge free but I dont feel better </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 10:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the first time since my eating disorder began 5 years ago I have not binge/purged or gotten sick after eating for 50 days. 
Even just in May of this year that would have been a daily thing. 

So thats a huge thing, massive, insane, and Im almost at a healthy weight too, just the tiniest bit below the bottom range of a healthy BMI.. 

But the problem is I dont feel any better, I feel miserable all the time, I hate myself and I hate the way I look and I have all the issues I had before. 

I dont know what to do. I feel so fucking disgusting and ashamed, like I cant bear the thought of looking at my family when I go home for christmas and like the weight will just spill out of my clothes and everyone will see. 

Has anyone been here and it changed? I feel alone and miserable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Restrictive Eating Recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 10:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been dealing with a restrictive eating disorder since last winter. I have been diagnosed with an eating disorder, but I have not been diagnosed with a specific one, I'm thinking it's very similar to anorexia if that's not what it is. I am about to begin a recovery meal plan. I was wondering if anybody has any insights as to what I should expect in the recovery process. I am not sure what it's going to be like to eat until I'm not hungry anymore and what that will do to my body. It kind of freaks me out, but I know this is what I need to do.

Thanks
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Involuntary vomiting during bulimia recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 10:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed now that I've tried to stop purging, my body does it anyway, and I want to know if anyone else has dealt with this issue, and if they know how long it lasts or what I can do make it stop. I called my doctor about it, but she just said it will stop eventually and I have to wait it out, but it's still scaring me. It's making me feel like I'll never actually recover this, because now my brain can't even stop my body from throwing up. 

Has anyone been through something similar and can provide information? Does anyone know of any methods of recovery from involuntary vomiting?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: feeling sick when eating, help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 00:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I have an eating disorder, but involving trying to eat when I cannot, not trying to stop eating or trying to get thin. I have always been thin, and have always had difficulties eating. I have never come close to thinking I need to lose weight; if anything, I am often thinking about needing to eat to get bulkier. When I try to eat, I feel sick, and if I force myself to eat, I feel like I am going to throw up.

This is true for almost every morning when I wake up, I have difficulty eating anything. Drinking is no problem, I can usually do fine with a liquid or a smoothie. By lunch and supper, sometimes I can eat, sometimes I cannot. By the time it is late at night, I can usually manage most of a full meal, my problem is just during the day I am not capable of eating like everyone else.

I do feel guilty and shamed when I try to eat and fail. I make many full meals that all go to waste.

Usually I can solve this problem by smoking weed. Lately, however, it does not seem to be working all the time. I do also try to regularly weight-train, hoping to build up an appetite.

2 years ago I was given medication for acid reflux, which did not help me. I have not been to a clinic or seen a doctor since then, since they were too convinced it was acid reflux and would not pursue the case any further. I took matters into my own hands and just continued smoking to eat instead. 

I did stop smoking for a month to record the results. After a few days it seemed to get better, but only a bit. I was not always able to finish breakfast regardless, just more often than usual. It did not seem to be the cause, as I have been like this long before I was smoking.

I feel like I am starting to lose weight at an unhealthy level. Living in Quebec also means I have to wait 4+ hours to see someone (forget about that, I have to work like everyone else).

Can anyone offer suggestions on what I can do?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post Request: What constitutes being in recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 00:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone I know has a combination of bulimia and anorexia and is in pretty good therapy, I think. What I want to know is, what constitutes being in recovery versus the condition being in full force? How often can I expect this person to still be purging if she is working towards recovery? I know the DSM says that purging at least once a week for three months. Can I just assume that anything less than that is recover?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: EDA vs OA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 01:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have Binge Eating Disorder, and recently came out of three months of treatment at a rehab facility for it. I learned a lot and if I follow what I learned and the plans I made I will find recovery. 

However I can't do it completely alone and after exploring the world of AA, NA, CA at the rehab facility, I want to find a 12 step group that I can work with. Unfortunately the closest ones are 1 1/2 hour drive away from me, but there's both EDA and OA. So far I think EDA is the better way to go as they preach balance which is in my opinion and those of my therapists the best way to overcome BED. However OA seems to me to be more established, and have a higher membership.

I met one lady from OA who had been a member of 7 years and was adamant that being abstinent from sugars (her 'trigger food') was how she would find recovery but over 7 years she only managed 3 months of success. From what I've learned from various ED books from credited specialists in the field balance not abstinence from certain foods is the best way to have success. 

Was this woman just taking OA teachings and making it an extreme or is abstinence from certain foods something OA preaches?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Need advice about ED coming back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 01:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really know how this subreddit works exactly, but I'm sort of desperate here. 

I've been in recovery for about 6 months and lately I've been having strong feelings of going back. I don't know if it's from the stress of school or winter season approaching but I've been gaining a little weight from stress-eating and it's making me feel entirely horrible. 

Does anyone have advice on what to do when you feel like returning to old habits? I really want to be better but I can't seem to push it out of my head.

edit: Please PM the OP, /u/alyssajulianne , when you've posted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Need Some Input </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 04:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all,

I'm here today because I'm hoping to maybe find some answers or receive some input / direction as to what my situation is.
I believe I may have some sort of mild eating disorder, but I'm really not entirely sure. I should start this by saying that I'm a 25 year old male, although I'm sure you'll get that in my next paragraph, haha.

I was only recently clued into this possibility when I met a female a few months back that was in the recovery phase of her eating disorder (anorexia). She told me all kinds of different things, and some of which I couldn't understand (though I definitely tried and have been supportive of her).

Anyways, some background on me growing up:
I've always been somewhat small in size. I'm 25 years old, and I'm 5' 4" on a good day (lol). I am of normal weight. The odd thing is, I can sort of gain it, but I can't seem to lose it.

Throughout my life I was always one of the smaller kids in school, growing up, everything. Sometimes I was picked on for my size, so that definitely always impacted me and how I ate, especially my nervousness towards eating in public.

In 2014 I spent 2 months on work release in prison (for something pretty silly), but during that time I gained significant weight (from the poor diet), mostly in weird places. I noticed my face became thicker and my thighs and stomach got larger. I lost my natural "six pack" from being skinny. This has obviously bothered me a lot but I think I managed to just ignore the fact that it does bother me subconsciously.

Now, here is where I'm actually going to get into symptoms..
I've finally realized that I don't like eating. I have never liked eating, my entire life. Though I've gone through periods where I do enjoy certain foods. In general, I've come to terms with the fact that if I didn't have to eat and could just take a pill to get rid of the hunger, I would.

I've always thought I was a picky eater, and I am, to an extent, but I noticed that I have safe foods that I go to. I will find things that I like and those will be the main part of my daily food intake for months until I get completely sick of the specific food. I will actually continue to eat the food even after I'm sick of it, I just eat it because I know it was a "safe" food at one point. 

I will often wake up in the morning very hungry, and think about the food I will eat during the day - something that seems really tasty. But once I get up, get moving, and get a shower - I'm suddenly not in the mood to eat. Yes, I'm hungry, I can feel it, but I just don't want to eat. Again, I don't like food. It feels like so much effort to even eat a small snack and force them down. But I am without a doubt hungry.

Big meals are often daunting to me and I will pick through them or barely eat anything.

I become very discouraged to eat by certain things that I may find in food. It could be a texture, something that once happened with that food (hair in food), or anything at all.

I am nervous eating in front of people, because I don't want them to judge what I eat, how I eat it, how long it takes me, or how much of it I eat. I know these are all personal things I could probably deal with, but addressing them, I can see a problem. Just last week, a few friends and I went out on Thanksgiving to a restaurant and they all ordered food and I didn't have any input towards it. I just said "I'll eat whatever" - which is what I do ALL of the time, and then I end up getting food I don't like even more than the food I probably would've forced down anyway. I ended up having a few bites of the food that came, even though I was definitely hungry.

I will often limit myself in how much I eat, even though I know I don't need to. That is a good thing and a bad thing. I sometimes feel shameful when I eat too much of a certain food.

I frequently allow myself to become so hungry that the thought of eating ANYTHING makes me completely turned off by actually eating, thus prolonging my intake of food even more. When I finally do eat, I will eat a very small portion and be done with it. Only to be hungry an hour or so later.

As I type this message, I have not eaten much. I am hungry at this moment, but I just don't want to eat.

I'm currently living with my parents (that's a whole different story), so often times my mother will bring home dinner. Today she brought home dinner, and I'm hungry, but thoughts about the food and its texture makes me not want to eat food at all.

My mom will also often cook certain foods and I will force them down even though I don't like them, or I will pass on them entirely and just not eat for the rest of the day. My behavior towards food is very strange, so I can't really pin point it exactly.

Addressing these feelings is all very new for me, but recently I've been receiving medical help for depression, anxiety, and bipolar disorder. Because of this, I've started trying to take more of a notice in my behaviors and my emotions and start addressing them properly.

Also, I'm aware that depression can often impact appetite and food. But even when I'm not having bouts of depression and lows, I still don't like eating and will avoid it until I absolutely have to eat (IE: feeling light headed, severely weak, sick).

I'm under the impression that I can't technically be diagnosed with an eating disorder unless I am severely underweight or overweight (is this all correct? I'm not sure). And though neither of these are the case, I still feel like there's something more to my disinterest in food as a whole.

If there is anybody out there that can give me some input as to what I'm experiencing, I would be so beyond grateful.
Thank you so much for reading this!

Darren </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Do you think I should see a nutritionist or a psychologist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 12:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if I exactly have an eating disorder but I am aware that I have bad thoughts and behaviours about food.

I'm overweight. I eat way too much.

I don't know why. food tastes really good, I love food. Food is one of my favourite things and it hurts to think about reducing my portion size or refraining from eating certain things. I really don't want to do that. I feel like I'd be missing out on what I love because I can't eat as much of it as I want.

I eat really fast, fill my plate up with more food than other people and will often have seconds and sometimes 3rds. Instead of 2 cookies, I will eat every cookie in the bag if I can. I have absolutely no self-discipline, no willpower, nothing to help me fight my urges.

I even eat when I am not hungry at all. I will eat when I am bored. I will eat just for the sake of making my hands busy.

I have tried to lose weight 3 separate times. And every time I've eventually given up and gone back to my old habits because I don't want to eat less, I don't want to restrict my calorie intake. I don't want to lose what I love; food.

And I'm really not sure if seeing a nutritionist or a psychologist will make it better. because I know it's really bad for me, but I feel like I don't want to change my habits either.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My girlfriend has had an ED for years, but hasn't told her new therapist. Should I say something? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 01:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend has had an eating disorder for over 6 eight years. We started dating around about a year ago. At times its bad, and she throws up every few days. Other times, at least I think, she is able to handle it better. We have had many discussions about it, and I am always supportive of her and speak with her about it. She acknowledges its a problem, but constantly downplays the severity of it. She also suffers from anxiety.

After she went through a really bad week, I told her she had to get help. Before this, I obviously was suggesting that she get help, but not being as forceful. I wanted her to know that I am there for her, and was afraid to push her too hard. She agreed to start seeing a therapist. She has been going for 2 months. She has still not told the therapist about her eating disorder, because she doesn't feel comfortable yet.

About 2 weeks ago, she asked me to go with the therapist with her. During the session, we spoke about ways for me to best handle her anxiety and the problems within our relationship. But deep down, I knew that this time could be better spent and my girlfriend could open up to her about her eating disorder.

There have been numerous times that I've told her that I want to tell her parents, or someone else, because I think I am the only one that knows, and I feel that I am not doing enough to help her. She has asked me to go to another session with her, where we will discuss her anxiety and our relationship problems. I was considering, during the session, to move the conversation, and hopefully have my girlfriend open up to the therapist. I worry that this problem will just continue, and she is just going to the therapist to appease me. I only want to help her. **Would it be wrong to bring this up at our next session, and force her hand in telling the therapist that she is not only suffering from anxiety, but also has an eating disorder?** If I told my girlfriend my plans, she would refuse to go, and beg me not to tell her. I just want to help her :( I am writing this just minutes after I heard her throwing up. **How do I help?** Sorry for the rant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Eating disorders as an athlete </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 22:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there! I was wondering if anyone has experience with recovering from an eating disorder while participating in sport. I have recently started acknowledging that I have had an eating disorder for almost a decade now that I'm in college. I used to run track and cross country, but became a rower my freshman year because I was "tall enough for it." At the time, I was pretty deep in AN and very light/underweight, but I wanted to be strong and tough, so I rowed. I got pretty good over my novice year and gained strength and speed - but I also gained a lot of weight and exacerbated some really disordered eating habits, my BN and BED took over. I took my second year as a men's team coxswain, telling myself I needed less physical pressure to recover. (Yes, I was very tall for a coxswain. And much too heavy.) Needless to say, I lied to myself and really didn't get better. I ended up breaking my leg on a club run earlier this fall (freak accident/repercussions from years of AN and BED/BN) and I've been in physical therapy. I'm getting help and have had some difficult three or four months and I think I am actually getting somewhat better. I'm definitely going to be going to a campus group therapy (I unfortunately had a really nasty time with the eating disorder specialist at my Uni, which has one of the highest levels of eating disorders in the country, where she eventually just flat out told me I didn't have an eating disorder/seemed to positive and upbeat sometimes and too depressed and broken at other times/wasn't sick enough, and that wrecked me) and I ended up joining a sorority last spring when I was feeling super-alienated from the female population in general that has a big focus on positive body image and some of my sisters have experienced/recovered from a variety of eating disorders. I'll be living in with a set meal plan and never be alone (being alone is definitely when I start engaging in poor behaviour), so I'm really hoping that this will be the support I need.

The real question: Will being an athlete help or hinder my recovery? I can't decide if I should join the crew team as a women's team rower at my university again this spring (obviously only if my doctor clears me). It's a club team, but we practice 5 or 6 days a week and we have a great deal of competition within the team to be fast and I also hold myself to very high standards. I am very hard on myself and I know that. It's all I've ever known in college, but I'm also worried it'll make my eating disorders and disordered behaviour worse. But I also don't want to lose my friends and my team and the feeling of being on the water. I'm extremely on the fence about it. On one hand, I know that rowing is part of what really made things worse in the first place, but the team is now made entirely of last year's novice (not as catty or petty as my year) and I am more aware about what I am struggling with. On the other hand, I'm afraid I'll have no structured sense of exercise or eating (or life, let's be honest) without rowing; I know I tend to skip meals and over-exercise (or binge and do nothing) unless there's something like rowing holding me accountable to other people. So part of me sees rowing as a viable way of recovery, while part of me is scared that I'll spread myself too thin again. If I place recovery and myself above competition and performance, then rowing could be beneficial. If I approach it with the idea that I'm rowing to get on the water, to be with my teammates, to spend one last semester in a boat - second to my health and academics and recovery - then I can do it. If I can't make that distinction, I can't row. I'm worried I can't, or that rowing will be a downward spiral. That's where my struggle is. Thank you for any advice you have 3
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Binge Eating...how to stop a cycle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 19:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't have a single binge for 6 months and now I had 8 binges in 3 weeks.....What are some strategies to use to get back on track? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Do you think my student has an eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 19:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a high school teacher, teaching at a new school this year. I've grown really close with a student recently and I'm concerned she has an eating disorder. Of course, it could just be normal girl things, but I wouldn't know. She sits in my office with me and my officemate during her lunch period, but she doesn't eat anything. She just drinks no calorie liquids. She also talks about food. A lot. I know what she's eaten 4/5 days of the week for her breakfast. She doesn't ever tell me what she eats for dinner though, only that she skips a lot of  meals. Occasionally, she'll buy something low calorie from the cafeteria, but she usually doesn't eat all of it. 
She also drinks 4-6 cups of coffee in the morning (she's only in high school!) and sometimes gets disoriented from all the caffeine. I've brought up with her that I'm concerned about her eating, and she mostly laughs it off, but she is concerned that I am concerned. I don't think she's actually concerned about her eating, just that I am aware of it. She has told me that she's going to stop talking about food because I pointed out she talks about it a lot, but she can't seem to stop. She's not underweight, either a healthy weight or just above, but I'm still worried. From what I've shared, do you think I'm right in assuming she has an eating disorder or that one is developing?

Thanks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to recover from an episode of binge eating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 19:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a big binge yesterday. I tracked every calorie in MyFitnessPal. I've struggled with anorexia, orthorexia, and other body image disorders for the last five years.

I essentially I ate several days worth of calories in the span of 12 hours. I feel disgusting. I just want to know how to get over this particular episode because I'm confident that I won't ever do this to myself again.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> request: how do I prevent my dormant AN from both re-emerging and becoming more dangerous? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 12:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't been underweight or extremely restricted my diet for about 3 years, after 4 years of dealing with anorexia. I'd sort of considered it over and done with because I've been able to eat most foods without feeling a crazy amount of guilt or counting calories and because I am physically healthy and fit. But certain thoughts, feelings, and behaviors resurface. Recently, I've been working quite a lot with long stretches between meals, and when I get hungrier and hungrier during the workday, it instantly sends me back to when feeling hungry was a reward. The reason I describe this as dangerous is that it has resulted in me fainting - multiple times in multiple unacceptable environments. This has me really concerned with my long-term health and wondering how I can stop it from getting worse. I technically eat enough in a given day, but apparently my body is more sensitive to lack of food, probably because of my history with AN. How can I keep this eating disorder at bay and prevent it from coming back and/or really destroying me in the long-term? Are there any mental/dietary exercises that could help? Articles or resources that could help me better understand AN?

Without delving into my life story, I should add that I never received professional treatment for AN and there are few people in my life who know about it (or, if they know, they don't know how extensive it was). Because of this I haven't developed much of a medical/academic/professional understanding of the disorder other than moderate research.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Slipping again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 02:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if this is the right subreddit but during May-August I had an eating disorder. I lost a large amount of weight and was pretty happy, even if I was still obese. I got therapy at the end of August and I was pretty much recovered. However, I gained some of the weight back. I've tried losing it the healthy was but it just won't work. I've been trying for months and I have only gained weight. I am so close to going back to my ways of the summer, but I know it's not what's best. 

Please help, I don't know what to do. I'm still obese but I want to be healthy.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research: Recruiting for a study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 17:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! My name is Evan and Im from a Harvard University research team that studies the thoughts and feelings that motivate self-harm behaviors among individuals with eating disorders, anxiety, and other related mental health issues.

We are interested in recruiting people who use this subreddit to participate in our (Institutional Review Board approved) study. This study will be completed online over the course of one month and participation is completely voluntary. People who are interested in participating will be compensated up to $50 in online gift cards to Amazon.

You can learn more about our study and complete the brief (about one minute) eligibility screener here: http://projects.iq.harvard.edu/smartphonestudy/study-ad#

Please feel free to private message me at /u/HarvardPhoneStudy if you have any questions.
Thank you so much for your consideration! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: how long will it take for my metabolism to recover? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 14:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello there,

I'm in ED recovery right now (anorexia for several years on/off), and have been able to slowly increase my caloric intake over the last two months. So, I know I shouldn't weigh myself during recovery, but while I'm still around a few hundred calories under the amount that I should be able to eat to hold my weight, I'm already starting to gain weight (slowly). I've moved to just over the lower limit of "underweight"...I don't think it's water retention because it has been going up so slowly, but I don't know. It just seems as if my metabolism is still so damaged that it isn't able to cope with the "surplus". 

How long does it take for metabolism to recover? Is it possible that it won't ever do so fully?

Note: I have an underactive thyroid, but the last blood test showed that with the pills I take, the hormones are balanced right now.

Thanks for your responses!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My girlfriend is developing anorexia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 14:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend is developing anorexia. For the past few months she has been tracking her calorie intake with the app MyFitnessPal, with her life revolving around calorie intake. She gets visible upset if she goes near her "recommended" goal, which is a small number of calories, even though she should definitely eat more. Just today she went for a 8 mile run. She has lost body fat, most noticeably her with breasts and butt shrinking. I don't need any more proof that she is anorexic, but I can't get her to admit that she is damaging her body.

I've come here to hopefully gain other people's opinions to hopefully help her in a more discrete way, as a last ditch effort before her family learns.

She has not lost weight per say, which confuses me, but she has literally every symptom of anorexia nervosa. I just need help to help her, mostly for someone other than myself to warn her about what's she's doing.

I apologize for being vague, but she is underweight or at least at the edge, and definitely not eating enough due to the stress in her life right now.

I just need someone to confirm that she has something that at the very least resembles anorexia, so that it doesn't look like i'm the crazy one. She's crying for help in her own subtle ways, and even got me to write this.

Thank you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I think my girlfriend is developing an eating disorder and i don't know what to do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 21:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend hasn't eaten for several days and she says even looking at food makes her feel physically sick. I've tried to talk to her about it and convince her to try and stop but she gets defensive and keeps saying there's nothing wrong. She wont admit that its starting to become a problem and i feel like i need to tell someone, but she says if i tell anyone she will never trust me again and she wont speak to me. When we have spoken about it she says she feels guilty when she eats and shes worried that if she eats anything she wont be able to stop. She thinks that its a good thing that she doesn't want to eat anymore. I think she's in denial about how serious this is and she needs help but i'm worried that she'll resent me if i do tell someone. 

How am i supposed to deal with this without upsetting her?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Sister struggling with bulimia, our parents turn a blind eye and get angry towards her. Advice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 21:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed my sister (let's call her Jill) unhealthily losing weight a couple of years ago, as she was on the wrestling team and trying to make weight for her highschool competitions. I had a feeling about what was happening when my sister would disappear into the bathroom for long periods of time, but I did not confront her. My best friend and roommate at the time had been on the same wrestling team, and was battling with bulimia and severe depression also. Though I was not sure if this was the case for Jill and I was afraid of making her feel bad. In retrospect, I wish I had come to her sooner.

Recently, Jill came forward and admitted that she was a compulsive liar growing up. First, lying about the simplest things that make no difference in our daily lives. Then it became worse, like telling family members I had an abortion when I did not. I didn't feel angry, just sad and I told her I really appreciated her coming forward and I want to do whatever I can to help her. She then admitted to being bulimic for the past couple years. She wanted help, but when she brought it up to Mom and Dad they both flipped out, saying it was her fault and if she wants to do something about it she has to do it herself.

Jill has been silently struggling ever since, and I have been urging her to go to the doctor. I am about an hour away in University, but she is home still in highschool. I recently told her that I would bring her to the doctor, and get referred to a therapist. The only problem in money, and insurance. We get about 80 percent coverage on our health plan, but it is under our parents and they wont even take a second to listen about her problems. We are currently living in Canada, and there is a hope clinic nearby which has programs for people with eating disorders. That is what I am hoping we can get her into.

Just wondering if anyone has any opinions on a plan or a way for me to get the info from my parents, or if theres a loophole where I can act as her guardian (I am 21 going on 22, Jill is 17)

She will be coming to the same University as me next september, where they offer free counselling and health services- but we cannot wait that long.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Concerned for a long distance friend that has been undereating for 11 months </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 08:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently (a month ago) got into contact with someone that I've grown quite fond of. He's 15 years old, and based on some information he has shared with me, I'm very worried about his eating habits. These are my reasons:

* He admits to severely undereating since January of this year (so 11 months now). 

* He counts calories and attempts to zero them out with exercise. I'm not familiar with his exercising (such as when or what types) except that it's only a tool for weight loss.

* He began as overweight. According to the chart in the sidebar, it seems his current weight is healthy, but his goal weight (he has a range he believes would be acceptable) would be slightly underweight.

I've confronted him about how he plans to maintain his weight loss once he reaches his "goal," and his answer is that he'll simply continue doing what he's already doing.

His motivations are varied. One, he wants to be "smaller" than his boyfriend who is 3 years older than he is. Being slightly larger than his boyfriend bothers him significantly. Two, he's bullied at school, partly due to his weight. From what I've gathered, the bullying isn't overtly physical but emotional and passive; however, it is a daily occurrence. Third, I asked at the end of a rather emotional conversation about this topic if there were any other reasons for what he does, and he simply said "to prove people wrong." I think this references bullies but also his ex-boyfriend who he has mentioned was very abusive.

I've attempted to encourage my friend to approach his parents, friends, his boyfriend, or adults at his high school, but so far those attempts have not proven successful. He does hide his eating habits from his family and friends, though his boyfriend is aware of the under eating but doesn't press the topic. Regarding his parents, his relationship with them is not very positive so relying on them is not something I view as a viable option for further suggestion.

Why I'm requesting this post is to get advice on the effects his eating habits have or will have on his body, any creative ways I can help him even though I'm long distance from him (beyond just being available to talk), and if there are any resources he might be able to reach out to outside of his friends or family for help to lose weight healthily or to seek therapy. 

As a last note, I do know where he lives and could contact his boyfriend, a "close-ish" friend of his from his school, his parents, or the police in his city if I chose to, but doing so would likely lead to him cutting off contact with me.

Any help or advice is appreciated, even if there are small things for him to improve on, or steps that you can suggest. My heart breaks that I can't be there with him to help him, but that doesn't mean I'm willing to just ignore the problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Newly Married. Husband is suffering from Bulimia and i dont know what to do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 08:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really need help and some insight into my husband's bulimia. He originally suffered from it over 10 years ago and it has now returned. I've tried looking online but would love help from this community. 

I met my husband early this year and we had a whirlwind romance and got married quiet quickly. His bulimia started again a few months ago. He was very unhappy in his job and was struggling to find another, there was stress from planning our wedding and new home, and him and I also had some issues of our own.

We are now married and living together, he has found a new job that he enjoys, but the bulimia is still there. He binges every single night and then purges. I'm very careful with the way I approach him because anytime I've tried to bring it up he gets defensive. I've never made him feel bad or confronted him (I clean up the bathroom and never say a word). 

Another major point is our sex life. When we first met it was great, now it is pretty much non-existent. I went through the stages of thinking that its me, before finally realising that it might be the eating disorder. If any men can give any insight on this it would be greatly appreciated. I should add that he used to go to the gym and eat right religiously but that has also ceased. 

I know that his bulimia isnt due to body image only, but personal issues that he's gone through in life. I'm trying to be as loving and supportive as possible. But I don't know how patient I should be before I really intervene as I'm worried for his health. He takes tablets for the acid but that's all I know of. 

I'm struggling because I haven't known him for a long time so I don't know the best way to approach him and make him feel better. I've thought about speaking to his brother who knows about the bulimia to ask how he overcame it last time but I'm afraid because my husband will see that as a betrayal of trust if he ever found out. 

Is intervening the right thing to do? What options do I have? Please help. Any advice and insight would be greatly appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I help a friend with pica? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 03:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend often eats inedible things like plastic, sand, and glass, and they can't help it. Is there an efficient way to offer them support? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Girlfriend was treated AN as a teenager however she seems to be relapsing with over-exercise/restriction and now wants to weight lift with me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 22:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend was treated for AN when she was 16 in an inpatient facility. She had struggled with it for several years however had recovered pretty well as far as I am aware. She is now 21 and we live together (I'm 27). She used (one year ago) to work a physical job on her feet all day in a factory and it was very physically demanding. When we started dating she had just moved to the city where I lived and gave up that job. That job naturally gave her a lot of exercise and she now works in an office rarely on her feet. It seems to me that she feels since she isn't on her feet that she has to make up for it by exercising. 

Everything was fine up until about six months ago. It used to be fine as she would exercise a normal amount and she would eat a healthy amount of food and not really count calories or watch what she ate. However slowly she has increased the amount of time she runs for and started counting calories and switching all the foods she eats to the low calorie alternatives. We used to go out to eat pretty frequently but now its pretty rare as she feels bad if we do and must over-exercise. Now she only eats food that is low on calories and its nearly impossible to get her to take a break from exercising. 

She is currently at a healthy weight but is restricting her calories and has been losing weight. She's always been open about the eating disorder and what she eats and I don't want to change that by confronting her about my concern. 

What has worked so far is that she tells me everything she's had to eat that day and I add up the calories based on what she and show her that she is not eating enough even without the exercise and that's worked for now but I know there will be a time when she will still feel she needs to exercise or she will start telling me she ate something and she didn't. Both will be bad. 

Her mother has also expressed concern about her eating and exercising habits so I know I'm not the only one who see the problem. 

I am about to start weight lifting again and I am pretty knowledgeable in the nutrition side of it and she has expressed interest in joining me. Which I could see as an opportunity to use to get her to eat to gain weight and muscle to take advantage of the weight lifting. However my concern is she will add cardio on top of the weight lifting or she will still continue to restrict her calories. Advice?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I know I need inpatient treatment but I am afraid to be away from everything I know and care about </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 20:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm SO nervous. I have had an ED for around 4 or 5 years and have been underweight for most of it. I was hospitalized multiple times. I had to quit my job because of it and was put on disability payments because of that combined with depression/anxiety and a rare form of cancer (that's a story for another sub/post though). 

For about 3 years now I have been seeing a therapist/social worker about it, and I made some progress, but I am no longer getting better. I actually may or may not be getting worse again. So my therapist has suggested she make a referral for me to an inpatient treatment center.

Okay, fine. But HERE'S THE PROBLEM... The center is a 6 hour drive from my house in a different city. The program is 90 days long. I have a boyfriend that lives near me and a dog that lives with me.

My boyfriend is literally the most amazing man in the world I love him so damn much it hurts, and he has done nothing but support me and love me and make me laugh and make me happy through our whole relationship. He is amazing and I don't deserve him. He has a great job, a great car, he is smart and understanding and patient. I am SO SCARED about being away from him for 3 months. I would miss him terribly, he would miss me terribly, and I'm worried he would get overwhelmed with me being gone for so long and break up with me. Or break up with me for other reasons, like the reason I'm gone or the fact that I'm so far away or that he can't have sex for 3 months or like whatever. There are so many reasons for him to just leave me. I'm scared of that.

Now, for my dog. He is THE LOVE OF MY LIFE. He's a black lab named Zep and he's amazing. He's my best friend. He's gotten me through the darkest and hardest and saddest times in my life. He's been with me at my worst. We have routines we do every day, like his bedtime snack and stuff like that, and he sleeps in my bed and we cuddle every night. He hates it when I go somewhere without him, and I hate it too. 

Would he forget me if I left him with my parents for 3 months? Wouldn't he miss me? Would he be mad at me? I can't sleep at night without him in my bed. What would I do, just go 90 days without sleep? I just cannot be without my dog. I can't see that happening.

On the other hand, I can't get better. I need help. I can't live with this ED forever.

Any advise? Anyone at all? I don't know what to do. I feel lost and confused. Any advise or really any comment is appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I asked for help and didn't get it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 10:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My therapist said she won't be very concerned about my ED unless I become underweight.
I'd have to restrict for a month before I get to that point. But I'm so sick and I'm suffering so much. I just want someone to help me. Why do I have to get worse before I get better? How can I get help if my therapist doesn't think it's serious enough? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I help a friend with bulimia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 23:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend struggles with bulimia. I'm really worried. She already damaged her digestive system. What should I do?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Disordered eating during and after pregnancy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 23:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering about the experience of others with pregnancy and post partum.

I have BED and did really well with therapy and a medically supervised eating program before falling pregnant and the struggled with lapses into overeating, eating in secret, etc during pregnancy until I was diagnosed with GDM. 

Post-pregnancy, my eating has never been worse with almost daily binges. It's just been such a struggle to bring structure back and make healthful choices. I'd love to hear how there have fared, and if you have any advice for me. Did you have to go back to therapy?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Friend trying to battle food addiction. Concerned about them developing ED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 23:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,

so, I have this friend. We are not really that close, but we do share one experience that makes us particularly close to each other: we both have invisible illnesses.

One year ago my friend (who is overweight, but not obese) started a project to loose weight within the next 1,5 years to a number that would maybe maker her happy. Is has been going well, if one considers her illness and her circumstances. She herself says it's a food addiction (would this be classified as ED?) and that she goes to food for comfort, which she needs sometimes because of her illness. She made some healthy lifestyle changes. She's on a good track, with a few bumps. In August, for example, she gained weight instead of losing it, which caused her to be quite anxious about losing her progress, but otherwise managed to stick to her plan.

But this month was her birthday and she did get a lot of chocolate and did eat a lot of it. She gained weight, again, and this seems to have put her in a somewhat desperate place. Today she told me that she not only has started changing her meal plan drastically, but that she also has started to take appetite suppressant pills.

And I am becoming anxious. I have had friends in the past who dealt with anorexia and I remember that friend starting out similar. Still, I am not sure if and how I should intervene, seeing as I personally feel as if I have little authority on the subject of ED and weight loss (never had any experiences with both subjects myself). I do come from a family with a lot of overweight people, who are quite happy and don't care too much about their weight. I might lack the perspective of someone with ED/food addition and a heavy body, but I do feel as if there must be something I should say. I am afraid my friend idolizes weight loss because of her mental illness and strive for it on this way to feel happier once she is there, though she does not seem as someone who would ever be satisfied with herself. She has a very low opinion about herself, especially about her body and the way she generally looks. Maybe I am overly anxious because I have seen people drift into ED only after losing weight instead of being happy with the end result.

I am not sure if this post fits this board. I am just looking for input from more experienced people on how to approach this topic with my friend, what signs to look out for and how to be a good friend to her, as she has been to me.

Thank you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Sore teeth in AN Recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 23:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi. I've had very severe anorexia for a very long time and have gone through multiple cycles of inpatient and refeeding. At present I am trying to weight restore from a underweight BMI outside of hospital for the first time. I'm used to dealing with most of the side-effects that go along with this process but I'm struggling with something I've not dealt with before: really sore teeth. It's not related to hot or cold. Many foods, even softer foods, are really unpleasant and uncomfortable. Does anyone have advice for dealing with this? Are there foods that might minimize this side effect? My teeth aren't particularly sensitive to hot or cold, but just to the act of chewing itself?

Any guidance on this matter would be much appreciated. Thanks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I help my mother with BN? She is resorting to her past behaviors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 16:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I have a question for individuals who have made strides in their recovery of BN. I'm looking for ways I could help/support my mother.

My mother (52F) has been struggling with BN for her adult life. She had kept it a secret for the first ~20 years of her marriage with my father (58M), but took a leave of absence from work to attend an intensive group therapy for ED three years ago (she realized after taking care of my brother who was diagnosed with AML that she had an issue that needed professional help). It was a ~16 week program through the provincial government and she felt during it that she was doing very well and she was more open about it.

I know that part of her program involved her regularly seeing a therapist for her ED and relationship troubles and I think this helped a lot. 

I think she would benefit greatly by seeing a therapist again but a year ago my father had a cardiovascular event which caused him to be placed upon long term disability, and since this happened she has fully taken over the role as primary provider and housekeeper (I try my best to help but I get home after her) for our family. She doesn't have much free time during the day to attend therapy sessions, nor do I think she would want to (I'm not sure on the exact details of her previous therapy sessions but they very difficult emotionally and she also had a lot of negative emotions brought up in her marriage counseling sessions).

But since I've moved back home to finish my second degree I've noticed more signs that she has been slipping into her old ways. I've told her (in private, no one else knows) what I've noticed and she admits that she still does every once in a while (I'm unsure of the frequency, but I know it is less then before she went into her program). 

I'd like to note that she has told me that she has a large problem with constantly eating when food is present (if she is watching the tube with my father) or if she is knitting in the den. I'd love to go shopping (I'm very practical when it comes to buying food, no frills for me just the things required for the meals) but since my father is at home all day, he does most of the shopping and my mom does some on her way home.

I would like any sort of help/guidance that I could give to my mother in order to help her reign her BN back in check. It is very hard for me to see my mother struggle with BN because I know she has faced a lot of adversity in almost every aspect of life and through this she has developed an aura of confidence and pride that is infectious. But it's painful to see and hear her say how much she hates herself for falling into her old habits and how she wishes she could put it all behind her.

How can I help her?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: At my wits end but am worried sick about losing my best friend. What else can I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 15:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My best friend has a severe ED. She is honest with me about the fact that she restricts severely, abuses diuretics, exercises compulsively, and purges just about every day (because I've struggled with anorexia myself and I understand). 

She's over 18 and I live over 150 miles away. I've said all the "right things" and I'm consistently supportive, but there are no magic words and she won't see a doctor because she says she's not thin enough for it to matter. Her mother knows, but they don't live together and she has no idea how severe it is. I don't know how helpful she would be, anyway. 

In the past she's been a huge advocate for recovery, but things have been hard lately and she no longer seems to want to get better. I'm honestly afraid I'm going to lose her. Is there ANYTHING else I can do? If she gets any worse, I'm going to regret being a bystander for the rest of my life. I can't lose her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My weight loss turned into disordered behavior. Now I'm chewing and spitting, and it's out of control. How do I start to recover? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 00:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've dealt with this for the past four years. 

After healthily losing weight in September 2009, I started using diet products to keep the weight off. Eventually I started throwing up until I was discovered by my mother and friends so I read about chewing and spitting which is what I struggle with now. 

It has reached a point where I have spent thousands of dollars of food to simply dispose of. This has made it worse because I simply put it in the trrash, the garage, and my neighbour's trash can which has resulted in a putrid smell. I really want to stop but I have no idea how, I have caused my mother and my friends (who know about my problem) untold grief and I am sick of hurting them. I just want to stop but I do not know how...

What do I need to do to break this habit?

What kind of resources are available for this specific disordered behaviour? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I am making progress in recovery, but is it a good idea to help a classmate who is struggling with mental health problems? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 00:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had bulimia on and off from ages 12 to 19, then at 19 I had developed a severe perfectionist mentality. This is when things took a turn for the worst. Since that time [currently 22] I've gone from using behaviors a few times a day to once a month. I was diagnosed with anxiety/depression and was in therapy for two years and made a lot of progress. I recently moved away to school to get my Phd in biophysics. I have never felt happier than I do now, however there is a girl in my class who is not dealing with the stress of our first year as well. I do not believe she has an ED, but rather issues with self harm. I want to reach out and help her, but just thinking about bringing up all my old issues has caused me to have a slip up today. 

How can I help someone else when I still have trouble controlling my compulsions?

Are there ways to take care of myself when someone else's struggles are impacting me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post Request: Avoiding an Eating Disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 22:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I might be developing an ed. I have depression, so i didn't eat well, but now I'm starting to get better from that and eating better. But, I've been gaining weight, just a few lbs (still underweight) but I'm scared of gaining more and more. I've always been very thin just naturally, and I feel like it's a part of my identity or something and I'm scared and angry about losing that and becoming "normal". I've already started eating less on purpose. I don't want to spiral down this path, but I don't know how to stop it. I'm worried nobody will take me seriously. Sorry if this was too long.

Can anyone offer advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I eat normally in college while I am in recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 20:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a very bad eating disorder during my sophomore year of high school that included anorexic behavior. I underate until hunger hormones took hold and for a year I was caught in a cycle of binging and restricting, and later just occasionally binging. I gained back all of the weight I had lost and am now overweight.

Towards the end of high school I was eating well most of the time because the food in my home was very healthy. However, I'm now at college and am facing several issues.

I would like to focus on getting my body healthy. However, my school is fairly small and only has one dining hall, and the food here is...not so great. The food options are unhealthy and the healthier options are very limited, which I fear will leave me bored.

I have a job but most of my money goes to tuition and my family can't afford to send me a lot, so eating outside of the dining hall is at most a twice a week deal.

My problem is that when I'm not being healthy and eating healthy, I'm triggered and start to have major body issues, and resort to purging or binging. I just don't know how to eat healthy and not spend money here. I'm too tempted by all the bad foods and even though I try to work in healthier options as much as I can it's hard.

It's hard for me to stay on track if I have a slip up and tend to suffer with black and white thinking, seeing the day as ruined if I've strayed. I don't know how to exit this mindset.

Any help with any of these issues would be really appreciated. 

How can I get back to normalized and healthy eating given my circumstances? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: When is it time to go home? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 03:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a current freshman in college in recovery from anorexia and only a few pounds away from full weight restoration. College has turned out to be a great experience for me, I am happier and more socially connected than I have ever been before however the eating disorder is still an issue. I have a treatment team that I see almost weekly at the local children's hospital and I have weekly phone sessions with my therapist from home. A few weeks ago, my team wanted to send me home or admit me because my vitals were bad, but I convinced them to keep me here on the conditions that if I lose any weight or fail to gain for 2 consecutive weeks I will be sent home. I have a really great team and they have made it very clear that they want what is best for me and none of this should be seen as punitive and they always make sure to recognize progress that I make and set realistic goals.

Its hard, but right now I have been eating my meals, drinking my supplements (ensure plus) and abstaining from exercise because I want to stay in school so badly. I've started to have anxiety around meals because I want to stay so badly even though eating is uncomfortable and I don't want to do it. I worry that my desire to stay in school could cloud my judgement of what is best for me, especially since I am over 18 so I can stop seeing my team whenever I want to, and my parents can't be involved without my consent. 

Besides the obvious scary medical things, what do you guys see as signs that somebody needs to return home or to treatment? I tend to minimize things and have never thought of myself as "sick enough" (despite spending a month and a half of last year in residential treatment and needing weekly medical evaluations).

I'm scared of falling "off the wagon" because I want to so badly but I know that I will not be able to stay in school if I do not.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Scared to go to college (I don't want to slip back) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 03:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm considering attending an art school a few hours away from home. They'll be making me board with them due to the distance. I'm worried that without my best friend and boyfriend around I will relapse in self harm or start up with my ED again (I've had EDNOS on and off for about 4 years now, it doesn't get nearly as bad anymore but I still have some tendencies of starvation). The two of them tend to keep me in check with my eating habits and notice if I'm avoiding eating. My boyfriend and I will most likely be breaking up at some point if I go as well so I know I'll be unstable for some time. I don't have self control without someone who cares around. 

Has anyone gone away to school or dealt with something similar? How can I keep myself from falling back? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Anorexia recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 11:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need all the help I can get from you guys on Anorexia recovery. I am trying to do away with my food obsession/food restriction. I want to work with doctors and nutritionalists but I can't afford those resources. I like to workout everyday, and have always been active been before my ED (played sports my whole life). How much should I be eating? I want to listen to hunger cues but I don't think they're accurate anymore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I suspect my coworker may have some sort of ED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 11:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope this is the right place to ask what I can/should do to help, if anything.

My recently hired coworker is throwing off some signs that make me wonder if she struggles with an ED. I don't know her nearly well enough to straight up ask her (I suspect that's not a great idea anyway?) and am not really sure its my place to do anything about it, but I feel like I can't just let her hurt herself if she truly does have a problem.

Why do I (and others) suspect she has an ED?

* Every time she eats a meal, she immediately or soon after excuses herself to go the restroom for a longer-than-typical time.
* I'm told the women's bathroom often has poorly-cleaned up vomit in it...started showing up after she started. 
* I've had coworkers over to my house for lunch. After we ate she used my bathroom and I later noticed food particulate on the toilet bowl. 
* She's fainted before and has issues with vertigo
* She has some throat and voice problems
* She's not like crazy skinny, but she's definitely not overweight either.

Now, to be fair, some things detract from my theory...she eats a completely normal amount of food, that I see. She complains about "getting fat" like a lot of people do, including myself, but doesn't seem overtly focused on the issue (and she appears to be a normal weight, idk how much she actually weighs of course). In my home scenario, the bathroom is close enough to where the rest of us were that in theory we would hear someone throwing up...is it possible to silently throw up??

Like I said, I don't know if its my place to do/say anything. Maybe I'm way off base and she's just been struggling with illness these first few months or there's some underlying medical issue I don't know about at play. But I'm hoping there's something we could do to encourage her to seek help if she actually does happen to have an ED?

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Hello, I was looking for advice on talking to a friend with an ED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 03:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm new to college, first year there. I met this really nice girl who is a bit underweight, but very pretty. She has told me that she has bulimia over time. At first she was only saying she had an eating disorder in the past, then eventually said bulimia as the specifics, and then admitted she is still doing so "often". I am transgender, and have also told her that I self harm sometimes, but I am trying to stop as well.

To be honest, I do not know a whole lot about bulimia other than the basics. I wanted to know how I should approach her about it more often with the correct phrasing and wording to help her. To me, saying something like "you look great!" or "you could gain a few lbs even!" seems correct, but I have a feeling that it could come off wrong but I don't know what is the better way to word things. How can I help someone who has these kinds of issues?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to talk to a dentist... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 03:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've recently become much better with my bulimia (very rare occurrences typically only when extremely stressed) and know I need to go see a dentist. The bottoms of my teeth are a little chipped, and in my mind, extremely noticeable. My boyfriend and close friends (who know the cause of it) all say it isn't bad and you can't see it. I just want to go in and get them either filed or I think they do a kind of tooth coloured capping cement for small chips. I want to be upfront about the issue so they can make the most well informed decision, but I have no idea where to start. Any help would be most appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Looking for a support network. How to meet people to help you get over BED? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 19:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last year, I developed a very bad relationship, and ever since winter break, I have been binging, and exercising to try and compensate for all the food I ate (which usually never compensates) and occasional try and purge sessions (which have become more frequent). 

I have injured myself many times due to over exercising, and I know if I keep this up, I wont be able to run soon. I am in college, and since I started developing a bad relationship with food, I have alienated myself from my friends. 

I really need someone to talk to, someone to help me out, but I really dont know anyone, and since I am a guy, it is very embarrassing. I do not want to tell my family (although they know I love food, and overeat often). 

I was just wondering, how could I meet someone at my school to help me get over this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Eating disorder is back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 13:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been in recovery for bulimia for several years and I am doing very well. Of course I had the typical binging, fasting and purging but I also used exercise as a method of punishing myself for not being thin enough.

As part of my recovery I was encouraged to stop counting calories, monitoring my food and exercising, I complied and after several years I became a bit overweight. For the past few months I have been working on taking that weight off. I set a healthy daily calorie goal and focused on eating more veggies and meats than I was before. I'm now at a healthy weight and dont intend to loose any more. My relationship with food and exercise has changed dramatically. Eating doesnt make me as anxious as it used to and I dont binge anymore, if I want something calorie dense one day I'll indulge in a little bit but not enough that I'll feel the need to purge.

My workouts make me feel good and strong rather than drained and weak. I feel like my healthy eating and workouts are part of taking care of myself rather than punishing myself. I feel like I've adopted healthy behaviors but since I've reached this weight the "ED" persona has been a lot more vocal. I've been thinking about fasting or working out more and I've started fighting the old behaviors again and I'm worried about a relapse. I didnt have these urges a couple months ago and I'm very surprised to be dealing with this after all the progress I've made. Has anyone else had this issue and how did you deal with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been struggling with food for 3 years. Where can I turn for help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 06:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To preface this, I want to say I've never been diagnosed with an ED, but I went to treatment (for depression, long unrelated story) and had a pretty good look at what I feel I am currently dealing with.

When I was younger, my mother was very abusive and often used food as a weapon. We also ONLY ate fast food. I mean three meals a day. I fluctuated with weight a bit but was always on the thinner side until high school.

I was 16 when I got the first "wave". I ate only 1-1.5 meals a day worked out CONSTANTLY. Really more like snacks. I dropped a significant amount of weight (from technically overweight to technically normal weight) in about 3 or 4 months.

When I went in for depression treatment  when I was also 16, they put me on a lot of pills that equated ,to me gaining a lot of weight back. I was doing ok until last year and I lost several sizes in about 4 months.

I HATE food. I want to stomp on it, burn it, yell at it, and just crucify it. I get super anxious whenever my bf forces me to eat. I try to eat oatmeal in the morning and something at night, but I just don't want to be fat again.

It's so hard to describe how I feel. I don't really know how much to eat or when or what. I'm very lost and confused.

I want to get better because I love my boyfriend very, very much and I want to be able to enjoy life with him. I know I'm bitchier and more tired, but I can't.

What resources can I turn to? I have insurance, but I'm 20 with zero financial support from any parental people. What I make is not a lot. I don't know what to do anymore. I am very overwhelmed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My GF told me about her eating disorder, how can I help her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 17:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I(19) live in new york and my girlfriend (18) lives in europe. We've been going out since august but we had a thing since May. maybe a month or so ago she told me about her ED, and that she had never told anyone else, not her parents, friends, doctor, nobody except for me. 

She says she'll have long periods of time where she restricts to a dangerous level and her hunger cues have disappeared. almost 2 weeks ago she told me it was happening again. She hasn't been eating and the food she is consuming is making her physically sick. 

She told me she isn't purging as a behavior, but just looking at food makes her sick, and when she eats anything she can't keep it down. she told me tonight she hasn't been able to keep any food down in 2 weeks, and what she is able to consume is very little.

she was telling me the other day that she's been trying really hard to eat and that she managed to keep down a little, but based on what she told me tonight, i think she may have been sick with that later that day. 

I want to help her and I've been doing research on eating disorders and I want to say it's AN but I don't really know. Based on photos, it does seem as this is making her lose weight.

How can I help her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I recovered from AN 4 years ago. I'm still obsessed with food. How can I stop this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 18:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recovered from AN 4 years ago. The issue is, food was my coping mechanism before having an ED, and it is still a coping mechanism now. I'm still obsessed with food, organizing and storing foods, looking it up, comparing, thinking about it. I'll push other thoughts out of my mind to think about it and fantasize about eating it, especially when I'm nervous, insecure or wanting to clear my mind. I often prefer to eat by myself and if I've planned a meal I hate to deviate from it, but I do like to eat out as well and I'm a lot more relaxed than I have been in the past. People who get to know me will sometimes ask about my relationship with food. 

I don't feel like it will ever go away, or know how much it can go away - maybe it's something I'll always be stuck with, but as long as it's not dangerous, it's not a problem. :(

How can I stop this obsession?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to deal with a BED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 16:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, i am not currently seeing a therapist (they're expensive), and am wondering if i should.

When i was in year 12 (16 years old), I found it very stressful due to study and started paying attention to my weight. I found i was gaining weight and started eating restrictively on and off. The combination of both the stress, as well as the restrictive eating made me begin to binge eat. During this time, i wasn't motivated to study and found myself under a lot of stress. Near the end of this year, i forced myself to eat a lot more restrictively and found myself able to study all day. Becoming more and more restrictive in my eating behaviour, i eventually found myself as anorexic (and extremely skinny). I went to see a doctor as i had not had my period for about a year who told me that i had to gain weight. This also alerted my parents for this first time, as they were there with me. So, i did gain weight and ate normally for a few months.

However, after about a year, at my first year of University, I started binge eating (i think it was when i was stressed due to study). I met a fantastic person, my boyfriend, who supports me amazingly, however, when I am not with him, sometimes i lapse back into my former-self, losing control over myself, hearing voices convincing me to binge, and when i snap back into normality, i had already binged. I feel really guilty every time and this only happens when i am not with him. For example, once, when he was sleeping, the voice told me that it was okay to binge now because he didn't have to know, and that it would feel really good. That i could escape reality for a short while.

I just want to be able to eat normally and not think about food. To just live life like everybody else.

Any help or responses/kind words would be appreciated (this is the boyfriend and i'll relay any support)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My GF has recovered from bulimia but I worry her new habits are disordered - should I bring this up with her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 17:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend has always struggled with her weight and in the past has struggled with an eating disorder (bulimia). I have seen no signs of this and she claims to have not engaged in this behavior in years. She is however trying to follow a diet but it's very off and on. She will go a few days but end up on a binge.

My prime concern is how much she eats. She'll have a very small meal at breakfast and as far as I can tell doesn't eat anything else until 6pm when she will have a large meal. Her binges seem to be comprised of unhealthy foods. This seems to be a cycle she's caught in and I worry about her. 

Should I bring this up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I help motivate my adolescent GF through her AN? Do I tell her mom more information? I am feeling really lost. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 17:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, so I am 16 years old, male, and my GF (also 16) has had anorexia nervosa for about 6 months. It seems to be getting progressively worse and she is getting more lost as time passes.

She has told me all about her illness and how she feels. Like the voice in her head which she is best friends with and enemies with at the same time.

Right now, she says she is too tired to even try fighting her anorexia.

She takes in one quarter of the recommended calorie intake per day for her gender and age, which she is adamant is perfectly normal.

She goes to weekly counselling at the hospital (UK) and she tells me that it doesn't help her, and just makes her feel worse about herself. She also says she doesn't tell the nurses everything, which I'm sure is probably a bad thing.

She has also previously self harmed and attempted suicide.
Basically I want to know how I could motivate her to fight this and to try, because right now she is just embracing it. I comfort her as much as I can, but anytime I try to suggest something she shuts me out and doesn't listen.

Should I maybe tell her mother some things? Like how few calories she is taking in etc? Because I know she doesn't know those details.

Right now I am just lost and don't know how I can help. Someone please give me some ideas? 

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Would seeking a dietician be helpful? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 15:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my very first reddit post and first time on reddit. My husband has been on this site and has informed me that I may find more information here and assistance as opposed to facebook.

I wish food and I didn't hate each other! Have 11 freebies for my birthday and am so overwhelmed by it! Wish there was some magic off switch to the part of my brain that says "you cannot eat that" or "that's a lot of fat and carbs, so can't do that"...

I am debating seeing a nutritionist to get a meal plan going or to figure a plan. Whether I follow it or not is the question, but it would be easier then deeming all food as bad. A healthy relationship with food would be nice. Has anyone gone through this, Was it helpful?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I help my girlfriend with her BED? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 16:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend for the past 5 months has had BED, very rare purging. She goes to a therapist but it doesn't seem to help much. She is currently reading brain over binge piece by piece very little. It tends to be during more stressful times she will binge more. She wanted me to post this for her as well. 

What can i do to help her? And how can she help herself? Please respond, i care so much for her and only want her to be happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I think my girlfriend has an ED, what can I do to help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 04:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some context, we're in high school and have been dating a couple months. I've known this girl for almost a year now, and a few months ago she confessed to me that she that she wasn't actually a vegan like she'd been telling people, she was just using it as excuse to not eat when others were. Since we've started dating I've realized that it's a serious problem. She used to be overweight, but she's lost a significant amount since then. She appears to be at a healthy weight now, not underweight as far as I know, but she is still hardly eating and has body image issues.

I want to know how I can help her, or get her the help she needs. I've talked with her about this many times, but I don't know enough to be able to make real progress, and I'm afraid of doing something wrong and discouraging her. I've been able to get her to eat a few times, but she has difficulty digesting most foods now after having practically starved herself for so long. I know that professional therapy is probably what she needs, but how can I convince her to get it? Her mom knows she doesn't eat much but doesn't seem to realize how much of a problem it is.

I'm sorry if this is vague, but I'm lost on what to do and worried for her.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teens with bulimia recover faster when parents are included in treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 19:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to deal with seeing myself as I truly am in mirror reflections? I am small but see something else. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 19:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'm a 17 year old male and I have BED, anxiety, and depression. Even tho according to the chart on the sidebar, I'd fit one the small figure, whenever I look into the mirror all I see is fat. Sometimes this comes and goes, and mostly isn't there if I just purged. Although it's there most of the time. 

My question is, how do I get rid of this "anorexia mirror" and see myself as I truly am, because I'm sure my image doesn't actually change this often. As well as the reason why it happens in the first place? Thanks for reading this and for any help or support I get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Is developing healthy habits that fulfill my need for control okay? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 18:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently went vegan for ethical reasons and I've found that, as an unintended side effect, I don't feel the desire to restrict as strongly as I used to. I wouldn't say my attitude towards food is positive and I still worry about my weight a lot and have to force myself to eat sometimes, but I'm definitely doing a lot better than I was. Checking ingredients and having certain foods that are off limits is comforting and familiar to me too. Just being able to eat any food all willy nilly makes me feel out of control. I'm also working on goals around staying away from negative, being ok with gaining weight, and comparing myself to my sister.

So obviously this is a good thing because it's helped me to start eating again (I haven't restricted in almost a month), but what I'm wondering is, is it enough? Is it okay to just replace all my bad habits with healthier habits and call myself recovered? Or do I need to eliminate my need for control and to be better than my sister altogether to truly recover?

Whenever I tried to stop restricting in the past, I started having flashbacks of being sexually abused. I don't think I can separate my need to have absolute control over what I eat from my need to have absolute control over what happens to my body--period. Maybe this is just the little voice in my head that always needs to tell me that nothing I ever do it good enough talking. Or maybe this really isn't good enough. I can't tell. I just need somebody to tell me so I can either try to stop worrying about this and focus on my recovery or know that this isn't enough and...I don't know. I guess try to do more? I'm reluctant to try therapy because for me in the past it's only ever made things worse. I feel like even trying to let go of that control is only going to make me cling to it tighter and I might end up going back to restricting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to help my girlfriend during recovery? She is convincing herself she is not sick enough for further treatment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 17:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my girlfriend has had anorexia for almost 5 years. She had been living with and has had a very poor relationship with food and recently exercise. She feels the need to balance eating with over-exercise.

I got her to start going to a therapist around 3 months ago and the therapist has really helped her deal with some anxieties, but her relationship with food and exercise is still bad, but recently my girlfriend has started eating a bit more and exercising a lot less. I convinced her to go to a dietitian (hasn't seen the dietitian yet), but is now having severe anxiety towards the dietitian has gotten quite bad because she believes that because she is only a bit underweight, that the dietitian will think she is a liar. She believes that he dietitian will "laugh at her" and will tell her to leave. Now she is beginning to convince herself that she does not actually have an eating disorder because she is not severely underweight.

So i guess my question is really what can I tell her to comfort her in terms of the dietitian and her not being severely underweight, and what can I do to help her with this?

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My Best Friend Doesn't Listen To Me When It Comes To Her ED! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 02:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, A few months back i made a post about my best friend who is suffering with her eating disorder and a not so supportive boyfriend. I'm happy to report that she has dumped said boyfriend but is still struggling with her ED. I love this girl more than anyone on this planet and i just want to see her smile everyday. I have noticed and stated it to her that she just wants to be loved like most but she is not looking in the right places and letting men and others use her and in turn at times using me.

However she has been doing okay lately she has been eating well compared to the past but however i know her very well and she is not as fine as she says she is. She has fallen into a pattern of dating just sub-par men and although she thinks she's doing okay she is not as i know she is going to struggle with any rejection or feelings she obtains the only way she knows how.

She and i have started to go to the gym again after her avoiding it for years due to over-exercising in the past. I am keeping a careful eye on her because i refuse to let her take control of her exercising habits again.

My concern is that her father has returned to the picture and he is the core trigger of her ED. She gets these periods of time that last a week or two when he decides he wants to "fix" their relationship and i get thrown on the back burner and she won't allow me to be there for her and help and support her. She has coping mechanisms which include her ignoring the problem completely and distracting herself and it hurts me so much to see her do that to herself because when she sweeps things under the rug it all boils over eventually. I have tried inviting myself to her house and inviting her to mine so we can just relax and not let the ED become her support system as it often does. However it seems almost impossible to get her to relax as she is now working two jobs and is looking at returning to uni and it is clearly wearing her down.

I'm tired of stepping on eggshells with her and i am reaching out to those of you on here to see if there is a way i can go about this because although i may not be her boyfriend, i do love her and she is treating me like one, aside from her letting me be there night and day. I want to be better than the ED i want to fight for her but i don't know how to when she won't let me in, regardless of how many times i tell her she can trust me and she knows she can trust me but her actions are not at all following her words.

All suggestions are welcome especially from boyfriends of sufferers and those in recovery.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Questions on behalf of a loved one, how to know when it's safe to take the next steps in recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 10:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi. I have built up a relationship with a recovering anorexic girl, she does not know much about the reddit dynamic and I knew that it was a very good channel to seek out help for her.

I met her outside of my office adjacent to a treatment center roughly a year and a half ago and we've been keeping in touch since. She's been a recovering anorexic for about 3 years and she's regularly upset about not making enough progress recovering from her eating distorder. She went from daily counsel treament sessions to a month's residency to tackle her conditions and she's gone through a very frequent shift in seeing different physicians, nutritionists, trainers and psychologists that have contrasting opinions about her eating regimen/recovery process.

The other night she felt like she was going through a positive revelation with eating and wanted to discontinue sessions with her trainer so she could listen to her body tell her when to eat. She's currently seeing a trainer a few days a week and adheres to his strict diet schedule of daily caloric intake/exercise limits.

She's very dispirited in this process because eating her same scheduled calories every day(it's been four months of this process) curbing any intense activity propels her into wanting to abandon this process. Her family has grown fatigued with her and she's currently staying with me, I love her and I want to develop a deeper understanding to best be there for her.

What steps should we look into? Is staying with the trainer a good idea or should we consult a nutritionist? When is it safe to go back to eating normally after recovery? Thank you reddit.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: BED, depression, and poor communication is affecting my relationship with my wife. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 00:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife has had a BED problem since she was 16 (she's 32 now) which hits her in spurts. She can be fine for a few months, and then completely crash and binge for weeks in a row. She tries to hide it, but her mood during the day gives it away if she's binged or not. Normally, I just ask her how her day has been, which she normally replies with 'good' and changes subject. Sometimes she says she's had a bad day, and I ask her if there is anything she needs? She always says no.

Lately her binging has been getting really bad, with her becoming increasingly depressed. She sleeps in late every day, doesn't interact with the kids as well as she used to, neglects her share of the house work, and has increasingly been less and less communicative with me.

I have mentioned several times over the past year that we should go and see an eating disorder specialist, or attend group meetings, and she has always just said 'no.' However, since things have been getting so bad lately, I've been insisting on it more. She doesn't give me any reason to not wanting to get help, but does tell me that she can do this on her own. I have my doubts, mainly because she's been at this for over 15 years.

Our relationship has gotten bad lately. We've stopped talking to each other. We haven't had sex for a month (we even had our third anniversary last week). She's always depressed. I sat down with her two nights ago, and laid my feelings on the line. I told her that she needs to get help, and the effect her depression and eating disorder is having on our relationship, and she just sat in silence. I came home from work late last night and asked her if she had given our previous nights conversation any thought, and she told me she had, but indicated that she's still not interested in seeking help. I don't get it, I lost my cool and I yelled at her. She left the room and disappeared downstairs, and I slept alone. This morning she didn't say two words to me before she left to work.

I regret losing my temper on her, and I've never raised my voice at her before. However, I feel that my feelings are being completely ignored. I can't understand why, with our relationship and happiness on the line, that she still refuses to start a meaningful process to recovery. I feel that I'm being asked to just 'sit this one out' and let my wife continue her destructive behavior on her own time. I've never had an eating disorder or depression before, and I do struggle with understanding what such a negative relationship with food feels like. She doesn't share her emotions with me, so all my opinions on what she's going through are speculative at best.

I love her, and I love our family, but I'm scared about the direction we are heading. However, I must insist on us getting her the help she needs, but she flat out refuses. What is my next move? Do I have a next move? Why is she so against making strides to help such a painful part of her life, and why won't she talk to me about it?

Any advice is appreciated.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to initiate physical intimacy with SO of 1 year suffering from an ED? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 21:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My SO of 1 year is recovering from an eating disorder and has had amenorrhea for the past one and a half years. We cuddle and make out but we have not had sex as of yet as I am afraid to initiate as I can tell that she has a low libido. 

How do i approach my desire for physical intimacy without affecting her recovery? I am concerned about telling her that i love her body, as she still needs to put on more weight to be healthy again. Also, is it possible for her to enjoy sexual stimulation and have orgasms while she is underweight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Try, try again - Need Advice for Developing a Healthy Lifestyle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 21:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 27 years old. Over the last few years I've been to counselling on the NHS twice and privately once - ended up getting nowhere. I've tried a few times to settle into a 'normal', healthy routine of eating and exercise at consistent times since starting work full time after Uni 5 years ago, but I'm having difficulty.

I find my motiviation to change highest in the morning, but often wane as the day goes on and find it increasingly difficult towards the evening. The thing I struggle most with is the routine - eating the same amount, doing the same amount of exercise. Doing the same things at the same times. Without this I tend to feel lost. Does anyone have any tips/advice/things which have worked for them which make things easier?

I'm hoping to find a way to just enjoy a ready meal and a generally healthy diet instead of stressing about every detail - what I'm eating, when I'm eating, who'll be there, whether it has too many calories, whether I'll enjoy it etc etc.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Anyone have experience with Prozac as part of treatment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 21:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently on only new 25mg of prozac everyday. I was anorexic and now bulimic. I was told prozac could help. So I'm just curious if prozac has helped anyone? I have a high tolerance, but I I'd love to hear other people's opinion about prozac. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I manage my sister with bulimia moving in with me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 23:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am looking for practical advice. My (25F) sister (21) has had bulimia for around 8 years. She has been living with my parents, and things got progressively worse until they now just pretty much live with it. 

As many people will know, like with any addiction, the whole family becomes ill. I have been living away for university, and have moved back to my home town to start studying again. I am living in a flat with my LT BF. We have allowed my sister to come and try living with us to see if being away from the family home, in a new environment could help. First few days she managed well, however, it is getting progressively worse, stealing, bingeing and purging starting up (my parents live down the road, so I don't think anything stopped anyway she just went there to do it, I think she was just able to hold things down for the few hours at a time she was here - which still IMO feels like a small win, at least there were a few hours a day of relief for her heart etc.). 

The original agreement was that if she couldn't stop here then she would go home again, and come back when she is ready. However, in practice this now feels so horrible to have to kick her out, and I feel we probably didn't work out the boundaries/guidelines/rules properly. 

So what I am asking for is if anyone knows what the boundaries are?? When is the line crossed? What are the repercussions? Do we send her back to live with my parents (who are really struggling under the strain of all this)? Do we (as some people have suggested) find a way to lock the kitchen at night? Lock my bedroom (so she can't steal clothes etc. another feature of her problems)? Do I discuss boundaries with her and let her help set them? Or as some others have suggested detach with love, and tell her these are the conditions (locking doors etc) of living here (without all the explaining and justifying and arguing)? 

I love my sister so much, and I am terrified everyday that she will have a heart attack and die. We are an open and communicative family, and have always been supportive of each other. I just wish I knew how to support her. How can I support her through this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Holding a job while managing a restrictive eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 00:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently moved several states away from home to live with a friend because my home environment was unsafe and not a good place to begin recovery. Things have been going good between us, but I think both of us are getting a little tired of sharing a one bedroom apartment and want more privacy. We've talked about getting a two bedroom apartment, but to do so I need my own job. 

I haven't been restricting since I came here, but I've been trying to avoid retail, food service, etc jobs. I used to work at a grocery store when I was actively restricting, and at the end of my shift sometimes I seriously thought I'd pass out, and it scared me. I've mostly been applying for office jobs and such that will allow me to remain sedentary for most of the day, but I haven't been having any luck landing one. I think I may have to resort to applying for things like retail or food service if we want to get the new apartment anytime soon, but I'm scared that it will be too much for me physically.

Is working physically demanding jobs with an active ED, or when you're just beginning recovery, a safe choice? Could I be further damaging my heart/other organs or worsening my chances of making a recovery if I'm on my feet for 8+ hours a day, doing heavy-ish lifting, running around the store, etc? Is there any way I can arrange to have accommodations made for me? I feel like your average store or restaurant manager is not going to be very understanding or compassionate towards someone who is unwilling to do basic tasks like standing or lifting, but I feel like I don't really have a choice but to apply for those kinds of jobs. I don't have a degree or any specific skills that would land me different jobs.

Please note I don't have a medical team overseeing my ED right now, I just haven't been restricting for the past month or so because a lot of the stress I had at home that was causing me to restrict is gone now, I have better access to food in general here, and my friend's been holding me accountable. I don't know if that makes a difference at all, but I thought it might be useful information.

Thanks so much for reading! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: What can I do about my bulimia when I can't get appropriate treatment locally? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 00:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am overweight and have been my whole life, except for when I was younger. Once I hit age 10 I started gaining a lot of weight, which led to me being made fun of for being bigger. I developed BN and I have been suffering from it the last 4 years. I am 19. I don't know how to go about getting help. They dont have any eating disorder help where I live, (like therapists or anything,) and I have tried to talk to my depression therapist but she told me she doesn't know anything about ED's and is unable to help. I talked to my primary doctor and he suggested I take prozac, because prozac helps with compulsive behaviors. It did not work. I really want help. But I feel like no one is taking me seriously because I am bigger. I have been having bad stomach pains lately, on the lower right side of my stomach and near the top of my stomach as well. And my teeth are suffering badly. Really badly. I am so scared and I just do not know what to do. I dont have the car to drive to a bigger city and I dont know anyone who would be willing to drive me. Is there anything I can do? I have tried to stop purging and I dont even binge half as much. I literally just cannot stand the feeling of even having the littlest of food in my belly. For one, it physically hurts. Not even mentioning the emotional/mental part of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Girlfriend decided to lose weight, but she has become anxious about food and her self esteem is crashing. What can I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 02:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently my GF has been having a lot of difficulties with her eating behaviours. 8 months ago she started getting really into losing weight and running. After 6 months she has reached her goal, but now she is as unhappy or even more than before, this up untill the point that she feels really quilty about eating anything "not healthy" and her overall looks. No matter what I do I cannot seems to break through her barrier of selfesteem. She knows she has a problem but is at lost on what to do. I myself am not sure either, since relating to her problem is near impossible and I cannot just make it a little better by talking. 

**What other steps I can preform to help my GF so it does not get anyworse?**

**What sort of support would help her at this point?**

Thanks for reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do I recognize I have a problem and stop comparing myself to others in treatment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 01:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently in an adolescent inpatient program for my eating disorder due to low weight and low BMI. I have AN with purging and restrictive subtypes, similar to the two other girls in the unit with me at the moment. 

My disorder is making me extremely upset at the moment, and I want to be able to recover my weight and make my eating habits normal again without constantly comparing myself to everyone around me and dubbing myself as a faker. I need to be able to recognize I have a problem that is serious and requires help, and I want to be able to think "I'm lucky because I got help before I had serious side effects" instead of "I'm not sick enough, I need to be sicker/skinnier".

How do I accept that I have a serious problem and stop comparing myself to the other patients? I feel like a faker, inadequate due to my condition in comparison to the others, like I am not sick enough to be in this position and undeserving of the help I'm receiving.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it bad to browse subreddits related to weight gain and nutrition if I have a bad relationship with food? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 11:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure I'm orthorexic and although I've been "in recovery" for 6 months, my weight has still been slightly decreasing. I wanted to take a positive approach to weight gain and browsed subreddits related to nutrition and weight gain, but I feel as if these sites make me think about my weight too much. I know how to gain weight, and I know how to eat healthy, but why can't I commit myself to do it? Why am I so self conscious?

To those of you who have recovered, would you recommend browsing subreddits such as these, or would you recommend other communities instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I feel less self conscious and continue living my life while keeping my weight up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 22:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently started my freshman year of college! I'm 10 hours away from home but I have weelky skype sessions with my therapist and have a team at the local childrens hospital. Mentally and emotionally I am doing great, I am not preoccupied with food, haven't been restricting or purging, have been exercising in moderation, I'm making friends and managing my stress well but I am struggling to keep my weight up. I'm kind of at that point where I don't want to be sick and resent not being able to do what everyone else does. I eat with my friends and eat a normal amount or until I'm full instead of following my meal plan which is so much more than everyone else eats since I'm supposed to gain 10-15 pounds. I tend to lose weight when I'm happy and active because I am not constantly focused on the eating disorder and spending my life planning meals. I'm so glad that I have a life and that recovery isn't all that I am but I want to stay healthy and in school. 

How can I feel less self conscious and continue living my life while keeping my weight up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to manage intrusive thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 21:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brain is constantly screaming at me to restrict or to purge. How do you deal with obsessive intrusive thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Inpatient facilities that have a spa atmosphere? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 21:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am looking for an inpatient treatment center that is like a spa.

These two were recommended to me: http://www.sundancecenter.com/ http://sierratucson.crchealth.com/

What is your recommendation and why?

I tried google and looking at general sites that claim to list all the facilities, but the information is difficult to understand what the facility is really like. There are no aerial pictures and when I use Google maps some of the facilities look like strip malls.

Are there any recommendations for inpatient facilities that resemble a spa? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm worried about my friend who's relapsing and indulging in fitness. Is it possible for her to balance fitness and AN? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 21:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am worried that maybe my friend is relapsing. She has become addicted to fitness and building muscle. She was treated for anorexia a year ago through a hospital program and she doesn't like to talk about it, but believes that she beat it. 

However, I've read that people struggle with EDs their entire lives and she is under her doctor's recommended goal weight. 

She has a very popular instagram that seems to be glorifying unhealthy ideals. 

I've asked her but she doesn't want to talk about it. She wants to be a personal trainer, and I'm having trouble figuring out the difference between health   fitness and obsession   mental illness. 

My question is is it possible for her to balance fitness and AN? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Relapsing maybe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 12:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been in partial recovery for several years, but over the last 9 months I've actually managed to be purge free, despite binges. I've put on weight, I want to start running again as soon as I can, but my psychiatrist put me on seroquel and it's made me bingey and I keep having cramps in my feet.

Today, I failed and purged after a small binge. I was feeling crappy all day, but purging made me feel a lot better and happier for a little while. Then I was desperate for a run. Then I just collapsed in a heap.

My eating disorder had been taking a back seat to everything else. But now, it's rearing it's head and I feel overwhelmed. I'm exhausted and I don't want to fight it. I just want to go with it in the hopes that I'll lose weight and finally for the first time in months, something will go right.

It's only one purge, should I mention it to my shrink next week?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: how to help a co-worker who I believe suffers from anorexia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 16:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have worked with her for about a year now. Over the course of the year, I have taken note of her eating habits. Since our company has frequent luncheons, it has been easier to see what and how much she eats. Not only do her eating habits make it glaringly obvious that there is an issue, it's also her physique. For a while, I tried to ignore the problem   told myself that she was just naturally thin. I am in no way trying to judge her. I honestly only have concern for her.

Recently, I have become her assistant. The urgency to approach her (gently, of course) about this since we are in more direct contact each day has become very strong. I have an idea of what I need to do, I'm just hoping for guidance before I talk to her about this. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Having digestive/gastro issues after 8 months of partial recovery. What can I do, and should I see a doctor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 03:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am partially recovered at the moment and I have not starved myself since January and have not purged consistently either. I have noticed some issues with my digestive system and my bowels.

My stomach is very weak still. I have thrown up multiple times involuntarily because of how weak it is. Also I now tend to get bloated more easily.

Here is the TMI part. I keep getting diarrhea even though I eat lots of fiber with plenty of water. The diarrhea is not that bad but it is still not good. I have been having issues with diarrhea for months and months now.

Has anyone had this problem and been able to fix it? 

Should I go and see a doctor?

Mod note: Please see a doctor before taking medical advice  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My friend with AN plans to restrict on a family vacation. What can I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 03:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend of mine is recovering from minor-moderate anorexia nervosa as well as moderate depression with some self harm (They have seen a general practitioner and will be beginning therapy at some point in the future). 

They are going on a trip to a foreign country with family and expressed the desire to try to lose as much weight as possible without arousing the suspicion of their family. When I said that that was an abysmal idea (not in exactly those words), they told me that this was 'the first thing [they'd] been excited about in ages' and that this will keep them from cutting. 

Is it appropriate for me to intervene, and if so, how?

How can I voice my concern in a way that is helpful?

**Mod note: The OP has requested that you PM /u/avret if you reply.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Visiting my cousin who is inpatient, what can I bring her to help or make her feel good through this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 17:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found out over the weekend that my little cousin who is 16 was taken to an inpatient eating disorder rehab facility for bulimia. I knew that in years past she had had a problem with binging and purging but was in therapy for other issues and that was being addressed. However, seems recently that it has gotten very bad, coupled with some fiercely aggressive bullying from a select few kids at her school...and so she (willingly) was taken by her family to this ED clinic. 

Family is about 90 minutes away, but clinic is just down the road from me... hence me wanting to help out.

Can anyone give advice on things I could bring her, what she might need, things that helped you if you were IP at a clinic, things you missed. I've read the guidelines for patients at her clinic on what to bring and what not to bring, so I know they can be quite strict, but hoping you all here could provide some personal experiences on what may be most helpful to her. Obviously I will ask her, but she is probably feeling quite vulnerable right now and may not be able to speak up for herself...

Thank you guys xoxo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Good materials for loved ones? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 00:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all,

I've been struggling with an ED and I am getting treatment from a dietitian and therapist. BED has been an issue of mine since childhood, but in the past year my ED has been leaning towards bulimic/restrictive tendencies, resulting in rapid weight loss. 

My sister is my best friend and wants to do anything she can to help, but she doesn't really know how. Her best friend is also struggling with an anorexia relapse, and between the two of us, my sister is having a hard time trying to handle it. 

My parents are pretty involved as well, but they aren't really as open-minded or understanding about ED's, so I've just resorted to setting boundaries and limiting contact. 

What are some good books, websites, or brochures I can give her? Some of the biggest things that have been an issue with my family are constant comments about my weight loss/body, commentary on what I am and am not eating, and trying to force me to eat more, etc. 

Any advice, reading materials, or even videos would be much appreciated :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Just found out my girlfriend has an eating disorder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 00:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been dating my amazing girlfriend for 8 months. She is a wonderful, extremely beautiful and caring person. She is very healthy now but yesterday she opened up to me that she sometimes makes herself purge when she eats something unhealthy. I starting digging in and asking her why she does this and the reason is because she hates what she sees and shes not happy with herself. I knew before we dated about 6 years ago she got very thin, and could not get her period anymore. Her mom forced her to the doctor and she took away her treadmill and she wasn't allowed to see her friends until she got healthy. I thought she was over that horrible part of her life but it seems like she somewhat isn't. She eats very healthy and eats well, and shes in the gym almost daily. Its when she eats chocolate or something sugary that she wants to vomit sometimes. I'm afraid she might be relapsing. I asked her if shes seen a therapist and she said she has few times and she says they just make her angrier because it won't help. I don't want her to have low self-esteem. It hurts to know that someone you care about so much is thinking so negatively of themselves, because she doesn't realize I love her more than her looks, it truly kills me inside because she will never understand how much I love her. I would do anything for this amazing women. She is the love of my life and I would die for her, and i can't understand how a person with that much beauty can feel that way. 

What can I do to help her or convince her that seeing a therapist is ok?

 tl;dr: Just found out gf has eating disorder. She says therapists don't help and that it isn't a big deal. What can I do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I want recovery but I'm at a normal weight and weight gain terrifies me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 00:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

Background I've messaged before about thinking I have a problem with food and things have stepped up a bit. I discussed my issues with a GP and a counsellor who described me as having anorexic tendencies but probably not full blown ED - in part because my weight is in the healthy band for my height. I unfortunately had to leave the area due to educational reasons, returning home for the summer (2 months) and will then be moving to finish education for 3 months meaning I'm not really able to build up a long term relationship with a counsellor. Also, because of these short stays there is no way I would get near the top of an NHS waiting list for ED services - the GP who called it anorexic tendencies said it would be around 18 months. 

New Issue I had an appointment with the hospital for an unrelated issue. He is concerned about the large amount weight I have lost in the past 6 months. He is doing his best to sort out support for me. My parents are in denial. They give weird mixed signals with things they say.  

The problem is that I want to stop feeling this horrid about food. I want to mentally get better. I want to eat without guilt. I don't want to gain any weight, since the doctors have said I am a healthy weight. It is the weight loss I've had that they worry about. 

Is this normal? Is this healthy? Is it possible to recover without gaining weight when you aren't underweight? I'm living in fear of meal plans and forced weigh ins and calorie counting. Help.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I have BED and undiagnosed ADD. Is Vyvanse a good solution? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 17:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently in therapy for Binge eating disorder (which became bulimia) along with depression. There is one FDA approved medication on the market for BED called Vyvanse. It is essentially ritalin. 

Anyways, my therapist was asking me how much time I spend preoccupied with thoughts of food and my weight, impulse control, etc. I do not have trouble focusing like you would stereotypically imagine with ADD- I did fine in school, but my therapist said ADD and BED are related. 

For anyone who has taken Vyvanse, have you seen successful results? Is this a better course of treatment for this for those suffering ADD and BED?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I was using marijuana to help stimulate my appetite - what else can I use to stay on top of eating enough? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 18:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long story short I got an underage drinking ticket (I'm 20), and I got sentenced with 6 months probation, so no smoking or drinking. Drinking is not so much the issue its the weed. It really helps with increasing my appetite, it's been three days since my sentence and I'm just not eating as much as should... 

Any ideas to help me through the next few months? How can I make sure I am eating enough when I have little to no appetite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My girlfriend has AN and depression, and is purging. College is looming. How can I help her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 18:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My (18M) girlfriend (18F) has an extremely toxic home environment. Her mother constantly abuses her (emotionally) and her father is apathetic. Her brother never talks, to anyone.

Before we started to date nine months ago, she had three suicide attempts under her belt, and to this day struggles with depression, anger and trust issues, bipolar disorder, BDD, and - as I've realized - anorexia.

She is not underweight for her height. I love her so much, and honestly she'd be stunning with or without a different body. But due to her past and her issues, she has very bad self-esteem.

She seriously believes she is "fat" and "ugly" - and she definitely is not. Boyfriend bias aside - she is always complimented on her beauty, all the time, everywhere. But to her, none of it matters.

I'm going to be honest: I know what to do. Anyone with these kind of issues must want to help themselves, they must receive professional help, and they must have support. But how can I do that for her? I'm at a loss. My loving words and supporting actions go in one ear and out the other. There is, honestly, nobody but me who cares about her and has the authority to do anything about her bad habits. She lashes out on me often, and it is really hurtful, but she always regrets it. I can tell when she's seriously remorseful, and she really doesn't want to be like this.

She wants to love herself - which is the issue here.

She's going about her recovery all wrong. Neither of us have money for her to go to therapy, and her family don't care enough to involve her healthcare - so she takes matters into her own hands. To love herself, she feels like she has to have an ideal body (nothing wrong with that). She wants to lose weight.
To achieve that, she starves herself and over exercises. I've told her this is bad. I've showed her facts, reports, science, everything to prove that I'm not crazy when I tell her that is literally destroying her body, but she doesn't listen.

She is restricting to a dangerous point. And just last night, she confessed to me that she purged because she ate more than she usually allows (which was still severely low for a daily intake)

What do I do? I love her. I tell her that she's on a slippery slope to disaster. I support her recovery. I care for her. Nobody else does any of this, and even with my support, I can't stop her at all from crumbling into an awful mental (and physical) state. And in just two weeks, she goes off to college, and I follow a week after that. If I can't help her living in the same city, what can I do when we're states apart?

tl;dr: Gf is really messed up, and has started restricting/purging. I want to help, but I can't, and I definitely won't be able to when we both go to college. She is too weak to follow through with anything herself. What do I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I'm nervous that someone I love is relapsing - do I ask them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 17:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do I sensitively ask someone who's recovering from an ED if they're not relapsing? Should I even ask? If not, is there something else I should ask instead?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How do you cope with triggers in recovery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 17:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my two biggest triggers are junk food and my mother. My mother is an abusive asshole which I live with so I can't really avoid her. Also being surrounded by junk food sets of this massive anxiety spike which leads to me wanting to self harm or to binge/purge.

How do you cope with triggers in recovery? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My girlfriend has a binge-eating disorder, I'm the only person who knows, I'm in over my head. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 15:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I (17 y.o.) have a (17 y.o.) girlfriend. A few months ago, she told me she has been suffering from binge-eating disorder for the past 3-4 years. Leading to feelings of worthlessness, self-loathing, and issues with self-esteem/self-image (although there are probably some other influencing factors). This has lead to (occasional) self-harming and depressive episodes after she has binged. She has some other issues that complicate her ED, found further down. I am the only person she has told.

Her ED has become better since dating me, with her binges being more spread out and infrequent, as I am there to support her, talk to her, and reinforce that she is beautiful. No matter how much affection I show her, she still isn't beating her ED. She needs something more long-lasting. I am leaving the country in a couple of months, and although I will still talk to her, I will no longer be here to give her that complete support. I have talked to her about telling her parents, a close friend, getting professional help, but she is extremely ashamed about it and doesn't really want anyone to know. She hasn't got the greatest parents in the world, but I'm sure that if they knew the extent of her ED they would be there to help. She has one close guy friend that could help her, but I'm unsure of how trustworthy he is. I think she doesn't have faith in a professional to be able to help her (for some reason).

I need to know what to do, who to tell. If she says she doesn't want me telling her parents, should I do it anyway? She needs somebody to be there for her, other than me, when I leave.

Here is some extra information about her

 * She has had diabetes since she was a young girl, and her blood sugar levels are always wavering. I'm unsure of the link between her diabetes and her eating disorder.

 * She is a very, very picky eater. She absolutely loves snack foods and desserts like chocolate, biscuits, etc., and those are the types of food she usually binges on. But, when she wants to eat healthier (or more "normally") she will eat plain chicken, oatmeal, margherita pizza, french fries, and other plain foods. She has begun to experiment a bit more with food, but it's still very limited. This obviously makes it hard for her to eat properly. I really wish she could be less picky, but I don't know how realistic it is to get her to experiment with other, healthier, foods.

 * She seems to have replaced some meals (such as dinner) with one or two "Quest Bars", solely because they taste like chocolate, or oreos etc. I am unsure of how harmful this is, and how it may be affecting her ED.

 * She does a lot of exercise, maybe spends 5/6 days a week in the gym when she isn't at school, and 3/4 when she is. I find her body very attractive. She doesn't accept this, or see this and compares herself to models etc. she see's on her social media.

 * She keeps a daily track of her macro-nutrients (protein, carbs etc.) and is always worrying/obsessing about the values and sometimes won't even go somewhere if she can't find out the macro-nutrients.

I still don't believe that she has completely accepted that she actually has an eating disorder.

Any help would be greatly appreciated. Thank you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Terrified of weight gain! How do I cope? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 00:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 22. I have had issues with my body image and self-preception- mostly revolving around my weight- since high school. I have gained some weight since high school, even though I still have a mid-range, healthy BMI. I just loathe those extra couple pounds and have begun restricting in order to get them off me. 

I've put myself on a diet, and while I don't think the amount I'm restricting is medically unhealthy, it's driving me INSANE. I can't stop thinking about calories, food, and my weight. I can't stop craving food. I can't stop hating myself for the extra weight I have. 

I just want to be able to eat whenever I'm hungry, eat whatever I wish to, eat mindfully, and then stop when I'm full, but I'm afraid if I let go of the calorie-counting, even though it makes me miserable, I might gain weight. That would make me even MORE miserable and I have no idea how I could cope at all with any weight-gain, even a slight amount. 

This is becoming a serious problem, one that consumes my every thought, and I plan to talk to my therapist about it next Monday. This obsessing is hell. I don't know how I'm going to make it until then. I mean, realistically I know I'm not likely to attempt to harm myself in any way before Monday, but I'm just unbearably stressed out. I've begun resorting to other unhealthy coping mechanisms and I know I'm starting to go to a very bad place again. I just hate everything right now.

How can I begin to cope with the idea of weight gain?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: My adolescent friend comes from a traumatic home environment and is being treated using the Maudsley method - is this appropriate treatment for recovery given her situation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 17:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend has had an eating disorder for four years, but it only became apparent when she left home (she is an adolescent, and felt the need to leave because she suffers from emotional trauma at home). She has been staying with a friend who was looking after her, but had to be admitted to hospital.

The hospital uses the Maudsley method - phase 1 is to ensure she gains weight and physiological health, and mental health issues are not attended to until this phase is complete (as I understand it). Maudsley focusses upon family therapy. I understand it has quite a high rate of success.

My question is - is the Maudsley method appropriate for someone who has significant conflict or has significant anxiety regarding their family? Especially where that person suffered some level of abuse, felt the need to run away, and also where both parents are known to have some level of mental health issue themselves? As far as I can understand, these factors make Maudsley a less appropriate option, but I am unsure how to gain further judgement. The hospital that she is admitted to only uses the Maudsley method, so it is not as if she has had a method selected out of multiple options in order to find one that suits her.

I raise this as well, because I am of the understanding that this person suffers from some level of PTSD - again, this is only available to me from my personal judgment, but my friend has not had a comprehensive psychological assessment or therapy, so I feel that the hospital staff may not be attending to this part. It is my understanding that such disorders need to be treated simultaneously and not in phase 2 or 3.

I guess I'm asking if anyone has been in a similar situation and has any feedback that might help me understand the course that the hospital is recommending and whether or not my personal judgment has any legitimacy, though I understand that it is difficult to determine this from a single reddit post!

Any help is appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How can I prevent a relapse? I have struggled in the past and have gone through a very hard break up. Do I tell my therapist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 16:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had an ED off and on for a very long time but have been able to hide it because I have a curvier body type. Everyone just applauds me when I'm skinny, not realizing that it's usually because I'm eating little to nothing at all. 

I struggled with disordered eating for years until I met my last boyfriend, who said he loved my curvy (skinnier) body. I got off my disordered diet to enjoy dating him, and we ate out a lot, and cooked a lot, and I inevitably ended up gaining weight. I knew I was heavier but he appeared to still be happy with me. 

Fast forward five years, he broke up with me because he says he didn't love me anymore. I heard through the grapevine because it was actually because he wasn't attracted to me anymore because I had gotten "fat" since we dated. 

I've since gone into a tailspin and have been severely restricting my eating. At first I thought it was because I'd lost appetite from some normal break-up related sadness. But it has been weeks. I've been exercising a lot and I still buy food intending to eat it but it just rots in the fridge. I don't want to go down a miserable hole of endless fasting again, but it has always been my way of quickly feeling better when I feel shitty about my weight. And I can feel the pervasive thoughts about how great it would be and how easy it would be to just power through and lose a bunch of weight to make him regret breaking up with me. 

I have never seen a professional for my ED, but I finally got a therapist to get over this long-term break up. Should mention this to her? She asked if I had any self-destructive behaviors. Is there anything else I can do to mitigate these feelings of worthlessness? I guess I have to accept that I have a curvy/big body type that requires constant maintenance, and not everyone is going to like it. 

Help. I'm 30. I thought I was over this.

How should I bring this up to my therapist? How can I work towards accepting my body? How can I prevent a relapse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Stuck in cycle of restricting/binging/purging - should I tell my boyfriend how bad things are? What else can I do to break this cycle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 18:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to be long but I am feeling alone and scared and completely exhausted. I've been dealing with a variety of eating disorders for 8 years now and I'm finally really breaking down hard.

I've always struggled with weight but I never allowed it to really dictate my life as it has since 2007. In 2007, my university went through a very traumatic experience that personally impacted me and my friends. Then in the fall of 2007, I lost my virginity after being raped by a friend in his frat house. 

After that my self esteem went downhill rapidly and I stopped eating. The majority of the calories through alcohol binges most nights of the week. When I graduated from college, I stopped drinking as much, started over exercising, and continued my very tight food restriction. I went from a healthy weight to severely underweight in about a month. 

About 3 years later and numerous health problems, I began binging and went from underweight to obese in several months. My depression hit an all time because in my world being fat is the worst thing ever. After a year, I started purging and I lost a huge amount of weight and I now weigh a healthy weight. 

However I'm on the edge of being overweight which terrifies me and I'm in this terrible binge/purge/restrict cycle. I had really made good progress in recovery but one of my coworkers sexually assaulted me last summer (it's a he said/she said situation) so I still have to work with him and he teases me about last summer. That event through me back into this downward spiral. 

I met my now bf in 9 months ago and he's the first man that I have ever loved and he loves me. He know the high level of my ED history but doesn't know I still struggle with B/P/R. I work a very stressful job that requires 10+ hour days and the occasional weekend. 

I'm seeing a therapist and psychiatrist for talk therapy and medication but I still feel out of control. I've racked up almost 10K of credit card debt solely due to BP so my finances are overwhelming despite making a very good salary. I feel like I'm one step away from drowning but I can't seem to stop. 

BPR makes me feel better so when I'm stressed or upset or whatever, the urge is so overwhelming I often give in. I can't live the life that I want to live with a happy marriage with my bf, children, career success while still dealing with bulimia. What's worse is that I know this is physically in my control. No one is forcing me to BPR but I feel completely out of control. I feel gross and overweight and terrified that I'm wasting my life but I still don't stop. 

Any advice would be welcome. 

Should I tell my boyfriend about my continual struggles? (he knows nothing about my debt and previous sexually assaults. I need to get better and I need to recover and I need help)

How can I break this cycle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: I am desperate - What's the first step in helping my sibling with their eating disorder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 18:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sibling lives at home with our parents, one of which is an alcoholic and has been verbally abusive towards my sibling since they were a child, the other is in complete denial about the situation.

I have no idea where to even begin with this, it's been on going for at least three years (I had been out of the country) maybe more and I think part of me thought it would just go away, even though I knew deep down it wouldn't. 

My sibling is very difficult to approach about anything and keeps very much to themselves, and doesn't have any social circle to speak of, and could potentially cut me out completely for trying to talk with them about this. The only time he is with other people is at his job, which he really seems to like and that is a positive. 

I am so scared for them, they are caught in a cycle of binging an purging. The situation at home is a toxic one, our parents are in a financial mess, I am mid-twenties and self employed just barely getting by but I would give anything to help them. 

I hope this makes sense, I'm desperate at this point for any advice that anyone can offer. What's the first step in helping my sibling? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Stuck in a pattern of restricting/binging/purging - how to get out of this cycle, stop obsessing and rely on hunger cues again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 04:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, recently, I have had trouble with binging/overeating but I have a history of other ED behaviors. I have always LOVED food and was a pretty tiny kid. Tall, lanky, but loved junk foods. I didn't start thinking of my weight until puberty hit--I didn't gain a significant amount of weight, retrospectively a totally normal amount of weight. It all went to my thighs, guts, and hips (at 16 I was diagnosed with PCOS, which is why I gained there/still hold fat there) and coupled with my newfound fascination with eating disorders, which I guess I learned about through health class/the "media" I began to think about my weight/what I looked like more. I sort of half-assedly attempted to make myself sick, like severely restricting, overexercising, but this would never last. I would always end up binging and then going back to my unhealthy, although quite normal for a preteen girl, eating habits. I never had an eating disorder. 

Throughout high school I definitely emotionally ate. I was super depressed and didn't have a lot of friends and was sort of an outcast. But I never hardcore binged. I generally ate what I wanted. I was lucky in that I never gained a significant amount of weight. I was never as skinny as I wanted to be (which at this point I've almost completely accepted I'll never be) but was relatively thin.

Once I got to college I was really happy. I made friends, people liked me, talked to boys. Did not give a flying fuck about my weight. I gained weight freshman year without really noticing or caring. My weight fluctuated, don't want to go into that much detail because of triggers. Eventually, I went to Paris for a semester and began purging. It was really sporadic and still wouldn't consider myself bulimic. I began self harming that summer and eventually things got so bad I had to leave school. I lost weight because I was so depressed and that's probably where this started because after I was depressed I was so satisfied with the way I looked I wanted to maintain it. Anyway to the present:

About four or five months ago I began restricting and rather than binging and then going back to a semi-normal diet, I kept restricting. First by cutting out food groups and then on and on until I had way more not "safe" foods than "safe" foods. I was (and still am) miserable. But I lost weight. And it felt really, really good. People started saying I was tiny, which made me want to lose more. But I became irritable, tired all the time. I kept lashing out at my boyfriend, I stopped going out because I was afraid I would eat. I began purging if I ate anything unsafe. Sometimes, not often, I would buy unsafe food just to purge it. Recently, I had to leave my apartment and move home, because of this and also because I stopped taking my meds (I am diagnosed bipolar ii + OCD). 

Once I got home, I ate whatever I wanted. I was SO HUNGRY once I stopped restricting. I ate everything possible. I craved dairy, meat, bread, everything I hadn't eaten. I ate and ate and ate. And gained. And felt so disgusted with myself. So restricted again. And then binged again. 

Finally, I told myself I am going to get better. I am going to eat healthy, but an adequate amount. I am going to run, which I've been doing (and, not surprisingly, when I actually eat enough, I have enough energy to run!).

But now that I've fucked up my brain/body I have NO idea how to eat anymore. I don't know when I'm hungry, or when I'm full. I don't know HOW to eat.

So I am curious how you guys got out of this cycle, if you guys have a certain food lifestyle that has helped, if any of you have PCOS and have found a way to maintain healthy and balanced? And how to stop obsessing about food? Whether I am empty or stuffed I am ALWAYS thinking about food and am so tired of it. I can't enjoy anything anymore.

If there is any advice you have to spare, I would love it. I have been in therapy for years and I talked to my psych about going to an OP program which she didn't think was necessary, although she recommended a nutritionist which I am looking into.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: How to NOT feel guilty after a large/unhealthy meal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 23:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the normal/healthy weight range. I was an extremely chubby kid when I was younger and obviously dealt with some rude remarks from peers and family. However, even eating a large and unhealthy meal or munching on a crap-load of junk food, I'll feel extremely guilty of myself. 

I know that I won't suddenly gain weight from this one meal , but I can't shed myself of this mentality. My guilt might seem quite harmless at first but then all I do is think about the meal that I shouldn't have had for hours or even days. Like, if I hadn't eaten that meal maybe I'll be a few pounds lighter right now or if I hadn't eaten that snack my face will be slimmer right now. 

How can I eat without feeling guilt after eating a larger meal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
