<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3132</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To what extent can we rely on the perception of the artist to represent history? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 11:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello all /r/history dwellers! 
I have been thinking a lot the past few days about artistic representations of art in history and how their representation of the history can be influenced by their perception? 

Is the history that is thus being represented, reliable? 
Is it false history?
What are some examples of art pieces that may misrepresent a historic event?

I am simply posting these questions here for discussion. The constant debate with myself in my head was becoming seemingly repetitive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 02:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there! I am currently in a recovery program which is also compensating for strength training 3x per week. I am 168cm, 48kg and 16 years old.


**My diet is as follows:**

Breakfast: 2 eggs scrambled, 50g oats (as porridge), 60g avocado, 1 banana (OR other option) Shake w/ 1 scoop protein powder, 40 walnuts, 100g strawberries, 50g blueberries, 50g oats + a boiled egg.

10am Snack: Apple, Banana and 40g mixed almonds/cashews/walnuts

Lunch: 130g white fish, 110g rice/130g quinoa, green veg unlimited

4pm meal: Shake with 50g oats, 1 scoop protein powder, 100g strawberries, 40g walnuts

Dinner: 90g chicken breast, 130g sweet potato/rice/quinoa, 60g avocado, veggetables

Night snack: Banana


I have been on this for about 4-5 weeks. Only last week were the oats increased from 30 to 50 in the breakfast option and afternoon shake. The nut content for each meal was also doubled. It was initially really hard to eat all the food, though it has gotten easier. The hardest part of my day in terms of food is the final banana of the day. I love bananas but they're so filling.

I recommend you see a dietitian for a plan for YOU. Everyone is different and has different needs. 
Good luck OP, you'll get there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 20:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like mine soft too, though probably not if it is cold. Do you heat them up? Thanks for the tip on peeling them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 20:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eggs! I love them, but oh so difficult... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 19:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello fellow preppers!
I have a slight dilemma. Eggs have been added into my diet. In the form of scrambled and boiled. Scrambling eggs is manageable, however boiling them is not. 

Thing is, on the days where I have to have boiled eggs, I don't have as much time to prepare them in the morning. Is there any way I can prep-boil around 5 eggs? 

If yes, do I peel them and then store? Or peel when I need them? How long do they keep? and, is there any way I can heat them up? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 19:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello again, sorry to disturb. I think I have weaved my way through what problems I had before. Now the trouble lies in structuring my actual presentation. Any tips you can provide on that? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 10:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think from Kruidvat or Blokker in the Netherlands. You know of the artist/author?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 18:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roast the almonds prior to processing. It brings out the oils. Oil may help if you want a smoother butter though are not necessary. I am yet to try it out with oil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 18:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 18:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only almonds. Next time I will try it with some salt to bring out the flavour a bit. I don't think the oil is necessary if you have a powerful blender and a bit of patience. 

ALSO, the roasting process is what brings out the natural oils. It is absolutely necessary. I kept the heat around 170 degrees cel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 18:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cook on Sunday before lunch.
Fridge: Sunday (L/D), Monday (L/D), Tuesday (L/D)
Freezer: Wed, Thurs, Fri, Sat

Meat stays good for 3 days, in my experience. Freeze the others. Will take out Wednesday from Freezer on Tuesday night and put in fridge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 12:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Practice makes perfect... it just takes time. You'll get there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meal Prep Week #5 (ft.almond butter) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 09:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 17:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK YOU! You are wonderful! Great help :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TOK Presentation Help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 12:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there IBO comrades, 

I am not sure how the IB weather is for you all these days, but mine is raining IAs and presentations! 

Anyhow, I am at a loss at how to move forward regarding my TOK presentation. I know that I want to discuss history and have generated a few ideas from this. They are:
* Does historical knowledge exist to ensure there is no doubt of the past?
* (something pertaining to the following quote) - "The aim of the historian, like that of the artist, is to enlarge our picture of the world, to give us a new way of looking at things." (James Joll). Maybe something like "How subjective is historical knowledge to interpretation?"


I don't know whether these are too broad or not and would like to know if anyone here can help me pick/formulate a decent KQ. Thanks in advance!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 07:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I normally keep Sunday, Monday and Tuesday in the Fridge. Then on Tuesday night, I will take the next day out of the fridge. The fish can get quite dry on the Tuesday if you had initially overcooked it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 12:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello again all! Thanks for all the positive feedback last week. It was really motivating to read all your comments and messages :) I was able to stay on track with my eating last week and have (hopefully) done week 3 justice with these meals. I switched around some of the veg, got rid of the beef (it made my stomach hurt) and bought some new spices for the fish and chicken! 

Speaking of chicken, I bought some shish taouk (lebanese grilled chicken variant) spices. Normally, yogurt is used to mix with the spices and then marinade the chicken, though since I didn't have any yogurt lying around, I used CAMEL MILK! Yes, camel milk. It is slightly 'saltier' than regular milk though quite light on the stomach. It can be a bit pungent if not fresh though.

The sweet potato this round was roasted cut into cubes with some spices (lots of cayenne pepper) and the quinoa was cooked in a rice cooker. Thanks to those that suggested I do that. It is a great improvement from last week :)


EDIT: Apologies for the recipes not being that detailed. If you would like more info, don't hesitate to ask. They are quite simple. 

ALSO, I just had some of the camel milk chicken... IT IS GREAT and tender and yum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meal Prep Sunday Week #3 = SUCCESS (+ thanks, recipes inside) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 12:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 11:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gain weight, recover from ED.

I guess the ease that comes with simply grabbing my food when I need it is extremely gratifying too! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 21:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, makes complete sense. Thank you very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 20:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your help. SS it is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 20:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the input. I think I am set on SS with some abdominal accessory work. One question: Is there is a warm-up for the deadlifts? Only think I can't seem to find on the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 17:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too many times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 17:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderful to finally get a straight up answer. Two questions:
1) SS requires less sets than SL. What are the benefits/losses of this?
2) Thanks for the recommendation on bench as an accessory. What do you think of the cleans? Many people suggest replacing them with the rows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Program selection manic(x-post r/powerbuilding) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 16:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
