<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6681</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 18:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently at the 72 hour mark into my fast. I have no intentions of stopping. 


Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: Skipped

Dinner: Skipped

Total: 0 calories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 21:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I totally get this too. As a vegan, I have dreams/nightmares all the time where I'm eating meat/dairy/eggs. Ugh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 21:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Attempting another fast. Currently 48 hours in.

Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: Skipped

Dinner: Skipped

Total: 0 calories
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats great news! I'm so proud of you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 18:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished up another 48 hour fast. I'm tempted to attempt 72 hours, but my rational mind says otherwise. I just did a 72 hour fast a couple days ago, and only had 24 hours of eating in between. I guess we will see what happens.

Update: I gave in and tried to eat "Non disordered". My rational mind decided it was the right thing to do. I'll probably go exercise tonight though and abuse diuretics anyways. 

Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: Mealplan (540)

Dinner: Mealplan (340)

Snacks: Banana (105), Oranges (130), almond milk (110)

Total: 1225 calories

Scale: 126.5 lbs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 20:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: Skipped

Dinner: Skipped

Total: 0 calories

Scale: 127.5 lbs

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 19:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did a small 24 hour fast between yesterdays lunch and todays lunch. Trying to stay under 800 if possible, on the non fasting days. 

Breakfast: Skipped

Lunch: Meal plan (Quinoa, rice, veggies) = 470
 
Dinner: Skipped

Snacks: Banana (105), soy milk (110) 

Total: 685 calories

Scale: 128 lbs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, no. I think there might of been some miscommunication! "Vitamin Zero" Is a vitamin drink with zero calories! I had one during my fast in order to replenish my vitamins.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 21:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't drink any salt water;however, I did have a vitamin zero during my fast at around the 36 hour mark. 

If I were going any longer, I definitely would have had some salt water. It's a good idea to replenish your electrolytes when attempt a fast (especially one 3+ days)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3 day fast completed! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 18:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

As some of you may know, I've been doing some experimenting with fasting ever since I got to university. So far I have completed 2 separate 24 hour fasts, along with one 72 hour fast. In the past (when my anorexia was at it's worst) I completed a one week fast. 

For some reason, this new obsession has started where I am counting how many hours I can go fasting without food, instead of obsessing over how few calories I can eat in a day. Don't get me wrong, I still count calories very strictly - I've just been experimenting with the length of fasts as well. It's so much easier psychologically on me to because you don't even have to consider calories at all. 

Anyways, enough rambling - Here is the breakdown of my 3 day fast:

 nbsp;

**Start of Fast**

 nbsp;

**T + 0 hrs: 133 lbs**

- The first 24 hour of a fast is always the hardest in my opinion. Not much to say here, except for you just gotta stick through it. 

**T+ 24 hrs: 131.5 lbs**

- After the initial 24 hours it does become a little easier... At about 36 hours in I went to a concert which involved alot of standing. After the concert, I was invited back to a new friends place to have some drinks, but I wanted to stay true to myself. I went, but we ended up just talking and all staying sober.

**T+ 48 hrs: 130 lbs**

- By this point, all hunger stopped really. For me this is normal. I felt a little dizzy and weak at times but nothing out of the ordinary. My guess is that my body was switching into ketosis around this time. I also had a nap that day as I felt more tired than usual. 

**T+ 72 hrs: 127 lbs**

- After 72 hours, I ended my fast. Honestly, I felt completely fine (I wasn't even hungry). But I decided it was for the better to go out and try to have a "social meal" (which I seriously struggle with). They say if you can make it to 3 days, you have conquered the hardest part. I probably could have went a couple more days easily. 

 nbsp;

**After Fast: 128 lbs**

The day after my fast, I ate 1400 calories and weighed in a pound heavier than the day before. I tried not freak out at this, as I knew I would gain some water and food weight back. However thats still a 
**5 pound decrease in 3 days**! Hooray!!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
