<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3297</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope all went OK. My thoughts and prayers are with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's a bit more offensive here in the U.S. since we have a bit more of a taboo against religious associated words used in vein or in anger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I wonder if there's an alternate universe where we aren't translucent." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "(Whistles) Man we got some straight up freaks coming through here." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, I LOVE the first three seasons of Family Guy. I consider those seasons to be among the best in American comedy, not just animation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, is it scarring? Because if it is....gross. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say "Hell" is a curse word. Penis? I'm not sure. I mean, you wouldn't exactly bring it up in an every day conversation without getting some looks from people around you. I guess it's the idea more than the word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 09:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Demongo appearin' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 09:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sad there's a particular lack of "Da Sam-Mu-Rai" memes around here, as well as something to do with "Suddenly Demongo". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

 Or Cassian having one of the most hammy, cringeworthy monologues I've heard in a movie in a while to Jyn right before the final battle which goes nowhere. 

I didn't think so. It's Cassian admitting that most, if not all, of the people who worked with the Rebellion did terrible things, but for an end result they thought was justified, and that they would stick with her because this was a righteous cause regardless of whether or not they'd make it out of the conflict. It's their moment of redemption. 

 Or the shoehorned "hope" word everywhere. 

It's only discussed with Jinn, Cassian, and ending with Leia. It's literally a chance in terms of fighting for a better future. It's a through line in terms of emotional pay-off, but it's also a thematic thread of using trust in other people rather than only relying on concrete evidence or actions to secure a relationship. 

 Or Bodhi's incident of losing his mind that went absolutely nowhere in the long run. Amongst many other complaints.

Yeah, I admit, in terms of the overall story, it didn't go anywhere. It did however, showcase how much Guerrera fell to torturing someone who came to him with information and shown how outright extreme he treats this conflict with the Empire. For Bodhi, it's a case of "break the innocent" where he's the one who has suffered the most for the cause, and is STILL able to bounce back from Saw's interrogation to help the rebellion because he believes it's the right thing to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Most of these are super easy to answer and it honestly sounds like you let random internet out-of-context nitpicks influence you.

No. I've actually watched this film at least 4 times all the way through. These are my own criticisms of the film, and I'm not just picking them out of other peoples' criticisms. 

 The film provides context in his behavior, and the fact that it was his first mission, and the fact that he just witnessed a traumatizing event and was ordered to participate in it. 

Which is put into an even STRANGER context as this vital mission to the First Order is staffed with a firing squad that takes an inexperienced janitor with no actual combat background into the fray. 

 We don't need minutes of exposition into his backstory if it shows rather than tells--the former is usually a sign of bad storytelling (and is also a problem Rogue One has on numerous occasions).

The phrase "show, don't tell" has been rather badly misconstrued these days. Film isn't just a visual medium, it's also an auditory one, unless one only counts films passed before 1927. Showing instead of telling is good when the showing can be immediately understood. For instance, in "A New Hope", there's the iconic moment of Luke staring at the Twin suns setting in the distance, and we understand his longing to leave his boring life as a farmer. However, we only get the payoff for that 'show, don't tell' because the film "told" us by providing context to Luke's frustration and impatience in not being able to leave the farm. The setting Twin Suns is magical because we have understanding of who Luke is as a character and what he wants. Compare that to someone like Rey or Finn where the filmmakers are vague about what they want or how to achieve it. Did Finn want to be the best stormtrooper before actually seeing combat? Did he have any actual sympathy for the First Order or his stormtrooper brothers? He seemed to have a sad moment for his dying stormtrooper brother-in-arms at the start, but then seems totally okay with killing them in droves later. 

With Rey, the most confusing moments are at the very start of her journey with the "show, don't tell" policy. She's looking at the old woman at the start of the film. At first, I thought this was supposed to be her wondering if she'll waste her life and become like the old woman, especially since they're repeating the same action. But on a second rewatch learning about her initial emotional obsession with returning to her family (why in the world her family left her with that jack-ass of a merchant makes no sense), I then began to wonder if that was just her looking for a parental figure (which she finds later in Han). THEN as I thought more about I thought it may have been a visual indicating the pointlessness of her occupation. And then there were other thoughts associated here. THIS is our character introduction and these things are not clear! Showing and not telling in storytelling is good for when we have a basis of understanding for context, we have almost none of that for Rey, and it gets more muddled. With Luke, he wants to leave the farm for a new life. He eventually gets that but only because his family is tragically killed by the Empire and his maturation to having a moral goal rather than just escapism is his arc in the story. 

For the Rogue One explanation, these characters (in the scenes where they're more explicit in their backstory) are angrily arguing over what they consider to be "facts" to bring into the conversation. They need to be direct and explaining themselves plainly works with the dialog. People do explain themselves. When they explain themselves plainly without provocation or explanation, then that's when it gets odd.  

 His motivations of escape are purely selfish at this point. They're firing at him, trying to kill him in the act. They didn't try to escape too.

My problem wasn't the immediacy of his survival. My problem is that he seems to have a moral quandry about killing, or at least the problem in terms of violence in combat, then he kills a large number of stormtroopers (which who were his brothers), then afterwards there seems to be NO EMOTIONAL CONSEQUENCES for him as a character to work through. We don't know who he is as a person BEFORE the Jakku mission, so we have no idea how this affects his point of view. How did he feel about the First Order? Did he believe in their cause, or was he just put off by their tactics? He's grown up as a stormtrooper. Does that mean there are others like him? Does he consider that he could help other stormtroopers turn to the Resistance?

 Like her clinging onto past convictions to the point where it almost kills her and also gets her captured?

What are you talking about? Her running away from Maz has no negative consequence to anyone else, besides herself in terms of being separated and taken hostage (which is then pointless in terms of danger, because she then rescues herself, further making Finn's rescue kinda pointless). 

 Or her discovering a new family and shunning it?

Once again, I think that's not the case, at all. She runs because she's been given the opportunity to follow in the ways of the Jedi as Maz explains (although why she would believe someone who has NO KNOWLEDGE OF THE ACTUAL FORCE makes so little sense, who can apparently tell people just from a look). 

 By the way, Luke didn't show any demonstrable faults in ANH either, and he became a better shot than the Stormtroopers by halfway in the film, without ever firing a gun before.

Yes, he does. He's impatient. He's quick-to-anger. He's also learning how to be a better shot over the course of using stealth tactics. Leia is the far best shot out of everyone. 

 Not to mention her past is already quite a mystery that seems explicitly left open to solve.

Except that doesn't make for a stand-alone film. The explanation for Darth Vader, the Empire, the Rebels, the Force, Obi-Wan, Anakin, and all of the other elements of the original film are clearly defined in "A New Hope" (even if Obi-Wan was lying "from a certain point of view" about Vader/Anakin). It's stand alone. In The Force Awakens, it's just this really bizarre plot point that gets lazily tossed away and covered up during the ensuing chaos. 

 This wasn't when he killed troopers. This was when they blew up an automated turret that would try to kill them.

Yes, he was celebrating that moment. My point is that this is all together in terms of it being a scene, and there seems to be ZERO negative ramifications for Finn as a character when he betrays basically everything in his life to run away. 

 It was only in Empire where his faults started to show. Rey's actually already off to a better start in this regard.

No. Once again, he's impatient and headstrong. He literally rushes off to his family's farm when Obi-Wan knows it's too dangerous. He may have avoided danger by the fact the imperials already left, but that doesn't erase the fact that he willingly put himself in danger due to a rash impulsive (not to mention emotional) decision to leave. 

 Yeah, no context, dropped out of nowhere...except in the first 20 minutes. 

THAT'S where it's interesting! Where she admits she's waiting for a family to come back, but it's blown over by Maz who knows NOTHING about her situation. Her accepting a new family isn't the problem, it's the struggle with her letting go of her old habits to wait for her family vs. leaving for a new life which doesn't make any friggn sense.

 Not to mention her past is already quite a mystery that seems explicitly left open to solve. 

This movie is supposed to be an origin story. It's supposed to be well enough made to have enough story to satisfy it's narrative drives, not be lazy and leave it for another time. 

  "Why did Luke want to go off and fight?"

Because his family was brutally murdered by the Empire, he believed in the cause, his mentor was killed by Darth Vader, and his mentor had told him his father had been killed by Vader. 

 Why did he care about what his friends were doing? 

Well, at first he didn't. He wanted to learn the ways of the force. Then he had a begrudging relationship with Han which then they started to form a friendship through their trials. He wanted to the do the right thing and give back R2 to Leia, and THEY also bonded over their shared grief over the loss of Obi-Wan and the struggle to protect the rebellion. 

Rey's whole family sub-plot is haphazardly thrown in for mild intrigue and then dropped for the sake of narrative convenience, in my opinion. 

 I mean Saw Gerrerra having super cheesy dialogue during super serious moments

The "save the dream" moment? I felt that was earned. The guys been clearly through the ringer, and I thought Forrest Whittaker's take on the guy was fascinating in terms of him struggling to put sentences together and to be "all there" mentally to sound normal after all he's suffered through. 

 Or Jyn having a super cheesy speech in the war room out of nowhere.

I thought that worked because she gives the speech out of desperation, and merely repeating what Cassian had said to her. She wants vengeance for her father's murder, but she also realizes the necessity of creating a galaxy WITHOUT the Empire (after losing all the people that had cared about her).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you not seen the rest of this season? They've gone fairly passed what Cartoon Network has been happy to showcase for the past 10 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Akira Kurosawa films: Yojimbo, Sanjuro, Seven Samurai, Ran, Roshoman, Hidden Fortress, etc.. Even stuff that's not a samurai story, like Stray Dog and High and Low in terms of how he frames scenery. 

I'd also recommend "Hana-Bi" (aka "Fireworks") directed by Takashi Miike, and "Drive" directed by Nicolas Refn. Simple tales that execute their usage of blocking, cinematography, and sound effects with great tension. 

Takashi Miike also directed a great samurai movie called "13 Assassins"

* The Longest Yard (1974 films, not the Adam Sandler remake) was a big influence on Tartakovsky in terms of style. And I'd recommend "Nashville" in terms of showcasing a story that also knows how to flip between emotional extremes with style, subtlety, and ease.

* The Star Wars films episodes 1-6 with Rogue One. I think there's a lot of crossover in terms of knowing how to use archetypes, and how they utilize action well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the only way Scrooge McDuck could have survived jumping into his gold collection, though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, I'm talking about the kid in Witcher 3 in how his fictional father is Ted Cruz. GET ON MY LEVEL, SCRUB!!! :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No because his Dad is the zodiac killer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Poke) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of defending game covers, I have to go with defending DmC. Not only is it a great game, but there's also more imagery involving the demonic and angelic symbolism behind Dante, and the utilization of showing his "devil may care" attitude in how he walks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See You Space Cowboy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nightcrawler's cousin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotcha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn good game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're looking for great narrative-driven FPS experiences, I'd recommend the following:

* Wolfenstein: The New Order, Wolfenstein: The New Blood, SUPERHOT, The Darkness 1 and 2, Deus Ex: Human Revolution, Deus Ex: Mankind Divided, The Stanley Parable, Metro: Last Light.

I'd also recommend Portal 1 and 2 for great characters and world-building with great writing. 


Also, what did you like about the BioShock series and what are you looking for in other suggested games? Does it have to be a particular genre, or have particular elements?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So not as bad as Guardians of the Galaxy or Avengers where every other piece of dialogue is a cheeky one-liner, but enough light heartedness so the movie about a combat tournament for the fate of the world doesn't end up taking itself too seriously.

Okay. I liked Avengers and Guardians of the Galaxy (the former in terms of genuine character dialog, which reminded me a lot of a Robert Altman ensemble film with the superhero trappings I love, and the later in terms of great comedy). I think that because of how popular it has become, there's been a sort of natural blow-back because of how big Avengers had become. I think it earned every bit of praise it had, especially in terms of character moments and narrative structure, and there are a good number of scenes of dialog which are serious - I genuinely think that because the comedy beats work so well, that's all people remember.

 This would be cool to incorporate the Earth Crowd and community aspect to the fights, and some real world giant stadiums to host the fights.

True, but I think they are afraid to do that since the Outworld might be a little bit more visually interesting than just Earthrealm that we're sort of used to. There's also some great stadiums and arenas, I think the only problem is to have an environment in which the magic and crazy stuff wouldn't seem out of place in. 

 I'm a hollywood whore so wouldn't even mind seeing the Rock as Goro and someone like Zac Efron as Johnny Cage--idk if he gets a lot of hate here but he fits the aesthetic perfectly and could pull of the arrogant self absorbed pretty boy who is also a world class fighter.

As long as it's a good actor, that works for me. Yeah, I do like Efron and I think that he's a solid actor in stuff like The Paperboy or Me and Orson Welles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I find this to be a funny sentiment amongst Americans, to the point it seems almost like a programmed response (and I say that without trying to sound condescending) it's always "look I believe my country is the greatest country in the world... buuuut..." or "I love my country more than anything...buuut..."

I think that's actually the opposite. A lot of our culture is particularly focused on criticizing every aspect of the government, people, ideas, military, and (ironically) culture. I genuine love my country for the freedoms I can enjoy, the opportunities I have, the genuine community I share with my fellow countrymen especially on the country's focus on the rule of law, and I'm proud about the contributions the country I live in has contributed to the world. The reason why I say "I love my country more than anything, but..." is because I recognize (and am honest about) the fact that my country has problems. In some cases, there are SERIOUS problems, but even saying THAT, I still love my country with all of my heart. 

I've lived across Australia, England, Canada, France, Sweden, and Germany, and I still say there isn't another country I'd choose to live in over the United States.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Witcher 3: Wild Hunt (and I'd recommend getting the DLC). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good guess! I do love those games. My favorite game would be "Crimson Skies: High Road to Revenge" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will give it a look see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blaze/praise it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adventure! Dames! Good vs evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mortal Kombat by Christopher Nolan!

I do like Nolan as a director/writer, but I don't think he'd be a good fit for the series. He doesn't really like that kind of eccentric fantasy that the series has.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't subscribe to reboots but a gritty reboot to Mortal Kombat would be sweet. Even though it seems damn near impossible to make a good movie based off of a video game.

I was surprised as Hell when I found that the Mortal Kombat reboot (aka MK9) and Mortal Kombat X actually had pretty good narratives and characterizations. It was like an R-rated mix of Avatar: The Last Airbender and Game of Thrones. They kept the fantastical side of the series while imbuing the characters with a good amount of depth and intrigue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Those were $500 sunglasses, asshole." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention the enormous fees in terms of buying the rights to use his music.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Turn it off....turn it off....turn it off...." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US government is becoming progressively authoritarian. I still love my country more than anything, but this kind of crap where no one is held accountable for crimes or lying to the public (sorry, "misremembering") infuriates me to no end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Speaking of Star Wars games, Republic Commando one had one Hell of a soundtrack! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's because it's a far more introspective look inside individuals as opposed to the more fun and colorful explosion of optimism in the 80s (ironic given that the Cold War still loomed over everyone's heads). The 90s felt more existential and out there in terms of style, which may be harder to capitalize on. Grunge, hatred for office work places, the threat of Y2K. A lot of things that concerned the 90s were concerned with a bit more abstract notions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SHUT IT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget the obligatory box of goon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I'm sad that the remake didn't have 1/20 of the character the original game had </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, any of the first-person shooter Halo games are a good selection for "favorite from the series". Reach is a damn good game.

For myself, my favorite is Halo 4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I loved Halo 4 and 5. The macro story in Halo 5 was a real mixed bag, but I did certainly like some character moments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm cautious after the disappointment of Prometheus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well...mostly mostly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LIAR! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, in my opinion, the book seems more like a warning and the dangers of censorship of ideas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can you take place before the original trilogy and NOT be considered a prequel?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's put in that work to stay alive her whole life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do video games also belong in prequel memes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been seeing the "Watch those wrist rockets" meme around associated with the prequels (also with just regular Star Wars memes). Do the video games and cartoons during the prequels count as well? Because I've been dying to place some more Republic Commando memes when possible.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [autistically issues visual warnings on DVDs] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never knew there was so much eyebrows in the whole galaxy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That made me both happy and sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Captain Kirk, on changing the rules of a simulation of a no-win scenario, enabling him to win.

So....cheating, then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Revan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/guytrash, my allegiance is to Reddit! To shit posting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All right, so he still raped a 13-year-old girl and then left the country to avoid punishment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do prequel Memes also extend to the Star Wars video games? Because if they do...

"Need...bacta...now" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His new empire?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it red, red, green, or red, green, red? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's it!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget the terrific animated series as well! Only lasted two seasons but it is SO DAMN GOOD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "CREAM CORN! NO!!!!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Now, shut the FUCK UP while grown folks is talking!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There's no flipping between arguments.

Yes. There is. Some argue that the characters in the comic (including their race) should be kept in tact as much as possible for an accurate translation of the source material. Some say that they should change the race for more diversity. But when someone claims BOTH arguments at different points in time, they're being inconsistent with their beliefs and are just adjusting their strategy for the sake of promoting diversity regardless of what they actually believe. If they just said I "I want more diversity" that's one thing. However, it's quite another when they want more diversity, and choose contradictory arguments to get it. 

 I want more diversity in film. 

That's not the same argument as "You should keep the characters looking the same as they do in the comics", which was the accusation of The Ancient One. 

 The hell with fidelity to the source material.

Well, some people would like to see a faithful translation in terms of who they cast physically, and others want more diversity to be the guiding star for who portrays a character. I frankly subscribe to neither. I just want the best actor for the position, and only factor in race, gender, and culture into casting when it's vital to the portrayal of that character.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't at all address the fact a lot of people were angry that they were remaking a classic film for no adequately explained reason, and the trailers did not make the film look that funny (or at all). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once again, my problem isn't with showcasing how brutal and unfair Antebellum slavery in the south was to black people was, or event he use of the word. My problem is that Tarantino hides behind the "period accurate" defense when a good deal of his movie isn't. I'd rather he just say "I want to have my characters say it" (and I'd respect him for sticking to his guns on the matter). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There's nothing intellectually dishonest about advocating for minorities to be cast in roles that are traditionally white, while at the same time condemning casting white people in roles that are traditionally not white.

Yeah, that's fine. I have no problem with that argument in and of itself. My problem is the flipping of arguments when it suits your needs. Claiming to want a character be faithful to the comic (The Ancient One), then staying silent on changing the race of another character to another race (Mordo, Elektra, Heimdol), then decrying a character SHOULD be racially changed (Danny Rand in Iron Fist) despite the source material. If they made the underlining desire of seeing more diversity, then that's an honest argument to be made. However, it's outright flippant to the actual merits of an argument when you flip back and forth between particular hills to defend for the sake of diversity, rather than just outright saying you want more diversity. 

 It's an intellectually sound argument.

You are missing my point. Wanting more diversity is not a bad argument, constantly changing arguments that are not always the same argument for the goal of more diversity IS bad arguing. 

And by the way, all of those characters who have had race changes - I've loved those actors in those roles. Idris Elba, Elodie Yung, Chiwetel Ejiofor. I love those actors in those roles. 

Post-edit: I guess screw me for pointing out that a fallacious argument founded on a good idea still makes for a fallacious argument </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read this one. He basically lays all the negative reactions to misogyny. [Link](https://www.wired.com/2016/07/paul-feig-ghostbusters-qa/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that is your argument, then that's fine. My problem is that people seem to transform and shift their arguments in incredibly facetious ways. If you just want more minorities in roles in Hollywood, that's a completely understandable stance. Just be consistent. I can't stand these people who are so intellectually dishonest about what they want and how they defend it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   people hated it because the movie sucked.

Try telling that to Paul Feig.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was a bad film, but I do agree that the controversy was overblown by a huge margin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ancient One in Doctor Strange:

"That's RACIST! You should be faithful to the comic book!"

"You mean the Ancient One shouldn't be a woman?"

"Well...it's all right to change that part."

"And Heimdol in Thor, Ben Urich and Elektra in Daredevil, and Mordo in Doctor Strange should all be their races from the comic books, right?"

"Well....not if they're white."

The sliding scale of justification just pisses me off sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My problem with it isn't that it was used a LOT, but that Tarantino's justification of "it was period accurate" somehow doesn't pertain to a lot of other elements in his film. He really should have just said "I just wanted to use the n-word a lot for my movie for effect." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just the one swan, actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I can do this all day." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cleopatra 2525 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same goes for the stairway fight in season 2 and the Punisher prison scene. That show has great choreography all around

As much as it's kind of an "eh" sort of show, the Iron Fist vs Drunken Master fight was damn good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And HE'S supposed to be the demolitions expert." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "These underage kids are playing Titanfall instead of having unprotected sex! THE NERVE!!!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like he's angrily strangling a dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of my favorite scenes of all time from "Daredevil" - Matt confessing his sins to Father Lantom. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a lot of the small touches in the series that make it so good. 

The moment where Matt tries to fire the gun only to realize that he has no other bullets left and smiles is just....perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest, while I love both Oldboy's usage of a single-take hallway fight, the thing that takes Daredevil over the top is how they utilize the movement of the camera through the space they're in and how it glides within the space of the fight itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For Marvel stuff, I'd recommend the following that are worth the watch:

* Spectacular Spider-man
* Wolverine and the X-men
* X-men: Evolution
* Spider-man: The Animated Series
* Avengers: Earth's Mightiest Heroes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Samurai Jack for current stuff going on. It's a masterclass in visual storytelling.

For older stuff, I'd recommend Jericho - it's a terrific show about a small town in Colorado seeing a mushroom cloud explosion over Denver and about the community trying to survive and figure out what happened. It's TERRIFIC! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What are you....are you trying to cry?"

"I'm sad!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even like that show anymore, but I love that pilot episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite would probably be Daredevil. 

 "I'm not asking forgiveness for what I've done, father. I'm asking forgiveness for what I'm about to do."


But also, special shout-out to Band of Brothers, Cowboy Bebop, Prison Break, and Jericho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yeah I can't disagree anymore on that note. Not only were his motives clearly illustrated and given context, but the switch started small. He wasn't even trying to be a good guy at first--he was trying to get the hell out.

I personally hated the character of Finn. He starts off either terrified of the carnage of war or is just afraid to die (the film provides no context, which is a reoccuring problem). Okay, fair enough. But then he steals a ship and in the process of doing so, kills scores of his fellow stormtrooper brothers. This could have even been an interesting moment of reflection with Finn working through justifying why it's okay to kill stormtroopers who (if they were like him being raised from birth) could be turned to the good guy side, but instead, it's treated as a fist-pumping moment of "yeah, take that bad guys!!!" 

 And I have to disagree even more about that since just about everything regarding their personalities, motivations, and interactions with other characters were different.

I thought Rey could have been interesting, but the problem is that she really doesn't have any faults and all of her problems are external. You can even do that kind of character (which is difficult, but possible), but her own emotional through-line, waiting for her family to come back, is just dropped out of nowhere with so little fanfare and context that it seems like the writers didn't know how to organically make it end and just hope that a mad dash to a new plot thread would neatly end the old one. 

 ...Whose character development was completely unwarranted by the actual events, and whose "grittier" nature was always at odds with their extremely cheesy dialogue, and whose behaviors always seemed to be inconsistent from one moment to the next.

I didn't think the dialog was cheesy and often times moments of levity were earned in the film. The characters were consistent while still growing with solid arcs. Once again, I felt that the writing was just overall better with the writing, character arcs, narrative, and more classic sense of pacing, character growth, cinematography, and other elements that fit a better sense of what a Star Wars story is than The Force Awakens, but that's just my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a sequel to the prequels and closer in time line to the original films (Hell, it takes place minutes before episode IV). 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, I respect your opinion on those films, even though I feel the exact opposite on your views concerning both of those films.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it as good as the original Thrawn trilogy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jurassic Park, Gattaca, The Count of Monte Cristo (2002), Rush Hour 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a movie that I enjoyed in the theaters, but progressively hated with each rewatch. More power that you liked it, but I thought it ages incredibly poorly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a ninja, I'd have to say that show is pretty accurate.

In seriousness, I do wonder how accurate the show is at portraying legal matters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go back to r/sequelmemes our allegiance is to the republic to r/prequelmemes

...

 I find your treason vague and unconvincing.

So, why did you allow that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never knew there was so much treason in the whole galaxy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Yes?"

....

"Hello?!"

....

"This is dog!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I love "Jericho", Bonnie dating that one kid just to get back at her brother kind of goes nowhere, and you start to wonder towards the end of season to what was even the point about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not the biggest fan of breaking bad, but I do recognize it is an incredibly well-made show. The characters that truly pissed me off and have absolutely no bearing on the story is Walt Junior and Marie. What's the point of them except to be emotional motivators for the bigger protagonist in the show? I didn't hate the actors themselves, in fact I rather like they're acting in some scenes, but it just felt like you didn't need them in the damn show except to get emotionally invested in the main characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, I'm not a big Doctor Who fan, but for the most part, I think the seasons between the relaunch and the end of the mat Smith era have been good to great. In my opinion, and I don't think any less of you if you enjoyed it or liked it, I thought that season eight was absolute dog shit in almost every regard, especially the writing. They have an entire subplot about the afterlife that never sees any conclusion or discussed in any significant way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, they made a reference to Tumblr, what a hip and up-to-date show! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For myself, I would have to say that The Amazing Spider-man is still my favorite

Post-edit: the hell did i get downvoted for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tobire Maguire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 09:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem that I have is that I think this may run counter to the themes of the original 6 George Lucas films. I feel like Luke's revelation at the end of "Return" was that while the Jedi were the good guys, they ultimately misunderstood that an absolute strict dedication to an ideology is folly. 

I feel like between the Original and Prequel trilogy (and Rogue One, and a LOT of the Star Wars media) is that there is good and evil, and just the obfuscation between the two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HORSESHOE!.....right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Catch 22 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just a program trying to make his way across the galaxy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robocop has gotten a downgrade in recent years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read into that what you will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "In order to meet the demand for more of our consoles and games, we've decided to declare bankruptcy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  His failures resulted in the destruction of the new republic's government and the death of billions.

One of the many problems of The Force Awakens (in my opinion) is that we're not given an explanation as to how HE failed. Was it that he taught him too much too fast? Is it that he even revealed Anakin's history? Was it all Kylo's decision without Luke having the "wit to see what was happening"? Luke didn't fire the damn weapon, he didn't build the Death Star 2.0, and he didn't create the first order. Hell, even Kylo had nothing to do with the firing, or building, of the Death Planet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
