<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3278</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do I look now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rolling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been very tight the whole time but Nadal has won the big points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats what I said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6 set points to 1 and Nadal converts
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wowwwwwwwwww. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that he's 30 any little mistake people act like he never made mistakes before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is some of the best shotmaking I've ever seen from Nadal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daaaaaamn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This match has had some weird half powered hits from both players that seem unintentional. Anyone else notice this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monfils was on fire in the 4th. I need to watch the end again cause that was crazy how Nadal turned that around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 23:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my boy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 23:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could forget about Curry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 23:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Redemption dunk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 23:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd take Durant for Bogut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 22:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark Jackson called Lebron old for not converting the and-1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 04:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I knew more about VR development. What tools are you using? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 04:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, thanks for the tip. Worth $20 in your opinion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 03:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been meaning to setup Steam VR to try The Lab and Google Earth, so I'll add Call of the Starseed to that list.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Touch launch is the most fun I've had playing games in years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 02:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the time good new games that come out are more impressive than they are fun. I can count on AAA titles each year to have a slightly higher resolution with flashier effects, bigger online battles, an open world with a larger draw distance, quality of life improvements, etc. But at the end of the day gameplay won't have evolved much. Generally speaking, I'm satisfied to pick up a game like Titanfall 2 that remixes and innovates on the fps genre while having some of the best graphics I've seen, but the truth is... I'm playing it using two thumbsticks as I have since the first Halo. All the rest isn't much more than window dressing.

I was severely disappointed in the initial Oculus Rift launch as someone who was hyped through the roof about it for months and months. I think a lot of people here would agree it was botched as fuck in terms of their communication with us, but the bottom line was none of those games were compelling to me. I was impressed, sure, to be able to step into the VR world for the first time, but the gameplay on something like Chronos seemed liked it was right out of a game I would skip ordinarily (and I love Zelda and Dark Souls). Eve: Valkyrie was badass for about five minutes until the lack of depth and menu clunkiness set in, not to mention the motion sickness I'd get. But first person cockpit VR was at least a type of gameplay I hadn't experienced before.

Well, I'd considered the whole thing a bust for the last six months, though I'd been enjoying the gaming pc I built specifically for this. I knew Touch was coming out, so I preordered, but I had basically zero expectations after feeling let down. I figured there was a solid chance I would sell the Rift + Touch once I had the complete package. 

But holy f*** wtf goddamn - I can't even tell you how much fun I've been having the last couple of days. This is the real launch. This is why many of us believed virtual reality was the future. 

My friends and I have been passing the headset around and just can't get the smiles off our faces. I can't remember anything like it. Closest thing would be Christmas morning when I got Super Mario 64 and could run around in the three dimensions for the first time. We are playing games like Rec Room and laughing our asses off as we do things that we never thought we'd do. For fucks sake, we have team deathmatch paintball, and it feels like I am in another place with people from around the world. This is a free game somehow, and one I wasn't even aware of a week ago. The amount of pure joy that goes along with dominating Rec Room dodgeball - I don't know that I've felt it before. It's all too natural to break out in a victory dance.

Super Hot is an example of me not believing my eyes. I wasn't ready for this. I can't believe it's real. It's probably too good. I just never thought I'd be having this experience, and it already feels so perfect. To think how things will only improve.

All the Touch games I've tried - Rec Room, Super Hot, Dead and Buried, The Unspoken, Bullet Train, I Expect You to Die, Quill, Medium - have been more than impressive, they've been compelling and most of all fun fun fun. They represent a paradigm shift that gaming hasn't had in over a decade. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 01:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching old videos, it seems he got a lot of respect throughout the 80s and 90s as a perfect example of success. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exactly when did Donald Trump become a joke to most people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 00:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching videos from the past, it seems like he was very highly respected in the 80s and early 90s as a perfect example of success. Some time later - long before his presidential bid - it seems public perception of him flipped. What changed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When did Donald Trump become a joke? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Billie Jean parody starring Hillary, Donald, and Bill [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 00:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Billie Jean parody starring Hillary, Donald, and Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 00:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 03:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hungry... :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 01:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure they're all still living in ecstasy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twenty-five dollars for a cigarette is too much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My all-time favorite movie. Absurd to the highest degree. If I was ever a screenwriter I'd want to take movies from other genres and cross them with Naked Gun-style humor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going onstage at The Comedy Store in LA for the second time. First show went very well for someone like me who is new to stand-up comedy, and I was asked back. So it's a big opportunity for me to get up in front of a large paying audience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 21:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After rewatching games 5-7 all summer, I discovered recently that rewatching games 2 and 4 including the post game Stephen A. Smith stuff saying the Cavs are done is maybe even more satisfying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 10:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's something you stopped doing after people made fun of you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 06:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I calculate the IV of a level 1 (10 CP) Pokemon without powering it up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 02:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm working on putting together my Bubblestrat squad, and I've got a lvl 1 Magnemite with Spark that can successfully take down my lvl 1 Tentacool with Bubble. However, according to https://pokemongo.gamepress.gg/bubblestrat-possibilities, which I found on The Silph Road subreddit, if Tentacool has a 0 stamina IV, it can be powered up to 1.5, thus pitting a 10 cp against a 20 cp and earning me more prestige and xp per attempt. No calculators that I use are able to give me a definitive answer on its IV without requiring me to power it up. Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I calculate the IV of a level 1 (10 CP) Pokemon without powering it up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 02:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 20:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So then, my set up would be the strongest offensive psychic Pokemon, which makes it worth spending stardust on to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 19:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed that too! I'd be attacking with something on the weaker side and get one shot and not understand how it happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Exeggutor with Zen Headbutt/Psychic the strongest Psychic Pokemon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 19:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been sitting on a battle of the best Exeggutor with these moves all depressed that it's not the Zen Headbutt/SolarBeam combo we all want. Now I realize this one may be more than viable. Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 10:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything I saw related to that was prelease info. Nothing on it since launch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 10:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'd read a little bit about that but no one seems to fully know how it works. Something like if you put the warp drives together in a square shape then you'll travel a little further. And you're saying it also works for the guns, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a difference in ships other than the number of slots? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 04:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slots obviously, and it seems like the smaller ships are easier to land in tight spots. I have a 48 slot ships already that I recovered from a crash sight but I'm still hunting for one that is better looking and smaller. Anything else to consider? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 03:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lamar Odom for sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 06:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to do this, but after I activate it once, it won't let me do it again. What I am doing wrong? Do I need to find a communications tower without being sent to it?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 05:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see. Why is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Phelp's 50.33 100m butterfly leg in the relay would have gotten him gold yesterday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 05:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it's faster than any of his 100m butterfly gold's at Athens, Beijing, and London. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 04:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phelp's 50.33 in his 100 butterfly leg would have gotten him gold yesterday. It's also faster than any of his gold medal 100 fly wins.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 22:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's my defibrillator </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 22:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 22:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't get one in all of a sudden </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 22:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rafa coming up with the goods on hardcourt down 0-40!!!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 21:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Win or lose Nadal is looking more like himself than he has been all year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 01:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Kindle Oasis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 01:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What all can be done other than gaming emulation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fun gadgets for $500? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 23:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snorlax with Zen Headbutt and Body Slam. Is it the best defender? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 09:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 22:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The balls on some of these Pokemon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 22:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Santa Monica Pier? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 22:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt like Steph Curry at the end of Game 7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dragonite ran away... AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 22:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's shitty, I'm not going to lie. I caught a ton of other great Pokemon last night, but I'm not sure I'll recover from missing this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People who haven't spent real money, what level are you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 22:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been grinding my ass off around LA and got to 14 without dropping a dime, though it is tempting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
