<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1563</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not bleach, it's an implant. You can't bleach your eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Going out for a weekend could be a couple new games instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must be fun at parties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I guess so. Maybe I should blame myself for sticking around after beating the game and nearly completing all of the shrines/quests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> these low effort posts are getting really old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More so than just new costumes, I would really hope the champion powers would be included. Daruks protection should just be the default blocking animation , Revalis gale as the upwards special attack, and Urbosas fury as a special attack and then Miphas grace could function as absorbing projectiles or something. And then of course he should have his paraglider after revalis gale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think so too. I think there's just a stigma behind it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find the truth to be subjective  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's really insecure and takes everything super personally. He's obviously very emotionally immature as well and tends to be very selfish. Despite this, he genuinely cares about the people around him. It may take him a while but usually he realizes when he acts that way and offers a sincere apology. He wants nothing more than for the people around him to love him as much as he loves them. I find that redeemable. He's very flawed, but overall a good person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hated Andy in season 9. His character was ruined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think its just fap material  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might wanna invest in stamina, you can't wield the Hylian shield unless you have a second wheel.

Edit: apparently Reddit has no sense of humor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smarmy, thats it. Thats describes what I hate about him perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a self righteous prick though. That's why people don't like him. Telling Jon Jones to get his shit together and "get his academics in order" so he can "return to the classroom." It's not only a lame as fuck insult, but who the fuck is he to lay that judgement? He knows Jon Jones will beat his ass again. And he tries to portray himself as a good guy and role model, and gets bothered when people don't see him that way. I don't like that at all. It's self-righteous. Nobody gives a fuck that he's a "good dad" and a "role model." Being good to fans is important and being a good fighter is important . We watch the sport because we want to see good fights, not because the fighters we are watching are good role models and parents. He's lame as fuck.

Edit: not saying he's not a great fighter, obviously he is. I respect his hard work and skill as a fighter, but he's just not likeable to me. He's like your new stepdad that tries to lecture you on how you should behave. He rubs me the wrong way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should be mad at yourself. That part isn't hard at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this was the intended way to solve it, or at least one of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't cook the fairy, but you know be a karma whore thats cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not always about studying though. If you go to class, participate and ask questions plus do you work, that's infinitely better than slacking off and then trying to cram in studying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of autist refills a can? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably because its a hassle to go make something to eat or you're preoccupied. I tend to put that off too much when I'm gaming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you're totally right. It's really frustrating. I love my switch but idk why there wouldnt be a web browser at launch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I do. Honestly it's just anxiety I've come to realize. Anytime I find myself putting things off constantly it's because there's something about that thing that makes me anxious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, I actually have a lot of trouble putting on weight. If only i could but on about 20 pounds i'd be happy with my weight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Energies? Did you take some ayahuasca or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was so excited when they pressed that button, I really thought Eugene was about to get blown to bits. I like Eugene, but thats just cool television. So yeah, i agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly just random stuff that comes to mind.

The first horse I had I named Donkaru because I'm an autist and it's supposed to be the anime version of donkey from shrek. Donkey-kun and Donkey-san wouldn't fit.

The second horse i named Anna May.

The third horse I got was really fast so I named it Flash.

I named my giant horse Goliath.

And I named my white stallion Pegasus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean? This show is as bold as it gets, they never play it safe /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of times it's the only thing you can do to get past certain points in the game. Yeah you can upgrade gear, level up and learn some strategies, but if you can't dodge, parry and time your strikes, you just need to git gud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing you put that 5 there. I wouldn't have been able to count on my own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 05:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you use every dye color? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 05:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah honestly I agree. The first one with Teba I was like okay, this could work. Then Yunobos parents die, then Buliara dies and then Sidon is an insecure whiner. It's not good at all. I think the characters are all fine the way they are in the game. I think I was a little disappointed that Teba wasn't fleshed out more. He seemed pretty cool but you don't get much interaction with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 05:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way he's just looking kills me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 05:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't have a sweet tooth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i r8 it 8/8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/hailcorporate (but actually Contigo is the shit) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always hated that. People who smoke would always go outside and smoke and no one would think anything of it, but if I just go outside it looks like I'm just doing nothing. Also, smokers ruin the "fresh air" with their smoking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK Computer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes sense to say you think it's higher than 720p but originally you said it's definitely above 720p imo which doesn't make sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because you don't know whether or not it is 720p or not doesn't mean that it's an opinion. I can look at a jar of jellybeans and believe there's 1000 in there, but it doesn't change the fact that there's actual 1100. It's either higher than 720p or it isn't. You can say it looks great imo, but the resolution is not a matter of opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not really a matter of opinion, it either is or isn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely not. I prefer my not shit controls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is reposted at least once a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't leave the plateau without the paraglider, which you need the slate to get because you need to do the shrines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> git gud </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Immediately i thought of this in a romantic/sexual way so once you said brother... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you wear contacts/glasses? Glasses are way better for correcting vision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, because I'm always getting money back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> even better ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh okay that makes sense  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually thought he was great. I'd like to see more of Falco. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know finna is common, but does anyone actually know where it comes from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can browse /r/4chan at work and school safely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What disability do you have? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually loved all the Korok trials. Also love Eventide island. I really hope to see more of this from DLCs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you stun them by shooting them in the face you can run up behind them and mount them like a horse. Then you just keep pressing attack. You can also sneak up on them and mount them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mount them, your weapon doesn't lose durability that way. Just shoot them in the face with arrows and mount them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fit is just a gay community  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree unless I'm hammered. I am extending outgoing if i have enough alcohol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I don't agree that it's bad. I just don't think that the fact you have unlimited time makes any difference to the story at all. You have to beat Ganon when you're ready, it's the player's job to determine when that is. If you never face Ganon then I guess it breaks the story but like I said most people wouldn't do that because they'd wanna fight Ganon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people I'd venture to guess finish the divine beasts, do a bunch of shrines and upgrade some stuff and get some weapons and go face Ganon. If you're gonna go explore for months at a time before facing Ganon that's your own prerogative 
, but don't complain it doesn't fit in with the story. It simply would not be fun to play if you couldn't spend as much time as you want exploring. I probably put 50 hours into the game before I fought Ganon. Finished the beasts, unlocked the map, did a bunch of shrines and got ready to fight him. I've spent the last 50 hours just exploring the world after besting Ganon. Technically yeah, Ganon is "still there" and I'm just screwing around but idc at this point, I beat the game.

I'm willing to sacrifice a little bit of immersion for fun gameplay. If I was rushed to go fight Ganon and couldn't explore, the game would suck. It's very, very common for games to do this anyways and nobody really cares. In all reality almost any game time being unlimited doesn't make a whole lot of sense but you ignore that because it doesn't really matter. I don't think this is a legitimate complaint at all. Is it realistic that Link doesn't have to sleep or eat or take a shit? No, but I don't care. The game tells you to fight Ganon when you are ready, but not to take too long. I don't think it's necessary to actually put in time constraints because the player should intrinsically want to face Ganon. It's basic to any game to want to finish it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point isn't to get to Ganon as fast as possible. They even tell you in the game not to face Ganon until you are ready. You're advised not to fave him until you free the divine beasts and are strong enough to face him. Yes the player can choose to just explore and never fight Ganon, but that's more mechanics than story. The whole point is to build yourself to a point where you can face Ganon and then go do it. You can face Ganon whenever, but you cannot fail so you have to be ready. Also, having a timer would make this game not fun at all. There would be no reason to have it open world. As far as the story goes, yeah it's very minimal but that doesn't make it bad. The idea that you lost your memories and had to recover them was interesting. The memories were enjoyable and the characters were unique and memorable even though they weren't fully fleshed out. It leaves to the imagination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zelda has had Ganon trapped for 100 years. She's losing power and there's not a ton of time left but that's relative. It's not like you only have a few days or a week.

Edit: also there doesn't really need to be an explanation as to why Ganon is evil. Ganon is literally the embodiment of hatred and evil  that shows up throughout time in different forms. It's not a personal vendetta or revenge or whatever. It's just evil for the sake of evil. What reason has Link ever had to be the hero of time? He just is. That's his purpose. In another series your complaint might be legitimate, but this is pretty much how it is in the series. Ganon is the embodiment of evil that's all there is to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From posting cringey anime style drawings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if they smoke. I absolutely despise smoking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you mean cancer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> traps are gay, fapping to them is not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably Hylian hood and tunic but all as just one hoodie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beggars can't be choosers? How does that apply when I paid for it? Also yeah the soundtrack is somewhat disappointing, but that bothers me less than the fact that the best music isn't on the CD that came with the special edition. The CD was one of 3 things that came with the set so I think it's fair to be critical when the cd is lacking music. I love the case and obviously the coin is just a coin, but I'm not thrilled with the CD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's not there. The track list is definitely lacking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> somehow this is racist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's why i'm pissed. I'll find a download anyways but it just makes no sense to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best music in the game imo is in Hyrule Castle. That was the only super memorable music to me but it's not in the soundtrack. Lost Woods was cool too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Soundtrack is a huge disappointment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just now opened up the soundtrack that came with the special edition after putting in about 100 hrs. I was really disappointed to see that the Hyrule Castle music wasn't in there at all, nor was the music from the Lost Woods. It's mostly just the music you hear traveling around and battle music.




Here's the tracklist:

Main theme

Field(Day)

Battle(Field)

Shrine

Battle(Shrine)

Riding(Day)

Riding(Night)

The Temple of Time

Guardian Battle

Talus Battle

Hinox Battle

Stables

Kass's Theme

Kakariko Village(Day)

Kakariko Village(Night)

Goron City(Day)

Goron City(Night)

Zora's Domain(Day)

Zora's Domain(Night)

Gerudo Town(Day)

Gerudo Town(Night)

Main Theme(Live)



Overall the music in this game isn't memorable, but the few gems that are in the game aren't even on the soundtrack.I'm pretty irritated by this.

Edit: Seem to be getting downvotes, which I understand because I'm criticizing the game, but I wanna be clear I don't hate the soundtrack. I enjoyed Kass's theme, the music of each respective race and I enjoy the music while I'm playing, but lets be real the soundtrack isn't iconic. I'm more or less disappointed with the actual soundtrack that came with the special edition. It's missing some of the best music in the game.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The switch comes in two colors. Blue and red is god awful ugly and grey looks nice, but it's plain. This design is a bit much, but I like the idea of different colors and designs for the switch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah because Ed Sheeran is just so unbelievably masculine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fatness isn't attractive. That's just reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The words "toxic" and "problematic " are so overused that they've lost all meaning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah they are, but like I said theres not a name for it. It's just the haircut he has in the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean Bolson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normally people say "what is it called" instead of "how is it called" but I don't really think there's a name for the haircut. It's just Link's haircut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you lol that was totally worth it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Royal Guard weapons are the coolest to me aesthetics wise. Low durability but high damage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Farosh. Go to Lakeside stable, walk to the bridge and look to the waterfall. Wait a minute and he'll be here. He has been every single time for me regardless of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did the whole Tarreytown quest...I'm not exactly sure which part you're referring to? Something in the wedding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am i OP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never claimed he was. I just said he's predictable in the show compared to earlier in the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that at all. I haven't read the comics and I think he's become too predictable since the beginning of the season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only disappointment I experienced was that Sasha didn't swallow the pill. She's such a shitty character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how is this a shower thought? seems more suitable for DAE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No tbh I didnt watch much game footage. Didn't wanna spoil anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and I also hate misuse of apostrophes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was adding that your boyfriend said this necessary at all? Could have just been, DAE think McDonalds apple pies and hash browns smell the same?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same sex gender

wut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not talking "holy shit this game is so realistic that I have to control my bowel movements." But yeah, I feel immersed in the game when I'm wearing Rito armor in the mountains, or wearing climbing gear to climb a mountain, or I need to wear the desert set or gerudo set to withstand the heat. It's not perfectly immersive but I'm willing to give up certain elements of immersion for better gameplay and mechanics. I can forget that I changed gear midair because it would just be really inconvenient if I couldn't change clothes instantly. I don't think about it. If i'm just running around a mountaintop naked or I'm in Death Valley wearing Rito armor, there is a huge dissonance between the world and the player. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless they're really struggling I wouldn't offer. It's not worth it if they get the wrong impression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd really advise against doing this. You lose pretty much all of the story by fighting Ganon right away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but that's not a weapon made by a Moblin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not very practical, true. But god damn is it fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't tell what's a joke anymore on Reddit lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just found out a few days ago that you can surf on your shield. Sucks because I've done 80 shrines at this point and have beaten the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do know those balls provide electricity on their own...meaning none of that was necessary at all and you could have just put the ball on the platform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
