<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3594</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is there half a schwastica  there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 06:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like them but my problem with most of the other re colored ones is that they look very similar me to flags of native Americans or African tribes.  The normal person won't care about this and It doesn't really matter but those very much strike me as primitive but nice flags. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the worst experience you had when you old someone that you identified as a jumkey? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There already is, it is called red vs blue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with every thing but you can have a dictator for communism it just needs to be a good one really and power isn't transferred to the same family and you don't get any benefits. I just see it as another job.  Also could you explain why this has 5 downvotes?  I mean I'm a communist like is that why or what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Communism doesn't kill, horrible communist dictators do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but Paladins was changed to be more like overwatch and yes overwatch is defenetly inspired by TF2 it does add more UNIQUE characters and doesn't just combine a bunch of abilities one of the characters have and call it new </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 13:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No as much as a game conveniently has many similarities and releases just after said game that had massive success  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
