<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3191</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had 2 pass through entities. An S corporation and an LLC. You dont pay any taxes to the entity. The profit or loss flows to personal income tax and you pay it on your personal income tax. The tax forms for the entity are for your profit and loss. Basically revenues - expenses. I paid an accountant to do this. The final number went to my personal income tax.


You already get a ton of tax breaks as a business owner. I was pulling down about $250k and My total taxes was about 18% for everything. Federal, state, local, social security, medicaid. If my tax rate was 15% and im guessing this means you dont pay any social security or medicare tax if you are taxed through the entity, I would have paid maybe 5% in federal taxes and then another 3% maybe in state. Likely lower. I also didnt have all the gimmick deductions trump has.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope she likes the ny giants draft predictions. I live near dc so unlikely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He isnt building houses at his age. If he is out there its a photo op. You cant do manual labor at his age </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea if they are worth. News coverage of draft is shit. Half the guys espn says are good picks in the first round end up being busts. All I know is that Jerry Reece doesnt value tight ends. I dont know if McAdoo disagrees and if he does whether he has enough pull to change his mind.

All I really know is, the giants tackles suck ass. Fluker is an upgrade over the garbage known as Bobby Hart, but he isnt reliable. I also know the giants need to s ore more points. You cant expect to make the playoffs in back to back years if you cant score. Too much pressure on the defense.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What book did ot happen to rand? Was this end of book 12? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you were too young to watch LT.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The player was getting cut anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didnt get what they hoped to get for him. So no trade. Why go public about trading him? They can contact other teams quietly. There are a limited number of teams who can fit his contract and have a need. Just contact them. This made no sense.

Not sure what they expected. First round picks are very valuable with the new labor agreement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plaxico Burress going Wyatt Earp on himself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And risk injury. If he blows out his knee he gets nothing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is butler a free agent after this season? If so will the patriots franchise him or let him walk? I would think if they wont trade him, they will franchise him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coughlin got a qb right away at Jacksonville and New York. So it fits with what he does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Offense: Tom Brady/Joe Montana

Defense: Lawrence Taylor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder what I would get on the wonderlic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bills were terrible for most of their history. The 1990s was an anomaly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He got 1100 yards. How is he not getting enough passes to him. The patriots dont tolerate prima donnas. The #1 guy gets the big bucks. Imconfused. Do you have an article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think fournette has all pro written all over him. Not all players are the same. Carolina needs weapons. Does t carolina have a good line too? 

Anyone know if founette is a good receiving back? I think Carolina needs better receivers more than they need a great RB. If fournette is a good dump off back on top of a runner, that adds a huge demension. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 2016 defense had no talent and was injured. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fastest guy on the team. He said TK and me. Who is tk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Cruz gets in based on how popular he s with fans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jerry Reese doesnt value tight ends. The giants really need to improve the offense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was not that good down the stretch. He looked better due to the talent around him. He is a very nice pickup with upside. I think Darian Thompson should win the starting job if he is healthy. Real nice safety rotation though. Giants can do alot of 3 safety formations with them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do t get it. Can someone clue me in. Is he saying he had a kid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How good of a pass blocker is Blount? Our shitty tackles makes a good pass blocking back critical. He is a veteran so I have more confidence in him blocking over the young guys. People forget, but Brandon Jacobs and Ahmad Bradshaw were the two best pass blocking back back in their day. Our line was terrible n 2011. Their outstading pass blocking helped mask it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wanted a contract that matched his value. Im not sure why the saints didnt want to pay him when his rookie deal was up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Treason is a death penalty offense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is 30 miles west of DC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lawrence Taylor changed the nfl when he came into the league in 1981. Best ever. 

All he needs to know. Plus Robert Jordan is the best American fantasy writer ever.

Rest of history doesnt matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The new show is terrible. Bill Nye is not funny or entertaining. He s much better in youtube videos when he just gives us the science. The fake laugh track, etc... I never watched his kids show. If this show is for adults, we have really stupid adults. My recommendation is skip this show and just watch Bill Nyes youtube videos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming he gets back on the field that quick. He recovered from 1 knee injury fast, most knee injuries take longer to recover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder what would have happened if the police asked why the airline wants him removed. Asked how much money was offered to leave. Then said pay more money to get them to leave.

They need to change the cops training to, we will not remove someone until you go up to the max.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should have kept him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chechnya is part of Russia. So it comes from the Kremlin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tits for tots campaign </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hang all the traitors. I. See we need a rope for some reddit posters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a ton of epic fantasy being written. Google is your friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Average robert e howard fan is like 75. So they are elitists on bingo night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesnt make us elitists because you dont like it. You answered a question that was not asked. I dont like Star Trek. I dont see the crazy fans as elitists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fans who like literary SFF look down their noses at people who like pulp action stuff. They act superior and look down their noses at stuff that sells alot of copies. Most years I have never heard of any books nominate for the World Fantasy Awards. Its no one particular series. Its the general sense of we are literary snobs and you are not smart enough to get what we like. 

Now the biggest assholes are the right wingers who sell their books based on being right wing icons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dragonlance could make a great movie trilogy if done well. The cartoon they made was shit. Has good pacing, comic releif, memorable characters, killer dragon fights. Its a pulp series that is great for the big screen.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not fantasy, but Time Travellers Wife is the best audiobook I ever listened too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should add guess your age to the lists. Some lists say old fart, some say kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lincoln was a pussy. I would have been a radical republican. Hang all the generals and political leaders. Seize the plantations and redistribute the land to former slaves and poor white people.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try it in job interview </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They dont want unshaven fatties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you start taking it in the first place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my brother Daryl. This is my other brother Daryl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isnt housing really expensive in japan? How do you provide housing for poor people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this because there isnt enough land to raise cattle and chicken?

Is seafood cheap in japan due to it being a bunch of islands?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am confident that trump will be a shit ex president where as Carter built houses for poor people into his 80s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant even draw stick figured </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last pick in each round. Basically a 2 and a 4.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freedom to boo santa claus and piss on the sidewalk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Foreshadowing that they may be dying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Danni is too nice. Good people in the shit hole that is Game of Thrones are lame.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So there is incentive for HBO to kill off these characters to save money. Blood bath coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might as well put bananas up too. Trump is turning the US into a banana republic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brady sat 1 season. He won a a superbowl his second. There just are not alot of guys who can play qb well in the US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Filthydelphia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda looks like a swatzika. New patriots symbol? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope he doesnt hang with LT and really learn how to party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lawrence taylor failed a few drug tests. The last time he got suspended he failed with a team mates urine who was using drugs. He said recently that if they tested him, he would still be suspended.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get rid of your pro bowl young WR for nothing. Then pay a 31 year old rb with 2 major knee injuries. Its not even clear that Peterson will get on the field again. Saints will suck again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are not enough good qbs. With rule changes. The last 20 years qbs play an even more disproportionate role. There have been very few really good qbs come into the league the last 10 years. Most of the dominant qbs are old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does gaining water weight help at the combine?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every player who can get money goes for it, unless they are married to Jiselle Bunchin and get an allowance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real nail biter. I was nervous,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aviendha would be alot taller </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did rands eyes ever go black? I dont recall that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you miss how much they nagged him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is that thing she grabbed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont have to pay for those. I live in virginia. Fuck Dan Snyder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been years since I looked at a paper map. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christ is a false dragon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beta tester jobs for blowjob robots are jobs americans dont want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We found cat lady </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4% change is enough for trump to lose. He only got 45% of the vote and less votes than clinton. So his vote is basically the base.

Its only been 100 days, he wont get abandoned that fast. I think what put trump over the top was the open supreme court seat. Better poll would be if the supreme court. seat was not open would you still vote for trump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking not virginia. I dont want to pay for that shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sports illustrated has a history of articles where they string you along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to the washington post, bruce allen is busy lobbying virginia lawmakers to force the taxpayers to build dannys broke ass a stadium. Fuck that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Games Workshop. They claim to own the copyright for the term Space Marine and DMCA takedown books on amazon that use it. The term has been around before they existed. The authors they dmca are too small to sue them. You can google it for sources. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that you have to keep walking her tells me you havent actually picked any up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its terrible. I could not watch it for long. Moved on to Bill Nye </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lando Caleissian? Fuck Lando Calrissian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So they believed he invented cold fusion?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any American dumb enough to go to North Korea is on their own. Bunch of dumbshits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Americans. Fucking commies are still infiltrating us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brushing your teeth and flossing twice a day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like it could eat people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you want 2 of these shitting monsters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use a vpn. They wont know what she is downloading. There are plenty of free ones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ill be impressed when the CIA hacks sex toys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So someone with dual, US and UK citizenship get a letter from Trump and Queen Elizabeth. The one their family values more defines the red state/blue state divide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Spoilers) How will Jon Snow find out he is a Targaryen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phillip Rivers. He gets the fuck out of Chargerville. Goes to denver, he will likely end up in the hof </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants 19-0 . Let the bandwagon begin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think about 10-15 players on the same team 4 years later is the norm. Nfl has massive turnover </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeff Hostetler. He won the giants a superbowl.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants. Trading up to take Deshaun Watson. No talk of this wont happen, but its dumb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is afraid of Jenkins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have the #1 pick, im sure the pick is decided before draft day. You need to go around and talk further down in the draft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I saw the trailer for Titanic, I thought it was going to be a bomb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine the horny college guys trying to hit it with the Bush daughters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you work for the US interior department? Any concern about trump layoffs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> US cirizenship only applied to europeans right? Native Americans were not given citizenship were they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is Cli Fi? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darian Thompson giants safety. He was injured almost all of last season , but he was great in camp. Was the starter. He comes back healthy giants have the best secondary in the league and its not even close. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesnt he mean ancient history? 26 years since redskins have even been to a championship game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a game no one will care about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nunes is in a guarantees republican district. Politico is reporting that Chaffetz wants to run for governor. He doesnt want to have to defend trump in 2018 and damage himself in the utah governor race.

They are both from guaranteed republican districts. Their careers are not ruined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brady is the nfls Forest Gump.

I met the president, AGAIN. Same shit. Different day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Complex problems throughout a book then a trick ending where the hero kung Fus his way to victory or some xonteived bullshit to solve the complex problems </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cant buy lollipops anymore or creep catchers will beat your ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sold their souls then got stiffed and didnt get paid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There would be drunken muslums. No way russians would give up vodka </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So sales dropped due to mass consumers dropping dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine if he has an accident or gets pissed off at you and shits on the bed. Imagine the volume </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He can grab his maids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beck wasnt that big before he went to fox.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait a second, as soon as oreilly gets fires for harrassing women the right wing spin is that oreilly is a socalist? How much is Vlad the Putin paying you to troll this? You commy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beck rapes Teddy Bears </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He sings better than alot of people I know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I nominate you to be a beta tester </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if you take a kitten away from its mama too soon, will it never learn to clean itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans do this too, this sub is just propaganda. The lack of up votes is not brigading. Putin just turned off his bots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In virginia we have to get an emission and safety check every year. I could nit pass the emission test because i dont drive my car enough. So i have to go out and drive it for 2 hours then get back in line. Fuck me. Pros and cons of working from home and living in urban area where everything i need is 2 miles away. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. What would Brian Boytano do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He must not want the job. He has easy reelection in utah. Surprised he wants out. He hasnt been there long and he git national attention with purposeful bullshit. Guys who do that usually do it cause they want to be around for a while. We do so lower profile people from easy reelection seats quit because they dont want the job anymore.

Maybe he just spat out his attention whoring bullshit so he could get a high paying private sector job? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not illegal to be a lying douche. So no its not criminal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do t pay enough attention to local issues. Had no idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in northern virginia. Why does this matter? I never had an issue with dominion.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your kid has a future as a lawyer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is apples and oranges. Guarantees contracts without a way to terminate means they could tae oreilly off the air, but be required to pay him. My understanding is they have a clause to allow them to negotiate a settlement if the sexual harrassment becomes public. It was on cnn.

In a sense a guaranteed contract does protect you from breaking the law. If no out, you still get paid. I dont know where you would get a contract that has felony protection. So you get paid while in jail, but if its not there they would still owe you money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Press reports are stating they have an out clause in his contract about sexual harrassment. Supposedly he wont get his full contract. It was n cnn. I doubt they will release the terms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were less extraneous stuff to sped money on. No cell phones or internet. Cable as t everywhere, had less channels so it was cheaper if you could get it. Michael Jordan grew up without watching the NBA because there was no CBS affiliate in his small town. 

I think housing was cheaper because

1. Houses were smaller. Houses have grown in size so this leads to higher prices

2. Suburbs were not as crowded so lower prices. We have not spread at a pace that has kept up with population growth.

College was cheaper because administrators hadnt yet realized they could jack up their salaries by building more buildings and making students pay for it. They are treating a not for profit as a for profit for themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saving the world is too short sighted. We need a plan to save the universe from heat death. This is a massive task. It gets harder every year as the universe expands. If we dont act now, eventually all stars will go out and the universe will be a cold dead place for an infinite future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant be the only one who laughed at his stupidity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nascar should expand into south africa. Same with country western music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Non Americans: Who are the rednecks of your country? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Non Americans: Who are the rednecks in your country? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a 3rd party seller sells a new buttplug, i wouldnt take them at their word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cocaine is an outstanding weightloss drug.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alot of money in middle earth if you can teach people the Dewy Decimal System and how to make folders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw the premeire. I had read the first 3 books in 2000. You just reminded me that it has been 6 years since book 5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luckily most guys are ugly or the human race would go extinct due to women turning us gay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
