<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1772</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beat me to it. First time I encountered that place was during transportation to jury duty due to all the courts in that area. Had no idea such a trashed area existed in LA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You wake up 100% sure your ex is your soulmate, but only realize this the day she's about to marry someone else. What pick-up line do you shout as you burst through the door? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most popular programming language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is a fire and every book in any form is destroyed. Does this bring humanity closer or further away from world peace and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose I'm confused by what counts as making-up. But going by MastaJujubee's definition, that the lack of dating defines them as an ex, I feel I have a better sense of what the actual boundary is that separates the two. Next problem is what counts as "dating", but I think I have a pretty good idea on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, like if I start talking to my ex in a manner that it seems like we're back together, but there's no dating involved, she's still an ex, eh? Awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The second after you're not dating, love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It gets really confusing in my experience with at least one making-up attempt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At what point do you start referring to your ex as an ex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's the creepiest person you met through online dating, and what signs should you have paid better attention to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't respect your time and/or priorities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You swap lives with your SO. What do they see in you that someone else can't offer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a primary client, customer, or competitor started treating you like complete shit, and you always wanted to find a way to get "even" with them to teach them a lesson. Then you find some leverage, what sort of way do you test the air to reinforce the ego swaps? Like, it could be a customer that thinks they can make your life miserable and there's nothing you can do about it. Now that you can do something about it, how do you test the air to see if they understand you can now leverage them? It could be something as simple as "Hey, can you tie my shoe for me?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, the first thing you'd assign them to make them feel like you're the one in power now. Like, to sort of test the waters to see if they can handle your job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The CEO swaps your job with your boss's job. What's the first thing you do to get "even"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D'oh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starting off with a misunderstanding or setting a bad first impression. e.g. like in the parking lot, coming late, or not dressing in a professional manner. Unable to explain your work history in an optimistic manner, without making yourself look bad. Unable to elaborate when questioned on your resume and keep a straight story. Saying you're a lazy kind of person, and/or that you procrastinate with anything. Giving them a complicated answer to a simple question that should have a simple answer. Saying you already have your dream job and don't really need them, just but looking for slightly better. (thought this was a good idea in the past to show you're not desperate, but then if you don't need them, and then they don't need you) Resorting to vulgar speech, and/or getting physical. Not acting professional. And last, but not least, creeping them out, like by starring at their privates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a dude, it's like 90%, and 5 minutes into flirting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ratio of my texts to theirs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something you find yourself criticizing only the opposite sex on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men, what pick-up lines did you find off the internet that actually worked? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women, what percent of those you flirt with do you fantasize about? When does that usually start? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell Ya! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fans that sweep me off my feet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pandora, Uber/Lyft, Hill Climb Racing, MyFitnessPal, WhatsApp, Flashlight, and for the chess players out there: ChessTactics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Them rewinding it to catch the pick-up line they didn't hear well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...you other brothers can't deny... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens in Vegas, stays in Vegas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had to move mine behind my bed when little kids in the family discovered it. Preferred it in the closet though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What matter do you find yourself criticizing everyone on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rubber </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What post on reddit would you be most uneasy about if your boss found your account? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Extra points if you get them in the face </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to keep a sword in my closet, felt similar while having it there unlike a gun which I know I'd struggle to use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> makeshift flamethrower, very nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Attack their heart, good strategy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a hard one... Best I could think of for that sort of situation is ransack the cabinet and hope for something pointy, or a spray. Plunger is a good weapon I suppose. Wait, you're browsing while pooping? Ewwww </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kitchen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you grab against a burglar, if you're limited to your current room? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exploring, trying to find out of place things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 09:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steady job, which you love, with lots of flexibility, being in good health, and being loved back by someone you love which respects you and your time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Merlin in King Arthur, because he goes through a lot of books, absorbing the deep mysteries in their contents, and strikes me as more of an introverted, deep-thinker, that kicks ass at everything he applies his mind to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I commit my work to a repository. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wearing the same pair of jeans all day, and to bed, for several days in a row before deciding to finally change them for another pair of jeans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other than a relative that would fall into the same category, I can think of nothing else. Not really anything I can think of that one would want to hide their deed from the person it benefits other than charity related matters. Maybe Santa and Toothfairy-related stuff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hell is a wholesome secret... "I hid the wholewheat bread where you'll never find it, hahahaha." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last minute, making up for lots of procrastination, and actually successfully completing it within the deadline.
Edit: Oh wait, witnessed, not experienced. Meh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kept losing eye contact to look at the interviewer's boobs. I had no interest in her whatsoever, but couldn't control my eyes as I was inexperienced with the interview process then, and I was unprepared to expect it feeling somewhat like a date. I'm not used to looking straight into a smoking hot women's eyes when they're dressing to kill, returning eye contact, and so interested in hearing about me, much in the same way finding a job is like finding a soulmate. I've also ran into clients on the Ops side where it was obvious we liked each other's personalities and voices. Upon ending off, I found myself restraining myself from saying "love you" as the conversation felt a lot like speaking with a girlfriend that I've known for a while. At an older job, I always had a hard time processing what to think of my boss when he would speak to one of our vendors like she was his wife. Now I can finally relate to that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laundry, never can keep up with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in character with getting pumped up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twitter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> username checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Declaring you have time for family, and actually spending time with them rather than go through your internet habits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5d_WIJOnJrc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Block 'em. They don't listen when I tell 'em to remove me from their list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The XX - Intro](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jkhpZoPOfZI t=16s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing beats mixes in the car in my experience, especially for 100+ mile drives back and forth between cities. [Adam Sandler - Piece Of Shit Car](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Fw0OvKFKhw) really feels like a completely different song in the car, and can be quite amusing. [Agnes Obel - Fuel To Fire (Dexcell Remix)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DzNwsCDClgc) is a random song I found to be great in the car. Some more handpicked stuff I'd put would be [Justin Timberlake - Can't Stop the Feeling!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ru0K8uYEZWw) (great at parties too). I'm a big Linkin Park fan, and driving I was surprised to find that I like [The Catalyst](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=51iquRYKPbs) more than [Numb](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kXYiU_JCYtU) while driving. Gotta have some classics like [Beach Boys - Wouldn't It Be Nice](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nZBKFoeDKJo) and [Lynyrd Skynyrd - Sweet Home Alabama](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ye5BuYf8q4o). [The XX - Intro](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_VPKfacgXao) for some reason I associated it with Muhammad Ali, probably from [this video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jkhpZoPOfZI). Frank Sinatra - New York, New York. [Susanne Vega - Tom's Diner](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YjCsnI-3i6A) and some metal songs like [Enter Sandman  Metallica](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CD-E-LDc384).

But if I had to pick actual albums, I prefer Linkin Park's "Hybrid Theory" album. I've tried other albums from them such as Meteora, but doesn't work as well. Evanescence puts out some really good albums too, such as Fallen. Meticalla's Garage Inc. On rainy days, I can listen to Enya's Watermark album.

But on most days, honestly, I just pull up Pandora and jump back and forth between stations like Linkin Park radio, Smooth Jazz, and Easy Listening radio.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, for oneself or for like a family? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably the only series I ever completed: Harry Potter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I ditch work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to get a new one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a clip-on tie stuck in the shredder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like all of humanity, or just the current generation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> North and South are easy enough. For West and East, I just remember it spells "WE" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First in, last out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because we have the capacity to understand things better than anyone else, and are great problem solvers, with a lot to contribute to the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Windex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, long past that need which is "more of a recoil effect to help you be proud of yourself rather than shamed." At some point everything just stopped mattering, and I focus on the few things in life which do, like procrastinating and posting "meh" everywhere. :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having grown passed the need to feel special. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither, I pour it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone is desirable to someone out there, but if you're attracting the wrong crowd, it's important to be comfortable in one's own skin. Identify and celebrate your strengths, create a future-self, something you want to strive to become, a self you can accept, then strive to help that future-inner-self materialize because that's the direction you want to head in life. Once you've done that, there should be a greater sense of synchronization between one's inside and outside. Even if you fail to do this, if you meet people with similar insides which you also admire their outsides, then you can work out long-term even without achieving this synchronization. Sometimes finding people which aren't in sync with themselves either is enough compatibility to work out. You'll know when you've hit any sort of milestones in this area. And when you've done that, you'll start attracting the right sort of crowds because you're in sync with yourself and it's not a battle of present vs future. But until then, realize there's people out there which you meet which are meant as a lesson, short-term relationships, and there's marriage material. Things like nurturing your health is a great way to move in the right direction to open up opportunities. Know there's also people out there which don't need any sort of relationship whatsoever and don't need people to make them feel better. Accepting oneself, and playing one's hand as best as one can is about the best one can do. Again, everyone is desirable to someone out there. But desiring them back is not always the case. Communication is another issue. Probably half the people you meet actually want to bang, and you'd have no idea that is the case without becoming a better flirt. Sorry for the monstrous paragraph, but hopefully there's something helpful in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point being to bring more truth to the world. Why waste my efforts on a religious person associated with the "wrong" religion that won't get any closer to whatever truth I want to see revealed in the world? Or waste my efforts on someone already revealing truth in the world? Rather, target someone more neutral with potential to reveal more truth in the world as a result of my messing with their equilibrium by getting them closer to whatever truth that is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but you said CAN exist. So you'd benefit from such a haunting. Me on the other hand, I believe they do exist, so getting haunted wouldn't change my perspective on ghosts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they're that creepy, inform people you trust about the situation to get more people involved. Usually when enough people know about what's going on, they figure their cover has been blown and they back off. Or if it's really bad, seek professional help if you feel threatened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atheists, to give them something to believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would a secret admirer want to murder you? Too broad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a direct answer to the question without going into a specific religion. If you're looking for something more detailed, go pick up a book on theology that interests you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trial_of_Michael_Jackson#Verdict </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am introverted, therefore, no fucks given. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Early Retirement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That a man actually once won an argument against a woman. I keep arguing against this that Hilary had the popularity vote and therefore that's nonsense. I lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give him back to the living then :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> computer programming, author, music writing, and farming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michael Jackson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You know what, I'm gay... have fun with the kids." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Did you hear about David?" "Which one?" "The one that just got married" "My side or your side?" "My side. Wait, someone on your side just got married?" "Yeah." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the past catches up with you when you've been procrastinating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a scale from 1 to 10, what's your favorite color in the alphabet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it gives us something to strive for to keep ourselves fit. Took me many years to understand this, and only really appreciated it once I found myself lazy on my ass unable to even run for a mile straight, when my sister was running half-marathons, running the entire time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monty Python and the Holy Grail, MUUUUUST watch. And RE-WATCH.... Oh shit, I forgot I gotta go watch it again now :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Why were you so afraid to put yourself out there and meet new people?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It tries to connect with every bluetooth device nearby and fails if too many such devices are in the room, losing sync for no reason when walking by others with bluetooth devices... how do they work indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get the body I always wanted, but too lazy to build, and pick up some chicks, literally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my experience, it's always been health and/or diet related. Get out there and start running as far as you can, cool down, drink some water, eat something healthy, then do some more running. Cool down to a nice shower, and lay back on your couch in front of the tv and put-on something sports or fitness related, and force yourself to watch it, even the commercials. Eat some nuts or something and prepare for yourself a snack as you watch it. Got a craving for something junky? Remind yourself you want to work on push-ups. Do as many as you can comfortably, cool off for a minute or two, then work on some more and do some sets. Get some more water, then start focusing on some stretching. Got a sudden urge to jump on the computer? How urgent is it, is it just to mess around? Ask yourself what are you procrastinating from. And then start working on some situps. Run a bit more while you try to figure out what is it that you got to do better. Get back, work on some more food, and devour. You'll feel like a million bucks and be able to finally focus on whatever it is you're procrastinating from. In my experience, it's usually communication or understanding related why I'd push something off due to an unknown factor. Do your research and make it your business to become a good learner. It's not about being able to finish first, it's about being able to recognize when you're falling short and goofing off and adjusting yourself with proper priorities, inching your way through when it's the hardest. Like getting in sync with the rest of the world, whether that's getting on a better schedule, cleaning your room, organizing your desk, taking out the trash, doing your laundry, or whatever the heck is cluttering up your life. Start fresh and the world is yours for the taking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Final Fantasy 8. So much talk about 7 and so much coverage on it, don't get me wrong, I liked 7, but I really loved 8. The whole plot with SeeDs, down to time compression and Ultimecia was so well done, it inspired my username. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she doesn't laugh, dodges questions, and treats you like a lab experiment, you're playing with fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "He who laughs last, laughs best." HaHAha *cough* HAHA HA-*cough*-HA-*cough* (dies) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To make it a better world in some way, shape or form by becoming the change you wish to see in the world. Or be Batman: always choose Batman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh, because nothing else matters and nobody gives a rotten egg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I met a fellow introvert that laughed at my stupid jokes, and conversations would begin from complete utter shit and evolve into sophisticated gems of wisdom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you freaking talking about!? I'm laid back and don't go around freaking out if something doesn't go exactly the way I want it to! :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
