<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3183</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> except you didn't film the part where they started it. in fact, if they were acting like that, that's exactly when you would start recording, anyone would really. staged much? and regardless, other people both you that much? lol come on, get a grip? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol and this cryptic message:  
  
The next hero is the Star ( Pto Ross ) worldview </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so sorry! i was totally joking there. i guess i should ahve included /s lol!! 
   
my point being that many peopel ehre really have no idea how much work goes into even simple or small things. Whetehr it's animation or sounds or whatever. When you have all these elements that need to be worked on for a trailer that's a few minutes long it's a lot of work without and resources for something that 1. doesn't get a lot of views and 2. probably wasn't bringing new players in. 
  
The latter point is really what sticks too. The trailers were hoping to appeal to players who liked teh characters or lore. Not so much people already playing the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah! masters degree in sound design? what'd that teach ya? get ya far bud! 
   
pffft, a so called expert. clearly this intern's work with a company like blizzard's resources! 
   
lol people in this thread might be insane. thanks for the insight.and they clearly have no idea how animation works. it's a ton of work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jesus itt people who have no idea how insane animation is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think you hit the nail on the head, "keep the hype up in the *early* days." 
   
i don't think you need that hype so much anymore, for a lot of reasons.
   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you write jokes so bad that they're good? At least with the kind of beginning open mic act, that kind of newbie comedian feeling? 
   
BTW your stand up special was absurdly funny. The preview trailer/commercial me and my girlfriend saw this guy making faces, who then titled his stand up, Faces and Sounds...anyway I didn't know what to expect. 
  
And holy shit were you funny. And that Trumpet joke? Anyway, absolutely crushing on you right now. And if I'm being honest, if it's you and me, 14 days, tops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not even really the point. It's long been understood that the artillery fire was being launched form Russia. It had to be based on the ranges of the guns. 
   
This is the Russian response to the uprising in Ukraine. Not the separatist movement, just the uprising that removed the Russian leaning president for a Western leaning one. It was a movement done by the people of Ukraine and well documented in blogs and the press, internationally. 
  
 Russian Federation  The Russian Foreign Ministry stated on 19 February: "What is happening is a direct result of the policies of appeasement by Western politicians and European institutions, which from the beginning of the crisis turned a blind eye to the aggressive actions of radical forces in Ukraine, thereby encouraging them to escalate and provoke the legitimate authority."[378] According to the press secretary of the president of Russia, Russia considered the events in Ukraine a coup attempt.[379][380]
On 20 February 2014, Prime Minister Dmitry Medvedev stated that Russia could only cooperate fully with Ukraine when its leadership was in "good shape".[141] He added that Russia wanted a "strong government" in Ukraine "so that people don't wipe their feet on the authorities like a doormat".[150] Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov likened threats of EU sanctions "on those responsible for Ukraine violence" to blackmail and said, "The EU is also trying to consider the introduction of sanctions, and at the same time they come to Kiev on uninvited missions."[160]
On 24 February, Medvedev questioned the legitimacy of the authorities who replaced President Yanukovych, saying, "If you consider Kalashnikov-toting people in black masks who are roaming Kiev to be the government, then it will be hard for us to work with that government."[381]
The following day, Foreign Minister Lavrov expressed concern about the faith of the TV channel "Inter", Russian TV channels in Ukraine, freedom of speech in Ukraine, and the abolition of the Ukrainian law on language. He added that his government was interested in "preventing the influence of radicals and nationalists who are now trying to play the first violin".[382] 
  
It's form Wikipedia but it's pretty clearly standard Russian statements. What absolutely can be gleaned from reading between the lines, particularly the Ukrainian Law on Language, is that Russia  lost their guy and is already establishing a situation that discredits the current government. The Law on Language, allowed some regions to allow Russian as an official second language. Now, normally, I would be against a move like this, but considering the circumstances that produced the law it feels much more like a move by Russia to establish solid cultural influence.  
  
One of the things that was a reality post the USSR was Russians travelling to Ukraine who spoke Russian were usually treated poorly. It's a bit of a historical point between the two countries considering the USSR and Russification.
   
The whole thing reeks of Russia striving to reclaim it's 'former glory' it had as the USSR. That's what I'm getting at. And it's probably not a good thing. 
   
And in case someone wants to lob the hypocrite card about the second official Russian language, It's not something that has to do with free speech. Nor does it have to do with people being allowed to speak Russian. In the context of the situation striking down the law was a necessary action both to stop the spread of sociopolitical influence and as a clear message to Putin.   
  
If you think this invasion was Russian plan A you probably haven't read much about Russia. Besides having their man in power the very well were probably trying to influence the regions they wanted the most for a few years already hoping to win them over in a treaty with the leader they had in power. When that changed they used the turmoil as an excuse to make it happen faster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah and pets are different than old people. There's the same people who leave their grandparents and don't help them, visit, and forget their alive or all sorts of cruel but not abusive, jsut fucked up behavior. 
  
That said, it's the exception in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even in the U.S. we have Do Not Resuscitate orders which aren't assisting dying but you feel a person this a certain point that when something does happen there won't be life saving interventions. And you can even get other forms that outline exactly the type of care you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh is that clear? the bucket would fill up eventually wouldn't it? if i had that bucket down everymorning in a shady area it's take teh condensation, a lot because of the fog, and it'd eventually accumulate. 
  
i think. so maybe not the best barometer. 
   
also someone called is occult precipitation. not sure bout that though. he's a radiologist. pretty sure that's like a 'fake doctor.' 
  
man isn't life so cool now? we don't even have to say why or how we disagree with something. We just call it fake and walk away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah but you're a fake scientist that beleive in global warming. 
  
hahahahah. 
  
i'm kidding. please don't stop. but if you want to use this opportunity to berate me, i'll delete these few sentences so the plug looks natural. cause god damn we need more people on the right side of that issue. 
    
one way i always put it to people is that lets say the worst, most shitty done model of global warming is the one to go with. because we al lkind of agree that something is happening. let's say its natural and lets say its slow and lets say there's a 1% chance it's right. that 1% is the end of the world. it's not just a little warmer and nice where we live. it's not oh we don't have to retire to fllorida now kind of change. it's apocalyptic catastrophic kind of shit.  
  
so if you'll agree that there's a 1% change but the results are that bad, why would you risk it when someone says the current models are showing we either act now or don't bother? if one person gave you odds of 100-1 with that outcome and there's a whole bunch of peopel saying it's closer to odds like 2-1 why wold we risk that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol can't help but think of this as a whole big metaphor for a healthy sex life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canada tried it and a couple European countries. 
   
Those are real life trials with populations. Then it's been studied in theory, a lot. I'm not sure if it technically falls under game theory as far as economics goes but I imagine it sort of does?  
 
 Anyway, speculation aside, when people are given free resources it doesn't become a 'eh fuck it *puts feet up*'. They tend to utilize em. 
   
edit: this is an extension and correlate with studies of poverty too. one example from a study in NYC was how could you spend 50 cents on a loose cigarette? As far as price and cost per unit goes, at the time, it was an incomparable mark up. Incomprehensible in our heads. Like you don't have food or rent but 50 cents goes to a cigarette? And part it had to do with poverty being such a stress on the brain, a few things happen, but small enjoyments like that become huge reliefs. There's a lot more going on but simple example. 
   
When they can afford a pack though, things change. Usually they end up saving money, they'll treat the upfront pack as a resource rather than the single cigarette as a 'prize' and most importantly he's not in the store 5 times a week possibly spending other money on other shit. And he has more free time to put toward other constructive efforts.  
  
Like life gets so tough all he wants to do is sit at home and have himself that cigarette. When eh can afford a pack he might sit at home and apply for a better job. Because thigns aren't so shitty that all he can care about and hope for is sitting and smoking that smoke at 7pm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, that's not entirely true. 
   
Iirc, in Britain too there was that long shot horse that put some bookies out of business because of the wagers on it. 
   
Or like the financial housing market crisis in the U.S. in '08. At face value highly unlikely but in reality if you knew more than the rest it was bound to happen.  
   
So in that scenario if you knew something about that team and put down 10k and the bookie, still believing that your just a nutter (--nailed it!) might not be able to pay out the other wagers because of the amount you'll win, or might do so at a drastic cost to operations. 
    
That said, you set the marker for 'black swan' as something to put bookies out of business. And I don't think that's quite the point, at all.   
  
Take horse racing. A horse caps at 99-1 on the boards because anything over that isn't really that different once we get that high. When one does win exact odds are tallied for payouts but it's considered a rare enough event that they don't even show exact odds for it. 
   
In fact, looking at the facts of the situation, the bookies here no it's such an outlier option that giving odds to reflect it's chance would truly not take any bets. These are more likely done up as money makers. If enough people agree with OP to throw 50p on it, the bookies will make a pretty penny.  
   
edit: nvm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 football fans* ftfy 
   
it's a natural part of their psyche </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and generally most of the recipients don't waste. and overall there are improvements in qol.  
   
most importantly their's an increased chance for social mobility. which is really the end goal at the end of the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pffft trying to maintain your privacy in this world? 
   
how noble of you, ha! lol, jkjk. 
  
Def wouldn't share em. It's also why even though I have facebook, I'm super spare about what I put on it. Just seems so odd to me to make facebook read like a biography if someone wanted to. 
   
edit: is that a coating that's crumbling away there? What's it made of? I find it pretty interesting that they 'painted' or coated them and that lasted until today. Sure, it's eroded on the side the wind comes in, or it looks like that, but half of it is still there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ain't that the truth. i moved right through bargaining, "it won't be that bad, I can do my part'. Now i'm firmly in depression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i saw /r/hotones trending and i thought...risky click? it can't be the show! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha cracks me up *it* is the show. Sean Evans is the man, a beast, a legend, and perhaps a god. Is he real? An android? We might never actually know he doesn't have a genetically enhanced tongue. Perhaps the long term damage of dabbing has create a layer of iron there.  
   
I'm kidding though, it's a great show and enjoy it a lot. Glad to see there's a subreddit for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> rawr rawr! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, yeah I'm not sure... WaPo did an interesting article on the idea that he is still in campaign mode vs governing mode. 
   
He's not a politician. He got into this 'way' about him on the campaign trail but it wasn't for the campaign trail. In his head that's what he needed to turn into *to be POTUS*. He never switched off or moved off certain topics.  
   
The saddest thing really is how vehemently people defend him. I hate to really call him out on this but my Dad went berserk the other day. I'm honestly not that liberal. A couple ideas, sure you can paint me with that brush, like healthcare, but I'm a strong believer that my country can do more or the same, at the very least, with less, that we need to monitor and control our spending, and that outside some areas the Federal Government, moving ahead, probably shouldn't be too much bigger. 
   
That said, my pops instantly saw me as a "liberal" talking about the Flynn thing. And the more I think about it, despite not wanting to, I think I have to bring it up again. He kept focusing on the fact it was illegal to leak it. Not because there was any merit to the point but because that's what *Trump* **said**.  
  
And that's why when people joke about the Authoritarian shit I'm not too keen to laugh. There's people who look to Trump and only to Trump for their information and recognition of information. It's not even a GOP thing anymore, it's a Trump thing. 
   
I can't help but imagine that it's very similar to how Hitler gained the support he did in 1935 with all eyes turned on him. And I hate to say that. TO me, that's an absurd comparison, or it should be, except it doesn't entirely feel that crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol i want firaxis to send me...oh wait, i'm not so much an artist. you earned that. 
   
guess i got to keep an eye out for a sale maybe or i'll just wait a bit longer. patience tis a virtue and one i'm actually glad i have a healthy relationship with.  
  
absolutely loved this too btw! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i dont think it's cat and mouse to figure out the leaks. it may be to a degree but this isn't an issue that has had leaks, immigration enforcement. the leaks were intelligence and foreign/domestic security side guys. FBI, CIA, DHS, NSA, DOD, DOS, DOJ and a couple of the other ones you never really hear of the initials or.  
   
There's certainly overlap though and I doubt it would have been leaked by that guy himself. That's just too haphazard.  
   
Just a quick note on the leaks too, I was going to write a medium piece just because it felt like people don't understand how they work in regards to the press. Trump lambasted the leaks particularly in regard to the Flynn leak. That's because Trump was notified weeks prior to it being leaked to the Press. The concern was that Flynn may be blackmailed with the information based on the conversations he had. When the President didn't act the individuals took to an alternative avenue for some accountability for the wrongdoing. Most importantly it was to safeguard the nation and our national interest in being able to make decisions without the threat of personal reprisal (blackmail). The fact he lied to Pence about the nature of the talks was already warning enough that he knew them to be wrong. Those people who leaked it did the right thing. And imo it's a relief to know, that despite his ardent stands in the absurd the Press can still hold his administration accountable.
  
. Granted his Administration is leaking like a sieve, to quote one journalist, but I think that's more with having people not used to this scrutiny and people genuinely concerned with what's going on. Mixed in with a power struggle.    
    
I'm just disappointed. After the election I saw those interviews and said, man he sounds like a President. I had a lot of hope that he'd really put America first at that point. The campaign is over the circus is over. He had to know what the right thing to do is certain situations and he was appealing to what we all wanted to hear, not the 'pc' or right thing. But now that he's in power, and those interviews, he knows what's up.  
  
Who was I kidding. The only thing he did do immediately was the 'travel ban.' Which he effectively made moot by letting it get struck down in court. Which now opens up a flood of people getting in. Like, really man? 
   
Sorry this is off topic, I'm just sad and worried now.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So are we just in a window where the Earth isn't pelted with big meteors? And are they really that hard to track? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 06:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It feels like that, at least the last couple years with the greater prevalence of video camera's we've caught on camera the meteor burning up over Russia and this year one over Michigan (iirc correctly, or that area).  
  
If something like that impacted would it be bad? I imagine even something the size of a football moving at that kind of speed would have a tremendous impact.  
   
I feel like there would be no way to know if these would burn up in time, especially the one in Russia that was larger or is there like an assurance that only Meteors this big traveling at this speeds wouldn't burn up? I guess that makes sense. I know we track some of them but It feels like we'd hear more about those two in particular if we had known about them. Or was there announcements and they weren't big news cause they wouldn't impact, obviously.  
   
A part of all this is whenever you see history of the Earth as it formed it shows period where there were almost constant impacts, bombardments. Now I get this was a younger universe that basically had shit flying all over the place. Since then though there's been a couple (iirc) attributed to mass extinction events. And what feels like no major impacts for a while. Are we in a window of reduced risk at the moment? 
   
I know this all ties into some of the theories of how as advanced life we haven't been wiped out particularly. Which really kind of scares me because when you think of all things that could go wrong all the way down to how our heart cells use sodium and potassium to channel back and forth, it's kind of crazy the details of life compared to the bigger picture too, they really are.  
    
Hold on to your hats, we still got to get through the next 4 years.  
  
It's a joke! Things just feel very combative at the moment, don't take it any other way or ignore it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm curious if a topic has been researched at all, haven't had much luck on google. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey man, i'm not saying i'd get it personally. but for originality alone i think that piece get's a lot of credit.  
   
and generally i think, for a lot of people here in business or just participate, it gets easy to be a critic rather than just a fan. like all art. but if my first impression is positive i'm not going to find a reason to dislike. and that's really what it comes down to.  
   
when i looked at it a bit more i noticed the shading on the water myself. the scale, to an extent, isn't a bad thing.  
    
i have a couple friends with full back, thigh, arm pieces, done in the japanese style. and you're right, maybe incredible isn't the right word because by comparison that's clearly incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah people who like grammar and naturally pick it up...we're much more the unorganized artist type.  
  
the ones who are 'nazi's' bout it are just arrogant and think they're smarter than the other people/dicks for putting it out. 
   
although, to be fair, decent grammar and communicating well aren't exactly things to shun off. probably warrant a bit more consideration than putting things in order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the real question is, at this point, who is receiving the 2 shits? I mean it can't be the first time he's said it, he must have a default 2 shit receiver somewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is it me or is this tattoo incredible? 
    
that's some dope shit, both in its creativity and the work itself. cool stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh don't make fun of me for not actually jumping that high! Sigh, i'll never play senior basketball. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bam! 8'4 vertical! Grabs it! I got it!  
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 01:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it isn't? But you know, you keep on keepen' on in that delusion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's wroth noting you can bake or  suos vide and then sear... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only funny because it's probably true.  
  
I'm jsut not sure how else i'd have worded that in so few words? Sometimse I forget I'm on a website with children though. Because really only a child would read that, think, and chuckle like huh huh! that hurts mah heeead! He must be extra dumb!  
   
Sometimes things get written and it's hard to not make them awkward. Or easy to read. And frankly, I'm not sure why I have a duty, outside of possibly upsetting a couple people's feelings about grammar, for making it easier to read.  
   
It's like everyone need their hand held through everything and it be perfectly laid out. Forbid you make a conclusion yourself. 
  
But ya know, teenagers.
   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You clearly haven't read my comment history then. :) Cheers mate! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh, I don't know. I mean I have no problem taking criticism for being lazy while writing a comment on an anonymous internet board that deserves criticism for being poorly written. 
   
But don't actually imply something that isn't true. That pisses me off. Like you couldn't actually give a valid critique so you just went with, 'oh i don't get it, uhhhh!' 
   
When in reality there would be no other way to word that in so few words.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah must be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's important here is to stop defending Trump by comparing him to Obama. 
   
What you showed there says nothing of the sort, doesn't mention sanctions, or anything remotely near that. How you take that as evidence. It was made in 2012, when we were really sanctioning Russia for anything that bad iirc.
   
Our sanctions on russia didn't go up till 2014 when they invaded crimea. Ukraine is still actively fighting separatists who use artillery, mortars, and heavy weapons (grad rocket launchers) against ukrainen troops. All provided by Russia. That's why we have sanctions against them.    
  
There isn't any argument there. Listen I'm the first person to consider a better relationship with Russia but after the Crimea thing I think it's important to come down on them hard before they have the full Soviet Union together again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hmmm, i don't know what the original quote said but there's is a slight difference between quoting a verified twitter user vs a non verified. in the same sense of quoting random 'new' source x vs quoting the nyt or something. 
   
i'm not sure i'd take any of the two above sources seriously. i mean is it a crime to hire someone as a foreign policy adviser, early on in your campaign because he did business in russia?
   
this is about as conspiratorial as it gets. and all it does is discredit the actual story. which strongly suggest trump new about flynn's meetings and the topics discussed. and all that jazz.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol...i mean...it could be a good source but def not one you should be citing like that. 
    
yeah the ship's sinking for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahahaha no they haven't! sorry, they really really haven't. 
   
but this made me laugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 06:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL there's a claw grabber community on youtube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 06:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ahhh what was that post a few weeks ago??  
   
We're becoming a rare breed.  

Born in the 1980's, still don't have kids! 
   
I was like damn yo, that's some truth. Me and my girl, god it gives me shudders and I probably really shouldn't have children, but sort of have conversations like, well if it happened before 35, right? Yeah def has to happen before 35. Actually our child talk started with, is it ethical to not adopt living in America? Then I get why I'd want my own kid though, I got some dope genes, sort of. Maybe a bias view but, you know. 
    
Anyway, yeah I know what it feels like. I mean I love kids. Other people's kids. For now, maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 06:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's a shame because there's some good content out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 06:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> was it really that hard to discern? I mean Jesus this isn't WaPo or the AP here. I wasn't breaking out my MLA to make sure my reddit comment was grammnazi'ed. 
   
A basic legibility through inference is enough on the internet. We're just lucky there's not emoji's in these comments or they'd really go to shit. I didn't set the standard or status quo, just abide by it. 
   
And really, really. That was made perfectly clear. Haven't these guys ever owned a dog? Or played with a dog? Or any animal? Or had some wild sex even with another human?  
   
Come on.  
   
edit: speaking of inference and implications, *that* last part could have been taken out of context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 06:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i guess it wasn't too far of a stretch considering the starting point.  
  
everything's relative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you also got to remember that people like that it's usually taught culturally/socially and coming from a place of deep insecurity about their own place in the world.  
   
generally a lack of understanding and a willingness to. really you gotta feel bad for someone so sheltered in their own existence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm confused. was the father encouraging it, in the attempt it would bite him to teach him a lesson? 
   
or are they just pos's. 
   
i think to a degree other cultures have a waaaay different relationship with nature and animals than we do in the west. 
   
that said, it doesn't excuse being unnecessarily cruel to something. and not that i want to excuse anything if the lizard was seen as a pest or overpopulated i might understand how a poor attitude forms, especially if it's something commonly killed.  
   
still absolutely no excuse for blatant cruelty. still the kid hadn't quite physically hurt it and got taught a lesson. so without a total translation/understanding i don't want to totally pass judgment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> even if he got the beck proper unless he was biting through it to actually eat it it'd probably be fine. although that isn't an area i'd chance like the shoulder.  
   
then again i also wouldn't trust a child to bite to pick it up vs bite to eat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha i'm really bad at like 'seeing' people too. i'm always like it's blah blah but my girls like no you fucking idiot. i do pick up on the ones that like no one can tell who it is though but i think that's from their voice.  
   
not sure i'd ever put my bets on that one though. seems like a bit of a stretch on the best day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's a good point i forgot that happened.   
  
economically, a trend does seem to emerge though that the more money people have the better off everyone is. and it's the root of a lot of the arguments for universal income. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and i guess to a degree the law is law but on the same note the reality of the high seas is pretty lawless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yall took something way too seriously. i wasn't even going to cite the article. honestly, i don't care so much what yall think my intent was. i'd hate for someone else to see it an assume it was actually true.  so i made that point to everyone else who's taking an ama by some junoir state representative way too seriously. or maybe yall taking yourselves way to oseriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 12:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah like defining the problem as depression and getting into therapy. 
   
not that seasonal depression isn't depression or that an emotional depression isn't depression. 
   
but there's this...man, i don't want to get into some pissing match or invalidate someone's experience. but to me, it sounds like if all i had to do was make a list and break things down into smaller and smalelr tasks to do them, that... 
   
that actually sounds fucking absurd to be honest. and they may think tehy were depressed and very well could have felt when they thought or think is depression.   
 
but hey, whatever works, i'm happy for them. it just seems like...i don't know. and maybe it isn't that it works. it's that there's this tone of oh well it's that easy. and really the only that really will turn that shit around is some form of therapy and possibly medication.   
   
yeah the more i think about it. all this sounds like to me is one day they decided to stop being depressed because they wrote a list. even on a depressed persons best day, it's going to take at least a few tries of this list to get through it. or they'll just pick up their list look at it and feel nothing inside and lay back down or throw it out, because a peice of paper with pencil on it doesn't matter. 
   
this kind of sounds like bullshit to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 11:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't know how true that is. Lotta plankton and shit be floating around. And fish just swim, you know? Lets other fish eat em. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 11:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> neither do i. i've never heard of that. ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 11:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to a degree, because of the nature of the containers not being actively recovered you might be fine. if they aren't actively looked for regularly and it is assumed abandoned, like every other container ever, you'd probably be fine.  
   
especially because it's not like it wasn't recoverable, like a wreck but because they made 0 effort to ever in any instance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 10:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, any kind of scumbag approach is similar to Crassus. He'd probably be a damn good CEO today though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 10:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in its cultural context it was incredible. as someone who loves jazz too, it's awesome. 
   
my girl thought it sounded too much like frank zappa. she's not wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 09:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> very few people in existence have had to continuously tell a story as long as they have. 
   
Even compared to something like ASOIF, which is the only remotely comparable thing, and even that was told over 7 or however many installments written by *one* man. Not monthly patch up dates worked on by 100's of people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 09:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend some fire drills for team building.#justsayen 
   
Think i'm going to wait for my MBA first. Not that I like making excuses. Reality though is finishing my bachelor's this semester, at 29, and don't have any experience to carry over really into that field. Doesn't mean it's not attainably on the horizon though.   
  
To be fair, I guess people presume finance. But I wouldn't presume financial adviser. And a lot of things, can make you a lot of money.  
   
I am a bit curious though. Like the financial advisers I know don't seem to really...I know there's some ass busting work, I don't want people to get the wrong idea. 
   
But I hear so much of 'my advisor has it in Vanguard/Blackrock ETF's.' I got 8% back on my 403b, with a little bit of research. Me and a buddy hit our short calls to the penny. Then again I'm good at picking horses too (kidding that's a ton of work too unless you like to lose money). I guess I'm just wondering, something just doesn't feel entirely right is all. And not in that sense of 'fuck the rich guy.' I can't stand that attitude. I guess with big enough clients though fire trucks become a reality.   
  
Actually, where in finance would you recommend going into? Today and in the next 5 years? I know there's a lot less hands on nowadays with computers. Currency trading interests me a lot but seems a bit niche. Investment banking and analysis related to the tech field definitely interests me. Analysis and research are things I'm definitely good at.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 08:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at the early 20th century. We had a laissez-faire government. They butted out of the economy big time. And sure you can say it was a different time. And to an extent it was. That's why they let 5 year old kids go to work for them. Or families *needed* the kids to work because they couldn't eat. 
   
at a certain point the government has to step in. Now, state or federal? It's hard to make that decision. State can't afford it probably, federal government might not do it right. 
   
That said, they finally did step in on a minimum wage issue. You know how that originally, i forgot what it was called exactly but originally the ruled against interfering to defend the rights of the worker too.  
   
So the heart was way in the right place. Practically though. Not so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 08:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i got told my rx was bad because it was more than a year old. more bullshit. 
   
to be fair though, this isn't an issue with the eye industry, costs including. it's more an indication of the rising costs of healthcare overall and the restrictions insurance puts on those costs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 08:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually this company makes regular glasses too. like prada, gucci, lv, chanel, they don't make glasses. this company makes em all. ray ban too. 
   
too be fair, the higher glasses are good quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was playing NHL 95, or maybe 94 and played the Rangers vs Canucks. 
  
There's like 7 seconds on the clock. I win the faceoff on their end and kind of face off into one timer for the goal and win 3-2. 
    
I definitely just mixed up memories of real life and the game. I was also 7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i imagine people in the blizz office watching this wondering like, do we show him?  
  
or him walking in and everyone wondering, um has he seen it yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so not only did prohibition just suck as an idea it set precedence for the federal government to create laws on a massive scale. 
   
it's still sucking 100 years later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 12:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when i saw that i ahd to post the quote. i was like oh shit people actually end up here looking for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 12:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but that's not an apt comparison. The EPA was created reactively because, and only in the 60'-70's, companies were absolutely wrecking out environment with toxins. 
  
 If it weren't for the EPA we'd still have that nasty pesticide in everything and that other ozone killing shit in everything. 
   
The reality is you can't expect a company to be socially conscionable   
with a 1. uneducated public 2. a public that demands cheap goods 3. bottom line. 
   
If I lived in a world where every company opted for socially responsible practices and fair trade. I'd say man why don't we just adopt true libertarian values and an approach to the gov't.  
  
But socially responsible and fair trade business are the exception not the rule. The idea that without gov't interference companies would opt to do those things, when it was the gov't regulation that got them in line in the first place, is just absurd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 12:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's a fair point. but the direction we're heading in as a consumer is for the cheapest product always. 
   
it's why .50 cent wages and a $14 dolalr shirt are things we buy. or people buy.  and while you make some good points, i'm not sure people would give a shit about dumping. the people who lived near there knew about it "oh you don't swim/fish there, do it here" and the rest of us it's not our river or it's not our problem. 
   
i think to a degree the libertarian thing would only work when starting from scratch, on its best day. or when applied to very niche things.  
   
for the most part the market is run by companies bottom lines. in the sense that, today, the consumer has sort of lost the 'demand' leverage. because of how ingraind purchasing is in our lives. today that's dominated by the cheapest product for us to buy.  
    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 11:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol what? 
  
 it was clearly a ridiculous thing i posted. that i happened to come across and was totally not expecting a response or an equally ridiculous one.  
   
your would qualify except you clearly take yourself too seriously. you're probably 18-22, maybe 16-22 and a bit too smart for your age or you think you are. 
   
if you're not in that age bracket then you need to get out a bit more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 11:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fucking fire departments. 100 years of tradition for one year of progress. 
  
god damn jaws of life have been around for forever. and no, that isn't something a gi can lug in his pack. but it sure as heel fits on your truck. 
   
that's fucking tax money every new truck you order that needs a 'crash axes' compartment. and once you order the compartment for it when this one is done out you'll order a new one, cause what'll go in the 'crash axe' compartment but a 'crash axe?'  
   
bet yall voted republican too. not that there's anything wrong with that. i just think a lot of people get it twisted in their views of gov't bloat. it's bloated unless it's my area/department/field/budget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 11:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how'd you feel about crucifixion?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 11:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> []CaelestisSpiritus 108 points 8 months ago 
This place is dead now. 3 days ago someone took all the trucks and the place is empty now. http://i.imgur.com/zX7KYUq.jpg
   
  
is it really abandoned? dying to know what happened to them! lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 11:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can i ask what you do for a living that your boss affords to collect fire trucks? 
   
second question, do you team build running drills? 
   
third, can i come team build? 
  
fuck it fourth, you hiring? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 11:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah plus it's nature. think about how humans get in a mob mentality. imagine the oops moment that turns these guys into a mob mentality? 
   
then either you're dead. well definitely you're dead and maybe a couple sharks too either from ingesting the chain suit, your gear, or someone defending themselves.   
  
we're too much of the mind we can control nature and shit. there's a saying that compares the east vs the west and it's like, there they build in the flood plain but know they've built in it and expect it to flood, and eventually are forced to move. 
  
here, we build a dam like, fuck you river. actually goes we build a dam or levee's and when it floods or breaks we go oh shit wtf river i built a home here!
  
i might have(!) paraphrased that a bit but think it fits this gif somewhat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 11:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> those are makos i think in the video. i mean i don't know much about sharks aggro but mako's can't be the friendliest sharks to dive with. 
   
outside of the tail threshers would seem better. 
   
like i said though i don't know jack just speculating. 
   
neither would be ideal though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 11:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> those are makos though. not exactly the friendliest shark in the bunch. 
   
i'm pretty sure they're makos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 09:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're lucky to have been far enough away when you flipped over. 
  
Having spent a lot of time studying the ecosystems in the Caribbean nurse sharks came across my periphery enough. The only attacks I ever heard of were of swimmers on their backs or in a similar motion. Because it resembles the rays they often defend their young against. It's also why you see streaking scars on them from the tail whips.  
    
A nurse shark attacks, while rare, often happen with rays near by and/or young. A couple theories suggest that in the sun we look like a big shadow and alert the shark to defend. 
   
Essentially, it's an interesting theory. That said, the bite from a nurse shark is another interesting little science tidbit too. With humans it's mostly just a 'normal' shark bite but for rays the lining of the nurse shark's mouth causes an extreme degradation of the ray's outer skin/protected layer. Essentially allowing the nurse shark to only deliver one good blow before the ray will back off in pursuit off the young. It's being looked into if it's like a kind of slimy venom or just shear sand paper, some of which evidence points to the latter as some human attacks have some resemblance to their wild ones. 
   
So, all in all, I think you should consider yourself lucky that cramp came so late in the getaway. On St. John no less! Imagine! 
    
  
And then you ask yourself, really? really? is this real life? and, you firmly, can tell yourself, no, no that guy is certainly full of shit.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 09:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, i'm sort of in agreement with you. it's something you bought.  
  
But the reality is, Microsoft is probably a company that doesn't need to, but someone else will.  
   
And that's got to be, hands down, the most unobtrusive, meager ad i've ever seen.  
  
in fact, unlike most 'suggestion' ads that actually just looks like a suggestion. Like, hey, if you want to edit photo's we recommend photoshop. and honestly if you got a deal on it too...what's the harm? It's not offering some trumped up fakeo photo editor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 09:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To remove Windows 10's lock screen ads, click on your Start menu, and open up the Settings app: From here, choose the Personalization setting, and then navigate to the Lock Screen tab. Once this is open, find the field that reads Windows Spotlight, and click on the box. 
   
derp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 09:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is it though? those ads are miniscule. also, i don't get those.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 09:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically did the same thing is a gross overstatement though man. 
   
Obama did that, in reaction to two refugees being arrested for providing material support to terrorists. Trump did it on how he felt about these countries and safety.  
   
And a slow down and review vs a complete travel ban and review are two different things. Especially when you look at how it was instituted. 
   
This is what frustrates me. Trump didn't talk to one of Obama's or Bush's foreign advisers. No one who was on teh ground in Afghanistan, clearly. I don't know, he's jsut a guy who does stuff on a whim. It's not how a CEO acts. It's not how a President acts. And it's not comparable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 09:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a quote attributed to you? 
   
Caleb explained to me, I considered myself a Solider of Satan, under the guise of darkness. It was all to kill, steal and destroy,  
   
from this article:https://ourspiritualquest.com/2014/11/27/from-demon-worship-to-worshiping-jesus/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 09:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the biggest and best point against libertarian stance in government. 
  
Like most government, things will come down to a compromise of sorts. You'll get some of what you want and won't win other parts. The biggest gain you'll probably get, or at least hijacked in the name of libertarian, is the repeal of Dodd-Frank. and it'll be like but wait! what about...and it won't happen and we'll be left worst for wear. And it would happen over and over. 
   
It's too much of an ideal. On top of that, the 'free market' just doesn't work. As early as the 60's we were dumping tons of shit into rivers and lakes. The EPA is the first thing most republicans and libertarians use as an example of too much regulation.  
  
I'm not saying our environmental impact studies don't take too long. They do, but even in cases where they think it'll impact this or that, companies tend to get what they want or move to another location in more extreme situations. At least it's good to know if we built there we might have killed off x or y animal or plant rather than just doing it and saying 'oops' later.  
   
Libertarian gov't, in today's world works on the basis that you'll have sociall responsible companies. if it were up to them we'd get paid .50/cents an hour. How can I say that? That's what companies pay workers in foreign countries. And they would here too if they could. When a company makes a decision based on its bottom line the only person that's good for is the company. 
   
And I know, 'well no one could afford the products then it wouldn't last!' 
   

You're right. It wouldn't. Until the gov't stepped back in with minimum wage. Hell 100 years ago we just started passing *Child* Labor Laws. As it is today people can't afford the stuff their own companies make, let alone food and rent. And sure, prices will drop, a little bit, but...lol hell, no they won't NYC just wouldn't have anyone who couldn't afford it living there. *Like* now.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 05:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuck that i can afford ten points easy. 
  
 plus, and i hate being that guy with things like this, but you can keep your self sharp with crosswords and shit. like rig it to take the test every 6 months and score one or two points higher and sell em off. in between just crush out vocab, practice tests, crosswords, brain teasers, etc, and take the test again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, to be fair Scientolojesus might just be that kind of username that needs downvoting...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah the search history thing actually surprised the shit out of me. that that's a legit concern for people because it's just so...arbitrary? i think to adegree there's probably good cause for things like CP but with a warrant they might be able to go back, find what dynamic IP was... 
   
Oh wait, that's not how they do it. They get a warrant, when they know there's CP on the computer and go in and search the computer for it.  
  
It's also why downloading music...now we torrent movies but dynamic IP's make it really hard to pin someone down. Plus recent rulings that IP doesn't equal a person. 
   
Something else people don't realize happens when they investigate or want to know what's up, so much of it really is through a warrant to get your actual computer. But they usually say, hey Matt, we know that's your google account that's logged in. We know that's your Pin you need to put in to start the computer, come on, no one else is using that. And then maybe you blurb something out and it all goes to shit.  
  
Things like facebook posts or revenge porn cases are pictures posted to a website, usually with your name attached or you in the picture. So come on.   
  
And as for the NSA...well...lol. I don't know why this veered into a more LE kind of focus but to me it feels like as far as ad tracking goes there's plenty of disclosure nowadays and the stuff people seem to be referring to takes it to that sort of level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well gotta tell you how much i've enjoyed the ride up until now! 
   
oscars, emmy's, baftas! you'll win it all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I don't mind them so much on some sites and sometimes I turn them off or on. Personally I'm indifferent to the ads I get it.    
   
I kind of get a chuckle when I get something for gray hair or a prostate check. And that's what I mean. If you kill all tracking, you'll know it because your ads won't be targeted at you.  
   
So unless you're going to use adblocks *all the tim* which is kind of a shitty thing to do, especially on some sites who need the revenue, your ads will be for totally unrelated and even out of region stuff. If you leave tracking on you'll get ads that are relevant to your interests and make for an overall more enjoyable browsing experience.  
   
That's what I'm getting at.  
  
And after we talked about this I thought about it a lot more. I'd much prefer a company give me the option to opt out. I know I can trust that. Why? Massive class action lawsuit if they're bullshitting and google is one of the few places to stand up to the government on a lot of  issues, you can encrypt your account, they encrypt a lot of their traffic (even to outside mail servers), and they delete their profile on you when you opt out. Again, I know people don't trust shit but you can't agree to terms, both parties, and then blatantly ignore them The reality is all of what's going on operates inside the law. Doing shit like that is breaking it.                         
  
So, I'm split. Part of me says I have a facebook. I dont use it but I have one so is there a profile of me out there. And if anyone watches youtube signed in or even embedded on another site...lol i don't know man, it's really hard to choose between good ads and understanding what's being sent my way, and even possibly from what source it was tracked vs just totally non relevant ads vs totally unrelated ads vs keeping adblock on 100% of the time.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks 3 do i write something like one love?  
  
nah, nope. that'll ruin the whole thing lol. 
   
jsut kidding man! lots of thanks, really! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha nice!                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                             </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I don't know if I'd generalize like that. Or, perhaps, all you can do with that statement is generalize. 
   
IIRC most scientists believe in some sort of higher power, like a deist philosophy or belief more than a specific god. Or maybe it's agnostic. That said, there is quite a bit of irony with it when you look at how atheists, or the average /r/atheism atheist does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/PhillyD/status/829043047371452416  
  
i got the shirt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's what i thought but we're not supposed to get the snow to start till the early morning hours and i expect it to be cold by then. nyc here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 07:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL:DR I find it frustrating that people will fault an individual for finding a bit of faith and solace in something you disagree with as an institution. When, in many cases, there's a huge gap between the individual and the institution itself.  
   
Yeah you're being overly cynical and just flat out denying the reality of it. Religions often put up a building, sure in the name of spreading it, but in places no one sees any value. And of course they see value in gaining in converts. In doing so they do a lot of good work though, and help feed places that no one else will bother going to or can't get through the hoops of applying U.N. aid. Just as an example.  
  
Religion brings out the best in people and the worst in people. Often blaming the whole organized institution and it's mistakes for its believers good or bad deeds is showing a fundamental lack of understanding of the religion, its faith, and its followers. My personal experience comes from Catholicism and a couple other Christian religions and some Judaism. Besides that I've studied a few others too. Bit of Islam and some of these more unique groups like Shakers, bit of the Mormons. 
   
They're all different. Mormons take to their organized institution and stick by it as a pillar of the community within Utah especially. The further out you go the more like other religions its followers tend to behave like. Similar to Catholicism in the sense that while the Vatican certainly influences some peoples beliefs on abortion for the most part, and this encouraged by every priest I've met, it's a personal decision in how you feel. They'll state the Church's stance on it but ultimately it is up to you. 
  
For all the good and bad in the world, the standard religions probably are about net neutral for the harmed they've caused over the years vs the good they done. As for the average Joe in the Church they probably helps them live a little bit of a better life. 
  
In today's world though the Church and religion hold much less sway and really barely influence anything anymore.  
   
I'm a devout Atheist and no apologist. I just think once people find science they swear off the Church and take "the opiate of the masses" to an extreme.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's even more interesting for me, lately, is to consider if these peopel are using adblock or not as well. If you are, it...I understand the frustration at times but on the same note, not everything is going to be free, forever. 
   
ANd thigns are the way they are at the moment. But besides that, you'd never know if you weren't being tracked if you didn't turn ad block off to check. 
   
And then when you turn ad block off, and if you're oging to keep it off, you have to consider, do I want my ads to suck? or be shit I actually might be interested in?  
   
I don't know. It seems a hard line stance, in either direction, while at root a positive ideological stance, really isn't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 07:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. As a google user who has an encrypted account and exercises the option to turn off all tracking I'll take some risk with transparent invasions over anything else.

Plus if you really insist you can have your history auto clear daily. If you're concern extends past having an encrypted account with tracking turned off you probably should be using a VPN and public WiFi.

There's certainly a level of want into protect your privacy that's reasonable and one that's not, or almost paranoid.

The reality is most of this isn't nefarious to begin with. And to a degree having everything catered to my tastes and interests doesn't seem to be the worst thing really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your tag is kind of white txt on a sky/light blue. so i couldn't read it. my initial reaction though, was why did he use silt as his analogy? 
   
wait! i'm in /r/askscience! lol. 
  
since you opened it up, any other good analogies to come up with? i'm kind of hard pressed to think of any. is a fine layer of silt as thick as a single sheet of paper. maybe newspaper? or a layer of paint? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a feeling that you think you only spoke about it but really have used, clicked, watched, etc something about it that was somewhat related. Or spoke on messenger about it, at the least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree. I think the whole "fb knows x and y about me" this is super creepy but not really a problem.  
  
In the sense that I keep a fb. I rarely use it, so I don't really post and shit. Or talk to people on it really that much at all, once in a whil and usually overseas. I don't know, if you're not on it it can't sell you anything. And if you're not going on it regularly it's not making active money on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol yeah that's a bit of a stretch. just a liiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiitle littlotta bit.   
   
get it? like i made little really big to make it a contradiction sort of.    
  
i'm kidding but really, once people start making claims like that things have basically just become a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah but your'e straw manning that too. he wasn't talking about *jsut* weight gain. he was talking about heart disease and obesity. pointing out that someone might erroneously think switch out ground turkey for ground beef is a cure all when they're still ordering a 32 oz coke from mcdonalds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's true. since oil is used to a degree in a lot of cooking.  
  
or some form of fat. or there's always something to splash. 
   
that said, having working commercially in a kitchen that heat is nothing compared to home and the summer is hot so the beater comes out, sometimes the shirt/top is off completely and just deal with it. 
   
your tolerance for heat goes up a lot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dogs too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't know about this advice. unless it's something that seems particularly difficult to make... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually i think it'd be important to note the graph of routine, non routine, and creative vs menial jobs. It's a chart that basically breaks into 4 sections.  
  
The non routine creative type jobs, like advertising or design tend not to be done by computers too well. Sure a car with ten years data seems to work but other things where creativity is applied are difficult to pinpoint in terms of trends and stuff like that. The other end of it are things that require a delicate touch from humans. It's worth noting advances are happening in this field too and they're even making robots for things like home care for seniors. 
   
Generally of the 4 areas of the graph that are made the ones that are non routine and creative jobs will be the most difficult to replace. Sure a computer puts together on an Earthquake automatically but other events the time u take for data input means you could have just written the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does Syria have Christian minorities and ethnic groups too? Yeah, of course. It doesn't have ethnic divide, nor has it been divided ethnically, for a couple reasons. It doesn't seem like a valid point at all. 
   
To me, it sounded like you read something, applied it successfully to one conflict, Afghanistan, and figured it would apply to Syria too.   
  
Not once have I heard or read about Syrian's considering themselves an ethnic minority from x over being Arab, like a lot of Arab countries. The problem in Syria were much more of a radicalization of group and fighters than anything else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 13:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the contrary here is fire sinking 
   
https://www.reddit.com/r/mildlyinteresting/comments/5rw84n/sunset_reflection_looks_like_demonic_uprising/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 13:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yall just casually talking chemistry over here...lol 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 13:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm not going to. The point being, that theoretically addressing the country's motivations you gloss over their preexisting relationships. To start, addressing the unity of degrees of nations is misguided as well. Especially in a truly Arab country that is run by a totalitarian government. Radical Islam has driven a divide among parallel groups but not parallel people, per say, and often through the use of force. 
   
My point being that you seem grossly detached from the realities of the Syrian civil war and the theories you're talking about are probably more applicable in Afghanistan. Even then it'd probably too simple.     
   
edit: and if you couldn't understand the point being that, in my abrupt halting of making an argument, that there was so much missing in your point that I couldn't go on, then surely there is something missing here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 12:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they suspended the emplyee.  
   
no one is killing their own family dog to sue peta. 
  
then again...still you're insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 12:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah except the company already proved he's worth more by promoting him. They probably didn't realize he is earning less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 11:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear you on you original post too. 
  
It is an entirely valid point. Were you ever in Afghanistan though?   
  
A big part of the recent backlash from these countries wasn't our involvement. It was our abandonment. After the Soviets loss in Afghanistan we didn't build schools or offer aid. We let the country devolve into a brutal civil war and continue it's cycle of violence. So to add to your point, I guess, is that we've only brought war.  
   
It gets a little more complicated when people look at this policy and see us as leaving again. Thus why you had so much ISI support for al-Queda while we were fighting the same terrorists (al-Queda and the Taliban and then just the Taliban).  
   
We've support Saudi Arabia and Pakistan to positive ends right? Where's the love there? lol.   
   
As far as Iraq goes the debaathification and disbanding of the military were two huge factors to the violence in Iraq and the point we are at today. Things weren't so bad when we entered these places and initially liberated everyone. If the hate was that strong there would have been preparations to kill all the Americans when they arrive. There weren't. It only started after certain catalysts and it became easier to point the finger at us. 
   
Unfortunately we were applying more of a you guys are free! You got it! mentality while we redrew roads and people only had electricity for 6 hours a day and the sewers backed up. Youth unemployment skyrockets and the security situation is already not that great. Then a local cleric says, you come and pray diligently like good Muslims, come protect our village too.  He's not going to say protect it from the criminal Muslims, he's going to pick up the rhetoric that's always worked. Protect it from the infidels that are here. We had food and jobs and electric before. Look at us now, obviously it's America's fault (not the rampant looting we did to our own country). Where's the money from the oil? America's stealing it!  
  
Then you have an insurgency.  
  
I think it is important that the 6 year old kid who's house gets bombed does have options in life, because if he doesn't it's pretty easy to convince him to take $10/day and hold an AK-47 in the name of Allah. That said, a big part of why Iraq calmed down was the counter insurgency strategy Petraeus built but, more importantly, the Anbar Awakening. 
   
With the infrastructure we did provide and an example set by their leaders, it takes as much for them to break the cycle of violence as it does for anyone. They now have a historical example set where they stopped fighting and destroying their country. 
   
These things are complicated and I loved your post. I just hate to see a bunch of people walk away like US ME foreign policy sucks, no wonder they jihad! duh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 10:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I don't know if you actually have ever been on the ground in any of these countries or literally just read those three books. Because this realpolitik breaking down of it just is kind of detached from reality in so many ways.  
  
I'm sorry, your explanation of the three nations while valid is even simplifying issues to complex. 
   
And in Afghanistan, certainly this would apply a lot more appropriately. In Syria, with Arabs that consider themselves Arabs first. Over local ethnic lines. It doesn't even begin to touch on radical Islam as a factor nor it's role in converting...  
  
man...I'm not even sure I can take this seriously. 
   
Iran Russia and Syria have long been buddy buddy. Iran palyed a part in maintaining the peace in both Iraq, Basra specifically, and Afghanistan, as far as Herat.  
  
I'm pretty confident you just war gamed this out in your dorm room in Princeton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 10:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> edit: It's more complicated that 'realpolitik' explanation tries to describe. Eventually the war went on a bit too long though and peaked as a humanitarian crisis. It wasn't going to resolve itself, no one was putting boots on the ground in favor of the FSA and that was enough of a green light for Russia to help Assad start to put an end to it. No, it wouldn't be 'crushed' either. Air power helps but it's the same people fighting the same people. The air support and advisers turned the tide, slowly.  
  
To be honest, I'm not entirely sure he...in the top comment's post (the should have been 'best of' really explained it well).  
  
He was on to something with Turkey playing the double game, but then kind of went off a bit on a realpolitik rant, to be frank.  
  
Parallels can be drawn between Afghanistan and Syria actually. In the same way ISI was palying a double game fighting terrorism and supporting it. Turkey offered passage of people and weapons, allowed for a somewhat porous border, and generally was sort of apathetic to letting it play out until we pressured them a bit more. 
   
Most importantly, Turkey sees it like after ISIS is gone everyone will leave. When everyone leaves, again, Turkey will either be left with an autonomous or claimed autonomy of a Kurdish state that is now empowered. To a degree with Assad Turkey had some stability and a big rock on the other side of the Kurds that if it needed to it could squeeze them against. 
   
If Assad looses, there's a good chance Turkey looses the rock altogether and is left with a Kurdish uprising. So they had no problem with letting ISIS do it its thing with the Kurds. After a while enough is enough and they stepped in. I think to a degree, again in the comment from the top post, he's minimizing jsut how complicated teh rival factions issue is and how difficult an enemy embedded with the population and using IED's can be to defeat. 
   
In fact, that post is flat out wrong and I'm pissed it's upvoted as much as it is. The more I read it.  
   
Iran is actively engaging ISIS with Hezbollah brigade and offering advisor's to Iraq. It's one of the reasons Iraq is taking Mosul as we speak. With U.S. air support. And it's not a matter of 'crushing' them. No one wants to put boots on the ground for Assad. Like really?  
   
When the FSA eventually started losing ground, ISIS got some money and oil and people could get paid to fight for them, tehy went to them. Or ISIS rolled up to your FSA brigade and said, "You're all Muslim brothers, we don't want to behead you. We're offering you forgiveness, [Salaat al-tawbah] (https://islamqa.info/en/98030) or the prayer of repentance." I've also seen it spelled salah-a-towba or just referred to as towba.   
  
I'm not going to go ahead and refute all of the top comments referred to post. Russia doesn't need an excuse to help Assad, nor does Iran. It's so far, for Russia, been a bit of a play test of their military's new toys to a degree. Real combat for a generation of pilots that probably, to a degree, hasn't seen any yet.   
   
All things considered people don't want to put boots on the ground. For Russia and Iran it's less of a concern. particularly running it through proxies or strictly through an air campaign now with a terrorist threat. It's also gone on long enough that the humanitarian crisis has hit a peak where people kind of want it to end for the sake of the civilians. 
   
You can't crush a fight like this without soldiers. The Syrian Army probably isn't the strongest fighting force on its own and is probably fighting quite a number of deserted or anti government soldiers who put up an equal fight. Now with modern air support and Russian military advisers the FSA is losing ground faster. ISIS looks stronger, recruits more. Gets its aid through TUrkey for a while and ended up being the somewhat more hopeful, to a degree having a bit more cash at times, and, like other situations, always had no problem using the threat of violence to convert FSA or any other group's soldiers to their own cause.  
  
Especially when they don't jsut threaten you, but threaten to kill everyone in your village too.   
   
Sorry I got a little repetitive there but that 'realpolitik' explanation is borderline at absurd. At best, it's a gross exaggeration of what's going on. The reality is the war has gone on a bit too long. Has peaked as a humanitarian crisis and people kind of used it as a reason to step in and encourage someone to end it. The lack of stability is never a good thing and t here's a bit of oil and future influence to grab. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aww man. when it came out i had a couple extra bucks and should have got civ6. at first i said, oh not sure my pc would run it. bullshit. then i said, let me see how it is first. bull shit ( we know it's good). then i saw all teh screenshots and said oh it looks okay. (bullshit) 
   
now that i'm like damn i should have bought it, i'm stuck waiting a bit more till  i have some cash to spare again. :(. 
   
i was gonna boot up civ 5 or beyond earth but it's just not going to get the fix that civ6 us clearly providing, what it seems like, every person in the world (this sub?). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i love how we can all fill in the missing part of the title: 
   
Then fights [insert bruiser on team x]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 19:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lolol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So imagine that is a tiny fire that we've all seen around a camp fire. 
   
Probably a sunset.
  
edit: still probably a sunset. It does looks like a fire in the ceiling that's busted through and a piece of ceiling just fell down catching whatever it did on the way. 
   
we're used to looking at controlled fires that are a certain way on purpose. An uncontrolled fire is just that. And, naturally, isn't going to be recognizable to the fire's we make on purpose. That said, that much fire, the room would be hard to see at all from the smoke build up.
  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
