<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1137</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'll probably stick with this for a good while! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I though it couldnt be helped, but its no problem, i kinda wanted the sight anyways haha. I didnt buy it for collecting or something like that, as i said just a simple rifle to go shooting, and get back into hunting. 

Maybe I'll buy a more expensive/ more nice rifle later! :) 

Thank you for the help dude, really appriciate it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright thanks guys.

I know this post is probably shitty for the community, and im sorry about that. Guns are really not my area. I know you all have your inside jokes here that takes a while to get used to, i know all about that since im part of another community where i've been for years.

I just needed help with the rifle since i wanted to know a bit about it. Not very important to me if its raped or not, i just wanted a simple rifle to go shooting with every now and then. 

Anyways, thanks for the help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 70 bucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least i'll take good care of whats left of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just bought it since it was cheap as fuck and i need a cheap simple rifle, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like living dangerously </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love these photos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help identifying this Rifle. I've bought it and its on its way to me, but this is the photos the seller sent me! :) Thanks! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 10:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, didnt really buy it for colelcting, i just got it cheap off some dude and I wanted a rifle to go hunting :) 

He said the rifle was modded at some point and fitted with a scope.

Thanks dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 08:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A repro? Who made repros? 
I'll provide pictures when i get it.
Im still waiting for it to arrive hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 08:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okey thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help identifying a rifle! Thanks! :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woaw, thanks for the info! 
Appriciate it!:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Paid Request] Need someone to draw me sitting on a Norwegian WW2 Tank! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,

Im looking for someone to draw a artwork of me sitting on a Norwegian L-120 Landsverk Tank from WW2! :) 

I looking for someone with some kind of cartoon/anime style, it does not HAVE to be one of those. I will consider every style! :)

Here is photos of the tank: http://imgur.com/a/uzd8t

I will provide pics of myself to whoever i chose to work with :)

Though:

Me sitting on the tank with a rifle on my shoulder. 
I would like to have some pouches and maybe a backpack on me too. Also i would like a cigarette to be drawn in my mouth, like a victory cig.

The Tank will be standing in a field with a forest behind it, and i would like there to be some fire and some devastation around the field and on the forest. 

I would like the picture to be at least 1920x1080 in size, so i can use it as a wallpaper! :) 

Message me or leave a comment if your interested! :D 
Also i need to be allowed to use the artwork for my website.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 11:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll be playing mostly CS:GO, League of Legends and Heartstone! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EVENT]Setting up for our anual local LAN-party in Norway! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 09:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Black, i changed out all the seats and the interior of the doors, from grey to black. The old seats were a bit worn down so it was nice to get them out. 

Switched out all parts that needs to be switched, since none had been since 86 x)

Threw in a subwoofer and some new speakers wich made it pretty nice. Also very litlle rust! Picked this car up in Amsterdam last year and drove it back to Norway! ;D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, thats really a long time, 100 % sure i'll sell it within 2 years xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Logitech C922 or C930? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 13:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey!

Im gonna get myself a camera for doing informative videos on my Military collection items. (i collect gasmasks, helmets, etc).

Wich of these camera would fit best? 
I've heard alot of good stuff about the C922 but the C930 is newer? 

Anyone know wich one is the "best"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 07:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha damn, decided to keep it 

https://imgur.com/gallery/qj31W </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck, i feel you my dude  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it so hard for me to sell my car </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im planning to sell my 1986 Mercedes 190.
Its my first car and i've had it for 8 months.

I want to get a 2007 Volvo V50, cause i miss the comfort in new cars.

But for som reason its so goddamn hard for me to sell the car. Im always torn between selling or keeping it. Like, i would love a new car and it feels great when i think of the new car, but i become so sad when i think of leaving my 190 to some random person :(

Does anyone have any tips on how to deal with this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
