<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3288</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Release date? (probably not but still) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Immersion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GET HYPE!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that`s something I guess. But I would rather have the truck drive themselves out of the map after transporting the inf. I mean, if they already have a system for units falling back on their own, why not aply that to trucks so that u controll the truck untill u order the inf to unload, and after that the ai takes over and drives the truck out of the map? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is known. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this what people would call a "shitpost"?
:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don`t know why people say that, it does not look like Mcfarlanes ranch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, doesn`t look like Mcfarlanes ranch to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do 1 or 2 horse racing missions there, and Cueva seca is where Nigel West Dickens hides out. Also there are some plants needed for some challenges only found there I think. But yeah, it`s kinda underused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything by johny cash. Would like to see a radio feature like ing gta 5 but it would never fit, but having the ability to make your own background music could be cool. 

The music in rdr 1 was fantastic, so I feel safe that whatever Rockstar does it will be beyond good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love that song! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first opinion is that the game overall looks pretty good, but the aracde aspects turned me off a bit (not too much though). But after reading some comments from players who apparently played the beta they say that the gun trails and overzised units and bombs can be turned off if the player wants to, and that solves most of the problems. Still don`t like the fact that transport vehicles just dissapear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. Very good. That was my main concern I got from the stream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah true that. We`ll just have to wait and see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just hope we can turn it off or tune it down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it was good but looked more arcady than wargame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think u can just find it on the site later???
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best stream ever. :)
Edit: Don`t like the arcady way the inf transports just dissapear when inf exit the vehicle. And I really hope the gun trails can be turned off or tonded way down, same with some of the AA, it looks like they are shooting giant flameballs. Seems so arcady.
Also, is that a healthbar I see over the units??
2nd edit: Where was the pegasus bridge? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember reading this article a few weeks ago, talks about the same subject: https://www.rdr2.com/news/red-dead-redemption-2-gta-online-comparisons-pointless/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I gotta say you have me convinced, I`m a bit worried now thb. I did some reaseach on the gta 5 singleplayer dlc and it is true that they basically confirmed that dlc was in the works, but then gta online happened. I Hope they don`t do the same to RDR 2. Any free update is a good update, but when I think of rdr2 is first think abour singleplayer, then online, and I hope that they don`t change whatever plans they have/had because of gta online sucess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I hope this isn`t the new way they are going, grabbing the money instead of delivering on promises. But that said, RDR 2 must have been in development for years already, before the great success of gta online, so I would think that the outline for RDR 2 online was already set before the micro transactions arrive in gta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess we`ll just have to wait and see. True about the "no more singeplyaer dlc" for Gta 5 though, there were rumors a few years ago but that seems to have died down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda true, but I guess we`ll find out in the stream later today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hm, could be I guess, bot red dead is more serious than gta so I kinda doubt they will add that kind of craziness in the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. All multiplayer updates ro Red dead were free as well.
2. Shark cards are really not game breaking, since all they do is add a n easy way to get money for people with big pockets or little time, nothing is locked behind a pay wall.
3. Rockstar has not stopped update GTA online with new content, just yesterday they added a new car. For free.

And besides I think Rockstar knows that the GTA fanbase and Red dead fanbase is different, and we don`t know if they will add microtransaction to red dead 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that would be great. But they would have to give us the option of deciding who to let in or not, I don`t want no random dude walking inot my cabin at will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dunno, but I dobut Rockstar will turn anything into an mmo. They add what is fun, so I feel safe that whatever they do it will be fun. If not we can just scream very loudly and ask them to remove or add something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then my answer would have to be: Who knows? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just really, really hope they bring back and expand on the newspapers from rdr 1. Loved reading every bit of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubt Rockstar would want to spent time and energy on a nintendo console. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they bring the housing option over from gta 5, I really like it. You could by a little cabin in the woods, a ranch on the prarie or a house in one of the citites. And instead of a garage you could have a stable where you could store all your mouunts and choose at will which one you want to use, instead of having to go into the bloody outftter which takes forever. In your house you could also change clothes etc. Maybe if you could by a farm you could get money from it and run it like a business? (could fit singleplayer more though)
And I don`t think people need to worry about dlc, Rockstar is one of the best game devs out there and all dlc they make is free, just look at gta. Sure, they added the options to buy in game money but it`s nothing you can`t get by just playing the game. And the dlc they could add would most likely be in the way of more mounts, weapons, clothers (houses?) and game modes, so the online part of rdr2 has a lot of opportunity imo.

It would also be cool If they added a bandolero systems, where the ammount of ammo you can carry is based on the bandolero you have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just remove the colour and it could almost be taken for the real deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they add a saddle system like in the Witcher 3, where the saddle U use can boost horse stamina and enable you to carry more in the saddlebags. There was far too little horse customisation opstions in rdr 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can only get so hyped :) The frontline mechanic looks badass, the way it shifts and moves, and can even turn into pockets. It`s my ww2 rts dream comming true! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well they just posted an update about a little blue car thing so their 2 days silence is over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would they release anything this Thursday? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somone should check out how much time went by between the first teaser trailer for rdr and gta 5 untill the next trailer arrived, maybethere is a pattern?
Ok so kinda depressing: The first trailer for gta 5 was released on november 2. 2011, and the next trailer on November 14, 2012, almost a year later.
The first rdr trailer arrived on may 6, 2009, and the next arrived November 30 that same year. Not a full year between these two trailers but still a good half year. So if these trailers are anything to go by it could be at least another month untill anything new, and at worsk quite a while longer, maybe not untill summer (at least if they plan to release the game by fall) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
