<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2577</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone else in my group has had a good 10 items and I've still not had 1 :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except that it's mostly middle class gentlemen at rugby games where it's 99.9% working class at football games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ni. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking m'ladies telling us we should be offended by postive comments made about our people. You can make positive comments about my race all day long! It's only the negative ones that we are offended by. You need to live in the real world and not the internet world where everyone is 'offended' by everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How quick we are the jump on the racist bandwagon, how about doing your research first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your 4 edits, for example is essential what a thesaurus helps you to do; i.e. find alternative ways to say the same thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no way a normal person wouldn't look up when you're told you're on the kiss cam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hatched 8 pinsirs in a row when they were 10k eggs. Was absolutely furious, especially as I still don't have a snorlax! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the usual kind of children interfering you get with the BBC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's already 20 to see a movie in London cinemas, probably be 50 to see a movie at Heathrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not the messiah, he's a very naughty boy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I've ever seen an episode of match of the day where there weren't any dive replays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents are 5'4, grandparents under 5 foot but I someone managed to be 5'10. I'm quite happy with that.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whereas in Europe 'people of colour' is super outdated, so it's odd for us when we see it being used on American tv. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe I haven't heard this. Well, done

Really? It was on the first page just yesterday :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was a dirt poor teen/youngadult, saving up for/during university, I worked double shifts making dough balls in a warehouse; it would take me 2.5 hours to cycle to work, I would then work for 16 hours then cycle home in 2.5 hours. I used to get in, shower,eat and be asleep in under 10 minutes.Then I would have just under 3 hours of sleep.

I did this for 6 days a week and basically spent every sunday recovering.
I did this all summer long and during our other school breaks.

Looking back I don't know how I did it but honestly at the time I didn't think anything of it as I desperately needed the money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 02:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snow White and the seven dwarves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At my uni we had an unwritten rule not to take any photos of professors who came to any house parties. At the time I didn't think about it as it was just a professor dating a student and they are both adults.

By the time I hit 22 I had outgrown freshman girls and looking back I find it a lil' creepy that 30 year old men/women were dating 18 year old guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand in what accent mom rhymes with Vietnam.

Does the whole world not pronounce it mum? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won't lie, I shock quite a lot when I hatched an 100 dratini, the fear of crap moves when I finally evolved it to dragonite was immense. All good though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once get sent out of my biology class because when the teacher turned around and asked why I wasn't writing I told her I'd already written it down; which I had because she used to speak outloud was she was going to write.

I had to wait for 15 minutes outside the class before she checked and apologised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full time mums always thinking they're experts on children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh my friends have all seen me a lot worse than what's in my phones photo folder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My books to read before 30 list is going to take me at least 40 years to read! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I closed my Santander account because they would constantly take  a week to put through my monthly wage but would take out instantly my bills due on the 2/3rd of each month so they were constantly fining me for being overdrawn even though I never was.

Changed banks and the problem was solved straight away and haven't looked back since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 12:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently I'd be 62.41% less likely to go to prison. Yeah if I kept my mouth shut about gays being equal :X </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The North remembers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first idol that I can remember dying when I was a kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If ever I asked my mum a question she would *always* say 'if I tell you, you'll forget but if you look it up you'll remember'.

Years later she confessed that she was just too lazy to answer all of my childhood questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subject2577 will always know the next perfect line to write in this book.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 00:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if your mum had a last minute chance of heart and decided to cancel the hit on you two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 00:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still not pick up any evo items :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm suprised it didn't air alongside the UK release, you guys are in for a treat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably the deathly hallows symbol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wearing a red shirt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My main concern would be against skeleton Jesus and the other prophets. That's an extra layer of magic right there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nukes would kill us and the radiation fallout would kill countless more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 800 coins for a tophat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 03:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PILLOW! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 03:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had one sub teacher for our French converstation class; except she couldn't speak a word of French and then she started to cry (hysterically) when we began speaking in French to one another because she thought we were mocking her. Truth be told we were talking about football.

The head of year had to escort her out and then told us we had a free period. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 03:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can put a man on the moon but we can't have a smartphone that lasts for a week on one charge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know hermano you can just tell your Netflix you're in the USA ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You 'just' need 50 candy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As if the UAE will have any money in 100 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  107.7 * 10 = 1075
  TIL

OP did ask for maths tricks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 04:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought spotify would be bossing this, every part I've been to has spotify playing. Who in the hell is using itunes :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was Friday's episode, we've had two follow up episodes since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are these crows, I'm gonna start puttin $100 bills on the railings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They still use my picture, from 1998, on my old schools prospectus! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I must be in Tom's house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A later Owen quote

"Hitler didnt snub me, it was FDR who snubbed me. The President didnt even send me a telegram.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Running used to be but it's over $100 to enter some races. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope it comes out soon, both my parents desperately need them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even as a child I knew the Daily Mail was full of crap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 04:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a broke college graduate. I have neither the time nor the money to play games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 00:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realise America still practices MGM right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cut his dick off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 01:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone got a mirror? Link is dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 01:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some trivia for you.

Whipped cream in Dutch? 'Slagroom'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 23:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always watch the super bowl on the BBC, they don't have adverts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's soo weird when Americans have to say the country too. Just say Paris, Berlin, Madrid etc., unless you state otherwise we will automatically think of France, Germany, Spain etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given that Jen is 14 years younger and female, odds are Pratt would die first, in 40 years. That would still give Jen the chance to go into hibernation after and still be the same age as if they alternated/lived alone for 44 years. She'd only be mid 60s, so would still have her chance to become a famous writer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you get an edited version of websites, so many people don't know it's edited. Like the BBC news website in China is very different from the uncensored version we get in the UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened during my A level exams, one guy coughed and it ended with the entire hall coughing and the head of year shouting for everyone to be quiet or he'd fail us all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember a few years ago New Scientist wrote a brilliant article basically saying that mdma is fantastic for vets with ptsd as it allows them to talk about their traumatic past, without the negative emotions/breakdown they would have if they talked about it normally. Then afterwards they would feel much better for having talked about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're telling me that I would have been a leftist uni graduate at a time when my grandparents almost died of starvation, whilst living under a Fascist regime? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing an interesting thread on reddit but then seeing it has thousands of comments and knowing that whatever you contribute, it won't turn into a discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came in to to ask who can't see properly underwater. Turns out I'm a 'sea gypsy', swam most of the time as a kid tbf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only like 250 ($315) a month in the UK! Try living off of that!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That men are expected to pay for all dates. I also find it's a very disproportionate ratio the amount of women who say they wouldn't mind paying (in theory) compared to those who actually offer.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Original Picture](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C2zWT1WVQAALLRG.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> According to wikihow this is a drawing of Obama, Beyonce and Jay Z </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit ChunkyLaFunga! I literally have that username across hundred of sites, I bet the few major ones that I don't have you're the one that's taken them!

I can't imagine there's more than two of us using that username! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never spent $8 on a sandwich, that's just ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 03:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who would have thought the white Englishman would have gotten bored of a tribal tattoo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 03:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've literally never wished it was colder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to date a girl that was always late for everything, it wasn't until we lived together that I realised she just didn't realise that on average it took her 2 hours to get ready. She thought she could get ready in just 30 minutes.

After I had a candid discussion with her she then arrived on time 99% of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came in to say that I just tried this (from a wiki page that I created) and I got stuck in a loop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At our company when people do have records, we always have a candid discussion to find out what happened and what they have done to get their life back together.

We had one guy who had spent 20 years in prison because he got home to find two men raping his wife and murdered them both with his bare hands.

He wasn't a violent man or a psycho, he just reacted in the moment to a devastating scenario.

He's been at the company for 10 years and he is an absolute star but soo many places instantly rejected him because he had a criminal record and didn't bother to find out what happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 04:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 00:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Online petition to have him removed](https://www.change.org/p/pour-la-destitution-de-roman-polanski-comme-pr%C3%A9sident-des-c%C3%A9sar-boycottc%C3%A9sar) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Child Rapist, Roman Polanski, picked for The Csars (French Oscars) panel, sparking outrage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 00:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 20:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is more Jerry reasons but my friend broke up with 2 girlfriends because.

Girl 1. She had 'man hands'.
Girl 2. She wanted sex too often (i.e. daily). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 20:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where can I buy a hoverboard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm struggling to understand this observation because I pronounce it this way. I wish I could hear how people are saying it incorrectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 14:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pure water gets you passed drunk after one shot and alcohol has no effect on you. To the work you would look like a severe alcoholic.

It also be very expensive to drink day to day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact, Adolf Hitler ignored the Christmas truce. Honestly the more I hear about that guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Source](https://www.etsy.com/au/shop/JosephGuilfordArt) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 13:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downvoted for stating an [actual fact](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/British_Isles) :S
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really thought it was only last summer. 3 years!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I created the Stevie Wonder page, I feel like that was the highlight of my life :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smart Car, Dumb Parking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 11:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 03:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find, that if I just sit down to think the solution presents itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 23:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're actually taught about this in the medical profession. It recently came up in my yearly tests, it's called [Bataris box](http://www.mmr.fr/images/newsletter/betaribox2.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 15:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [Source](https://www.worldwidebreastcancer.org/), has a bit more info too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Signs Of Breast Cancer Explained; Using Lemons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 15:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 01:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't even afford to live in a tent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Matt Damon in 'blacking up' controversy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 01:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 22:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> European here, no need to worry about saving for medical bills. Higher tax and all medical bills covered  lower tax and paying for medical care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 21:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a question, I just wanted to say thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 18:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no greater feeling than leaving home, starting a new life abroad and freeing yourself from the cultural shackles than your family tried to impose on you as a kid.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 03:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to university and I earn less now that my uneducated mother did at my age and that's before inflation! Absolutely ridiculous how shitty wages are for our generation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 03:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's one box ticked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still part of the British Isles though :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every country in the world has censorship, at least the East is blatant with it. Westerners don't even know it's happening in their country 90% of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 11:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always money in the banana stand.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
