<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3788</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 13:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh absolutely. Unless I know the item I'm buying, I will never buy something without first purchasing it. That is my general rule of thumb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a good shot at Retail Arbitrage? If so, what should we all lookout for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had that on my completed listings for a while now; helps determine the velocity of sales for a given product.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's their business plan and for them to figure out. If you know your market and have done your research, as long as you get paid at the level you want, then you have won the sale. I make a lot of money purchasing items that Sellers have not done their research and just list it for a garage sale price to get rid of it, when a small inquiry into the going rate could have grossed them 25% more profit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In those instances you can sit back and laugh. 

Basis of the story is he took a risk and it didn't pan out in his favor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There isn't anything wrong with it. It's how a lot of us on here make our money. We buy something at a low prices, compared to what the item is worth, and then sell it at a higher price to make a profit. Where the item is sold is pretty irrelevant. 

I exclusively sell my items on eBay because there is a larger base of customers. But, I buy most of my items on Craigslist and Letgo; that doesn't mean though if I see something on Amazon or Craigslist I won't buy it and resell it on eBay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was an antique book I watch as a collection. I don't generally flip college books unless I pick one up at a garage sale SUPER cheap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make your own with ALOT of tape and cardboard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just did this. It's actually REALLY common on eBay. 

Bought a book for $50 and sold it three days later for $135.

They may have had an auction already going and their item sold once they bought yours, that's not how they should do business. They should have received the item before listing theirs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I do this pretty regularly. I have a few categories of items I watch and know the prices the variables sell at; anytime I see something $20+ below the market value, I snatch it up quick! 

Arbitrage for the win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bought a book on eBay for $50.00 Buy-it-now...re-sold it on eBay for $135.00 five days after I received it from the Seller.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm super cheap. I will actually buy the biggest ones and cut the size of what I need and just use tape to make my own; I usually get 3-4 mailers out of a 12x18. Lmao

That's a great find though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are making that much you may want to ask your CPA about forming a business entity and taking the sub-S election to avoid the self-employment tax. Also, the sub-S election will allow you write off more of your expenses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the whole point of the shotgun clause. Any of the shareholders owning stock attributed to the buy-sell agreement, which has the shotgun clause within it, has the right to invoke it; it's just a type of exit clause. 

It's going to come down to how and what effects result from the triggering shareholders perspective. Remember these types of issues are rules by the language of the contract.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get a better paying job with a High School Diploma... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two Burton Snowboards...told myself I was going to list them in the Fall, before the snow. Winter is now officially over and it's Spring...still sitting in my basement unmolested. Maybe I'll get to it this Fall...maybe not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fatboy ones? I love those old things. I had a 64gb one, but sadly lost it camping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UPS Insured.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure one of them is Mark Wahlberg.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would do it for $0.50 per listing. 

I've been on eBay for over 10 years and can do this in my sleep. 

PM me I take Paypal payments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea,man! You gotta watch out for those damn fireworks, you never know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a hotel. I would recommend it just to take some extra stress out of the picture.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have refi'd  your loan through a private lender you DON'T qualify for the PLSF.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 03:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. If you have PV panels or other forms of renewable energy the surplus you generate can either be stored in a battery or sold back to your electric company. Most electric supplies have requirements you'll have to meet in order to qualify, but it is possible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the damn disclaimer AFTER viewing the photo... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Undoubtably the same heritage...and the same personality trait! Haha 

I love beer as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might need a permit from your city. Also, your homeowners' association may need to approve it (if you have one). Alsoooo, if you want to sell back surplus electricity to the grid there are certain requirements you may have to meet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife and I have lived in our house for 3 years...have never turned on our air conditioner. 

I unplug everything I can if it's not in use.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would second this. You use to work with her, but now she is looking up to you; your relationship is in a different capacity now. I would schedule a meeting with her and just sit her down and explain how shit works. Be real with her because no one else is going to look out for her, all they will do is take her money and leave her with no skills gained.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand what you're saying. I have a few people one both ends of the spectrum, and my state has a mentorship program for young Attorneys as well. I'm not one of those newbies who is too afraid or proud to as for help if they need it. I pride myself on being able to be taught something 1-2 times before I can take off on my own. I'm humble to the fact that I still don't know a lot.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just lost it too. "LAW HAWK!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The eagle sound at the end is the icing on the cake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's seriously misleading! BAHAH...why?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I...would...NOT want to mess with this lady.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. 

I found that the outline I obtained had the law right there for me. The cases can be extremely dense and it's difficult to extract everything you need. 

I don't have the outline because my computer crashed, but I will reach out to a buddy I took it with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's part of the game dude. 

I got the same treatment 2nd term contracts II...teacher caught me unprepared week 1 and wouldn't let up for the entire term. I made it a point to over prepare for class and answer fully every time she called on me. 

Towards the end of the term she would call on me and ask a simple question and then abruptly cut me off and shoot a random harder question to someone unsuspecting; it was like clock work actually. I found it annoying at first because I had shit going on as well, but towards the end I found it amusing, almost like a subconscious game we were playing with the class.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, simply amazing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As of this moment I do not have my license. I'm aiming to hang my own shingle and focus on business, real estate, and estate planning. I was going to also do traffic violations/tickets as well, but no major crimes or personal injury matters. 

I do have a few mentors that I can and will ask questions when I get stuck or need a nudge in the right direction. If it comes to it I know they would all jump on board and help with something if it arose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did this judge get reprimanded by the Georgia Bar?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thought...haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valid points. I'm in a similar boat rank wise. I started Law School not knowing what to expect and piled way to much on my plate. From my second term on I held a A-/B+ average, but still closed out the degree slightly under a 3.0 because my first two terms were horrendous. Realistically, I'm one of those individuals who has both sets of skills and that's why going solo always peaked my interest. I didn't get in this game to drown under someone else's paperwork. I'm actually learning a lot about myself in this time of transition and it has helped me understand my true goals. I'm a hustler by nature and always buying/selling things. My true passion is real estate; I'd like to eventually invest once I'm financially stable to do so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Appreciate this. 

There are a lot of job opportunities in my regional area with the title "Attorney" and I know once the license comes it won't be as hard to find a full-time position. My goal is to alleviate some of the stresses my Wife has encountered while I went to law school. We understood it was an unconventional investment and was going to take time to produce. The goal is to make $45k+ which will allow her to quit one part-time job and focus solely one her other one. I'm just frustrated with the current status of my life and the fact I'm being severely underpaid. I was given the opportunity to work over time and have put in 60 hours each week since then, even then I'm still underpaid in my opinion ($15/hr base; $22.50 OT 1.5x). 

I have been networking with the Attorneys I work with and they have introduced me to a few others who have came to the office. I will continue to build a network and create possible opportunities as time moves forward. I know it will be easier once a few other variables fall into place...the rest will work itself out. 

Thanks again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Understandable. I've had to turn down a considerable amount of work I could have done had I been licensed. I have a base established and I know I could expand on that if I was able to market myself as an Attorney. This license is really holding me up from moving forward with anything, I don't know what to do and I don't know if I should do anything else before seeing if I'm going to get licensed; it's quite annoying. 

Edit: Everything I've worked for is contingent upon a license I may or may not receive. I don't know what to do if I don't get licensed. If I do get licensed, I know what I am going to do. I'm in a phase right now of uncertainty and it is wreaking havoc on my life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing IBR currently. I was victimized by a notorious private school. My wife and I live a very low key and modest lifestyle, we wouldn't have an issue using my salary to pay off my loans. Even if we did it for two-three years we would still be much better off, in my opinion, than going IBR for the 25 years. 

Why do you say a clerk position would derail the career I don't have? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate the candor. I think that's the crux of my issue, I don't know what to do because I haven't been doing it...so how do I know what is what without trying things. 

It's not that my heart isn't in crim defense, I just have never done it and always shut it out of my head...until now. I just want to work, make money, and pay my bills; I don't care what I do. I see what your saying, I have always done things in a semi-linear pattern so my experiences/education have lined up so that's how my brain thinks long term. You just helped me decide, thanks. 

Fuck student loans. I would ideally find a job that qualifies for the PSLF program, but getting into a municipality is like hitting the fucking lottery. All the job descriptions are like those jokes you see where they require you to have everything under the sun...then when you go and deal with those people your stunned by the level of shit they hire. SMH!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm severally torn on. I did not take steps in law school to be on Moot Court or Law review and don't have a strong drive to practice criminal defense...even though that's what by background is in. I am more interested in business, real estate, and other transnational work--but criminal law is something that has always come to me and it's something I know intrinsically. I feel as though I could leverage my background to get the job at the firm, even thought I don't have a strong interest in practicing criminal defense. All my friends are law enforcement at local and state levels and I forged that route to venture off to law school because of something in my past I couldn't personally live with (part of the long story). I just don't want to walk out of this document review gig not having an idea of what my next position is going to be with a mortgage and my student loans due.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 12:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not barred to practice law in my given state, again, that's part of the long story. I'm still in the licensing process and should know in a month or so.  

However, I've done the research in anticipation. I live in a location on the cusp of rural/metropolitan area where it would be easy to serve both types of clients. I have major highways in and around me which would make it easy to get where I need to go. The legal market where I live is very under saturated; relatively un-touched I'd say. The county I live in barely has a functioning bar association, I thought about stepping in and helping run it once I do get barred.  

The counties around me are over-saturated in my opinion; one of them is in a way the mecca of the state and there is an overwhelming number of attorneys focused there. I don't have the exact numbers, but its something like 10,000 vs. 1,000, the latter being my location; it's something insane. 

I work in a law firm right now doing document review for them and have networked pretty hard with all of the attorneys in the office. I'm confident once this review is done, I can go to them to find my next position. My confidence is founded on one of the younger associates telling my flat out to ask the president and other partners if they know of anything; it's a smaller firm focused on a niche area, but push out big numbers. I've been working my ass for them to show them I'm no chump and I mean business, they've gotten the hint I am business first, but I'm also someone who can hold an intelligent conversation. 

I have some savings, but I was holding off on spending it on going solo immediately upon licensing. I have a substantial amount of student loans and would much rather find "somewhere" to work to develop the solo on the side before jumping with both feet. I have a relatively small amount of bills (house, student loans, insurance, monthly expenses) each month. With my wife's two jobs, I need a job that pays $45,000 or more, anything over that mark would be a plus. We have been living off her salary for the past year or so and have been living decent and still have managed to save. At the $45k mark we would still live of her income and any remaining would be dumped on my student loan along with my entire salary; we plan to aggressively pay down the loan. 

I studied a wide range of subjects while in law school and I'm naturally intrigued by anything that floats in front of my face. Realistically I would be comfortable doing transnational work. I have some Bankruptcy experience as well. 

I have not reached out to anyone in the area I plan on practicing because I'm not at that point yet. I know of a few places that would more than likely allow me to work in their location, including the firm I'm working at now. I was going to cross that bridge when it came.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 11:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Individually speaking, I've graduated form law school and have passed the Bar Exam in Michigan; I'm currently in the licensing process to practice law. I specialized my degree in business transactions and real estate law. That being said, I would seek the advice of an attorney anytime you encounter a scenario where you yourself individually are going to be taking on financial risks, where there is language regarding how ownership is divided, or where there is no paperwork at all. 

I'm a firm believer of the fact that in the contracting world many of the problems that arise come about due to poor contract execution or none at all. Many of the problems in business can be ironed out before hand. For example, if you have a Partnership, but there is no Partnership Agreement. Or further, if you have a L.L.C, but there is no Operating Agreement. These documents are essential to how the given business is ran. However, even if your have these documents in place they still may be written in a way that touches all the bases, but essentially does nothing for you specifically. Websites like Legal Zoom, while they serve a purpose and are successful, their documents are not specifically tailored for each individual client; there what you call a boilerplate document which is the bare minimal of what the law requires. When ever your in a negotiating stance you want to put your best foot forward and get in a position that best suits you. 

In relation to the structure, you hit the nail on the head. How is the business going to be structures, i.e. what type of entity is going to be used. There are many types of business (partnerships, LLC, Member Managed/Manager Managed LLC, S vs. C Corporation, Non-Profit) and how you choose will depend on the type of business your getting into. There is no right way to choose, but you want to choose right because the wrong choice can make you personally liable for your cohorts screw-ups.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely agree with this comment. It's pretty clique, but individuals in those scenarios have learned skills to keep themselves alive. They have perfected and found their skills over a long and hard road through life. But, I also agree with running a criminal record check. It's one thing to have a DUI vs. Assault/Child Abuse...you just want to make sure your not jumping into business with a hothead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recent Graduate Seeking Career Advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a long story, but I am re-thinking the type of law I want to practice.

I don't have any particular experience in Criminal Law, however, I have a Bachelors Degree in Criminal Justice, Counter-Terrorism Certificate, and over five years of experience doing private security in conjunction with the local police department. I went to law school based on the long story, it's not something I regret entirely, just a few choices would have been more beneficial. 

Regardless, I specialized my studies in Business Transactions and Real Estate. I'm having trouble finding a "law job" post graduation and I'm tired of doing the document review thing. 

There is a criminal defense firm hiring a part-time law clerk on craigslist...and I am truly torn on sending my credentials. 

Any thoughts? Much appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does the paperwork say? 
Do you understand what your getting into contractually? 
Is this something you should consult an expert on? 
How is the start-up structured? 
Does the start-up have any existing debts you would stand to incur? 
Is there set goals and plans to achieve those goals? 
Is this something that your comfortable taking on the risk associated with the endeavor? 
How will you, and or, will you get paid? 

...I could probably continue for an hour...

You can never be to sure of something without asking the proper questions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thought!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool! Glad I could help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think your over-thinking the question maybe, do you have facts we can see? 

I found this link, it's a good read, [2A LINK](http://www.jdsupra.com/post/contentViewerEmbed.aspx?fid=743c9c65-6168-4e63-8ca8-86c5ea4e3e6f)...Read Section D,E, and F.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LMAO! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who knows. She's in far to deep to pull out now; she's gone full retard. This is something she will have shadow her forever, maybe she could write a book.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, I was actually. I wasn't comparing her intellectually because I don't know her personally to have enough personal knowledge to make that determination. I was more so making a comparison based on the beach photo of her holding the dog. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why they will hold their value if not increase. The market won't die off it will only respond to the decline in viable merchandise and the market rate will increase in response. It's different with games because they don't break down, other than batteries going dead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should take a stab at it. Worst case scenario you fail and have to wait until Feb. anyways; best case you pass. You never know what life is going to throw your way bud.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 12:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a life changing decision. I came to a same fork in the metaphorical road and pushed through till the end. I learned a lot about myself as well, but at a heavy price; I would't change it at all even if I could. Don't let this define you and learn from this journey you've embarked on. Make goals and take a daily step towards them. Keep your head up high and truck on my friend.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check your inbox.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it. Let me indulge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll take a stab, shoot me a PM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, are you advertising? I'm not understanding the context of your post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *The Adventures of Tom Sawyer* by Mark Twain...great reminder of how childhood was before all this *shit* was in my head.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can second this, heavily. The Bar is an exam to test your capabilities, it will not ease up on you. You have to be disciplined and deliberate in your studies. Themis will not hold your hand and you have to be proactive, have a place, and execute that plan. I can attest to the exact same thing--had friends take Themis and skated through thinking just because they got more % done they were good; they were wrong.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 12:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, that is another reason why I was turned off by Barbri. I had a buddy who took the Bar at the same time and did Barbri, he passed, but also supplemented their writing portion with a state specific writing course through a 3rd party. 

I did Themis' schedule for the majority of my studies, then with about 1.5 months to go I started to review and practice on the Flex study to tailor it more specific to my needs. I completed 67.6% of Themis' course and passed will a 10+ point spread in points; I was a B to B+ student in law school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did Themis and thought it was a good course, passed the first time. 

The course allowed you to change course if you did not feel you needed to cover something. For example, the term before I graduated I took a Sales course covering negotiable instruments and Article II of the UCC. While I was going through the Themis course it called for lectures tailored to those subject, seeing I just took them, I skipped those lectures and was able to apply my time towards something more beneficial. 

My point: Barbri is more ridgid in their course flow, where Themis is more relaxed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 13:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote a clause into my will, it's something like a treasure map. 

"You know me. Don't be naive, for every nook and cranny could contain a piece of something I've left behind to the one who knows my true intentions; upon my death, what awaits shall transfer to the possessors' hand."  

I have hollowed out books and other hiding places all over my property. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Savage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What country was that? Haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It amazes me that those buildings are still there. 

Realistically, every inch of those earth has a story to tell. Photography has given us the ability to capture that minuet position in time to be able to compare it as time drones forward. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 17:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, with any collectible you have a peaks and valleys. 

The generation that played N64 is at the prime nostalgia age, thus they want to escape back to their youth. As time goes on that base will collect what games/materials they need for their setup. As time passes there will be less of a demand for the products, in turn, prices will have to become more competitive for a smaller market. 

When the competition is not at a peak, the more collectible/rare items will hold their value; while the more common games will be low. 

I would say the accessories will hold their value more; everyone is going to need parts for their controllers or new ones all together.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. 

I would say start with your Letgo/Craigslist search to find local people selling stuff. You local market is going to be the most potential for cheaper stuff. You can easily find a system and a controller for $40-50 to set you up. It's going to be the games that your going to have to search for diligently for the best price. 

I got back into the N64 game two weeks ago and it was a surprise to see how much this stuff runs; and I yelled at my parents for selling all my childhood gear at a garage sale (smh). 

If you can find games locally, great. If not, your going to want to go on Ebay and just vulture games at a price your comfortable paying. Today I bought Super Smash Bros for $39.99 w/ $4.00 shipping. I would say from watching for the past few weeks that $44.99 is a decent deal; I've seen them sell upwards of $60.00, so it just depends on your comfort level and value of the game. 

This Reddit Sub is excellent and has a TON of information. I must admit I've spent A LOT of time on here in the past two weeks getting my setup going. 

EDIT: There is also a big difference in "Collecting" verses "Reminiscing." If your looking to just step back in time your going to spend a lot less money; if your collecting, your not going to get out cheap any way you look at it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did I pass? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boy, me too, I wish I could take that stupid person test.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same issue too, I returned mine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Catsup.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 01:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha. Same thought.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. You'll get hooked. I use the app at garage sales all the time. Once you practice finding your items it's really simple to use/list. 

(1) I search for item based off trigger words (name, manuf., etc.)

(2) I see how many current items are listed. I look for exact same item or similar items, it's going to depend on what you have. 

(3) Then I hit refine and look up sold/completed listings to see what has sold most recently. That way you can judge how fast that item moves and the variance in price. Then you can go back to the current listings to judge what price you can pay/sell for based on what's available and to compete with the current listings. 

(4) Once you've bought the item redo the search and find your item. There will be a "Sell Similar Item" button you can click on. This literally will copy and late the entire listing you looked up except the description, shipping, and price. Once your in the template you just go through each part and put in your desired information. Then you list it. 

I can literally do this in 5-10 mins depending on the item. I can find an exact same item it's a lot easier. I hardly ever create my listings from scratch anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 12:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can list something in 2-3 mins. Where a laptop takes a bit longer to upload photos, write in data, etc. 

I've bought items at garage sales, listed then in my car, and by the time I'm at another sale--they've sold. 

It's just very user friendly. 

I typically know my shipping costs or offer free shipping in the items I sell so I don't fuss with the shipping charges; I deal mostly in smalls. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 12:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking maybe some scales of justice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Understandable. Most of the expensive ones are going to be the first edition 90's ones that are hard to come by.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Simpsons Retro Merch. 

I've made A LOT of money off the Simpsons, their fans are super loyal and are all around the World.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they printed them like crazy. You have to know what cards to look out for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use my bookcase for most of it; they complement books very well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Perfect explanation and example.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you use Mperks? My wife and I have been using it and there are a lot of savings with it. Also, even though you have this budget, do you take advantage of their 10/10 sale? I get a lot of soup (Campbell's To go soup for $1.00) and take it for lunch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man did I have it backwards. I didn't know it was like that, I drank the koolaid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shop for smalls/medium items. 

I have to at least make $20.00 on most of my items, but with items under $20.00 I will spend the money to make a few bucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iphone camera. The app makes listing SOO easy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vintage Nintendo Video Game Lock: Bought on Letgo $4.00; Sold for $85.00 two days later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Understandable. I totally agree with you. Educate yourself a little and then go to another Attorney. Real Estate stuff is pretty simple, but it is a lot of paperwork; most of the documents are forms. A Real Estate Attorney should have deeds/titles on hand at a cheap rate. 

You just want to do this right the first time because it can create a headache.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree. Taking on that much water the land couldn't naturally consume it. The spillway looked like it gave out instantly, and by the time they knew what hit them, it was to late and half of it was gone! I would be concerned about the others in the area too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is one of the best things to relax and just sink into a pool. If you can fit the bill into your budget, and you can name more then 5 advantages, I would say go for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's plus. 

You can always take a swim or sit in the sauna as well; those were also positives I didn't have at home. 

There isn't much wiggle room around their initial fees. You might be lucky to find a sale, but then you just sitting and waiting for one to come by, which is not what you want to be doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. 

You may want to find an Attorney and a CPA who will give you free consultation to discuss your options. You going to need some help with this road; I don't feel any amount of Google will help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I've been paying attention to it as of late; I think that Dam outside Sacramento is interesting scenario. I just can't believe how many sinkholes and landslides there have been, that does not seem normal, is it? I live in MI and we have a shit ton of lakes, including the "Great Lakes;" we always hear "oh, the lakes have risen or fallen X feet this year, so we kind of take it for granted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hat do you want to get out of the gym? Seriously. What will you use when you go there? I did this thing with LA for three years, then realized I had everything at my house. 

Everywhere you go there is a floor: Push-ups, sit-ups, lunges, etc. 

Sidewalk: Running, walking, jogging, etc. 

Most of what I did was doable at home. 

The only benefit from it was being able to play basketball and using their water to shower. But over time the gas I used to get to the gym 3-4 times a week would have covered my own water at home. 

If it's being around people who have similar mindsets, that's commendable, and sometimes a good reason. 

My point is everyone doesn't need a gym
Membership and if you want to save $30 a week and that $100 start up cost...try out the home gym you're already a member of.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Maybe it's an update of some sort.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incredible how it can go from a record drought to over saturated. How are y'all gonna catch this water to save and use in future droughts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that simple. They signed a contract with their lender that has an acceleration clause in it, which states that any unauthorized transfer of the property would give the lender the right to call the entire loan due. 

If you really want to do this correctly, you should consult a real estate attorney in your jurisdiction. Find an attorney who will give you a *free* consultation and just lay out what y'all wanna do. 

By drafting your own deeds and doing it hokey, your going to create issues in the chain of title which could lead to thousands to clean it up. 

Ask your Attorney what: 

1) Assumption vs Subject to means 
2) Novation from original Promissory Note means  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
