<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3093</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 01:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're correct...he said so on the special  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 18:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This person has been trolling all the trans related posts, just ignore them   exercise your power to downvote  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 04:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wtf i especially hope that dog one is untrue omg :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nathan's EVEN WORSE because as terrible as Adam is, he isn't violent :l </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 21:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in all fairness, farrah made a comment about kail in the newest article someone just posted. i'm guessing thats what she's referring to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 23:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think what bothers me most about this whole argument, is that it doesn't take into account that there may very well be trauma involved in someone's aversion to certain genitalia. Whether that's rational or not, isn't the point. Someone not disclosing to some who is already a victim of sexual trauma, that they have certain parts may in fact really fuck with them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 23:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So would you expect someone who's infertile to tell you right away? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 08:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh good ol' TERFS  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 06:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> perfect, looking forward to it (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 23:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im so happy to hear of someone else with the same set of unique circumstances...I know of many who were already with someone who later transitioned or people who met someone after, but none who met before   got together after as well... how does your boyfriend feel about your sexual identity? Mine doesn't seem comfortable with mine   it's mostly something we avoid  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 00:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because your scalp provides the oil that keeps your hair moisturized, so extensions become dry   brittle very easily without washing w/ special shampoo   conditioner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 08:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She looks like Jodie arias to me :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 18:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree :/ well for now, I'm working on my degree in NY   don't really see myself leaving since I Work in Fashion Design which is limiting. He doesn't want to leave his government job in Denver because of his health coverage plan while in transition :/ it's just tricky for the time being ya know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comforting long distance boyfriend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 15:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a basic overview; I've known my boyfriend about 6 years, though we were merely acquaintances for the majority of that time. At such time, he wasn't out yet   identified as a lesbian, as have I. Fast forward to a few months ago... we started chatting casually on facebook,   seeing that I'm now currently living 2000 miles away/had nothing to lose, I confessed how I've always found him attractive. From there we began texting, calling,   realizing how genuinely compatable we are for one another. He visited me last month,   though I was iffy if I'd still find him attractive because of pheromones etc [he's 9 months on T   undoubtedly a man], I'm truly very much in love   incredibly attracted to him. Being that we are long distance in the midst of his transition, he's expressed the fear that the further he goes on T, the less I will be attracted to him. He's scared I'm just attracted to the version of him from years ago, that best aligns with my previous homosexual identity. I assure him that what attracted me then was his smile, dimples   puppy dog eyes. Those are still a part of him. Not only that, but I find myself attracted to the things I thought I'd be turned off by; I.e. His tummy hair, deep voice etc because I know these are all things that make him feel better aligned with his authentic most self   his confidence alone is sexy. It just gets hard some days reminding him of all this, especially when dysphoria hits :/ anyone else in a similar situation or able to offer some advice in aiding him to feel more secure in my love for him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 21:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally feel Amber is well aware of all these tweets, KNOWS they were him, knew he was a Teen Mom creep from the beginning   LIKED that about him... she knew how desperate he is   is just as desperate to be idolized. Its sick   I feel no sympathy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 22:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's a fashion design student now @ FIDM in California   laying low I believe
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 05:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clowns are racist you ignorant shitlord </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly think routinely talking in third person is a sign of mental delusion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 19:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Photographer copyrights maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 15:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a dream I bought a pretty new eye shadow palette   Sophia's jelly covered hands ruined it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 19:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm so confused...how does going from stick like to healthy make someone fat nowadays? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 18:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either you DO relate or you DONT, no "almost." God what a terrible person </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 10:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ugh

But also

She's ADORABLE  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
