<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2240</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 02:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whaaat?! The Dylan version is great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 02:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny, I love Springsteen's version more than Manfred Mann. Great song choice though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 02:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which cover songs do you think are better than the original? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 01:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What God did on the eighth day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 00:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too late. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha excellent point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, Admiral. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesante - gracias! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How come we called children minors but we don't call adults majors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 04:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 03:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "TOILET PAPER! SAVE ME! TOILET PAPER!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ovechkin Excited To Captain Russia To Silver Medal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 19:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MOSCOW, RUSSIA  After being named captain for Team Russia at the World Cup of Hockey, Washington Capitals star Alexander Ovechkin announced that he is enthusiastic to lead his fellow countrymen to a rousing second place finish.

Im sure something will come up and cause us to not take gold, Ovechkin started.

Following a disappointing end to an incredible season with the Capitals, Ovechkin is ready to repeat the heartbreak.

I figured Ill make a thing of it, at least for a bit. Well put our all into it and then come up short. Im excited to see how this plan goes! the eager captain told.

Russian President Vladimir Putin, an Ovechkin fan, was less than pleased with the captains idea. Let me just say this. Russia does not go out there to be second to anyone. I hope Mr. Ovechkin does understand that there areconsequences, Putin finished sternly.

At press time, Ovechkin and his teammates were seen getting their fans hopes up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 01:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Congratulations on being let out on good behavior, you're free to go!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tortorella Would Bench, Pummel National Anthem Protestors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 05:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> COLUMBUS, OH  In the wake of San Francisco 49ers quarterback Colin Kaepernicks national anthem protest, notably entertaining and boisterous coach John Tortorella had strong words for his Team U.S.A. players regarding the national anthem. Tortorella claimed that any player who sits during the national anthem will be benched the entire game, as well as be beaten with his red, white, and blue-colored brass knuckles.

Yeah, I said it, started Tortorella. Thats because these players play for two things: me, and the flag!

Tortorellas extreme patriotism is nothing new. Said one former player, Hes crazy with this stuff! He overheard me say that I dont like apple pie, and he put me in a headlock, feeding me an entire apple pie, until I said I liked it. It was the scariest moment of my life.

Hockey fans are meeting this with mixed reaction. Seattle resident Nick Caperno, 25, seemed to be in favor with the coach. I think patriotism is important. Maybe he doesnt have to beat them, but if that gets them to have pride in the flag, then Im okay with it. Phoenix resident Mary Ashe, 34, did not agree. People have free speech! They can express it however they like  even if that means not standing for the flag! I fully support players like Kaepernick, and think its extremely wrong to forcibly and violently make players stand for the flag!

At press time, Tortorella was seen imprinting images of bald eagles onto a pair spiked boxing gloves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 01:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The Walking Dad is pretty good. Wish it had more zombies, but not bad overall." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 01:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm so sorry for your loss. Here's a tissue. Feel how soft it is? It's Kleenex's patented new extra-layer soft tissues!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
