<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2159</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 13:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make CVs more encouraging to play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I haven't lost a single gun in a long time and here you are converted to a slow torpedo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 16:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't get too wrapped up in her face from some concept art. Concept art is usually about the aesthetic and not delicate facial details.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 13:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $10 is a lot better than $120. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being able to justify this ship becomes much more difficult when I remember that I already own basically every ship I want and am sitting on 80mil credits. 

I guess I'll just grind out the free xp eventually then. I owe it to myself to not spend money on this ship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 21:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like the perfect definition of "some". I personally know 2 people with 800k free xp already they've just saved up naturally anway and a few more about halfway there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 21:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hosho was scrapped on my birthday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 15:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People just want to hate on wargaming for everything they do. Sometimes they deserve it, this is not one of those times. Just because the ship is expensive doesn't make it a cash grab. A cash grab is something quick and easy everyone will buy. There's only going to be a handful of people dishing out $120 for this. Most will probably be like halfway with free xp, some will get it for free.

Edited for grammar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 15:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree 100%. I'm going to start saving my free XP now since it looks like the ship is going to stay available indefinitely. It's a better Iowa, but it's a huge reward for a long term goal. I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 05:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ironically, I'd be more inclined to accept the capabilities of their products if they weren't so dirt cheap. Good shit aint cheap. 6 knives and 2 titty sharpeners for $10.99? dafuq kinda cheap ass heat treated aluminum foil is that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 22:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me neither, but I still like watching it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 18:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't even notice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 16:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liver cancer is inoperable and terminal in most cases. TB's only saving grace is that he's young and liver cancer hits mostly older men.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 18:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder how long that much food will hold that guy over for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 19:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they're not bad balanced right now. The T9/10 IJN ones are a tad strong but other than that they're good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 16:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her knife fighting ability vs enemy DDs lost the high alpha aspect, but her sustained fire on larger ships should be better now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 14:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OH BOY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 16:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Excuse me sir I need your license and registration"

*tornado flings his squad car* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 15:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fires do not need penetration to be set.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 21:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Montana has best sigma and shell dispersion. Those shells stick together like crazy and there's 12 of them!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 19:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a tad hyperbolic, dontcha think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 17:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, I've seen those 12 accurate Montana shells wreck cruisers and DDs more than any other BB.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 15:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they are all strong. Yamato still has the best guns, being able to pen everything through the nose is always useful. Kurfurst has hydro and turtleback making it the hardest to kill without torps, Montana has the best concealment, maneuverability, and gun accuracy which I think people underestimate when played well. 

But all of them have proper weaknesses. Yamato gets stuck bow on and HE spamed, Kurfurst can't turn and is bigger than the maps, Montana has the lowest caliber and shell velocity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 15:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High tier cruisers are great, if any cruisers are in a bad spot it's T6 and below. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 00:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree USN DDS could get their torps reduced, but most of them play close since their gunboats, and sniping BBs lose whereas torp sniping Shimas won. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 21:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's clear WG wanted to remove long range torping as a viable tactic because it does not provide very interactive gameplay. In an effort to bring IJN DDs closer to the fight, we have what we're getting nkw. Time will tell how viable they have become, but a bunch of salty dogs miss the torpedo soup gameplay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 17:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck shitting on a 20k HP DD that can stealth fire from 9km. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 17:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew I'd see you here QQing.  Akizuki will be a strong ship and you haven't even played her. As flamu stated, she looks like a better Tashkent, so it'll be a different role than Benson.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 22:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From 0 to 2 is infinitely more, but also only 2 more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 22:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that MM actively trues to lower your winrate, but I've always considered that it tries to balance out each team based on winrate or something. Im rarely on the same team as other 60%+ winrate players that I recognize. 

Of course this is completely anecdotal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 15:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would take her to a nice dinner and make her laugh all evening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 02:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The HE is mediocre, but the insane fire rate makes up for it. Run demo expert and don't be afraid to spam HE unless it's the perfect situation for AP. Steering gears mod 3 vs concealment is up to you, I prefer the steering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 05:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cruiser accuracy... all I needed to see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 05:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And 20 second Soviet reload </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm dying here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 13:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T3 is +/-1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 02:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant in the case where T7 doesn't get the tiering it does (like it was before). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 01:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good players can handle being down two tiers and then being top tier is more rewarding. 

At least that was the result of the mobile world of tanks test.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 01:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MM would probably slow down a lot. And as stated elsewhere, the more skilled players prefer +/-2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 00:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could also be said that they will lose players that hit the T7 ships (which most can be a difficult transition to) and MM beats them over the head vs T8/9 all the time.

I don't think there's a solution that makes everyone happy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 22:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've said in QA the current state of MM is intended and expected. T5/6 is rough, but those tiers are still quick to get through compared to T7/8 which have the best MM now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully Dasha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What part of any of this made you think any of that? I didn't say anyone was above criticism, only that your criticism was juvenile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cared enough to answer because I don't like seeing good games get bashed for unimportant stuff. There's plenty of actual shitty games/devs to bash out there to waste it on skin lootboxes. 

It's clear that the devs are putting a lot of effort into making this game as good as it can be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 20:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares? It's a bunch of shitty skins that no one notices.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 15:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mainly because the USN smokes are so good for teamplay. Benson could use a torp range nerf imo too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 15:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the line is splitting into anti DD gunboats then reworked torpedo boats afaik. If WG just moves some ships around and dials back the torp detection, viola. The line becomes insanely better. Then a skill like keen intuition is gonna be one of the few real tools you can use vs stealth torping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 13:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IJN DDs are also getting a rework soon so I am holding judgement until we see how they change. Keen Intuition is good in very specific situations which is pretty pricey for a tier 4 skill as other skills are constantly good in multiple situations  (CE, AFT, MA MS) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 13:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People have said torpedos have been killed over and over and yet they're still viable. DDs have been nerfed over and over and are still yet hugely influential over battles. Radar was added, people thought it was the end of DDs. If you look at the latest ranked season though, it tells a different tale.

Keen intuition will be good late game in 1v1, but knowing a DD is right in front of you won't stop torps hitting your nose.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but no AFT with that build. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 04:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still have a few more playthroughs planned though. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> :'( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 02:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 21:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Load Images 130 More" 

:O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would make sense to give it good accuracy. Poor accuracy and it's just a shitty BB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 22:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real stat that'll make a difference is whether the ship gets cruiser dispersion or battleship dispersion. I'm expecting the former. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USN CAs are much more situational. They are very good at bullying certain ships they are good against and providing support in the form of Radar and AA. I find myself abusing terrain much more in USN CAs than any other cruisers. And without torps, you need to stay around you concealment range. You can only really yolo agaisnt another cruisrr or something that you can takr on bow forward. Most of the time you don't want more than one or two ships able to shoot at you. 

KM CAs are much more well rounded and have different tools that allow them to handle different situations. The general playstyle for them however is to stay around your concealment range 12-14km and snipe with HE and AP while dodging shells as best you can. Both are solid at T9+. I actually found myself shooting HE most of the time and only going AP when the situation really called for it. The amazing hydro and torps gives more yolo potential but the higher tier you get, the less yolo you're gonna be able to do. You shouldn't be going for yolo unless it's way late in the match really.

My opinion is the T9/T10 KM CAs are the most fun cruisers in the game. Pro tip, run DE/CE and both steering gears mods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No shit, 8x is an insane amount of AA. Use like 2x or soemthing lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my experience, Hindenberg can get away with steering gears. It doesn't matter if you're spotted when you can win a fight vs anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 15:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wargaming is making so much money with this game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool concept. I think it would be much more viable as a gameplay addition if it was something like "reports the distance of all ships within 15km." So it won't reveal any ships location still, but you can use it know how danger close you are to a DD or a radar cruiser or soemthing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 17:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They might also make it to where you have to have researched the Iowa already. Would make sense if they want to keep it out of as many noob hands as possible (for a T9, they should). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they probably did. But they probably justify it by it being punished so harshly for misplays.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That wasn't a detonation. That was a good shot into a poor broadside.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My goal is for this to be my first ship I have an 80% winrate in after 100 battles. Best contender yet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 14:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have it set to auto pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 13:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For $34.99, this thing will be everywhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 15:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I plan on dismissing him instantly anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 00:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atago is still good for $$ and training captains.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My body is ready.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 18:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it when things rhyme.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 03:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming you land all 9 shells, it will still not kill them, which is the point. Realistically you're going to land like 2 to 4.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 22:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Propulsion only works for the first bit of acceleration and you shouldn't be slowing down that slowly usually. Every bit of rudder shift helps on those high tier CAs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 21:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noo, steering 2 and 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 20:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still run CE on every cruiser. /u/Flamu is a good player and running max concealment is still vrry viable. I guess it is down to play style but I think my results speak for themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 20:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put steering gears mod 3 on it and dodge shells. On the T9/10, you're going to be firing so constantly you'll be detected anyway and it's better to stay on the fight just dodge incoming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finished up 100 games in my Hindenburg shooting mainly HE on a demo expert build and am currently #1 on NA for the ships avg damage according to warships.today. 

https://na.warships.today/vehicle/4179539760/Hindenburg

I vote go for Hindenburg. It's my favorite cruiser in the game and I've played most of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even 9 overpens is barely 10k damage. Wouldn't oneshot any DD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 17:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet jesus. I still think BB AP shouldn't be allowed full pens on DDs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 16:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Helluva plunging fire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 16:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DX12 usually increases performance on lower end rigs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 14:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50% discount AND 20% credit gain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 14:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If those T10 camos had been out a year ago, I'd be sitting on like 200m credits by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 23:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People keep saying that these ships need poor HE to help them, but those AP shells still do decent damage to angled targets. Not a serious amount, but that's what poor HE would doing too. I suspect if these were given poor HE with poor fire chance, you'd be better off shooting AP anyway. I saw flamu getting 4k salvos on that angled Iowa.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 19:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Base package $119.95. Bundle $149.95. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 17:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bismarck doesn't have shitty handling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They get paid. A lot. That's probably all they feel they need to get right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depth of field implemented </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 19:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but that's true most T9s though. Only a couple can handle T10 MM well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iowa is faster, slimmer and has more armor and HP. Also gets the reload module so it's a nice upgrade. About standard for the power differences for most T8 - T9. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 17:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's up to you, battleships pick up at T5 and start becoming kings of the sea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 14:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bow armor is good, the ass armor is not so good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 07:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the best video I've ever seen in my whole life  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 18:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What bike is that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 14:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Camo I think is down to preference and can be excluded. Premium Consumables  (especially the health regen) is an absolute must have. You'll make more money since your combat effectiveness is enhanced.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 20:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm subscribed because it's usually cool pictures  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IJN- focus on stealth gameplay and ambushes. Reliable solo and DD escorts role.

USN- going to be excellent vs RN cruisers. 

KM - Hindenburg is the best/most fun ship in the game. IMO, of course. There's always going to be broadsides to punish. HE isn't the best but your rate of fire at T9/10 is so strong it doesn't matter. You'll set plenty of fire.

VMF- Long range spam because of poor maneuverability. Radar is the strongest with team play.

RN - Plays like DDs. Getting into good smoke positions, best concealment, constantly moving into flanks on their sides, torps. You'll like if you like DDs. 

Just adding some more stuff you didn't mention. Maybe it'll push you one way or another.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I checked this last night and both flags increased my secondary fire chance on Scharnhorst.  Didn't check any other ships. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please enjoy your stay. Buy premium time pl0x.

-wargaming  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 17:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've dealt with their customer support a couple times and they've been timely and pleasant. No complaints. 

The first time was similar, I bought some stuff for WoT on accident during an event they were doing and they transfered it to WoWs no prob. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 14:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, I'll put those Type 6 to work on the RN line. 

Speaking of which, gimme Belfast pls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like most cruisers. Maybe these are little thinner than others, but a Yamato triple citadel shell grouping into a broadside  (I saw the video) isn't going to be stopped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, that is a good HP boost. Seems like the way to go. 

Don't get deleted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like sarcasm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I saw more CVs (hopefully one day) I would do it. But for pub stomping randoms that potential HP might go a long way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's 2%/second for 20 seconds so a potential 40% heal right? So a difference of 3200 at T10 per heal x4 = 12.8k potential MORE HP with SE given full use of heqls. 

This is all head math, please correct if I'm being an idiot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I don't doubt it. I saw your Minotaur vs 4 Hak video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repair party heals based on %hp per second.

Edit - "2.0% of maximum hit points per second for 20 seconds" for T8+ RN cruisers. Source - http://wiki.wargaming.net/en/Ship:Consumables#Damage_Control_Party

The wargaming wiki.

Since I'm being downvoted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SE seems like it might be good on these if you don't care about AA. It'll stack on the OP heal and give a lot more potential HP than just the base increase.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 19:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or expert loader.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 18:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe I'm upvoting this... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 18:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you chain smokes with Jack of all trades? I noticed in Flamu video, when his smoke ran out, there wasn't much time till it was back up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 18:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see plenty of CAs still. Not to mention HE spamming DDs will also cause the same effects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 17:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I support any extra revenue for Frictional. Those guys have been blowing me away for years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 16:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 16:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a few weeks, Hindenberg will FEAST. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
