<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2797</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you mean an UNexpectedly  bad grade? try failing calculus 3 times IN A ROW  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're not alone. people stress me out a lot. I wish I could wake up the last person on earth sometimes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this sounds like the greatest thing ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 05:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SAME  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 05:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its never true
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its been a longgggg time but she hasn't eaten for so long it can't be just that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 07:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh you mean you're a male? apparently being male means you're worthless and you don't matter and nobody cares about you or wants you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 07:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you think there is even a single woman on the planet who would say a party without guys isn't a party? NO!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 07:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that right there is exactly why I want to kill myself. why the fuck even bother existing if my presence is valued by no one? thank you for admitting that women have it easier than men. this is the point I live and will die trying to make. life is such a fucking joke for men. its absolutely miserable. I hate everything and everyone and have nothing to live for. I honestly want to find my ex, beat the shit out of her, kill her, then kill myself. thanks for confirming this is a good thought  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 07:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but they get invited out and I don't. that's my observation. I never get invited anywhere while everyone (especially my exes) gets to party  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im very sorry to hear that but this is my point. I feel like these people are the only reason I am alive. not a single other person. I just cant relate to anybody. I feel like no one else at a university has this problem everyone around me all day seems to have it together  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes I am lol we are all one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy shit same I love talking to people who are 40+ and im in my early 20s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no response right? yup thats usually what happens when I win arguments with women  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you wanna explain to me why it is that women are viewed as perfect and always innocent to the point where even if the woman cheats its fucking justified and morally correct ? what the fuck is this shit? how acquiescent have men this day and age become? all these little fuckin white knights. being a guy SUCKS these days. if anything men should be marching  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> my avic avic refuses to eat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it has been several weeks. there are a couple nice sized roaches in her enclosure and they have walked directly next to her and she didnt pounce on them like she normally does. I don't understand what to do but I am very worried </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what do you do when you realize that the only people who would really care if you killed yourself are you parents and siblings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 05:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean this is a given for most people so despite the fact that I love them.... big whoop? that doesn't change how fucking shitty everything is and the fact that I can not relate to a single person and nobody hits me up on weekends why the fuck bother anymore?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 05:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuck you. its not sexist its called being fucking observant. clearly you have never dealt with women  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 05:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this this this this this. without weed I have no reason to live. alcohol sucks. pills and other drugs are just stupid and expensive but yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 05:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> people react to it differently. this statement is not valid. you can be eating and still have no fucking energy or confidence or motivation and constantly wonder why you haven't just killed yourself already  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 05:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omg thank you. all I associate with college is my girlfriend breaking up with me AFTER 2 YEARS, because she wants to be a little cum whore party slut  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 05:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> saaaaaaame  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 05:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel this way because I always assume they will rip my heart out just as badly as my first ex. Breaks up with me because oh bla bla bla college. leaves me for dead as I have no social life or friends and she gets to party and be a fucking slutty little cunt bitch. women literally have it so fucking easy it makes me sick they get everything they fucking want and deep down... they actually have no emotion. yup I said it. they have none, they have no idea what heart break is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 04:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hint: use the quotient rule  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 04:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my honest opinion is the first line of this trailer https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jo18VIoR2xU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> double if possible. math otherwise. you need to be more comfortable with theory than experimentation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is worthy of being in /r/math thanks   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha Im aware Im trying to get an even better picture tho  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could anyone kindly help me understand the intuition behind groups? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I now have some linear algebra under my belt and would like to get started with more abstract algebra, but I am having trouble understanding the importance of groups, even though the definition of a group seems pretty straightforward. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im thinking either topology or fluid dynamics. maybe both. im still an undergrad  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks French and German were my top 2 choices  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks I was thinking French. and lol I may learn Python also  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> best foreign language for mathematics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there languages that would be beneficial for someone going into mathematics research? My school is requiring me to take a couple semesters of a language  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> write more. it helps. plus this was a pretty solid read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree so much with all of this lol. you're not alone. just one more thing to add... people are fucking STUPID. like seriously if you're depressed there is STATISTICALLY a good chance that you have above average intelligence. try to use this to help you move forward and feel better. because the average person is just a fucking notch or two above downs syndrome  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 18:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this made it more clear thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 18:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is this supposed to be similar to how we think about closeness in calculus just a bit more abstracted ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 05:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that makes sense. but is it just necessary in... say topology because we want to be able to use the part of the definition of the limit that says "about a point except possibly at the point itself" ? Does this property of open intervals/sets hint at the idea of a Hausdorff space? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what is the intuition behind the importance of open sets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 05:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is lately becoming apparent to me that in higher maths such as topology and analysis among many others, open sets are very important. Is there any intuitive or almost pictorial sort of way to think about why this is so?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 08:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
