<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2472</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The top Democrat on the committee is Adam Schiff, a congressman from Los Angeles who was first elected in 2000. Before the election of Donald Trump, Schiff was known in Washington as a milquetoast moderate. But, appalled by Trumps muted response to the Russian attack, Schiff has emerged as an unlikely face of Democratic resistance to the new President, using his position on the intelligence committee to pursue an investigation of the Russian influence campaign, its potential links to Trump and his associates, and how America should respond. Hes convinced that the Democrats wont be the last American victims of the Russians. One of the things that the intelligence community concluded was that there will be a next time, he told me on Monday. They will do this again. Despite his understated reputation, Schiff has gained a quiet respect among foreign-policy liberals and reporters for his nuanced views on surveillance, war powers, and press freedoms. He championed reform of the Patriot Act after the revelations by Edward Snowden about the N.S.A.s bulk collection of metadata. He pushed for a new, more tailored war authorization against Al Qaeda to replace the overly expansive one put in place after 9/11. And he has been outspoken on free-press issues, both in the United States and abroad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Unlikely Liberal Hero Adam Schiff Is Ready to Investigate Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Chaffetz's binary choice](http://www.sltrib.com/csp/mediapool/sites/sltrib/Pages/gallery.csp?cid=5027198 pid=4133121) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Russias activities were a major, complex event that requires additional resources to investigate fully, said McMullin. I simply dont believe that congressional Republican leadership are serious about investigating Russias activities and Trump and his teams connections to Russia. Republican leaders are interested in limiting the political costs and limiting the scope and depth of these investigations. [...] There are questions about the integrity of the congressional investigations, following revelations that the White House worked with Senate committee chairman Richard Burr (R-N.C.) and House committee chairman Devin Nunes (R-Calif.), asking them to contact reporters to speak on background to knock down news reports about the investigation. Separately, the Senate Armed Services Committee is planning a series of hearings related to Russias mischief both in the United States and around the world. Chairman John McCain (R-Ariz.) has been calling for a select committee for months but has said that without the support of Republican congressional leadership, it probably wont happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never Trump Republicans join call for select committee to investigate Russia and Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After 7 long years the GOP comes up with a plan that will make 24 million more uninsured? #ShitPlan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  President Trump will return to Mar-a-Lago this weekend, the White House confirmed on Monday, making it the fifth weekend he has spent in Florida as president. Press secretary Sean Spicer announced the Palm Beach trip to reporters during the White House press briefing, offering no other details regarding the purpose of the trip.


[Sean Spicer in December](http://www.foxbusiness.com/politics/2016/12/23/sean-spicer-word-vacation-will-not-exist-in-trump-administration.html):

 He will never take a vacation he cant sit still. Hes so eager to get things done and change things up  there is never an idle moment and so there is not going to be the word vacation will not exist in a Trump administration," </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump headed back to Mar-a-Lago this weekend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aka Baghdad Sean's daily lying session.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Its a little bit like President Obama," Trump said on Monday. "When he left, people liked him. When he was here, people didn't like him so much. Thats the way life goes. Thats human nature.

Is that why Obama [job approval numbers](http://www.gallup.com/poll/113980/gallup-daily-obama-job-approval.aspx) were very high?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  As Chauhan continues to ask about Russia, Spicer interjects, Such a great country that allows you to be here.In her Medium post, Chauhan, who is of Indian heritage, characterized that response as threatening and racist. Think about the sheer audacity of Mr. Spicer to say that to my face with a smile, knowing that he is being recorded on video and the position of power he holds in our government. I am still stunned by the boldness of having my citizenship threatened on camera, wrote Chauhan, who added that she has been on the receiving end of online harassment since posting about the Spicer encounter on Saturday. The go-to insult? They tell me to leave the country. They have told me to go back to where I came from, she wrote. To which my snarky reply is often, Go back where? New York? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sean Spicer gets confronted in Apple store; Trump responds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  On Sunday, the White House chief economic adviser, Gary Cohn, argued that CBO projections have been meaningless in the past because they said many more people will be insured than are actually insured. Mick Mulvaney, the White House budget director, even made the case that scoring big legislation like the GOPs Obamacare repeal bill isnt the best use of [the CBOs] time. But for the last several years, Trump himself has appeared to be a big fan of the CBO and its analysis. In fact, he frequently cited the offices work in attacks against former President Barack Obamas record on health care, jobs, the unemployment rate and the economy. [...] Based on his advisers recent comments, Trump appears to be having a change of heart with respect to the CBO now that hes president. Republicans are bracing for a report that will show millions of Americans losing health coverage under the plan that GOP leaders, and Trump himself, are championing as a replacement for the Affordable Care Act. Trumps opinion about government-issued statistics has been known to vary, seemingly depending on whether they favor him or not. After years of doubting official Bureau of Labor Statistics reports on the nations unemployment rate, Trump and his advisers cheered a strong jobs report on Friday  the first complete report under his administration  showing the nation added 235,000 jobs in February. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Loved To Cite The Nonpartisan Agency His Aides Are Now Discrediting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It's a madhouse!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DMnM_cQu6Fo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not there yet. CNN needs to focus more on investigative reporting and less on talking head panels. Rather than having two hours of AC360 or Don Lemon for example, they should allocate time for an in-depth interview program a la BBCs HARDtalk and a program that addresses the issue of the day/week in more informative way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Democrats are betting on health-care being as politically toxic to the G.O.P. as it has been for them over the past seven years. Public sentiment is against blowing up the Affordable Care Act, Chris Van Hollen, the chairman of the Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee, told Politico, before adding, Thats going to become clearer and clearer. Jettisoning the Make America Sick Again slogan, Schumer and his Democratic peers in the Senate have already branded the House bill introduced last week as Trumpcarea harbinger of the messaging strategy the Democrats plan to employ in 2018. Or as Rep. John Larson of Connecticut laid it out to Politico: If you want a check on Donald Trump, just look at whats happening with the Affordable Care Act and elect Democrats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smelling Blood, Democrats Prepare to Put Nail in Trumpcare Coffin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What credibility?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Jim Sciutto](https://twitter.com/jimsciutto/status/840728750983659520)

 Among many high-profile cases, #PreetBharara busted a Russian spy ring in NYC in 2015 

This is the case he was referring to.

[U.S. Attorneys Office - Southern District of New York](https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdny/pr/attorney-general-manhattan-us-attorney-and-fbi-announce-charges-against-russian-spy):

 Attorney General, Manhattan U.S. Attorney, And FBI Announce Charges Against Russian Spy Ring In New York City: Spy Ring Attempted To Collect Economic Intelligence And Recruit New York City Residents As Intelligence Sources </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Donald Trump in 2002](http://nymag.com/nymetro/news/people/n_7912/):

 "**I've known Jeff for fifteen years. Terrific guy,**'' Trump booms from a speakerphone. "**He's a lot of fun to be with. It is even said that he likes beautiful women as much as I do, and many of them are on the younger side. No doubt about it -- Jeffrey enjoys his social life.**" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reposting from another thread... 

From the [NYT article](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/01/19/us/politics/trump-russia-associates-investigation.html?_r=0): 

 The counterintelligence investigation centers at least in part on the business dealings that some of the president-elects past and present advisers have had with Russia. Mr. Manafort has done business in Ukraine and Russia. Some of his contacts there were under surveillance by the National Security Agency for suspected links to Russias Federal Security Service, one of the officials said. [...] The F.B.I. is leading the investigations, aided by the National Security Agency, the C.I.A. and the Treasury Departments financial crimes unit.

This was an operation by law enforcement and intelligence agencies to investigate connections between Trump's team and the Russians. But for Trumpesters like you who are screaming to the sky that "trump was being wiretapped", you're willfully ignorant of the fact that any surveillance done by the various law enforcement and intelligence agencies was legal.  

Ask yourself why his team was under surveillance? The way you phrase your first statement make it sounds like you believe that President Obama was targeting Trump for political reasons when in fact this was a legal surveillance done by various agencies. 

If you really think there is nothing of substance regarding Trump's Russian connections, then why Trump's team kept lying to the American people time and again about contacts with the Russians? Why did Flynn resign? 

And FYI it is not just our agencies that are monitoring Trump's team, our European allies as well. From the [New York Times](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/03/01/us/politics/obama-trump-russia-election-hacking.html): 

 American allies, including the British and the Dutch, had provided information describing meetings in European cities between Russian officials  and others close to Russias president, Vladimir V. Putin  and associates of President-elect Trump, according to three former American officials who requested anonymity in discussing classified intelligence. Separately, American intelligence agencies had intercepted communications of Russian officials, some of them within the Kremlin, discussing contacts with Trump associates.


Everything that we have seen so far shows that his team was working alongside the Russians in 2016. 

Edited a word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Im not going to be part of a dog-and-pony show that is not a serious effort to do an investigation, because this is really serious, said Representative Jackie Speier, Democrat of California. If its not a legitimate and comprehensive and in-depth investigation, why would we be party to it?[...] Democrats are already wary of moves by the committees chairman, Representative Devin Nunes, Republican of California, to undercut the purported Russian connection. Mr. Nunes has belittled news stories about the Russian ties of Mr. Trumps associates and has pledged  along with Senator Richard Burr, the North Carolina Republican who leads the Senate Intelligence Committee  to examine Mr. Trumps accusations, made without evidence, that President Barack Obama ordered the surveillance of Trump Tower. Mr. Nunes was a prominent supporter of Mr. Trumps campaign and served on the administrations transition team. [...] Democrats expect the first major test of the investigation  and Mr. Nuness stewardship  to come on March 20, when the committee holds its first public hearing. An initial list of invited witnesses included James B. Comey, director of the F.B.I.; James R. Clapper Jr., director of national intelligence under Mr. Obama; and Sally Q. Yates [...] Absent from the witness list was Michael T. Flynn, Mr. Trumps first national security adviser, who resigned after it was revealed that he had misled Vice President Mike Pence and other White House officials about his conversations with the Russian ambassador. Though Mr. Nunes emphasized it was only an early list, he referred to Mr. Flynn as a tangent, portraying him as more of a victim of the intelligence leaks Mr. Nunes is seeking to investigate than a target of the inquiry.

I wonder why? Could it be the fact that the heads of the investigations in the House and the Senate were involved with the Trump team and that just recently the White House enlisted their services to undercut the very investigations they are leading?

[Washington Post](https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/trump-administration-sought-to-enlist-intelligence-officials-key-lawmakers-to-counter-russia-stories/2017/02/24/c8487552-fa99-11e6-be05-1a3817ac21a5_story.html?utm_term=.38ee5220c77d):


 The Trump administration has enlisted senior members of the intelligence community and Congress in efforts to counter news stories about Trump associates ties to Russia, a politically charged issue that has been under investigation by the FBI as well as lawmakers now defending the White House.[...] The decision to involve those officials could be perceived as threatening the independence of U.S. spy agencies that are supposed to remain insulated from partisan issues, as well as undercutting the credibility of ongoing congressional probes.[...] The effort also involved senior lawmakers with access to classified intelligence about Russia, including Sen. Richard Burr (R-N.C.) and Rep. Devin Nunes (R-Calif.), the chairmen of the Senate and House intelligence committees. A spokesman for Nunes said that he had already begun speaking to reporters to challenge the story and that, at the request of a White House communications aide, Chairman Nunes then spoke to an additional reporter and delivered the same message.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask yourself why his team was under surveillance? The way you phrase your first statement make it sounds like you believe that President Obama was targeting Trump for political reasons when in fact this was a legal surveillance done by various agencies. 

If you really think there is nothing of substance regarding Trump's Russian connections, then ask yourself why Trump's team kept lying to the American people time and again about contacts with the Russians? Why did Flynn resigned? 

And FYI it is not just our agencies that are monitoring Trump's team, our European allies as well. From the [New York Times](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/03/01/us/politics/obama-trump-russia-election-hacking.html): 

 American allies, including the British and the Dutch, had provided information describing meetings in European cities between Russian officials  and others close to Russias president, Vladimir V. Putin  and associates of President-elect Trump, according to three former American officials who requested anonymity in discussing classified intelligence. Separately, American intelligence agencies had intercepted communications of Russian officials, some of them within the Kremlin, discussing contacts with Trump associates.


Everything that we have seen so far shows that his team was working alongside the Russians in 2016. Once we have real   serious investigations we will know for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It makes no sense to run a government this way. This is a completely chaotic situation, and then Gen. Flynn lied about his contacts with the Russians, lied to the vice president, and weve had the attorney general in testimony before the Senate Judiciary Committee say he did not contact the Russians when he had contacts with the Russians. People are not being honest about their foreign contacts, and talk about this deep state' theory as if there are somehow Obama moles in the government under the Trump administration. Its the KGB agents running around the West Wing or the national security council." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ethics lawyer on Trump WH: 'Chaotic situation' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the NYT article: 

 The counterintelligence investigation centers at least in part on the business dealings that some of the president-elects past and present advisers have had with Russia. Mr. Manafort has done business in Ukraine and Russia. Some of his contacts there were under surveillance by the National Security Agency for suspected links to Russias Federal Security Service, one of the officials said. [...] The F.B.I. is leading the investigations, aided by the National Security Agency, the C.I.A. and the Treasury Departments financial crimes unit.

This was an operation by law enforcement and intelligence agencies to investigate connections between Trump's team and the Russians. But for Trumpesters like you who are screaming to the sky that "trump was being wiretapped", you're willfully ignorant of the fact that any surveillance done by the various law enforcement and intelligence agencies was legal.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 15:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In an interview with CNN's Don Lemon, Painter spoke about reports that former national security advisor Flynn was working for foreign agents while also working for the American government. It makes no sense to run a government this way, Painter said. "This is a completely chaotic situation, and then Gen. Flynn lied about his contacts with the Russians, lied to the vice president, and weve had the attorney general in testimony before the Senate Judiciary Committee say he did not contact the Russians when he had contacts with the Russians." People are not being honest about their foreign contacts, and talk about this deep state theory as if there are somehow Obama moles in the government under the Trump administration, Painter continued. Its the KGB agents running around the West Wing or the national security council."

First they vigorously deny any contacts with the Russians   when they get caught they respond by saying they don't recall!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  President Donald Trumps revised travel ban executive order suffered its first legal setback Friday as a federal judge blocked the directive's potential impact on the family of a Syrian refugee living in Wisconsin.[...] The court showdown in Wisconsin was just one of at least five expected to play out in the coming days as various states, organizations and individuals try to block some or all of Trumps redrafted travel ban order from taking effect as scheduled just after midnight Wednesday night. In Maryland, a federal judge set a hearing for Wednesday morning on a lawsuit brought by refugee aid groups. Another hearing is set to take place in front of a federal judge in Honolulu on a travel ban suit brought by the state of Hawaii. In addition, the states of Washington and Minnesota are asking a judge in Seattle to confirm that an existing injunction against key parts of Trump's original travel ban executive order blocks similar portions of his revised directive. No hearing has been set on that dispute, but one is expected next week before Trump's new order kicks in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Revised Trump travel ban suffers first legal blow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   By partnering with the Kurds in the Raqqa assault, the U.S. also risks being seen as entering into an indirect alliance with Russia and Assad's government, which Moscow backs. With Russian air support, Assad's troops and allied forces like Lebanon's Hezbollah have advanced against IS in northern and central Syria. In the Syrian army's advance against IS troops in Palmyra, the troops were indirectly aided by U.S. airstrikes against the group. Promising to scale up the war on the Islamic State group, Trump has hinted he would be less averse to an implied alliance with the Russians and perhaps even Assad, which he has described as a better option than the rebels. But even a perceived lean toward Moscow and Damascus could bring a backlash from fiercely anti-Assad factions on the ground, threatening to draw American troops into the wider civil war in Syria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analysis: US troop increase risks tangling in Syria's war </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [House of Cards](https://twitter.com/HouseofCards/status/840281091718205441):

 Your loyalty has not gone unnoticed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two degrees of ~~separation~~ Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The State Department asked the New York Medical Examiner not to publicly release information about the cause of death of Russia's ambassador to the United Nations. Vitaly Churkin died unexpectedly in New York last month, one day before his 65th birthday.

Polonium-210 maybe?

Edit: In 2015 a former aide to Putin was found dead in a DC hotel. Here is what it was reported in the media: 

 [**Russian official died of blunt force trauma in D.C. hotel**](http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2016/03/10/russian-official-died-blunt-force-trauma-dc-hotel/81607816/): A prominent Russian millionaire and former official under Vladimir Putin found dead last year in a Washington hotel died of blunt force injuries to the head, Washington's Office of the Chief Medical Examiner announced Thursday. Beverly Seals, chief of staff, confirmed the finding involving the death of Mikhail Lesin, former head of media affairs for the Russian government. Initial reports placed Lesin's cause of death as a heart attack. He was found dead Nov. 5 at the Hotel Dupont, where he'd been staying. In a joint statement released Thursday, the Office of the Chief Medical Examiner and Washington's Metropolitan Police Department identified the cause of death for Lesin, 59, as "blunt force injuries to the head." The statement also identified "other contributing factors" as "blunt force injuries of the neck, torso, upper extremities and lower extremities." The statement said the manner of death was undertermined. 

Few months later, the cause of death was ruled "accidental":

 [**Death of former Putin aide at D.C. hotel is ruled accidental**](https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/public-safety/2015-death-of-former-putin-aide-at-dc-hotel-ruled-accidental-result-of-alcohol/2016/10/28/f5b2a63e-9d1f-11e6-a0ed-ab0774c1eaa5_story.html?utm_term=.2cc78e179f8a): A onetime aide of Russian President Vladimir Putin whose body was found last year in a D.C. hotel room died of head injuries suffered in accidental falls after days of excessive drinking, authorities in Washington said Friday as they closed the death investigation. Mikhail Y. Lesin, 57, a former Russian advertising executive who helped create the Kremlins global English-language Russia Today television network, was found dead Nov. 5 in the upscale Dupont Circle Hotel, and for much of a year, the manner of death was ruled undetermined. The manner has been amended to an accident with acute ethanol intoxication as a contributing cause, the office of U.S. Attorney Channing D. Phillips said Friday. Lesin was alone in his hotel room at the time of the falls, the statement said. The new ruling was made by the office of the D.C. chief medical examiner.

Edit 3: 

 [Just sent this to a former State Department official, their response: "I've never heard of diplomatic immunity surviving after death"](https://twitter.com/yashar/status/840249378749198337) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> State Dept. seeks to keep Russian diplomat's cause of death private </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "January 2018"

 however Mack tells TrekMovie this is only a guess and that for now all he knows for sure is the book will come out after the premiere of the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  His habits in the White House so far comport with what friends in New York say about his pre-political life. He has long been a creature of comfort, eschewing some of New York's glitzy balls and galas to instead stay at home, watch TV and dine in his apartment, while watching sports and calling friends. After winning the presidency, he largely stayed in his apartment or at Mar-a-Lago, venturing out once in New York to the 21 Club for dinner. He is happy to not go outside. 
He's not a guy who likes to be away from his own bed, said Chrisr Ruddy, a longtime Trump friend and the CEO of Newsmax, who visited Trump recently at the White House. He doesn't want to tour or travel for the sake of traveling. If he can get in a round of golf in Scotland, he'll do that. But you're not going to see him just spend three days shopping and visiting friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps in the White House bubble, and he loves it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 01:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Sean Spicer was just asked about Trump ally/advisor Nigel Farage meeting today with Julian Assange earlier today. When asked whether Farage was delivering a message to Assange from Trump, Spicer said "I have no idea."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spicer Asked About Farage, Ducks Question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 01:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Later...

 But he added in a separate email Thursday that he has no evidence he was surveilled last year. My phone looks clean to me, he said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yep.](http://variety.com/2017/tv/news/american-horror-story-season-7-theme-election-2016-1201989834/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think it is an affirmation of the presidents decision to ask Gen. Flynn to resign, Pence said in an interview with Fox News.

Funny because that same president called Flynn "a wonderful man" and whined that Flynn "has been treated very, very unfairly by the media, as I call it, the fake media in many cases, And I think it is really a sad thing that he was treated so badly."


 "Hearing that story today was the first I heard of it," Pence said of Flynn's connection to Turkey.

Sure, it is not like the media reported about it before! Oh, wait. Here is an article from Politico in November 2016 about Flynn: 

[Trump adviser linked to Turkish lobbying](http://www.politico.com/story/2016/11/donald-trump-turkey-lobbying-231354) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From [Fox 40](http://fox40.com/2017/03/09/white-house-cancels-open-press-events-by-trump/):

 Trump did hold one open press event on Thursday. When asked about the Wikileaks matter by a reporter, he smiled and did not respond. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paramount's Chinese Partners Haven't Paid a Penny of Promised $1 Billion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Election Set for HBO Miniseries from 'Game Change' Team </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Questions about the possible connection were widely dismissed four months ago. But the FBI's investigation remains open, the sources said, and is in the hands of the FBI's counterintelligence team -- the same one looking into Russia's suspected interference in the 2016 election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "I was invited for example to both conventions. I was, uh the first, that was the Republican convention, but then unexpectedly while being there, I was called back to Moscow for reason that has nothing to do with the elections.

So like Sessions he volunteered information to deny any connections between his sudden trip to Moscow, after the GOP convention, and the elections even though no one asked him about that!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Retired Adm. James Loy, a former Coast Guard official who served as deputy homeland security secretary and TSA administrator under President George W. Bush, told Politico that the Trump administrations plan is ignorant of what constitutes national security They simply dont understand the equation. Politico also talked to Stephen Flynn, a retired Coast Guard commander, who pointed out that as you harden the land border you open up the maritime border It makes no sense. Whether the border wall will even enhance the national security of the U.S. is debatable. Last year, Reuters reported that U.S. Customs and Border Protection agents dont think a wall is necessary. Instead, they seek better equipment and technology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump wants to make America safe again by gutting Coast Guard and TSA budgets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WH: 'No recollection' that Trump met Russian ambassador at event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jason Isaacs on twitter: Nice chair. Hope it's comfy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since TV networks are churning out so many shows based on movies, might as well add my own wish list for the next batch of movies to be adapted to TV shows: 
 
* The Fugitive. (The Harrison Ford movie was based on an old TV show from the 70s iirc)
* Enemy of the State. 
* L.A. Confidential.
* Die Hard. 
* Ronin.
* Bad Boys.
* Deep Rising.
* Species.
* Invasion of the Body Snatchers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Star Trek' Enlists Jason Isaacs as 'Discovery' Captain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Speaking outside his firm's offices in Belgravia, he told the Press Association: "I'm really pleased to be back here working again at the Orbis's offices in London today. "I'm now going to be focusing my efforts on supporting the broader interests of our company here. "I'd like to say a warm thank you to everyone who sent me kind messages and support over the last few weeks. "Just to add, I won't be making any further statements or comments at this time." [...] Mr Steeles friends say it is currently unlikely he would be willing to travel to the US. But it is understood Democrats  as well as some Republicans  in Congress are prepared to facilitate discreet initial meetings in the UK or on other neutral territory. Earlier, it was reported that the FBI had been considering paying Mr Steele to continue his research once the election was over and the Democrats withdrew funding. In the end, Mr Steele was so worried by what he had found that he ended up working on the dossier for free, as The Independent reported in January. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-British spy Christopher Steele breaks silence over Donald Trump Russia dossier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI Director Comey backs out of SXSW interview </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Survivor' Hits 500: Jeff Probst Reflects on the Journey Toward 'Game Changers' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House on the defensive over wiretapping allegation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mulvaney: Parts of border wall could be 'see-through' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking Republicans. Two days ago Grassley rejected calls from the Democrats to have Jeff Sessions testify before the Senate Judiciary Committee about his meetings with the Russian ambassador. And now he's going after the MI6 agent Christopher Steele to discredit him and the FBI? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [John Schindler](https://twitter.com/20committee/status/838519508843245569) twitter thread yesterday:

 AHEM: US IC has considerable SIGINT featuring high-level Russians talking about their collusion with Team Trump. You heard it here 1st.

 SIGINT is from #NSA   partners. This is called "reflections" in spookdom, ie readouts from convos about current ops.

 Individually these convos are not all that persuasive, analytically; but collectively, they demonstrate collusion.

 BLUF: 1 intercepted convo between 2 senior Kremlin guys talking about collusion w/Trump isn't a big deal; a bunch of them = a very big deal.

 I'm confident that any SERIOUS investigation of #TrumpRussia will find enough intel to end Trump's admin   send people to jail. cc @GOP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From a previous [Politico report in February](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/02/reince-priebus-trump-white-house-235076) Priebus comes off as an insecure chief of staff: 

 Some White House aides say theyve seen Bannon or Conway in conversation with Trump  and then observed Priebus rushing to insert himself into the discussion. At times, he has seemed determined to convince others of his influence. After the botched travel ban rollout, Priebus made a round of calls to senior Republicans to relay that the president had made clear that Priebus team, and no one else, was in charge of day-to-day operations. "He's not been set up to be a very strong chief of staff," said one staffer. "I think there's an insecurity there." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Others complain about Priebuss West Wing management, which they argue has become suffocating. They point to his habit of sprinting into meetings  He literally runs, said one senior administration official  which has led top aides to believe that he is trying to edge his way into their conversations or monitor their discussions with the president.

Run, Reince, run!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL. Are you living in a cave? 

From the Trump campaign alone we have:

* Paul Manafort, former Trump campaign manager

* Carter Page, former Trump foreign policy adviser

* Roger Stone, informal adviser

* General Michael Flynn, former Trump national security adviser

* Jeff Sessions, Trump attorney general

* Jared Kushner, Trump son-in-law and senior adviser </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Its not paranoia at all when its actually happening. Its leak after leak after leak from the bureaucrats in the [intelligence community] and former Obama administration officials  and its very real, said Rep. Devin Nunes (R-Calif.), the chairman of the House Intelligence Committee. The White House is absolutely concerned and is trying to figure out a systemic way to address whats happening.

This is coming from the guy in charge of the Russia investigations in the House.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You should not be messing around with the White House Counsels office.

You mean the White House counsel that didn't bother to tell the vice-president for 3 weeks that Flynn lied to him about his contacts with the Russians. The same office that was responsible to the catastrophic rollout of Trumps travel ban. 

Yeah, the Democrats are definitely fucked!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Declined to comment means it is fake?? You guys are hilarious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Timeline: Trump team and its Russia meetings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  that they didn't have enough of a case for a FISA approval is shocking. 

What are you talking about? According to media reports the FBI was denied a FISA warrant in the summer and the court asked them to narrow the focus of the surveillance. The FBI did that and they were grant a FISA warrant from the court in October.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need a lip reader to figure out what Bannon was saying in that video.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. 

Former Bush Attorney General [Michael Mukasey on ABC](https://twitter.com/ThisWeekABC/status/838398335861981184):

 Fmr Bush AG: Wiretap would mean "there was some basis to believe somebody in Trump Tower may have been acting as an agent of the Russians."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A senior White House official tells the New York Times that White House counsel, Donald F. McGahn is now searching for a FISA warrant  or series of warrants  allegedly issued in an Obama-era investigation of Donald Trumps ties to a shifty Russian bank. The official says that McGahns office wants access to any order, issued by the ultra-secretive Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Court, relating to President Trump, his campaign, or his immediate associates. Those documents are usually only available to law enforcement, and while the White House has the authority to request the documents, they typically dont  largely because the Department of Justice is supposed to be insulated from political pressure to take on, or complete, an investigation.

Edit: People are downvoting without reading the article!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump Directs White House Counsel to Find FISA Warrants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 17:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was really excited when I heard the news in late 2015 that Star Trek is finally coming back to TV. Then I learned that it is another prequel and my enthusiasm for the show dropped. 


Ill give it a shot and see what they will come up with; but it is frustrating that since 2001 they keep going back in the timeline rather than moving forward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 17:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mike Rogers](https://twitter.com/TeddyDavisCNN/status/838397371482587140):

 Mike Rogers - fmr. chair of House Intelligence Committee - on Trump/wiretap: "He just put another quarter in the conspiracy parking meter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In an interview on NBC's "Meet The Press," Schumer said Obama has "flatly denied that he has done this." "And either way, Chuck, the president's in trouble. If he falsely spread this kind of misinformation, that is so wrong," Schumer said. "It's beneath the dignity of the presidency. It is something that really hurts people's view of government." Schumer said if this is the case, it shows the president doesn't know how to "conduct himself." "On the other hand, if it's true, it's even worse for the president," Schumer said. "Because that means that a federal judge, independently elected, has found probable cause that the president, or people on his staff, have probable cause to have broken the law or to have interacted with a foreign agent." Schumer called that possibility "serious stuff." "So either way, the president makes it worse with these tweets. Now, is he trying to divert things here? Yeah," Schumer said.


His second point align with what former Bush Attorney General [Michael Mukasey said on ABC](https://twitter.com/ThisWeekABC/status/838398335861981184):

 Fmr Bush AG: Wiretap would mean "there was some basis to believe somebody in Trump Tower may have been acting as an agent of the Russians."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schumer on Trump claims: Either way, the president is 'in trouble' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "There is one page in the Trump White House crisis management playbook, Earnest told ABCs This Week. And that is simply to tweet or say something outrageous to distract from a scandal. And the bigger the scandal, the more outrageous the tweet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earnest: The bigger the scandal, the more outrageous the Trump tweet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Former Bush Attorney General [Michael Mukasey on ABC](https://twitter.com/ThisWeekABC/status/838398335861981184):

 Fmr Bush AG: Wiretap would mean "there was some basis to believe somebody in Trump Tower may have been acting as an agent of the Russians."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 15:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ExtraTV asked the actor if "another Star Trek" is in his future. Pine replied: "I havent really heard anything about it. I havent gotten the script, so we will see what happens. But, I love  I love this group of people." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Pine Hasnt Heard Anything About Next Star Trek Movie + Paramount Searching For New CEO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 15:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Tomorrowland' happened. In 2015 Disney was working on Tron 3 and then the $180 million Tomorrowland tanked at the box movie and weeks later Disney pulled the plug on Tron 3. 


[Disney Cancels Tron 3 Following The Disappointment Of Tomorrowland](http://www.indiewire.com/2015/05/disney-cancels-tron-3-following-the-disappointment-of-tomorrowland-263287/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disney Wants to Reboot TRON with Jared Leto: Sources say this new project is not a direct sequel and is being built out of the source code of the deleted Tron 3 script. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekend Box Office: 'Logan' Scores $33M Friday for Huge $80M Bow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you're Russian, it's in the interest of every American citizen. 

Edit: Never mind, it looks like you've nothing to contribute but to [deflect](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5uuy4f/russia_says_it_wants_a_postwest_world_order/ddx1od3/).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Attorney General Jeff Sessions is slated to attend a dinner with President Trump and other administration officials on Saturday night at the president's private Mar-a-Lago resort in Florida, the White House said. The dinner comes after reports that Trump was angry Sessions recused himself from any investigations into Russias interference in the U.S. presidential election.[...] Sessions will attend the dinner along with Commerce Secretary Wilbur Ross, Homeland Security Secretary John Kelly, White House chief strategist Stephen Bannon, White House counsel Don McGahn and senior advisor Stephen Miller, according to the White House.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sessions to attend Mar-a-Lago dinner with Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Vicente Fox](https://twitter.com/VicenteFoxQue/status/838086002489053184):

 A "so-called" President is calling a real President and true leader: bad and sick guy. What a shame, America you need to do something now!

Indeed, it's way past time to remove the lunatic from the White House.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Jon Favreau](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/03/trump-obama-wire-tapping-trump-tower-phones-235679):

 Obama's former speechwriter, Jon Favreau, pointed out in a tweet that the former president's avowed lack of involvement does not mean that a legal FISA warrant could not have been granted to tap Trump's phones if the intelligence community had reason to do so. I'd be careful about reporting that Obama said there was no wiretapping. Statement just said that neither he nor the WH ordered it," Favreau tweeted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The FBI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to media reports the FISA court asked the FBI to narrow the focus of the surveillance, apparently the FBI did that and was granted the warrant in October.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might be a good time to invoke section 4 of the 25th Amendment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a fine-tuned machine! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Some political observers discern a deliberate pattern of distraction and diversion in the early morning tweets that are the product of the presidents prodigious fingers. When the media coverage, or the congressional pressure, gets too tough, a simple tweet is enough to send the press stampeding in the other direction.[...] Still, the reality is that the Trump administration has every available tool to block the Russian investigation. Sessions would need to appoint a special counsel to investigate Russian ties to lead to any prosecution. Without a special counsel, the current FBI investigations will grind to a halt before any decision to prosecute. Congress could pick up those investigations and lead to impeachment. But given the solid Republican control of both sides of Capitol Hill, that is unlikely  unless public opinion turns even more decisively against Trump, especially among Republican voters.[...] Minutes after declassifying this blockbuster intelligence about a new Watergate, Trump had already moved on to more weighty matters. Arnold Schwarzenegger isnt voluntarily leaving the Apprentice, he wrote. He was fired by his bad (pathetic) ratings, not by me. Sad end to a great show. You can almost feel the burn, or the narcissism, or the attention deficit disorder. Its up to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out of control? Or is Trump's tweeting designed to distract? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By itself it doesn't imply guilt. But taken in the context of the constant contacts between Trump's team and the Russians it shows that unlike what Trump was saying that "there was nothing here" the FBI has reasonable grounds to seek and to be granted The Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act (FISA) warrant.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  One former policy advisor for President Obama quickly pointed out that the president doesnt have authority to order a wiretap. While it is possible that Trumps communications were intercepted by American intelligence agencies, that would also suggest that a FISA court granted a surveillance warrant after finding probable cause that members of the Trump campaign team communicated inappropriately with Russia. And that could bring an avalanche of pressure onto the sitting president.[...] If the FBI felt Trumps campaign warranted wiretaps and a federal judge signed off on surveillance, then it could mean there was noteworthy communication between Trumps team and influential Russian officials.


Edit: [Rep. Ted Lieu (D-CA)](https://twitter.com/tedlieu/status/838056836783730689) 

 Mr. President: If there was a wiretap at Trump Tower, that means a fed judge found probable cause of crime which means you are in deep shit. [...] Either @realDonaldTrump is paranoid like Nixon, or judge found probable cause of crime for #wiretap. Either way our President is in trouble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump claims he was wiretapped. If hes right, it could be his undoing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it is not. Try again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time for a 'use it or lose it' rule for Canadian streaming rights, advocates say: In-demand shows kept off Canadian streaming services by traditional broadcasters who hold the rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Guardian](https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2017/jan/10/fbi-chief-given-dossier-by-john-mccain-alleging-secret-trump-russia-contacts) reported about it in January and I'm sure that we will have more info after Trump's tweets. 

 The Guardian has learned that the FBI applied for a warrant from the foreign intelligence surveillance (Fisa) court over the summer in order to monitor four members of the Trump team suspected of irregular contacts with Russian officials. The Fisa court turned down the application asking FBI counter-intelligence investigators to narrow its focus. According to one report, the FBI was finally granted a warrant in October, but that has not been confirmed, and it is not clear whether any warrant led to a full investigation. 

Also check this [twitter thread](https://twitter.com/JYSexton/status/838042338882633728) from someone at the New York Times:

 The Obama wiretapping accusation, on its face is ridiculous, but the thing is that, if his phones were tapped, it was by a court order 2/. Trump, in midst of Russian scandal, should know not to point at something incriminating. It never occurs to him it's an investigation 3/ All signs point to him having done something wrong, but it's obvious he doesn't understand that he did. That's...baffling. 4/

And this [one from John Schindler](https://twitter.com/20committee/status/838001204206649344):
 

 SIGINT collection authorized per FISA is hardly illegal wiretapping. If POTUS has evidence of different, he needs to show it -- or shut up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The FBI was granted a FISA court warrant in October to probe the activities of Trumps campaign ties to Russia. Trump is basically incriminating himself by admitting that his team was under surveillance.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The FBI was granted a FISA court warrant in October. Trump is too stupid to realize that he's confirming that his team was under FBI investigations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "No President can order a wiretap. Those restrictions were put in place to protect citizens from people like you," Ben Rhodes tweeted Satruday morning. He also said "only a liar" could make the case, as Trump suggested, that Obama wire tapped Trump Tower ahead of the election.

Touch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Teams Links to Russia Crisscross in Washington </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Scott Pruitt. What he said: In his written testimony to Congress, Pruitt said he never used a private email address for business while he was Oklahoma's attorney general. What really happened: A spokesman for the Oklahoma attorney general's office told Oklahoma City's Fox 25 that Pruitt used his personal email during his tenure in the office. The email was discovered during a public information request.

Another Pence!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sessions isn't the only Cabinet member who gave testimony that turned out not to be true </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did and once it was discovered by the press they deleted their RNC accounts!

 In late January, we learned that top White House officials, including Steve Bannon, Kellyanne Conway, Jared Kushner, and Sean Spicer, were using email addresses from the Republican National Committee  with a private server! Once the story broke their addresses were deleted, but presumably had it remained secret, they would have continued to use them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And Pence is not the only one: Scott Pruitt, President Donald Trump's Environmental Protection Agency administrator, not only used a private email account to conduct official business as attorney general of Oklahoma, he lied about it during his confirmation hearings.[...] But this actually matters beyond the question of catching Republicans in the act of hypocrisy. That's because there are strong reasons to believe that the Trump administration is leaving sensitive information vulnerable, and may not be complying with the Presidential Records Act, which mandates that White House staff retain their communications  including their emails. In late January, we learned that top White House officials, including Steve Bannon, Kellyanne Conway, Jared Kushner, and Sean Spicer, were using email addresses from the Republican National Committee  with a private server! Once the story broke their addresses were deleted, but presumably had it remained secret, they would have continued to use them. That's not the only cybersecurity issue we still have to worry about. At the end of January, the New York Times reported that Trump was still using his old, unsecured Android phone, which is unbelievably reckless for the president of the United States. As Wired magazine put it , "All it takes is clicking on one malicious link or opening one untoward attachment  either of which can appear as though it were sent from a trusted source  to compromise the device. From there, the phone could be infected with malware that spies on the network the device is connected to, logs keystrokes, takes over the camera and microphone for surreptitious recording, and more." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commentary: Mike Pence is a huge hypocrite on emails </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "I can cite the media that say all this is very much reminiscent of a witch hunt and the McCarthyism era which we all thought was long gone," he added. Lavrov's wording was nearly identical to Trump's. The president on Thursday tweeted: "The real story is all of the illegal leaks of classified and other information. It is a total 'witch hunt!' "

Russian puppets think alike! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian foreign minister decries 'witch hunt,' echoing Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a coincidence! Trump is calling the revelations ["total witch hunt."](http://www.nbcnews.com/politics/first-read/trump-cries-witch-hunt-russia-questions-pile-n728611) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Although the chairman of the committee in the Senate, Richard Burr of North Carolina, has promised to conduct a thorough investigation, he has been extremely close to Trump throughout his campaign serving as his national security adviser. There have been disclosures that Burr helped the White House to push back against critical stories about the Trump-Russia connections. The problem with the standing committees is that partisanship is too powerful a force in contemporary politics to trust them to do a good job. This investigation revolves around a very serious question -- the integrity of the electoral process and the potential high crimes and misdemeanors of key members of Trump's inner circle. [...] Establishing a bipartisan select committee to investigate Russia would give both parties equal power in handling this investigation. The committee would also be able to devote all of its time and energy to this single issue rather than relying on standing committees that have a lot of other work to do. A select committee could do its business in public, just like Ervin and Baker did in that long, hot summer of 1973, so that the public could see and hear for themselves exactly what happened.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's time for a Watergate-style select committee on Russiagate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've got hacked!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far from the campaign alone we have:

* Paul Manafort, former Trump campaign manager

* Carter Page, former Trump foreign policy adviser

* Roger Stone, informal adviser

* General Michael Flynn, former Trump national security adviser

* Jeff Sessions, Trump attorney general

* Jared Kushner, Trump son-in-law and senior adviser </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Who's Who of the Trump Campaign's Russia Connections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [John Schindler](https://twitter.com/20committee/status/837420972319846402):

 Team Trump's defense now boils down to; "We've all had so many meetings with top Kremlin officials we can't remember what was said, when." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The New Yorker reported it first and then the White House confirmed it when they were asked by the New York Times, the WH didn't volunteer the info.  

 The New Yorker reported this week that Mr. Kushner had met with Mr. Kislyak at Trump Tower in December. Hope Hicks, a White House spokeswoman, confirmed on Thursday that Mr. Flynn was also at the meeting in response to questions from a New York Times reporter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of this has happened before and will happen again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CNN's Chief National Security Correspondent Jim Sciutto:
 
 [Setting him up for the fall?](https://twitter.com/jimsciutto/status/837361342541619201) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   The FBI apparently spearheaded a probe into Sessions' potential ties to Russia while he was still an adviser to President Trumps campaign, the Wall Street Journal reported late Wednesday. The investigation was part of a sweeping counterintelligence inquiry into possible contacts between the Trump camp and Russian officials. The investigation looked into possible conversations Sessions could have held with Russian officials while serving as Trumps foreign policy adviser last spring, a person familiar with the matter told The Journal. The CIA, the NSA and the Treasury Department were also pursuing the investigation, according to sources. [...] The investigation could prove awkward and unusual if it remains ongoing, since Sessions oversees the FBI as the head of the Justice Department.


And according to Sen. Mike Lee in a comment to [Business Insider](http://www.businessinsider.com/jeff-sessions-russia-ambassador-2017-3)  


 FBI had not yet offered an explanation for why it did not inform the Judiciary Committee about the investigation prior to Sessions' January confirmation hearing. The spokesperson said the senator learned of the investigation through news reports Wednesday evening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intelligence officials investigated Jeff Sessions' Russia contacts during Trump's campaign: report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did the president know, and when did he know it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  W. Hunter Walton, a former aide to Sessions who also worked for Mitt Romney, pointed to his past work of trying to get Supreme Court Justice Elena Kagan to recuse herself from an ObamaCare case since she worked in the administration while the law was being written.I spent countless hours working on argument for Kagen [sic] to recuse from ACA cases for Sessions. Recusal should be no brainer for him, he tweeted on Thursday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Sessions staffer: 'No-brainer' for him to recuse himself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legion of Doom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's getting there but let's remember that Watergate took two years from June 17, 1972 the day of the break-in at the DNC headquarters to August 9, 1974 the day Nixon resigned the presidency. And Congress was actively investigating the actions by the President and his administration, we don't have that yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This is standard fare in U.S. war propaganda: we fixate on the Americans who are killed, learning their names and life stories and the plight of their spouses and parents, but steadfastly ignore the innocent people the U.S. government kills, whose numbers are always far greater. There is thus a sprawling, moving monument in the center of Washington, D.C. commemorating the 58,000 U.S. soldiers who died in Vietnam, but not the (at least) 2 million Vietnamese civilians killed by that war. [...] By dramatizing the deaths of Americans while disappearing its victims, this technique ensures that Americans perpetually regard themselves as victims of horrific, savage, tragic violence but never the perpetrators of it. That, in turn, is what keeps Americans supporting endless war: these savages keep killing us, so we have no choice but to fight them. More importantly, this process completely dehumanizes the people the U.S. Government bombs, attacks and kills. Because theyre never heard from, because we never learn their names, because we never experience their familys suffering, all of their human attributes are stripped from them and their deaths are thus meaningless because theyre barely human. This dehumanization  the suppression of any humanity on the part of the U.S.s foreign war victims  is the absolute key to sustaining popular support for war. Nobody knew that better than Gen. William Westmoreland, the U.S. Commander of the Vietnam War, which is why he insisted that Orientals do not experience death and suffering the way that westerners do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  An initial effort to release information took an embarrassing turn when US Central Command, in an attempt to prove new information was discovered, released excerpts of terror training video scooped up in the mission that turned out to have been available online for years already. The video was quickly removed and the planned video release cancelled. The analysis of the material gathered remains ongoing and there is no final assessment yet on the precise intelligence value of what was gathered, two other administration officials emphasized.

Perhaps they will release a video of the Afghan Mujahideen from the 80s this time around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Late summer, early fall, late winter or early spring! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CBS Chief Les Moonves told investors today that 'Star Trek: Discovery' will premiere in late Summer or early Fall 2017. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Stupid movie. I never seen it

Does not compute, insufficient data.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 00:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baghdad Sean at it again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 00:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yet like billionaire investment banker Vincent Viola, who withdraw his nomination to be secretary of the Army earlier this month, Bilden ran into too many challenges during a review by the Office of Government Ethics to avoid potential conflicts of interest, the sources said.

Extreme vetting, everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The New York Times ad: The Truth Is Hard](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gY0Fdz350GE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In 1989, two centuries after our Constitution was promulgated, the man who is now our president wrote that civil liberties end when an attack on our safety begins. [...] The aspiring tyrants of today have not forgotten the lesson of 1933: that acts of terrorreal or fake, provoked or accidentalcan provide the occasion to deal a death blow to democracy. The most consequential example is Russia, so admired by Donald Trump. When Vlaimir V. Putin was appointed prime minister in August 1999, the former KGB officer had an approval rating of 2 percent. Then, a month later, the bombs began to explode in apartment buildings in Moscow and several other Russian cities, killing hundreds of citizens and causing widespread fear. There were numerous indications that this was a campaign organized by the KGBs heir, now known as the FSB. Some of its officers were caught red-handed (and then released) by their peers. A Russian parliamentarian announced one of the terror attacks several days before the bomb actually exploded. Putin blamed Muslim terrorists and began the war in Chechnya that made him popular. He thereafter exploited more terrorist attacks to consolidate his rule: three years later, Russian security forces ended up gassing to death Russian civilians in a botched response to an attack at a Moscow theater. Putin used the negative press coverage as a justification for seizing control of television. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Reichstag Warning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good job Orange One, he just made sure that the media will focus again on the real story Russia rather than wasting time on the silly White House correspondents dinner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really shocking when a fake news network hires a fake expert. Also this is not the first time this happens at Fox News, nor the last time. 

[Washington Post](https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/public-safety/fox-news-analyst-still-wont-admit-he-was-not-in-cia/2016/07/14/eb61b5e4-478e-11e6-bdb9-701687974517_story.html?utm_term=.adcc0b82bf4b):

 **Fox News commentator who feds say faked a CIA career sentenced to 33 months in prison**: Wayne Simmons was a professional football player, a drug trafficker, a nightclub doorman, a Fox News guest analyst and an intelligence adviser in Afghanistan. What Simmons, 62, was not, according to all available evidence, was a CIA agent. In federal court in Virginia on Friday, just before he was sentenced to 33 months in prison, he apologized for lying about his security clearance, his criminal history and his finances. [...] Through his Fox News contacts, according to prosecutors, Simmons in 2008 got a job with defense contractor BAE Systems to help the military in Afghanistan deal with the local population. But Simmons was cut before he deployed because he got such low marks in training, according to court records. Col. Steve Rotkoff, deputy director of the program, told prosecutors that the defendant was act[ing] like a fictional CIA character instead of an actual CIA operative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From a previous article:


 US military officials told [Reuters](https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/feb/02/trump-approved-yemen-raid-five-days-after-inauguration) that Trump approved, [over dinner], his first covert counterterrorism operation without sufficient intelligence, ground support or adequate backup preparations.


And the outcome of the raid that was approved over dinner?


* Failure to capture or kill their main objective Qasim al-Rimi the leader of Al-Qaeda in the Arabian Peninsula (AQAP).
* One Navy SEAL was killed.
* 25 civilians were killed including 9 children.
* An aircraft was damaged   later destroyed by US forces. 
* Three US special forces were wounded. 
* Some of the important intelligence that were obtained in the raid were 10 years old videos that were already public.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Did they rig the election? No. That part is bullshit.

No, we can't rule out anything. 

 [FBI director: Hackers 'poking around' voter systems](http://www.cnn.com/2016/09/28/politics/fbi-james-comey-election-cyberattacks/) - The FBI has discovered attempted hacks of voter registration sites in more than a dozen states according to two law enforcement officials. US investigators believe that Russia is behind those attempted hacks the officials said. Earlier Wednesday, FBI Director James Comey spoke of additional attempted hacks at a House Judiciary Committee hearing in Washington, but did not specify a number. "There have been a variety of scanning activities which is a preamble for potential intrusion activities as well as some attempted intrusions at voter database registrations beyond those we knew about in July and August. We are urging the states just to make sure that their deadbolts are thrown and their locks are on and to get the best information they can from DHS just to make sure their systems are secure," he said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There need to be a thorough investigation to be sure. Here is the FBI said in September: 

 [FBI director: Hackers 'poking around' voter systems](http://www.cnn.com/2016/09/28/politics/fbi-james-comey-election-cyberattacks/) - The FBI has discovered attempted hacks of voter registration sites in more than a dozen states according to two law enforcement officials. US investigators believe that Russia is behind those attempted hacks the officials said. Earlier Wednesday, FBI Director James Comey spoke of additional attempted hacks at a House Judiciary Committee hearing in Washington, but did not specify a number. "There have been a variety of scanning activities which is a preamble for potential intrusion activities as well as some attempted intrusions at voter database registrations beyond those we knew about in July and August. We are urging the states just to make sure that their deadbolts are thrown and their locks are on and to get the best information they can from DHS just to make sure their systems are secure," he said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The idiot doth protest too much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He also questioned why the president approved the raid a week after taking office. "I told them I didn't want to make a scene about it, but my conscience wouldn't let me talk to him," Owens told the Herald. "Why at this time did there have to be this stupid mission when it wasn't even barely a week into his administration? Why? For two years prior, there were no boots on the ground in Yemen  everything was missiles and drones  because there was not a target worth one American life. Now, all of a sudden we had to make this grand display?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Father of fallen Navy SEAL refused to meet Trump at ceremony </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beside all the movies that already mentioned here, Paxton was also great as the racist guy that was invited to a dinner with a group of liberal students in a little movie from the 90s called 'The Last Supper'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure Fox News will have wall-to-wall coverage and demand an investigation into this matter, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, they yet to held their daily press briefings since the inauguration. And it looks like Trump is sidelining his own Secretary of State.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Sen. Ron Wyden of Oregon, a senior Democrat on the Intelligence Committee, also warned about the reports. "If Chairman Burr is discussing classified matters with the press and pre-judging the committee's investigation, all at the behest of the White House, it's hard to imagine how he could convince me or the public of his impartiality," Wyden said in a email statement. "If that is the case, I intend to co-sponsor legislation creating an independent commission to investigate Russia's interference in our democracy."

Yep, and it is not just the Chairman of Senate Intelligence Committee who is pre-judging his own investigation. We have the [Chairman of House Intelligence Committee Devin Nunes](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/02/house-intel-chair-trump-russia-investigation-calls-almost-like-mccarthyism-235405) undercutting his committee's investigation as well by telling reporters that the probe is "almost like McCarthyism revisited" and that it is not fair to "go on a witch hunt against, against innocent Americans ?"

All this before completing their investigations. Given their public statements and the revelations from the [Washington Post](https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/trump-administration-sought-to-enlist-intelligence-officials-key-lawmakers-to-counter-russia-stories/2017/02/24/c8487552-fa99-11e6-be05-1a3817ac21a5_story.html?utm_term=.279b21904c2a)  we need a special prosecutor to handle this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Spicer also warned the group of more problems if news of the phone checks and the meeting about leaks was leaked to the media. It's not the first time that warnings about leaks have promptly leaked. The State Department's legal office issued a four-page memo warning of the dangers of leaks -- that memo was immediately posted by the Washington Post.

This read like the Onion!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. If they are not that happy, then leave and form your own party.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted this on another thread about this issue. 

[Here is what  Sarah Huckabee Sanders, the principal White House deputy press secretary said on ABC today](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/post-politics/wp/2017/02/26/white-house-too-early-to-say-whether-a-special-prosecutor-should-look-into-apparent-russian-election-meddling/?tid=sm_fb utm_term=.086b0660b449)

 Were extremely confident that, whatever review, theyre all going to come to the same conclusion: that we had no involvement in this, Sanders said.

I wonder why is she "extremely confident" of the outcome of the congressional probe? Perhaps it has something to do with this little news from Friday that the [Trump administration sought to enlist intelligence officials, key lawmakers to counter Russia stories.](https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/trump-administration-sought-to-enlist-intelligence-officials-key-lawmakers-to-counter-russia-stories/2017/02/24/c8487552-fa99-11e6-be05-1a3817ac21a5_story.html?utm_term=.279b21904c2a) 

And I'm sure that the White House was very pleased that House Intelligence Committee Chairman Devin Nunes, who is in charge of one of congressional probes, [said this on Saturday](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/02/house-intel-chair-trump-russia-investigation-calls-almost-like-mccarthyism-235405):

 This is almost like McCarthyism revisited, the California Republican told reporters at the California Republican Partys spring convention in Sacramento. Were going to go on a witch hunt against, against innocent Americans ? 


And then people wonder why the Democrats are pushing for a special prosecutor! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  While Rubio led the Florida House and held office as a state representative, Florida had one of the highest rates of the uninsured in the nation and none of Rubios proposed reforms made a discernible impact in reducing the cost of health insurance or the number of people who lacked coverage. Only after Obamacare mandated that most people buy coverage did the rate of the uninsured tick down notably in Florida. The number of uninsured would be slightly lower if the state Legislature had not refused to expand Medicaid under the Affordable Care Act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rubio on skipping town halls: Activists will 'heckle and scream at me' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is he hiding? Why he won't show his birth certificate? We need to get to the bottom of this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Were extremely confident that, whatever review, theyre all going to come to the same conclusion: that we had no involvement in this, Sanders said.

I wonder why is she "extremely confident" of the outcome of the congressional probe? Perhaps it has something to do with this little news from Friday that the [Trump administration sought to enlist intelligence officials, key lawmakers to counter Russia stories.](https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/trump-administration-sought-to-enlist-intelligence-officials-key-lawmakers-to-counter-russia-stories/2017/02/24/c8487552-fa99-11e6-be05-1a3817ac21a5_story.html?utm_term=.279b21904c2a) 

And I'm sure that the White House was very pleased that House Intelligence Committee Chairman Devin Nunes, who is in charge of one of congressional probes, [said this on Saturday](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/02/house-intel-chair-trump-russia-investigation-calls-almost-like-mccarthyism-235405):

 This is almost like McCarthyism revisited, the California Republican told reporters at the California Republican Partys spring convention in Sacramento. Were going to go on a witch hunt against, against innocent Americans ? 


And then people wonder why the Democrats are pushing for a special prosecutor! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We begin by building strong parties in the 50 states and the territories, Tom Perez told ABCs This Week. We didnt invest enough in our state party infrastructure. We didnt invest enough in grass roots organization. We ignored rural swaths of America. We cant do that. We need an every zip code strategy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perez: We need to redefine role of DNC to reverse GOP victories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Expanse: Home - Caterpillars and Butterflies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pruitt mails show lobbyists seeking puppet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a reply to a future question about it

Trump: I am the least Islamophobic person that 'you've ever seen in your entire life, okay? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Washington Post](https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/trump-administration-sought-to-enlist-intelligence-officials-key-lawmakers-to-counter-russia-stories/2017/02/24/c8487552-fa99-11e6-be05-1a3817ac21a5_story.html?hpid=hp_hp-top-table-main_trumprussia-720pm%3Ahomepage%2Fstory utm_term=.43b34326a6ce)


 Acting at the behest of the White House, the officials made calls to news organizations last week in attempts to challenge stories about alleged contacts between members of President Trumps campaign team and Russian intelligence operatives, U.S. officials said. The calls were orchestrated by the White House after unsuccessful attempts by the administration to get senior FBI officials to speak with news organizations and dispute the accuracy of stories on the alleged contacts with Russia.[...] The effort also involved senior lawmakers with access to classified intelligence about Russia, including Sen. Richard Burr (R-N.C.) and Rep. Devin Nunes (R-Calif.), the chairmen of the Senate and House intelligence committees. A spokesman for Nunes said that he had already begun speaking to reporters to challenge the story and then at the request of a White House communications aide, Chairman Nunes then spoke to an additional reporter and delivered the same message.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP intel chairs push media on Russia story at Trump behest: WaPo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, they were trying to undermine their own "investigations". 

From the WP article: 

 The decision to involve those officials could be perceived as threatening the independence of U.S. spy agencies that are supposed to remain insulated from partisan issues, as well as undercutting the credibility of ongoing congressional probes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm watching it as well, that's how I found out about the Washington Post article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Acting at the behest of the White House, the officials made calls to news organizations last week in attempts to challenge stories about alleged contacts between members of President Trumps campaign team and Russian intelligence operatives, U.S. officials said. The calls were orchestrated by the White House after unsuccessful attempts by the administration to get senior FBI officials to speak with news organizations and dispute the accuracy of stories on the alleged contacts with Russia.[...] The effort also involved senior lawmakers with access to classified intelligence about Russia, including Sen. Richard Burr (R-N.C.) and Rep. Devin Nunes (R-Calif.), the chairmen of the Senate and House intelligence committees. A spokesman for Nunes said that he had already begun speaking to reporters to challenge the story and then at the request of a White House communications aide, Chairman Nunes then spoke to an additional reporter and delivered the same message.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump administration sought to enlist intelligence officials, key lawmakers to counter Russia stories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Reeves did, however, draw the line at Speed 2. Even after director Jan de Bont and Bullock doorstepped him. "They said, 'You've got to do this'," he remembers. "And I said, 'I read the script and I can't. It's called Speed and it's on a cruise ship'." The studio were furious. "I didn't work at Fox for 15 years," Reeves says. That's some grudge. "Yeah." Is that how it works? "Yup! It's a jungle out there." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Oscars of Porn" vs. the Oscars: The Surprising Similarities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Esquire Interview: Keanu Reeves - Bill   Ted. Point Break. Speed. The Matrix. John Wick. For 25 years, Keanu Reeves has been one of the movie industry's most bankable stars. And he stays on top without ever losing his outsider cool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, used to watch it with dad when I was young.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I know but I prefer to call him Raymond. A long time ago and before HoC, I used to refer to him as Simon whenever I see him on new shows. Now it is Raymond Tusk.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Department reverses directive to phase out private prisons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Denny Crane!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Episode 4 was dumb on many levels not the least the revelations about the [father](#s "Raymond Tusks company was buying oil from the terrorists, and then the terrorists threaten Raymond to expose the deal. So in order to protect himself and his son presidential campaign, Raymond gives the terrorists information that allowed them to kill the US army rangers and in the process he framed his sons campaign manager as well")!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> '24: Legacy' Producers Apologize For Using Footage From 2013 Kenya Terror Attack in Recent Episode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2016 Movies: X-Men: Apocalypse, Star Trek Beyond, Independence Day: Resurgence, Hell or High Water and Ice Age: Collision Course.


'Mad Men' will be leaving Netflix Canada on March 1, and still no sign of season two of 'Dark Matter' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats Coming to Netflix Canada in March 2017? [Canada] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Alien: Covenant' - "Prologue: Last Supper" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ['Alien: Covenant' - "Prologue: Last Supper"](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EkXgRlRao5I).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Instead, what O'Keefe released on Thursday landed with a dud in the media world. Though not all of the hours of tapes have been made available for review and damning recordings could still come out, O'Keefe made clear the audio he obtained is from 2009 and for the most part features lower-level staffers at the network. In Project Veritas' news release about the tapes, the first highlighted segment are two producers talking about the use of certain polls and why then-CNN polling director (now NH1 News political director and anchor) Paul Steinhauser declined to use a poll by Rasmussen, a group whose polling methods are still not widely accepted. Another highlight is of an assignment desk editor saying "Fox News is unbearable," and a news desk editor talking about how "there's no debate" about climate change.

So scandalous! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If candidate Trump was upset about unfair coverage, it was productive to show him that he was getting fair coverage from outlets that were persuadable, Sam Nunberg, his former communications director, told Politico. The same media that our base digests and prefers is going to be the base for his support. I would assume the president would like see positive and preferential treatment from those outlets and that would help the operation overall. Politico reported that campaign staffers made efforts to promote Trumps good side following disparaging tweets. In one example, the staff convinced conservative media outlets to cover Trumps meeting with Gold Star Mothers of Florida after his disastrous Twitter diatribes against the father of a Muslim U.S. solider who died in Iraq. Politico also described how staffers undertook similar efforts during Trumps incessant tweeting about former Miss Universe Alicia Machado. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump campaign staff to White House: The president wont make embarrassing tweets if he doesnt read any negative publicity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 03:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Wachowskis would have to be involved, said Reeves. They would have to write it and direct it. And then wed see what the story is, but yeah, I dunno, thatd be weird, but why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 03:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Wachowskis would have to be involved, said Reeves. They would have to write it and direct it. And then wed see what the story is, but yeah, I dunno, thatd be weird, but why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keanu Reeves would be open The Matrix 4, if the Wachowskis were directing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 03:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keanu Reeves would be open The Matrix 4, if the Wachowskis were writing and directing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 03:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bates Motel: "Dark Paradise" Review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The White House is sending mixed signals as to whether or not it will rescind President Donald Trump's controversial travel ban even as officials seek to craft a new order that will be less vulnerable to legal challenge. The Justice Department told the 9th Circuit Court of Appeals last week that Trump will "rescind...and replace" the original order, which remains largely on hold after an appeals court panel upheld a lower courts broad injunction. But White House press secretary Sean Spicer said at the conclusion of his daily briefing Tuesday that Trump will not rescind the original order. Instead, the first order is being updated, Spicer insisted. The contradictory statements sowed further confusion about the fate of Trump's original order, which bars immigrants from seven Muslim-majority countries and halts the entry of refugees.

What a fine tuned machine!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House creates confusion about future of Trump's travel ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From page seven in the [Trump Dossier](https://assets.documentcloud.org/documents/3259984/Trump-Intelligence-Allegations.pdf): Source E claimed that Russian diplomatic staffs in New York, DC and Miami were using the emigre pension distribution system as cover for the exchange of information between Trump team and the Russians.

Make you wonder if the ambassador was part of that operation   his death was due to the FSB/GRU cleaning up their mess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putins holy war: In the former atheist stronghold, a law protecting the feelings of religious believers enforces Russian Orthodox Christianity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Godfather' actor Carmine Caridi, the only AMPAS member to be expelled for sharing screeners, reflects on his Oscar infamy: "I was doing a guy a favor, and he screwed me" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Sean Spicer last December](http://www.foxbusiness.com/politics/2016/12/23/sean-spicer-word-vacation-will-not-exist-in-trump-administration.html): 

"He will never take a vacation he cant sit still. Hes so eager to get things done and change things up  there is never an idle moment and so there is not going to be the word vacation will not exist in a Trump administration,


[Politico](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/02/trump-obama-golf-235217): Trump said last August that if he became president, he wouldnt have time for golf. "I'm going to be working for you, I'm not going to have time to go play golf," he said at an event in Virginia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Jared Kushner, son-in-law and senior advisor to president Trump reportedly lashed out at a senior executive from CNNs parent company, according to the Wall Street Journal, over commentary from some of the networks contributors. Mr Kushner has taken issue with specific CNN contributors including Van Jones, a Democrat who served in the Obama administration, and Ana Navarro, a Republican strategist, who have each criticised Mr Trump in harsh terms, the people familiar with the matter said, the report said.  Ana Navaro took to Twitter to reply to Kushner. 

[Ana Navarro's tweet:](https://twitter.com/ananavarro/status/832414138521497600) 

 Little  boy Kushner, tough guy who's supposed to achieve Middle East peace, is complaining about me to CNN. Boo-hoo!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the same guy that provided an image of a cover of a passport as a proof that he wasn't outside the United States.

Edit: Here is the tweet from Michael 'Says who' Cohen:

 [I have never been to Prague in my life. #fakenews](https://twitter.com/MichaelCohen212/status/818991277685567489)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
