<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3605</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] "Death had to take him sleeping, for if Roosevelt had been awake there would have been a fight" Teddy wasn't asleep. He was awake and waiting for Death. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bonus points if someone figures out which book I tried to emulate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah! Sit! Sit! Please, sit with me. You know the most difficult part about this restaurant is choosing where to sit. Do you want to sit next to the fire and watch the pizza being made or do you want to sit by the window and watch the streets. Nowadays the streets are bustling but not like before. And the glass of ros is excellent here. 

Have you heard? The government says they're introducing a new stimulus package, see if it can get the market going again. If you ask me, I don't think it'll work. It didn't work before, it won't work again and besides! Surely you don't expect old men in suit and ties to help us start creating dank memes again? No...I think we just have to let this run its course. There have been other times that this has happened. Years ago and it will happen againmaybe next time we'll learn. 

I hope I'm not boring you by the way, I'm sure you've heard countless tales of old stock traders like myself but if you don't have anything better to do maybe settle in, watch the fire, drink your ros, I know I've drunk plenty of it. 

Many say that the crash came suddenly, that none of the signs were there, that we were caught flat footed. That wasn't the case. Don't believe anything they tell you, they're just bitter over what happened. The signs were there. Memes were being made at a record high! People were investing in normie memes without any real clue as to their value but who cares? They were cheap and people were making a quick buck from investing in those normie memes, penny memes essentially. I got caught up in it to, one of my friends, hmm, if you can even call him a friend. 

He was one of those men they warn you not to trust, men with canes and fedoras but I was younger, more innocent back then, he seemed like a respectable fellow though he could use a shave if you ask me. Nonetheless he introduced me to the world of Memes and soon I made my first investment, it was an old Harambe meme. Yes, laugh. I know, who would invest in a meme that old? I didn't know but fortunately for myself I made some profit off it and soon just like the world I was buying and selling memes like there was no tomorrow! I still remember the flood of upvotes as I posted meme dumps, meme collections. I remember when you could actually make a profit. 

Along the way I met a girl and, well I seemed to charm her with my personality, whatever that was. I suppose the glamor of being part of the NASDANQ was alluring to her and so we dated, my old friend, the salty bastard that he was jumped from a bridge upon discovering this. Why? Turns out I had stolen the girl he was after though he was doing a poor job trying to woo her with talks of My Little Pony. Ah well, who needed him? It's just less competition in the end. 

One night we tied the knot and made love, smocking anything we could get our hands on, in the morning I remember us laughing aboutwelleverything. Everything was funny to us. It might have just been the rare Pepes we were on, though. As the months went on I grew richer and richer and our lives seemed all the more happier, in fact I even got her to try her hand at a little investing, made more upvotes than I did my first time and I was proud of her and I think she was proud of herself to.

The next part is hard for me, friend so excuse me if I drag this on but you know why the stock market was as high as it was? It was because we won the war against 4chan. 4chan for crying out loud! That cancerous empire at the corner of the world but we didn't do it alone, no, I remember reading the news of the new joint alliance between us and tumblr. Hell! Even Imgur joined in, our closest allies who was essentially our son and we won! It was a bloody fight but we did it, we drove them back and weakened them so much that they would never spread their cancer into this world again. 

And so the world got high. 

We got high on our own success, thinking we deserved to get high on all of this but because of what we did we only sewed the seeds for our destruction. 
It began when meme dumps, normally a great investment began to lose value, there weren't as many upvotes being given out. Perhaps people were just looking at other options, independent memes. I remember shrugging that day. I was still make a profit. A huge profit mind you, I had begun compiling 500 meme long dumps, that was all part of the problem. The inflation. Then the downvotes came, people complaining that there was not enoug OC. That they had seen it all 

I ignored them, there'd always be people wanting to look at the same old memes, at the same old reposts, always have always will, but I was wrong. Then one day in an act of desperation one company sold all their meme stocks proclaiming in this age they were worthless, you should have seen the panic as everyone tried to sell what they had. The market plummeted before our very eyes and then it crashed! Everyone had lost. 

Everything was gone. We had gone from rich to beggars in a day. My wifewell I don't think she wanted to become a beggar, that day I came home she was standing on the window sill, she looked me in the eye and smiled. 

That smile is etched permanently into my mind, her last words? "Dicks out for Harambe." She whispered those words so softly that I could scarcely hear them as she jumped. I ran to grab her but I wasn't fast enough! I wasn't fast enough! Sorry. I got emotional over this part, I need some ros. 

That's better, those weeks I laid in a depression, I considered jumping myself to but what good would that do? I remember coming to this same pizza place, sitting down and looking through the now empty meme market and saw a meme that made me chuckle. I can't remember what it was only that it made me smile. It gave me hope that perhaps OC could save us all but for now, we'll look outside. We're all beggars tonight. 

Oh! And before I go, if you're ever sad drink some ros and look at memes, they're much funnier that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this, it reminded me of Waiting for Godot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude. Dude. You're awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't mind having an Xbox...pls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would happen if China became the 51st state of the US? How would this affect, well, everything? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
