<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3065</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the opportunity to tour this facility when I was stationed in Alaska.  It's not too far outside of Fairbanks and there is a lot of aurora activity at that lattitude so that's why it's in Alaska.  Also the University of Alaska Fairbanks campus is fairly close.  There is a sweet spot in the lattitude range where too far north the activity tapers off and too far south same thing.  Anyway, the rockets don't go into orbit, they launch them in an arcing trajectory to fly through the aurora and take readings then they fall back to earth where they recover them down range to the north east if I remember correctly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much food so little time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The latest one I can remember is I straight up asked my daughter (15) if she was cutting herself again and she said no.  She is not a good liar and I knew she was doing it again.  She has anexiety issues and was using that as a coping mechanism.  We have been taking her to a counselor and it seems to be helping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The car wash guy...if they hustle and do a good job I'll give them a couple bucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't ever let them get away with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *click* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandparents didn't have time to play.  They grew up during the depression and had to work all the time, so it seems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aka addadicktome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  There are only a few websites that talk about this guy and they all seem to stem from this one that I found:  https://www.nationstates.net/nation=the_divine_empire_of_oranienburg/detail=factbook/id=247350


This site said he was awarded the Knight's Cross of the Iron Cross with Oak Leaves, Swords, and Diamonds.  This is not true.  There were only 27 awarded and the list can be found here:  https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Knight's_Cross_of_the_Iron_Cross_recipients

Also if you look at a listing of the top snipers of all time the highest number is 505 by Simo Hyh:  https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_snipers

Of course, wikipedia is not a peer reviewed historical reference but there is nothing else out there to substantiate NationStates.net claim.  The Nazi's were known for their grandiose use of propaganda and this may have been one of their tall tales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's obvious she isn't trying hard enough to find a job.  I bet she could work her way into managing her own shift at Mickey D's within the first 5 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having a bucket list </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Handicap license plates  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 05:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't stare at people.  Germans are terrible at this, it is normal in their culture to stare at people for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure how far you want to drive but there really isn't much around Wichita Falls.  I'm in Fort Worth and there really isn't that much good hiking here either.  If you feel like driving you can check out Guadalupe NP out by El Paso or Caprock Canyon state park over by Amarillo.  Also around Mena Arkansas is really nice and tons of trails. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived in Kaiserslautern Germany for 4 years and there are lots of old castle ruins and Celtic burial mounds along with Franco-Prussian war battlefields and bomb craters from WWII.  There is a very well marked and maintained network of hiking trails that go all over that whole area.  Here is a German website with some maps:  https://www.kaiserslautern.de/tourismus_freizeit_kultur/tourismus/gruen_und_aktiv/wandern/rundwanderwege/index.html.de </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 302 cu in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I was a little worried about his penchant to shoot his mouth off and say things that would get the US in trouble but there are checks and balances in place to moderate or even impeach him if he goes too far.  He is a smart guy but has a few personality flaws but nobody is perfect.  He makes for great entertainment also which has drawn so many people into politics such as myself who never gave two shits.  I have always felt my vote didn't count so why bother until this time.  I did my research to see where each candidate stood on topics that mattered to me and Trump more closely fit than Hillary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea he was making noise about the cost and supposedly they brought it down but we're going to anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so I have never voted before because I felt that my vote would not matter in the state of
Texas because they pretty much always voted republican in the past and that party is the one that I am more aligned with.  This election was different, the polls were very close and I could not sit and let the vote go to Hillary which in my opinion would mean an extension of what Obama was trying to do with health care.  I know a few people personally who could not afford the Obama care so they were left without coverage and had to pay the fine with their tax return.  I am hoping Trump will be able to do something for these people who slipped through the cracks.  I'm not worried about illegal aliens, they have been here all along and there really isn't much that can be done to stop them.  As far as improving the economy is concerned, in Texas the economy seems to be doing great, I have a job and I don't personally know of anyone looking for a job that really wants one.  I use LinkedIn and see jobs all over the place.  Bottom line, I had to stop Hillary from furthering Obamas policies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which part...voting for Trump or the F35? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take my chain off and clean it in a coffee can with some gasoline.  Let it air dry and lube it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last I heard it's ok to be gay...sounds like you may have yourself a lawsuit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Air superiority equals freedom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For real though, I was just outside Naval Air Station Fort Worth, home of the F35 and Lockheed Martin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I voted for the winner, Mr. Trump, and I am not from Russia...BTW I just saw an F-35 do a bad ass tail whip!  That's what freedom is all about right there ya'll.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to be stationed in Germany and you were allowed to collect nazi items but you could not display the swastica in any public setting, they would cover them up with price tags usually at flea markets and militaria sales.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 05:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traitorous tranny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 05:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A:  Dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smoking people on the downhill sections!  Uphill is another story though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome pic, I love this trail and hike it every time I go out to AZ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 08:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the directions on the ticket?  Call the police department and ask them what to do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 08:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude must have some kind of mental disorder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 07:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wanting something and it actually making it happen are two different things.  You say getting your GED is on your list of life achievements so get off your ass and get it done.  Nobody else is going to do it for you.  Imagine yourself 10 years from now, stuck in your same situation because you didn't feel like manning up and doing what was necessary.  Your life will still suck and if you ever have kids their life will suck too because their dad is a lazy turd that doesn't feel like doing jack shit.  The choice is yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 06:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Head straight to the alcohol and proceed to destroy my liver then setup a shooting range in the gun section. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cat...it lets you pet it if you want and when you're done it just leaves you alone.  Dogs constantly want attention and tear shit up...and stink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1,076 miles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 05:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are actually selling for $9,999.95 now:  http://m.ebay.com/itm/1985-Vintage-GI-Joe-USS-Flagg-Aircraft-Carrier-Keel-Haul-Playset-Complete-w-Box-/322408085767?hash=item4b1104f907%3Ag%3AAf8AAOSw-0xYaETn _trkparms=pageci%253A2b7b467d-f0d8-11e6-9d4b-74dbd1800691%257Cparentrq%253A307d21b915a0a2a474f1f144fff98d08%257Ciid%253A16 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had a psychology degree when you were 19? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes.  If it sounds like a military plane I'll look because most of the time I know what it is before I see it...I was in the Air Force for 20 years and worked the flight line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You named your cat dick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One upping your rich friends with huge parties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was funny when his hair caught on fire and everyone knew he molested little boys at his ranch and paid the families off.  Only girls and gay guys listened to him...and drank Pepsi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hookers and blow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does exist, but you are confined by the consequences of your actions.  Example:  I could punch you in the face BUT I would probably go to jail, therefore I don't punch people in the face ALTHOUGH if I were standing in front of you nothing could physically stop me from punching you in the face...and don't ever forget that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have in the past but don't anymore.  I was in the military and every year they had the combined federal campaign where the go getters would have to make 100% contact with everyone and try to get them to donate.  There was a book full of different charities to pick from and you could set up automatic withdrawal from your bank account which made it easy.  I'm no longer in the military and nobody comes around asking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 02:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started running again after 2 year break caused by a case of persistent plantar fasciitis...ran 1 hour on Monday and foot is doing fine!  AMA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 00:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After looking around I think it's a vise for leather working.  I'm gonna guess there are serious people out there that like to do things the old traditional way...maybe making saddles and other cowboy type stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 00:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was an auction...32 bids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 00:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was an auction so it did sell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 04:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wouldn't even make it through the Oort Cloud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't eat shit so looks good to me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been said for years but it's good to bring up every now and then if it helps to prevent trail closures.  Also don't be that guy out there tearing up the trails like you own the place (unless you literally own them). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes keep them.  Every time you use them you will think of your grandfather. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old guy is an old perv and young girl is getting paid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pay off your credit cards and never use them again.  Credit card debt sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure I'm not the only one with a junk drawer, you know where all your random stuff goes.  I would replace one of the paper clips laying in the bottom with the dinosaur...nobody would ever know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ride my bike </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you did there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 03:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to have access to oxygen bottles...crank one open and get some pure O2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 03:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a shitty dead end job out of high school and all my friends were losers going nowhere so I joined the Air Force.  They trained me how to be a mechanic and now I fix trains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 03:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at the top of all time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 03:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of places blast shitty music so you have to yell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 03:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was stationed in Germany for 4 years and recycling is mandatory for everyone.  They have different color bags to put stuff in and separate days for the trucks to run.  You had to take your glass to the recycle bin yourself and sort it by color...that was my favorite part, smashing all those jars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard of him but never read the book, I'll have to check that out, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm in Texas 1000 years ago and I'm a tall white guy which I would somehow use to my advantage.  I've watched a documentary on how they make samurai swords from iron ore so I would try to make iron.  I would need either coal or have to make charcoal to get the temps high enough to melt the ore.  Once I get a process down I could mass produce iron arrow heads and other medieval type weapons.  I would become a powerful warlord over time because I know how basic military tactics have evolved over time and I could fast track the Native Americans to become a formidable fighting force by the time the Europeans show up almost 500 years later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nigger nigger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nigger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I supported B-1's at Dyess AFB on the flightline...I can still hear them when it's quiet because hearing loss.  You could be INSIDE the Walmart 5 miles away and hear them doing engine runs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nigger? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 06:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I work for the railroad and I can see the benefit of having a union and paying union dues, for this job.  My wife works part time at Krogers grocery store and they have some kind of union that doesn't do jack shit besides take her money.  In those cases where the union is worthless I say they should be able to opt out for that reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 08:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean, I could whip my 20 year old ass right now if he were here...dad strength is real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your mother is a cum guzzling gutter slut and your little sister is a gonorrhea dripping whore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's funny!  I had a whopping 133 MHz processor and a smoking fast 14.4 Kbps download. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when the internet came out... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok I am wrong, there is a bill H.R. 621 that has been introduced and subsequentially referred to the House Comittee on Natural Resources.  It still needs to be passed by the House, Senate, and the President before becoming law.  https://www.congress.gov/bill/115th-congress/house-bill/621/all-info

But still, it is a shitty news article which links to other shitty news articles to back up its claims which leads me to cry "fake news".  Why can't they link directly to the source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stupid title...nobody is selling anything.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That's great you're able to get out and run!  I'm kinda in the same boat...I've had a persistent case of PF that has lasted years.  Finally gotten better now I'm running again but not as much as you, I'm easing back into it.  Good luck with your training plan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really only applies to the 1/4 mile oval tracks and inside tracks.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It keeps your gut from getting chaffed by your pants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 01:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm talking about! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yea you out alphaed that guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea you will piss off everybody else on the track </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next time point and laugh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I have read about it sugar makes your insulin levels spike which triggers your body to store fat when it otherwise wouldn't.  If you eat a 100 calorie slice of watermelon vs a 100 calorie slice of pizza the watermelon will cause a bigger insulin response compared to the same calorie pizza slice.  Now you can mitigate the insulin spike by eating a handful of peanuts or something else low on the index if you want to eat sugary foods.  The problem with saying there are better options out there now is what are they?  It's easy to say there something is wrong without providing an alternate way.  I'm not saying what I'm talking about is right just let's hear some alternatives to help this guy out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, he's a traitor and I hope they never let him come back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure about the sore leg thing, maybe try some other cardio equipment and see what happens.  For me I do a combination of things and none involve a treadmill.  I think treadmills beat you up too much but I'm old so I use the elliptical, spin bike and rowing machine along with some calisthenics.  Remember, the goal is to burn more calories than you consume and do some reading on eating food based on the glycemic index.  I'm no fitness expert so anyone feel free to throw in some ideas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to set a don't be lazy alarm...good idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 00:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have always just winged it.  I always take more water and food than I need just in case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 00:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still riding 26's and have a CST BFT on the front and a WTB velociraptor on the back and NEVER have traction problems bombing down the hills or going back up at Dinosaur Valley </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 06:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gives new meaning to still life photography </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 06:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pano-poo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 06:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biff was a dirty dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a young man from Nantucket
Whose dick was so long he could suck it.
    He said with a grin
    As he wiped off his chin,
"If my ear was a cunt I could fuck it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 04:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see pig people riding scooters at Walmart all the time...nothing new here folks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course you can volunteer but clear it through the front office first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link doesn't work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of the old adage...start no shit and there will be no shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in America, get this commie crap out of here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 26er here!  Been riding trails since '97 on 26 inches and I don't have any reason to change.  I'm sure when my current bike craps out I'll have no choice but until then I'm not gonna let the bike marketing folks make me run out and get a "better" bike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
