<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2482</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burning grass makes white smoke, not black smoke.  *shrug* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh.  I'll pay a couple extra bucks to have it in my Steam library...just because I know it'll always be there.  

If I got it from another place, I might forget I even have the game when I change computers, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't realistic at all.

No one plays Starcraft anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am definitely not a bot, just a fellow human, just like you!  Hooray for humans, of which I am.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FP] Lemon Cheesecake from I Breath I'm Hungry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Looks amaaaaazing](http://www.ibreatheimhungry.com/2017/04/easy-lemon-cheesecake-low-carb-keto.html)

I definitely have to make one of these next time I get a sweet tooth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Shameless plug at how slow light really is at a galactic scale, and how far away everything is.](https://aeon.co/videos/the-plodding-photon-or-how-the-speed-of-light-looks-sluggish-on-a-galactic-scale) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  When it's a red giant, all planets in our solar system will be destroyed. Nobody nowhere nohow will be around to wonder what the explosion will look like.

Just to be pedantic...Mars and the planets beyond will still be non-destroyed, they wouldn't be affected by the Red Giant stage of the Sun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much!  With some recipe guidance from OP, I modified it to make a larger "bun" for a hamburger.  Turns out I really didn't need to...I bet the original sized bun for the breakfast sandwich would have been the perfect size.  

In any case, [here's my first try at a Swiss Keto Burger.](http://imgur.com/a/O64eM)  Thanks /u/cheeseisthenewbread !

It tasted pretty great...and I can't wait to make it with sausage like a true breakfast sandwich, it would be perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't disagree with you.

However, I do think that the fact the only tax record we have is from that far back (making it pretty much useless and pointless to current affairs) is somewhat telling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's why Walmart is open 24 hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ranoik already hit on it.

A nuclear warhead is not like a conventional explosive.  It requires a long chain of complicated events to happen for the nuclear chain reaction to occur.  Any kind of outside interference (getting intercepted while in midair) will easily break the chain of events from occurring, rendering the missile relatively harmless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No proof you'd accept, unfortunately.  Just that the copy of the taxes is the client's copy....which doesn't really prove anything, since any number of tax lawyers that trump had on retainer would have had access to that copy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intercepting a nuclear missile isn't going to cause a nuclear detonation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhh, you're going to get a bonus this month, comrade!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course not.  No one has proof of anything.  Hence, why we are able to argue about this right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL.  No, no one took the worst looking one.  

The Trump camp took the BEST looking one and leaked it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump on Nero:  Fake news! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See...the difference is, you're able to find out the rate Obama and Bernie paid going WAY back, and in full.

Having a purposefully leaked one year return from many many years ago from Trump is hardly a disclosure worth comparing.

Even a bag full of rotten apples might have one good apple in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and destroy 2 countries like Obama did. 

Yeah...Trump is only working on destroying 1 country.  The U.S. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of a joke.

A highly distinguished Admiral in the Navy retired, and found a job in corporate America.  
He would always come in late, until finally his boss had enough of it, and pulled the retired Admiral aside.  In order to be nice about it, he said..

"Hey, Bob, remember when you were active duty and you'd arrive at the office late?  What would people say when you did that?"

"Well, they'd say 'Good Morning Admiral', of course." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I mean, who knew I could put my knees in my armpits?!

*Joey voice* Hey, girl, how you doing?!

lol, jk. ;)  Grats and very inspiring! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are we reading the same thing but interpreting it differently?  

He(or she) said "Keto is **a way to make it easier** to eat less calories"

He (or she) did **not** say Keto itself is low-calorie, like you are saying they did.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL: Walrus' eat a lot of sugar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/3ibal0e9 didn't say that Keto is low-calorie.  They simply were referring to how eating Keto acts to suppress a person's appetite, so that it is much easier to eat low-calorie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a Space Shuttle Tile in your pants or are you just happy to see me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If WWIII happens, then WWIV will be fought with sticks and rocks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. All inferences about sexual activity gleaned from the title lie only in the reader's sick, sick, twisted and perpetually in the gutter minds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol @ Kim.  Get rekt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 13:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They often kept prisoners isolated from each other, and they had a tap code so that they can keep in contact with each other even though they couldn't see each other. That's what this is referring to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 13:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is absolutely an SSN hanging out with those U.S. ships as cover.

If the Russian frigate does anything hostile, it'll find a Mk 48 torp in its centerline and crack in half like a toothpick before it even knows what happened to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's almost as if neither one even really exists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any good kidnapper worth their salt is going to cut off that trunk release and have you bound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, less than half of 1 percent of the country IS a niche. 

Also, the definition of niche serves it perfectly:
denoting or relating to products, services, or interests that appeal to a small, specialized section of the population.

Small section of population?
.46%. Check

Specialized section of population?
Just one state out of 50. Check.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1/50th of the States isn't niche?
Ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When will people learn, Christopher Reeves ain't around anymore! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To play Devil's Advocate....GoldenGonzo isn't wrong.  

He had one "hit".  I.E. a chart topping song.  Whether or not a niche group of people love his music is irrelevant to whether he's a one hit wonder or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy knows little bunny foo foo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely unrelated story.

I was a new guy at my job (very very large office building...thousands of employees)...and my boss says to me "Hey, let's go crash a pot-luck lunch down the hall."  I said ummm, ok.

So we go in, and my boss is glad-handing everyone...hey, how ya doing!  How are you! Hi!
I asked him, Wow, you know all these people?   He says no, not a one.  "But, if you pretend to know everyone, no one will admit that they have no clue who you are".

So, there we are with plates full of food that we didn't pay for, looking at the banner that said "Good Luck Tony!"
My boss says to a random passerby "Yeah, Tony sure did do some good work around here huh?  Wherever he goes after this is going to be lucky to have hired him on."

The passerby says "Ummm, Tony is a girl, and she's going through a dangerous medical procedure."

The look my boss gave me was priceless, very much an Abort! Abort! and we got out of there pretty quick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twist:  They only need data for one month, but no one ever makes it to two months, so they never have to pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...How does T_Donald subreddit spin this as being a good thing?  I'm curious. (without being curious enough to go there) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  gets shit done

You got one part right.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Recipes] 101 Casserole Recipes from i Breath I'm Hungry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Jackpot!!](http://www.ibreatheimhungry.com/2017/03/101-best-keto-casserole-recipes-low-carb.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL: Arwen's parents have bought a lot of birds when Arwen was out in order to spare their feelings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New horror movie...forced open from the INSIDE.  Dun dun DUNNNNN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the Simulated Universe theory is true, I hope that instead of just pulling the plug and us immediately ceasing to exist, they instead give a System Shutdown warning so we at least get a little bit of understanding before we go poof. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So, to my co-worker: Shut the FUCK up.

Great reaction to someone what seems to be concerned for your health.  /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barely.  I actually got pulled over about an hour away from my destination, for swerving and basically looking like a drunk driver.  The cop let me go and said I should get some rest.  *shrug*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once drove (car, not truck) from Maine, to California....it was a 63 hour drive, and I ended up taking a 5 hour nap sometime about 3/4 of the way through.  Other than that 5 hours, it was straight driving the entire time.  

Amazing the things we'll do for a sexy-time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not true at all.  She outsourced her business, and now she imports seashells from Hong Kong at 1/8th the price of collecting them herself.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best April Fools prank ever would be if the FBI announced its official findings tomorrow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People would flip out and not know what to believe! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It'd probably be worth it to seduce Adele

You could have stopped there and still earned my upvote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in the WH transcripts of some of his speeches and talks, he usually says bigly. Sometimes, Big League, but usually bigly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that.

Playing Devils Advocate here....but if the current legally sitting President (because they won't impeach) orders martial law to quell protestors, how is that an unlawful order?

You say no to a lawful order, you get to meet UC of MJ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screw that. I give no credits. The man goes out there day after day, and sells his soul and his integrity...lying outright, purposefully and willingly.

He knows that everything he is defending with lies, deceit, and misdirection is completely true. He has zero integrity. None. All for the "power" of being press secretary.

He is a jellyfish, for all the backbone that he has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just say "I don't do bread or sugar."  People seem to "get" that and never ask follow ups.  Most even agree that's a good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and at that point, our Russian controlled president declares martial law, imposes curfews, etc etc...all for our "safety"?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gtfo with your "authorized since Bush" crap.

Authorized?
What, did the National Committee of Walls have a special session and gave an "all-time pass to the U.S." to build a wall whenever we saved enough money in our piggy bank?

Go tell Dimitri that you failed your job today, and you need to take a nap before you start your next shift in order to make up some more bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My question is....

...what happens if Flynn sings like a bird, confirms everything that has been being alleged? What then?  What if the Republican held Congress is like.. oh well, we're not voting to impeach.  

Is there anything to be done at that point, or would we then just have an open Russian-Puppet country instead of the U.S.? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who said Below poverty line?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username doesn't check out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  After many trillions of years, after every last star has burned out and all has become darkness

Missing *quite* a few zeros there, my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out...supplements income in other ways </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
