<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3240</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't even imagine the insecurity issues you must have to be jealous of a 9 and 12 year old. I just don't get how she couldn't figure out it was probably genetic, considering all 3 of us looked like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need a drink </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some background on my family: Fast metabolisms and tallness are common genetic traits in my family. My mom and sister are both 6 feet tall (I'm 5'7") and all 3 of us are around 120 lbs. We are perfectly healthy and have no eating issues, our bodies just do not hold onto weight.

So anywho, my mom, sister (9), and I (12) were at a Kohl's trying on clothes in one of the dressing room stalls. We were laughing and being loud because my mom was trying on this really ugly shirt and a woman overheard us and asked if she could see what the fuss was about. As odd as this is, my mom opens the door to show her the shirt and the lady goes off about how sad it is that my mother is starving not only herself, but her two children. Calls us disgusting, diseased, etc. Even tells us she wouldn't let us into her classroom (meaning she's a teacher to young children). We were so shocked we couldn't even respond. My mom just closed the stall and the lady walked away. It was the first time I cursed in front of my mom and didn't get in trouble (I called her a bitch). 

Fucked with my self image a lot growing up, can't even imagine how my sister took it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, at least he hired a prostitute instead of trying to fuck his ACTUAL son... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell a black hole really is and what happens when you go in one. They're so mysterious and terrifying right now. I'd love for them to be solved (although probably even more terrifying) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only thing that's worked for me is ginger tablets. MythBusters actually did an episode on motion sickness "fixes" and found that the ginger tablets were the only thing that worked, too. Hell of a pill to swallow, but worth a shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friend of mine helped me make an account some time ago, but I couldn't get used to the layout and format of Reddit. Then after I left my Tumblr, I was craving a social media site that wasn't the usual Facebook/Twitter, and my boyfriend reintroduced me to Reddit. Funny enough, /AskReddit and /ama are what made me stay, I love reading and sharing stories with people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
