<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 15:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, Sanders didn't get a whole lot of policy coverage either in the mainstream media studied in this study. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 15:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the rocks (and the continents made of them) are older than the oceans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police chief: Investigation Shows No Excessive Force in Boylston Street Incident Between Off-Duty Boston Police Officer and Pedestrian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 13:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 13:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Submission statement**
A psychology professor dives into the motivations of the people who resort to violence for political causes.  It makes sense - they're both looking for meaning, and egged on by their social networks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why extremists use violence in their quest for personal significance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 13:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 13:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Based on radiometric dating of rocks, we know that no ocean is more than 200 million years old, though our continents are much older. The oceans opening and closing process  called the Wilson cycle  explains how the Earths surface evolves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the earth's current oceans are only 200 million years old, though the continents are far older </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 13:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 14:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A literary scholar uses insights from immigrant literature in Quebec:
A broad reading of these stories made me realize that developing relationships with friends and lovers contributed to the migrants sense of belonging. They helped him or her to forget their country of origin and forge a new beginning in the host society.

A close reading of the text led him to come up with actionable steps to help immigrants feel like they do belong.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want to prevent lone wolf terrorism? Promote a 'sense of belonging' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 13:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foreign Investors Are Causing Boston Real Estate Prices To Rise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 13:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 13:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Among those dead, the average age was 49, which is the same as Chad, the country with the lowest life expectancy in the world. The average American male has a life expectancy of about 76 years.

Or, as Billy Joel (still living) sang, "only the good die young" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL average age at death of Rolling Stone's top 100 greatest artists is 49, same as life expectancy in Chad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 13:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 13:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Memory researchers have, in fact, identified something called the reminiscence bump, which shows that our strongest memories come from things that happened to us between the ages of 10 and 30....

 Part of it is undoubtedly due to changes in the brains sensitivity to certain types of information during adolescence. Emotions signal the brain that important events are happening, and the teen years are chock full of important social feedback about ones skills, attractiveness, status and desirability as a mate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL our strongest memories are formed from ages 10-30 (the 'reminiscence bump'), in part because the strong emotions of those years cause memories to be deeply imprinted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 13:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 23:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peer-reviewed research in Annals of Internal Medicine: http://annals.org/article.aspx?articleid=2538663 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Low Risk for International Zika Virus Spread due to the 2016 Olympics in Brazil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 23:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 18:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's a complex article and you can't convey all the complexity in one line, but I believe I captured the essential element of the study. The cost savings in the article are savings to the U.S., not globally, so it really doesn't matter if it is a per capita cost or not.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 15:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Tragedy of the Commons](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tragedy_of_the_commons) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 13:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Duke University professor did the study. 
 In our study, we found that clean energy policies in the U.S. could prevent about 175,000 premature deaths by 2030, with about 22,000 fewer annually thereafter. Clean transportation could prevent about 120,000 premature deaths by 2030 and about 14,000 annually thereafter. Importantly, these benefits are realized almost immediately and largely within the U.S. We then put a dollar value on these benefits based on economic analyses that reveal how much society is willing to pay to decrease the risk of premature death, for example through occupational safety or health care. These near-term national health benefits have a monetary value of about US$250 billion per year between now and 2030. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
