<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Milk day! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or as you hipsters call it MLK day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MLK walks into a bar... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 06:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol jk he's dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 06:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Corby is my favorite comedian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a human experiment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 06:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Test #1

Removed a person's left arm, replaced it with a prosthetic arm  and asked them to walk straight. They walked straight without stumbling or leaning. Conclusion prosthetic can make a good replacement for the a missing left arm.

Test #2

Removed a person's right arm, and replaced it with a prosthetic arm, and asked them to walk straight. They walked straight without stumbling or leaning. Conclusion prosthetic can make a good replacement for the a missing right arm.

Test#3

Removed person's left leg, replaced it with a prosthetic, and asked them to walk straight. They walked straight, leaned to the left and fell over. Conclusion the prosthetic can replace the left leg, but will make the user drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Condoms are like rocket ships </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 21:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes they don't work, and explode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 20:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh I remember this joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I kinda feel bad when I play pokemon, I'm forcing small monsters to age rapidly faster so I can win a gym badge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 05:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I warned those kids about unprotected tickling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 08:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look who's laughing now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What lies on it's back, with 100 feet in the air? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 08:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A dead elephant with 100 feet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My uncle once said "if you put your mind to it anything is possible!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 04:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was confused and asked him what he meant

"You see my date over there?"

"Yeah, the pretty one?"

Pretty women don't usually go for men like me, but if you put your mind to it, you can save up the money for borrowing them for a night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 04:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ugh I hate it when my alphabet soup is too hot

*soup reads SEND NUDES* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 06:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> read the title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chuck Norris doesn't need to wear condoms when having sex with women. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 06:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every women wants to be impregnated by Chuck Norris. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Love is like a roller-coaster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll seem scary at first, it's happens fast, it has its ups, it has its downs, but what's most important is that you meet it's size restrictions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 23:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It varies, but it's either an amputee 30 year old woman, or just a 30 year old woman in a wheelchair. Either way your lady in a care home isn't original.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Rick Astley never existed A-ha would've taken his place as 80s viral. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 22:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 20:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saying the joke with an elderly lady just sounds gross, just stick with the original. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When 3 people have sex it's called a threesome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When 4 people have sex it's called a foursome

When 5 people have sex it's called a fivesome

When 6 people have sex it's called a sixsome

When 7 people have sex it's called a sevensome

When 8 people have sex it's called an eightsome

When 9 people have sex it's called a ninesome

When 10 people have sex it's called a tensome

When 11 people have sex it's called an elevensome

When 12 people have sex it's called a twelvesome

When 13 people have sex it's called a thirteensome

When 14 people have sex it's called a fourteensome

When 15 people have sex it's called a fifteensome

When 16 people have sex it's called a sixteensome

When 17 people have sex it's called a seventeensome

When 18 people have sex it's called an eighteensome

When 19 people have sex it's called a nineteensome

When 20 people have sex it's a fucking orgy alright, I'm done typing this shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm in love </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 07:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I might be rushing in, but I just need to find her. There's a hot single Asian woman located near me who wants to have sex with me, according to the ads on the side of this cool site I found which I can't link.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I agree when they say that love is like a roller-coaster, if only I was old enough to ride it though. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 05:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/antijokes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 06:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same. well played poster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Were video game life counters, based off of cats and their nine lives? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 03:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't always tell dad jokes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 02:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But when I do nobody laughs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unbelievable... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 03:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 364 days till Christmas and the people in my neighborhood already have their lights set up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japanese girls are the hardest to break up with. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially if you don't speak Japanese  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The seven dwarves from Snow White are players </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They keep singing about the "high ho[s]" they fucked in the hills.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 08:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm upvoting this in hopes something stupid makes it to the top of this subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 01:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's from snl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 08:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure amputees can still swim... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 01:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my new favorite physics joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A boy opens up his presents under the Christmas tree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 20:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With disappointment he exclaims, "Santa sucks he didn't get me the Xbox I wanted instead he got me a stupid sweater."

Father:"Now, now son, you should feel lucky to have that sweater. There are kids around the world who need that sweater more than they need than the Xbox I accidentally sent out." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did Shaniqua get for Christmas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 08:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> an arbortion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People say we'll never use Algebra in the real world after high school, but what if we want to be Algebra teachers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 04:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a pop song doesn't make it on the top charts, is it still a pop music genre? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 08:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why doesn't Santa have any kids? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 07:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he lost his sex drive years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oooo yellow snow! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 06:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guy 2: Dude don't lick that, you know what they say about yellow snow. That's disgusting.

Guy 1 starts puking.

Guy 2: What's wrong now?

Guy 1: WHY DIDN'T YOU STOP ME WHEN I ATE THE WHITE SNOW?!?!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 07:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should've just reposted the original, this is stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an old joke from Mad TV that I do know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 06:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww I remember this joke, brings back good memories. Good dark memories... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 06:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't even reposted correctly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey girl are you a physics equation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 05:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I fucking hate physics equations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if I told you that everything you knew was a lie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 05:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Including that question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
