<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3428</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [r/Gamingcirclejerk!](https://www.reddit.com/r/Gamingcirclejerk/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bravo Snyder, what a brave kino director. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 11:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't carry the cases with me I just like to have them(incase I want to trade or resell, and I just like knowing I have them). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 05:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this song? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am actually ordering online, and above where you can apply promo codes you can also put in the powerup rewards pro member card number. Just wondering if I can complete the order like this, even though my brother has pro and I am ordering on my own account? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'll probably try that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know if it would be possible to order them online, and if they came with generic cases take them to the store and exchange them for the real cases? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I use a family members powerup rewards pro account when I order something offline? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just asking because when I put in the number for his card on my account, it still showed the 10% discount. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking about ordering online, because it is free shipping on orders over $35, the coupon code CAG16 which saves 16%, powerup rewards saving another 10%, and the fact that half of the games I want aren't in my local store(the half that is are my local store come with the original cases, so if I buy online I might be get a sham case). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on where you look, Walmart, Best Buy, and Target offer really good sales from time to time.  Best Buy had Battlfront Ultimate Edition right after it came out for $20 on Black Friday, It was $30 on PC.  Some people may bring up shadier sites like G2A, but I have gotten insane deals at my local Pawn Shop(something you can't do on PC) and the clearance sales at Walmart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to figure out if some Vita games I want will come with the original case. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gamestop looks like they have some good prices on some Vita games, but I don't know what kind of cases they will come in.  Can I take them back if they have a generic case? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya I contacted support and some of the people said the digital version was cross buy and the other said it wasn't. I was asking them because the physicall wont let me get cross buy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know if the digital version of Playstation All Stars is Cross Buy still, because the physical one has apparantly expired. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you have the physicall or digital version beacause I can't seem to get the cross buy working on my physicall copy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here born in late 97 and I loved all of the movies when I was a kid, but Revenge of the Sith was my favorite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 11:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> where do you live in canada, I am in idaho which is pretty close
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the max size memory one can get from a micro sd on a OFW PSP 2000? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 21:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering becuase I have been looking to upgrade my 2gb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 19:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion, stick to overwatch and wait for Battlefront 2.  The game doesn't feel that great to play and it can feel like you aren't even on a team at some points of multiplayer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Suggestions) Pre-Owned games at Gamestop for PS4 and Xbox One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 18:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking into getting Ratchet and Clank new for $10 and then picking up the Order 1886 for $10 used, and I am trying to find 2 other pre owned games to get so I can get one of them for free.  Only looking for exclusives for PS4 and everything else on Xbox One.  I already have Killzone, Knack, Bloodborne, Uncharted 4, and Infamous Second Son.  Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 08:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering because allot of the holiday sales for new games make them less expensive than pre owned ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whatever happened to the 10% off the new price for pre-owned games? Does Gamestop still do it, but not advertise the lower price? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 08:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should I put like a thin peice of paper under it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not just use 4 pads.  Has this cause a problem for anyone, like disc scratching? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got a PS4 yesterday and I am only trying to buy exclusives, and there are basically none in this sale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 17:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love it, need to play it before I can play Dishonored 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] I think the three stands(two in front and one in back) cause the PS4 Slim to be unbalanced due to the hard drive in the top left side. Does anyone else have this issue and how do you deal with it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 17:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best buy gift card that came with ps4 is still processing, but the ps4 is already available for pickup. What should i do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 18:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can they complete the order quickly if I were to go to the store and just give me the gift card when I pick up the PS4, or do I have to wait until they both say ready for pickup? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PS4 for $210 with Visa Checkou, but it is not refundable if it is defective. Is it still worth it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 06:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 02:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Batman in the DCEU. We get it Batman is the greatest thing since sliced bread, but does he need to be the focus of the entire DCEU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 18:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might be because all of the podcasts I watch don't really talk about games like Gears of War or Halo, and won't shut up about uncharted 4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 18:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya I waited was waiting until I got a hard drive to get Halo 5 and now I can't find it for as cheap as it was before, so I am still waiting for it to drop again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do like Halo, but I have heard people were disappointed with the story and I have been waiting for the game to drop a bit in price as  it is already a year old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kinda regretting my Xbox One purchase and would like to know if the Xbox One has a game line up that can match the PS4. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just found this guy, and he is gold. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 10:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This video does a great job in showing why Spiderman 2 was so great. Great Satirical fun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 10:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 03:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me to thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 11:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 11:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 11:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Death battle: Truck vs. Fire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any way to fix scan lines when using component cables on a "Polaroid TLA-01901C tv"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 07:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When any of my consoles are plugged in to a "Polaroid TLA-01901C TV" using component cables it will create scan lines.  I have tried my Xbox original, PS2, and Wii, and their are no scan lines when using just the regular av cables or hdmi.  I have tried all of these consoles on other TVs and they work fine with no scan lines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
