<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject366</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone want to preview my campaign? Yeoman Gear - Yoga Gear for Men (and people who are not tiny) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 07:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 04:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm launching one next Tuesday.  It is all approved and I've been trying to contact relevant blogs and magazines via email and Facebook, but the response has been light.  

It's a project for Yoga mats and blocks for men.  It's called Yeoman Gear.  Our stuff is longer, wider, and thicker because men are too.  It's not expensive either.  Everyone we've talked to about it really likes the idea and I already have some friends and family lined up to pledge.  

Rather than launch it right away, I decided to take a week and use the preview mode for better PR.  I've been emailing around to yoga groups, journals, yoga teachers, etc. and after 50 or so personal messages sent, I've only heard back from 2 people.  That is my struggle.  How about you?  

By the way, the preview is here: https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/CalmTom/82726509?token=044685f1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 03:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with everything this person has said.  I came here to write almost exactly the same thing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 03:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand a which level you receive an actual physical copy of the game.  All of them seem to list "print and play" but isn't there a physical card game where you get a big stack of cards?  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 05:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neat Idea.  I pledged.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 05:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Websites that aren't tech related might still want to write a piece about crowdfunding.  If you are doing a project related to sewing, try writing to sewing outlets to see if they want to bite, but make the story about sewing and crowdfunding... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 05:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like you met your goal.  Congrats!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 05:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pledged.  Never discount the value of humor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 05:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done four Kickstarters now and those emails are relentless.  

If you want some form of inexpensive Kickstarter Marketing, go to Fiverr and spend $5 on some useless stuff.  It might be a scam, but its the same quality as the folks that are emailing you and it is only $5.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 05:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would suggest only allowing a maximum of 2 rewards that are not the actual item in the Kickstarter.  I'm tired of scrolling downward, past the $1 Hello, the $5 What's up, $10 bumper sticker, the $25 t-shirt, the $49 we say thanks on our website, to the $1,799 kayak.  Limit people to 2 of these things.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 05:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ummm.  isn't this what Kiva.org has been doing for over a decade?  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 05:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't hoverboards catch fire because the battery gets too hot during charging?  Wouldn't the insulating properties of this bag prevent the batteries from cooling off during charging?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 06:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are happy to see your entrance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Ballistics Engineer answers the question - Can you play Nerf in the house or will break a bunch of stuff? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 20:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 02:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like you have time to spare, so why send resume after resume to the HR departments of businesses in your area.  Many, many companies don't fill every position with a job posting or at a career fair, they simply can't afford to spend the time.  If they get a good resume in, they may hire you.  If you send out enough of them, you will probably strike.  What else do you have to lose?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 01:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't answer for everyone, but we are quite wealthy and we have a regular checking account and keep enough to handle just about any expense that would happen quickly.  So, maybe $10,000.  If it gets more than that, we send it over to a money market account.  My wife has a checkbook for the money-market account, so we can get money out of that quickly if we needed to.  I think that as you get wealthier you learn to keep most of the money in places that earn you money back.  The more locked up it is, the more you want in return.  So we have different levels.  Daily checking earns the least, so it doesn't hold much.  Good question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 05:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm mildly famous for pumpkin carving.  A while back I created a website about it http://www.ExtremePumpkins.com and invented some jack o lantern designs that are popular.  The most famous is that I invented the puking pumpkin.  This lead to a book deal and my book(s) ended up being best sellers.  I've been on a bunch of national talk shows, some twice.  It is really fun to be a celebrity for 7 days a year.  Each year I get invited to something really cool and just as soon as my ego starts to get big, November 1st hits and no one wants me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 05:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are free on Wednesday nights, join the Detroit Mower Gang.  We clean up abandoned playgrounds and have fun doing so.  http://www.MowerGang.com or http://www.Facebook.com/mowergang </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 05:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I carry an idea book everywhere as well.  Mine isn't small, but I'm kind of a spazz when it comes to ideas.  They start flowing and I start scribbling all over the page.  I love the books though.  I've been doing this for 16 years now and have about 30 of them.  I look them over from time to time, the best ideas have drawings, so they are easier to find when I look back.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simple Graphic That Explains What Type of Business You Should Start </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 23:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 23:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations!  We made our first sale a couple of years ago, but yesterday we made our first sale that was so large it had to be shipped on a pallet, so I'll celebrate with you!!!  

Here's to motherfuckers like us who are brave enough to sell our stuff!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 05:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend, I too found out that my girlfriend liked Anchovy pizza and married her.  That was 16 years ago.  The only person happier about this turn of events than I was, is my Dad.  Apparently having three anchovy pizza loving people in the house makes it perfectly acceptable to order anchovies on one pizza whenever pizza is ordered. Every time we do this I can see a little twinkle in my Dad's eyes. I think he waited 40 years for this to happen.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 02:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen this as well. I remember learning that, although most people know of the Dodo, that most records and skeletons of it are lost to time.  It's quite large!  It's an impressive thing to see in a fantastic museum.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
