<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject163</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't care to go to his party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eating healthy is overrated when you're poor. But when you make enough money to eat healthy you realize it's kind of expensive to eat healthy and you do it anyway because you can </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She wakes up frightened and goes for her jog. The mobster creepily follows her to the park where she can be seen stretching on a park bench while the sun starts to rise. The mobster rapes her and murders her and throws her in the woods next to the trail. Howard Beach hasn't seen such a grotesque murder scene in years, and now it was on the morning news.

"Turn this up"- says Mr Romano to his wife

"We are coming in live where the body of Alexandra Romano was found this morning"

"Mission accomplished". Murmured Mr. Romano. Now all his gambling debts have been paid off at the price of his daughters life.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 01:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah this was in NYC where we mind our own business for our own good...or at least that's how we  were raised. I've grown since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 23:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was once riding the subway and I saw 2 guys around this one girl talking to her and she looked really uncomfortable with some bruising on her legs and arms. I knew something wasn't right. I wish I could've found a way to say something then. It's disgusting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If there is a ban on muslims they can just pretend to be Christians, you know, kinda like how republicans do. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 07:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That I give everyone "happy endings" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dogs of Reddit, what is the best part of your day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 07:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was John Lennon purposely assassinated because he wrote the song "all we need is love" and that is actually really all we need? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 18:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 08:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right but then you actually have to make the sandwich as opposed to having it made for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 08:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10 years later this boy went on to produce the world's first porno to broadcast on TV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever happened to dodgeball? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Safe to say Timehop might be anti trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 06:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And giant nuggets of cannabis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 04:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess is that whatever time traveler is traveling they are trying to let us know that planet of the apes might just be real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 05:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what fake news looked like before the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does smoking weed effect fasting before a blood test? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 17:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, bees are officially an endangered species. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 07:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take my money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 07:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my wife is a mother of 2 boys...so she will go through menopause when the first one gets his first girlfriend so in 10 years? 46? Sounds about right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have been driving everyday with an expired registration from august 2016. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 19:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enrique Sanchez for best Facebook comment on a live video in 2017. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 09:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 08:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember the Wii being a hot item even 1 year after its release. And by hot I mean I sold 2 on eBay for $100 over the normal price at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 07:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about true or false? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
