<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1417</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9/11: The Falling Man (2006) - "This documentary examines the story behind one of the most unforgettable images from 9/11, a photograph of a man falling from one of the towers." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 11:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those backing dancers aren't even trying! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to have more context to this. I get the hellraiser reference and assuming it's a party trick the guy in the hat is performing but what the actual fuck?

Also this really makes me want to start watching this show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 18:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the only DVD I've bought in the last few years. Sometime I put on the concert as a background thing and I always end up stopping what I'm doing and watching it all. Such a great show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These kids know more about parenting than most the adults I know. (Especially the one in the Tupac t-shirt) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 17:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every episode of Fifth Gear: Series 1 back to back. 4 hours of retro car action. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 18:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 13:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way they laugh off the bit when he said he'd kill the journalist if he got the order is so surreal. It's all so sad, he looks like a rabbit in the head lights.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British journalist meets a teenage Suicide Bomber in Afghanistan. It's shocking how young the kid is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 12:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comedian Johnny Vegas messes with host and tries to make them laugh during promo recording on The Last Leg. He nails it! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 22:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The baby looked at you!" is mine and my friend's favourite Simpsons quote, it's such a ludicrous reaction to Ralf's story; it just cracks me up every time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British comedian Alistair Barrie takes apart a drunk heckler at late show at the Edinburgh Festival. (Starts around 2 minute mark) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 11:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 01:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This! I fucking loved that video. I'm a stand up comedian and I even have a joke about this porno. You can see it at 30:18 of this video - https://youtu.be/Zfgts4KxR1k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Payara - one scary looking mother fucker! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 16:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 15:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the bit about kids being on the tube was hilarious but then again I suppose comedy is subjective. Each to their own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 15:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you watch it all the way through?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American comedian makes a hilarious video about The Sun's story 'Man Snorts Coke on the Northern Line'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 15:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 21:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is from the official youtube channel so it's a pretty good standard. Also that shit at the end of the OP video was annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here the longer version of the clip](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YArJcth7ywc feature=iv src_vid=RBzaf0bjxd8 annotation_id=annotation_1390163993) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U Wot M8? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 09:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say what you will about Michael McIntyre, that is a perfectly formed joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think this video should be compulsory viewing before anyone is allowed to create a YouTube account. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 18:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 18:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Mum's reasoning for forcing her young daughter to be a Model. Yeah this definitely won't fuck up the child for life... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 17:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 16:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, like [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V5HLCnZGqTU)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Derren Brown debunking 'Christian Faith Healing' with fake service. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 12:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 11:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly I found out after watching this that Hayley passed away 2nd April 2015. She seemed like such an upbeat person. Really sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hayley, The World's Oldest Teenager (2011) - "Hayley Okines suffers from the rare genetic condition Progeria, which causes her to age eight times faster than usual. She enters her thirteenth year full of hope that she can avoid the fate of so many of the friends she has lost to the disease." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 11:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 16:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Episode 2 - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-eGC49yOZno </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How To Avoid Getting A Parking Ticket - Trigger Happy TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 17:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of these were pretty dark. Hilarious but dark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dog using a toilet, she even flushes afterwards. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 13:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 18:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can also confirm this.

Source: I am Samuel L. Jackson and I also fucked both of those male cheerleaders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That does have a certain ring to it. I'm fascinated and creeped out by these people. There's a whole documentary about them and it's compelling watching.


EDIT: Here's the documentary - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ukok0oeIFoQ feature=youtu.be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Davecat And His Sex Doll Shi-chan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 12:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facejacker. It was a hidden camera/character show in the UK. It had some classic moments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just take the pickles! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 19:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of gaming. Of course watching old footage of old games you can see that graphics have developed massively in the last 20 years but to watch people describe it as beautiful with the same passion we see people talk about games today is a nice view into the past. I actually remember playing Screamer Rally on my neighbours PC (mine wasn't powerful enough to run it) and just being amazed but it's easy to forget this when looking at old footage. I just enjoyed the contrast in graphics between then and now but the excitement being the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason the link starts 20 seconds before the review. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two seemingly stoned game reviewers give their verdict on 1997's Screamer Rally on old UK gaming show 'Gamesmaster'. It's amazing to see how far we've come. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 12:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was my 13th birthday present and I still love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 11:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just posted this to r/videos and it made me aware of this post. I never knew this subreddit existed. Amazing! 

I love this show so much, I can remember crying with laugher the first time I saw it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the funniest hidden camera shows ever made, Trigger Happy TV - Series 1 Episode 1 (Full Episode). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 11:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trigger Happy TV - Great pranks with none of the dick-ish 'It's just a prank bro!' behaviour you see on YouTube. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 15:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 20:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a wonderful sentiment to end on after such tragic facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 11:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realise that isn't me in the video right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dispatches: Meeting The Taliban (2007) - "A British journalist witnesses the battle for the town of Garmser in the Helmand province of Afghanistan from not only the side of the British Army but also from Taliban forces they were fighting." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 20:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 17:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah look at that comedian promoting their trade by making people laugh. The audacity of it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 14:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The flip chart is just amazing, the animations and timing is all on point. So impressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comedian translates "Non Je Ne Regrette Rien" (Edith Piaf) with hilarious flip chart. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 14:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This always goes through my mind when someone says something stupid to me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 13:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 21:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) post content reddit likes 

2) get up-votes

3) annoy DOL8

4) profit 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 22:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must own it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Friday so to celebrate here's a Simpsons moment that never fails to make me laugh. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Williams F1 vs BMW M5 - Fifth Gear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 12:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, maybe my knee jerk reaction is a bit much, I agree that her rights to have kids shouldn't be rescinded (I know that's not a thing) but it just doesn't seem healthy to me. Creating an obsession with body image and forcing it on your child at any age is wrong, let alone when they can even walk. Allow your children to be children, being an adult is hard and it sucks worrying about how others perceive you on looks alone, so why force that onto a kid? Especially one so young. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 12:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda feel like that baby could do with less bows... and a completely different mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Goliath Tigerfish is the most terrifying thing I have ever seen. Fuck that! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 11:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 16:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After seeing [this](http://www.reddit.com/r/WTF/comments/35rvch/this_should_not_be_a_thing_nsfl/) earlier on WTF today, nothing is going to shock me again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 15:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Plastic' surgeon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 14:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's so Taylorswiftfan69! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Real Doll' Maintenance - Guy repairs the vagina of a sex doll that has been pounded into oblivion. (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 14:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 12:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... it's not the greatest song but I admire their commitment to it. I have a feeling this is the kind of thing that will get stuck in my head in a months time and I won't know why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 16:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, compelling viewing but ultimately really sad. It gave me a mix of being creeped out and empathetic, which is an odd feeling. 

I also really felt for 'Davecat's' Dad, knowing when you go out to work your grown son is at home shagging a doll... tragic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Love Me, Love My Doll (2007) - "This extraordinary film meets a group of lonely guys who have fallen in love with their customised, life-sized dolls." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 12:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 15:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His nuts are the real River Monsters! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 12:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'd be a grim way to win a Darwin award. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swimming With Red Belly Piranhas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 12:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 00:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks hilarious, can't wait to see the whole thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 19:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Made my weekend](http://replygif.net/i/1187.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A drone flies round an abandoned UK theme park, both creepy and fascinating. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 17:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 16:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one in my group of friends has got fat for this exact reason. Every now and then one of us starts to put on the pounds and the others will mercilessly rip on him until they lose the weight. I was once that guy, I was resting on the beach and they threw water over me and screamed they needed to get the whale back in the sea before it died. Sounds cruel but it was pretty funny and I'm grateful they did as I started running again and watched what I ate until they couldn't take the piss. We're all really close so it never feels mean-hearted and it honestly works. One obese guy joined the group and he's already run a marathon and is now one of the healthiest of us.

Not for everyone I know but it works for us. Except Gareth... Gareth is still a bit fat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 16:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was always gutted that this diorama wasn't the actual final level. When I saw the advert as a teenager I thought it was how the game would go down, a battle with hundreds of characters going at it. Humans v Covenant in one final free-for-all but I suppose the 360 wouldn't have been able to support a battle of that scale.

Shame, as I ended up feeling shortchanged even though 3 was still a solid game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 11:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got this and played it solid for 3 days. Almost every hour for 3 days but then I stopped and thought "Am I actually enjoying this?" and when I realised the answer was no I never played it again. I hated how I would work really hard to upgrade my character but then the enemies upgraded at the same level so there was no sense of accomplishment, it was all just too repetitive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 19:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just remember heath ledger being cast as joker. People went crazy and to be fair I was one of them, I thought it as going to be terrible and I was so wrong. Since then i've always given castings the benefit of the doubt. You never know when an actor is going to blow it out the water.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terry Tibbs - Paddling Pool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 12:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 00:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not you naan bread!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 18:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What you doing mate, I'll iron ya out! Get out of it!" Without a doubt he's on the district line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could You Paint Using Your Eye? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 10:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 18:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just out of curiosity where does link rank in all of this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
