<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3750</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Turn off the water when you are brushing your teeth for two reasons.For one you will save money on water, and the other you will do a much thorough job, when you are not subconsciously rushing it in order to save water. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 15:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also known as "The long dongo from Congo"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its like the Barca game sucked out all the fun and goals from this game, and used them on Nou Camp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very appreciated. I have learned my mistake and promise not to hit him, he definitely does not deserve that. Sending him out is the last resort and I fight strongly against it. I just struggle, cause he is so goddamn stubborn, cause he is a Beagle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in the Balkans. No such thing as and experience trainer or rescue groups. Our animal shelter is a death row, and I dont want to give it to my grandpa cause I dont want him sleeping outside.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you are on the spot. Training methods we dont really have, besides no and sit, and he was just put on us and we couldnt refuse. Grandfather is very old and unable to do it, and could you refer me to some articles or how to find out if i can stop this behaviour and rediscipline him, if its not too late, he is 9 months old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 12:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wimbledon 2016?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i got that but just the Raps ML pays that much on bet365. All of them combined are 2.95 or something like that which means on every 100 you get 295 dollars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems an incredibly low payout. On bet that would be about a profit of 190 with a hundred. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 20:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had J10, 3BB bet, two guys call. Flop QJJ checks all around, turn a 9, bet 5BB, one guy folds the other one shoves half my chipstack, whats the proper course of action? He had K10 in the end, and i lost all my money, but just couldnt resist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You keep the cigarette in your mouth duh!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For 300k? I would fuckin die.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we take that Robin Lopez of your hands in exchange for Terry Rozier?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fuck you gonna do with 67 point guards?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Celta hit the bar and missed a sitter in the last 15 minutes, if they got a goal I'd have hit a 150/1 parlay, netting about three hundred </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had pocket kings, he had Q6, I flopped a full house check-raised all in, the fourth six came on the turn, figured I should probably stop playing for tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really really like him but I dont know why. I like his tenacity and feel like he could evolve to a decent bench point guard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smart, Rozier, and Fultz if we get him is the future core. Want Bradley for like 15 million a year but I am not a fan of paying 30 year old IT 25 million a year or perhaps even more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The old bamboozle,Im on to you Brad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good draft coverage TV show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most definitely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you refer to Michael Jordan using Brian Scalabrines nickname?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too much, I would hate to give up Smart, however Bradley can go instead, and as a prize they wont have to deal with Zeller </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If im not mistaken he scored 50 not 51 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was the clearest penalty I have seen in a while, clear as the day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that does happen when your best assets arent Troy Daniels and Z-Bos headband.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trade him a photo Vlade Divac and a donut for a years ammount of rent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I figured, but I didnt get the comparison, so I decided to be stupid in one way instead of another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didnt say it would be worse, unless something is going over my head, but I think that the fast flowing offence of the Warriors would benefit him much more than he iso-heavy offense lead by Westbrook and to a lesser extent Harden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah fuck off. It was a bussiness decision, what if you leave you have to sign with the Suns or your rings arent any good. There is a limited number of teams able to compete, like 4 probably, with him that number rises to like 7 when you add the Clips, Raps, and us. A million things goes in a decision, coaches, staff, city, crowd, moving etc. Its not like he joined the Third Reich with Hitler at the point and Mein Kampf as the playbook, he simply went to a team where it would be easiest to win a ring, since he has been struggling his whole life, as you hear in his MVP speech. With all that being said, fuck him for not signing with us, other than that, a perfectly okay decision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didnt we sell Zukanovic aswell or loaned him atleast? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F R A U D I O L A 
R 
A
U
D
I
O
L
A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, this was unexpected... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely timing and hustle. Im a 6 ft guy, have a pretty big leap, but catch by far the most offensive rebounds when I play, and I am usually the shortest guy on the court. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I probably speak for all Boston fans when I say that Tony Allen died when his dumbass went for a dunk after the whistle and left his knee on the court.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 13:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually he does, today is an exception because of all these injuries, but his goals come outside the box mostly, as a CM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 13:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A national team game, Montenegro vs England. My first game in the stands in my life, we were in second place and losing 2-0 at home. Scored 1 at the end of the half, and then news broke in that Wales were winning against Switzerland so we only needed a point to get through to the playoff in the qualifiers. Spent the whole time attacking and then scored in stoppage time to make it 2-2.[Probably the greatest game in the history of our national team.](https://youtu.be/KVrDWZs3PtA)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, so they switched baccarat with poker in the movie? Huh, I mean its a commercially good idea just thought that it was original. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not an avid book reader but want to read a book that has a gambling premise, simmilar to "The Gambler" but prefferably involving poker instead of roulette. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, understood, thank you for your response. I've been reading this sub for like 2 weeks, trying to catch up with the lingo and strategies, and in that period I made around 50 euros which for an 18 year old in a country where a salary is 300 euros is not bad, but sadly threw most of it away on sports betting. Hopefully when I start understanding more, I'll switch over to only poker and lose money there like the rest of this sub. 
/s or is it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it has been pointed out to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
