<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3535</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. Are there any updates on it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. I did not know that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What historical events would you like to see as miniseries? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently watched Band of Brothers and the Pacific on DVD (god, I forgot how good they both were) and I wanted to pose this question to you guys. What historical events, which don't have to be military, would you like to see get their own miniseries? for me, I'd like to see: 

1. A miniseries on either The Untouchables or the Gangster Squad: Both movies did a bit of a disservice to both the books and the events they were based on (Gangster Squad more so than The Untouchables). I would like to see a miniseries on either one of these stories in the vain of something like Boardwalk Empire and that is more authentic to what really happened. 

2. The Harlem Hellfighters: I've come to grow fond of this story due to my own personal research and the graphic novel written by Max Brooks. In my opinion, a miniseries on the Harlem Hellfighters could be just as impactful as Band Of Brothers or The Pacific. Last I heard, Will Smith was optioning it to become a move, but I think this kind of story is suited to long term storytelling more than a 2 and a half hour movie. 

3. The expedition of Lewis and Clark: I'm surprised this hasn't become a miniseries already. 

4. Queen Anne's War

5. The OSS in WWII



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just now realized that. Is that a good or a bad thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, fair point. I could also see the writer running into the problem of having a team thats more powerful than anyone or team in the current DC universe. I still think it could work if, like the F4, the Superfamily would deal with large scale threats only. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fair. I just feel like we haven't really had a proper "Super" family in a while, and that DC has an opportunity to fill the void left by the F4 by giving fans a bright, optimistic, family centric book, and Superman is in the perfect spot to fill it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What I'm hoping for with the Superman books </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion the rebirth Superman titles have been some of the best books I've read out of both Marvel and DC in a long time. One thing I'm thinking/hoping will happen is that eventually Lois gets powers of her own and rest of the family, along with either Supergirl or a returning Kon-El Superboy, become a Fantastic 4 esque team where they go on missions as a family.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was from Birthright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IJW: The Untouchables (1987) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had heard about the movie for years from friends and family who had seen it, and those who told me that I, a major history buff, would like the accuracy of it. 

Holy cow, that movie was corny.

 The thing that first got me was soundtrack. The theme that plays during the opening credits sounds like the theme of an old horror movie, and the rest was nothing but excessively upbeat scores, which, to me, didn't fit in a movie about the group of cops that brought down Al Capone.  

Secondly, the performances felt very cartoonish, especially Robert Di Nero's Al Capone and Sean Connery. 

Third, as a Native Chicagoan, I was kind of disappointed the film didn't show more of the city. 

I realize that I'm criticizing a movie that's 30 or more years old, but having not seen it before, I was surprised at how different it was from what I thought it would be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the creepiest non horror movie theme you've heard? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sophomore about to go into junior year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for advice from guys seeking/who have O billets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently in college and planning on pursuing an O billet after school, and I'm looking for advice on how to make a standout package from guys who are also pursuing/who already have O billets. 
And if there are threads where this topic's already been discussed, please leave the links to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Bioware knows how much fans wanted the twin to play a part in the game, and we'll have them as a squadmate in the Andromeda sequel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, that doesn't make sense. Still, it would have been cool if we weren't outrunning a purification field in every vault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Number 2 would have been cool. I like the idea that instead of a purification field, the Remnant left what were essentially 'guard dogs' to prevent intruders from activating the vaults. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you guys did, please leave the link to the original post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With Alec, I thought he was going to transfer his consciousness into SAM, and Ryder was going to be going around with his dad giving him advice like Jor-El from Superman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone thought to do this with their PT shirts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ME:A spoilers] What were some of your theories about the game that turned out to be true/not true/somewhere in between? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of a unrelated response, but I'm interested in going down the O route. Can I pm you and ask you a few questions about how to get an Officer billet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is an awesome idea, and you're absolutely right when you say that diplomacy is a major part of the Pathfinders job, and so being able to talk you're enemies down or into submission would be cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to see a combination of the systems from Dragon Age and XCOM 2, where you can place your squadmates in different positions in order to flank enemies, create ambushes, or pull overwatch or suppressive fire, especially with guys like Jaal and Vetra.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. I know Knights Of the Old Republic 2 and Dragon Age: Origins  had something similar to that, with the exception of the unlocakable perks. I think that would be a great system to have, especially with the new dialogue system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i've never played any of the Persona games. Can you describe it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] What elements/mechanics from other games would you like to see in the ME series? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, I would like to see: 

1. The wildlife system from Red Dead: Redemption: One thing that kept players going back to RDR after they completed the campaign was that there were other things to do, in particular the wildlife. I would love it if Bioware could create a similar system where we encounter wildlife that is unique to the planet its on, track them, and study them.  

2. The Gunsmith system from Ghost Recon: The gunsmith system was on of my favorite things about the recent Ghost Recon games. Not only were we able to see our weapons completely disassembled, but we were able to modify the smallest details. I think Bioware should develop a system similar to this where we can take our weapons apart, and be able to modify them, and see them come together.  

3. The loot system from the Borderlands series 

4. The alien designs from XCOM 2: XCOM 2 has some of the most unique designs for aliens I've seen in a long time. Whenever, I encounter, My immediate response is a combination of "whoa, that's cool" and "what the hell is that?" This is the type reaction I want when encounter the different species of the remainder of the Heleus cluster in next Andromeda.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you have to finish the story. If you've completed the story with this character previously, then you can start NG+ with that file and look up the slides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would suggest selecting NG+ and when you get to the CC you should be able to see the slides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, the two biggest things I want are: 

1. Better shaders for skin tone

2. Options for curly hair. As someone with curly hair, the options for me have been either nonexistent or I've had to find hair that barely looks curly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you post the slides? I want to see If I can get something like this on my next playthrough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. It was mentioned in the livestream that you'll go between the 1st ID, the British Special Operations Executive, and the French Resistance.

Proof: http://www.gameinformer.com/b/features/archive/2017/04/26/everything-we-know-about-call-of-duty-wwii.aspx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The big thing i noticed was that there was no blaring pop song. No Rolling Stones or Eminem. Instead, we got a dark, orchestral score. That tells me that we're getting something dark, atmospheric, and serious. And I couldn't be happier.

Also, is anyone else planning on re-watching their WWII movies and miniseries after watching this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think the 'going back to its roots' concept is going to spread to all three studios, so I think there's a good chance IW develops a Modern day set COD, which I'm hoping for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ME:A spoilers] Weapons in Andromeda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a lot of ways, Bioware made a ton of improvements in regards to weapons and armor in Andromeda. I especially love the small details they made with the sound effects and reload animations for weapons and the overall designs for the armor. However, after completing several playthroughs, I've noticed several things I think that can be improved upon in future Andromeda titles: 

1. Better modification: I think Andromeda had a much better weapon mod system compared to those in the OT. However, I felt that it wasn't as in depth as it could have been, especially when it comes to the selection of mods to choose from, as a majority of them look the same and provide the same kind of bonuses in terms of stats. In an Andromeda sequel, I would like to see a wider variety of scopes, barrels, receivers, and underbarrels from  different factions and with their own visual style(What would an anagran scope look like on a Milky Way weapon for example) I would also like to see things like bayonets from ME3 make a return. Additionally I would like to see Andromeda adopt a system similar to the Gunsmith System from the Ghost Recon games where you can see the mods going on and off your weapon. 

2. Melee weapon variety/executions: In regards to the melee weapons in Andromeda, I like that we weren't stuck the Omni-blade and had the option to Asari swords Krogan hammers, but I would have like to used Agaran daggers or Turian combat knives or different omni weapons. I would have also liked to have seen execution animations like what Gears of War 4 had with the combat knife. 

3. Weapon visuals: I think everyone was hoping to be able to customize the look of their weapon. Can you imagine an Assault Rifle in the color of the Initiative or a shotgun with Angaran markings engraved on it? 

4. I really liked the inclusion of heavy weapons in ME2, and I hope they come back. Who wouldn't want to wield an Angaran or Kett grenade launcher or a minigun fashioned from Rem-tech.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. Do you know if knowledge of another language is useful for SEALs. I know the mission set of the SEALs isn't the same as Army SF, where knowledge of a foreign language is a requirement, but do SEALs ever have a use for it during ops? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does how many languages a candidate speaks factor into getting selected as an O? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently I'm learning both Korean and Japanese on my own time, and and planning on learning one more next year. Does the selection board for SOAS take how many languages a candidate speaks into consideration during the selection process? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your first point is really good. You're right, It is compelling to have a character forge their own path and legacy, and Alec is a lot like Shepard, but I would say there are more than a couple of differences. The primary one being age. Alec's been through the Charon relay, fought in the first contact war, was dismissed from the Alliance and "lost" his wife. Going through these things would probably give Alec a perspective that's completely different from Shepard, and one that would color his experience with the Angarans, the Kett, and settling Andromeda. 

If anything, I would like to see some form of DLC where Ryder, using SAM is able to relive things like Going through the relay, fighting in the First Contact War, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm expecting Canadian Batman to swoop down and grab the guy on his phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Ryders being immortal would be a bit too far. It would take the tension and stakes out the story faster than air out of a punctured ballon. 

I think since we haven't seen a body, Alec is probably alive and working with the Benefactor and their faction behind the scenes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ME:A Spoilers] Regarding Alec Ryder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that most of us here agree that Alec Ryder is a badass character. After finishing the Ryder Family Secrets quest line, I thought it would have been more impactful if you could have [Spoiler] (Confronted Alec when you found out your mother was kept in cryo and watched Alec justify his reasons for keeping it from you and your twin) Also, Clancy Brown is an amazing voice actor and killing his character off an hour into the game would be a waste. This could have also been justified story wise by having Ryder being mortally wounded and unable to continue being Pathfinder, and thus, has to transfer SAM to you. 

Additionally, would you guys have liked to play as Alec Ryder? Playing a older, rugged protagonist who's seen some stuff would be col in terms of dialogue, character interaction, etc.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ME:A Spoilers] Should Alec Ryder have been kept alive/would you like to have played as Alec in Andromeda? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd be more interesting than the 'blah blah exaltation, blah blah you will be great stuff he spouts' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 1st and 2nd versions of the Pathfinder chest piece.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ME:A Spoilers] A quick thought about SAM and romance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw the Ryder and Cora romance scene and I had a thought. Since SAM has access to the Pathfinder's senses, does that mean SAM could see, feel, and hear everything Ryder did during their romance scene?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I remember rumors around the time of the first ME3 reveal trailer that Mass Effect was going to adopt a UI system similar to the one in Dead Space. Obviously, they weren't true, but I think Bioware is slowly transitioning to that kind of UI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] I made some adjustments to the Pathfinder armor color scheme. Thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made some adjustments to the original Pathfinder armor color design. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When that happens, I sometimes play the waiting theme from Jeopardy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair points. Speaking of Fallout 4, I think it would be cool for npc's to acknowledge your silence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the remain silent option; I think it would work if you wanted to give Ryder a 'Man of few words' personality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Should Bioware try timed dialogue options in ME:A 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other day, I managed to grab Alpha Protocol( its a pretty decent game despite it being unpolished. I hope someone tries another spy genre RPG), and one thing that stuck out to me was that the time you had to select your dialogue choices were limited, and if you couldn't answer in enough time, you responded with either silence or a default answer. This not only added a sense of urgency and tension to the dialogue scenes but also made the conversations more realistic. Do you guys think Bioware should try some variation on this system in the next Andromeda? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's got to be caring for an elderly, wheelchair bound Joker whose suffering from dementia though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Micheal McCann. The soundtracks for the Deus Ex and XCOM franchises are very similar to the ME 1 and 2 soundtracks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By roast, I mean the first option </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 11:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. That's a lot of old, salty meat. You might also bite into some cybernetic implants as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
