<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1239</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dog when she sees we're about to go for a car ride. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 07:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty simple, and if you've been paying attention to the rise of the regressive left, you're already familiar with the concept; Most people, including many of those who stylize themselves as "philosophers" and/or are active in the philosophy "community" are only there to validate their ego. Even those who attach themselves to "rational" ideologies and beliefs such as atheism, liberalism, and other mindsets that are popular among the more educated communities are all too often simply pursuing a neuro-chemical compulsion to validate their social standing, emotional preconceptions, and egos. 

This is why regressives, religious zealots, and radical ideologues exist no matter how flimsy and baseless they are shown to be. It's not "differing opinions". Most of the time, people are just being the animals they are and are desperately trying to validate their convictions. I'd even concede that Sam, myself, or literally any human being in existence is somewhat guilty of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 20:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These superhero origin stories are getting a bit out of hand. What exactly are Red Deer Man's powers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 05:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I brought a milkshake into the theater to see a movie.


That movie was Bruno.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 02:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Q from Star Trek TNG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 01:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/jailbait used to be a thing. 

There used to be a high profile subreddit devoted to borderline child porn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 01:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just....just go to hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 21:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Identity is not something YOU determine for YOURSELF. It's not a "right". You can control many things, from your actions to your thoughts (putting aside discussions of free will), and can certainly have ideas about who you are, but your identity is not something you get to just dictate to everyone all by yourself. Your identity is something that, by and large, others ascribe to you in addition to your choices in how you conduct yourself. You can certainly insist that you think you're an elf, or the reincarnation of Jesus, or some new gender term, but that doesn't mean you have the "right" to legislate that your "identity" be "respected". Other people will decide for themselves whether you are respectable on terms outside your control. Other people will generate their own ideas of who you and ascribe you identity based upon the way you act and present yourself. You have zero control over this, because you don't have this "fundamental right" to "self-determinate your own identity" unless you're saying that identity is entirely subjective and you can somehow force people to abide by what you dictate. 

What's to stop me from lying and cheating my way through life and then insisting to everyone I meet "Nah I'm an honest man because *I* feel like an honest man!"? If identity is totally subjective and people are obligated to respect it, why can't I proclaim myself as disabled because I "feel like I'm disabled" and get benefits for it? You're violating my fundamental rights, apparently! 

Now you can go around saying "I am X" all you like. You can dress how you like. You can behave how you like (within reason). That's fine. Go nuts. I don't have to automatically hold any kind of respect for you simply because you're "genderfluid", nor do I *have* to use whatever made up pronouns you demand people use, and nor do I have to be tolerant of everything you do or say simply because you think that your feelings dictate reality for others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 18:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this is why we're doomed as a species to resort to violence. People just need to have conflict to survive. We can't go a day without taking a stance that makes half the world want to kill us. It just feels too good to people when they paint themselves as the good and true. Their political beliefs not only give them this ego but also let them paint anyone who doesn't feed that ego as not just someone they dislike, but someone they can legitimately declare to be morally vacant and therefore you're doubly righteous because now you can do whatever harm you want to them because you're the good guy fighting the bad guy.

Honestly, we could never achieve utopia, because we would constantly be freaking outgoing "OH MY GOD THERE ARE NO PROBLEMS ANYMORE I DONT HAVE ANYTHING TO BE RIGHTEOUS ABOUT!" 

"WHAT DO WE DO?!"

"JUST MAKE SOME SHIT UP! CALL SOMEONE A NAZI!"

And then we would go right back to killing each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 04:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No! You'd spend $15 for an hour long DLC with crap gear additions and two bosses, only one of which is fun. The arena is a joke, since PvP is so unbelievably stale and broken, with insane latency issues, crap hit boxes, and a very narrow selection of viable builds and gear. If you disagree about PvP and enjoy it regardless (all the power to you) It's still not worth paying $15 to PvP when you can just go to Poniff bonfire like everyone was already doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 03:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have disagreed with my preconceived ideas and emotional opinions about X topic. Now I shall down vote you and throw petty insults your way as condescendingly as possibly. If you protest to this I shall call you a bigot and tell you to stop being so mean and confrontational. Also facts and opinions other than mine don't exist so if you use them you're objectively wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm mainly talking about the latency and hit box issues coupled with the poor balancing when I talk about what is broken. It's one thing to have lag. It's another to systematically have latency and hit box issues even when offline. Straight swords should not have longer reach and better stun than great swords, and the fact that they have is representative of the above issues.

As far as artificial difficulty, I don't think it's inherently bad. Sometimes you need to let a boss "cheat" as a way of showing how powerful he is supposed to be. Take Baldur's Gate 2. The final boss in that game is a powerful magic user, so powerful that the game gives in universe justification for him being able to ignore and bend the usually strict game mechanics and make him immune to your usual anti magic tactics. The problem with dark souls is it doesn't so much have this kind of artificial difficulty so much as it has "throw a chain axe through two walls to insta kill you" or "grapple you even though he clearly missed you". That's just my impression. I still like dark souls, I just don't think its issues were ever sorted out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 16:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still don't get why people praise this game endlessly. It's broken, filled with massive latency and balance issues, artificial difficulty, and repetitive mechanics.  I played all three dark souls and love the atmosphere and "spirit" of the game. But during that entire series, nothing was ever fixed because the moment you complain you're beset by the hordes of people whose main life achievement is beating this "hard game". If it were any other game, it would be vilified for the glaring issues it has. It's amazing to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 00:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always said that bleeding-heart idealists are the most dangerous people. Someone like this will seem nothing short of inspiring and flawless to anyone listening to her, and it would seem totally remiss to criticize her for fighting back against Nazi graffiti. 

Problem being, outside of the sensible limitations on free speech (slander,crying wolf,privacy, etc.) the people who take it upon themselves to decide what other people can and cannot say are the first people to turn towards authoritarianism and violence when they gain positions of power. Freedom is a responsibility, not something to curtail in the name of your personal idea of righteousness. Use your own free speech to combat others instead of pursuing the incredibly destructive narrative of thought policing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are probably plenty of people who despise you and think you're an asshole. It's an arbitrary thing to label someone. When it comes down to it, yes, I think Milo takes it too far or is just plain wrong. I think he's a hypocrite when he gets militant about rejecting fat pride (I even agree with him about it being bad to "accept" it) and yet he makes fun of people that are at the gym actively trying to fix the problem. However, being mean to someone doesn't make you a "hate monger", nor does it mean that you're wrong for being mean. I reject the notion that random strangers are entitled to my or anyone else's good graces and respect, and in an environment where those strangers are habitually slandering and insulting Milo, trying to shut him down and send him waves of threats, doing whatever it takes to silence him and make him feel unsafe and endangered, I don't blame him for having a guns blazing policy. I know that when I feel insulted, threatened, or otherwise accosted I'm quite liable to be aggressive toward them and those around them especially when the person that is coming down on me does so with the feeling they are entitled to my respect and morally superior to me.

There is plenty to criticize him for but the accusations of bigotry and white nationalism are taking it too far in my eyes. I might no agree with him about a lot but I do think labeling him a bigot is unfair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 00:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I read was "I don't like him, therefore he is universally despised as a symbol of bigotry" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 00:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Milo isn't a hate-monger, and nothing you provided really proves he is. I think Milo is pretty dumb on a lot of things, and I don't consider him to be a serious intellectual in the way that Sam Harris is. However, I do think he's an effective voice at ramming through controversial opinions despite all the efforts the regressive left can throw at him, and I view that as a positive thing for now. I really don't think he's honestly trying to be like Sam. He's outright stated he is a provocateur, his goal is to piss people off, his goal is to force people to have to hear things they don't like, and his goal is to expose and mercilessly ridicule people who don't actually know what they are talking about/are outright lying. That doesn't mean he's always right about what he says.

In the end, he's a human being like everyone else (including you), and therefore flawed (just as you are). Nobody is exempt from this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 01:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've felt like this for awhile. I always made the analogy of a burning candle.The fire is our consciousness, the light our perception. Most assume there is something special about us because we can perceive, some even take it so far as to say that reality is predicated on our perception. But the fire on a candle is not special because it casts light. It is simply an amalgam of physical laws and interacting components that sum up to the flame that illuminates-not magically, but because of the way it is composed. Such is our consciousness  too; an amalgam of smaller parts and universal laws that sums up to a form of interaction with the outer Universe. Like the flame, we "cast light" in the form of our perception, with our mistake being we assume this is some special quality, perhaps even what makes things exist. But if we snuff out a candle it has no effect on anything, and the universe does not stop existing simply because there is now no light to illuminate it. The same is true of our self; just a flame. Pretty, impressive, but simply a trick on itself, where all of it's components unite to form the whole of our flame and that flame insists that the universe is predicated upon the light it casts, simply because the flame can never know that what lies in the dark will exist after it no longer exists to cast light upon it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once dated a girl who was going to be a Physics PhD. She had great grades, but didn't know things like "heavy objects don't fall faster", "there is no sound in space", among most other basic bits of physics knowledge. Not at all the first of her kind that I've met... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 09:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can consistently find me with Star Trek TNG reruns playing on Netflix, even if I'm not actually paying attention to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 00:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Props to any of you that remember this old thing: 

Carsomyr, the Holy Avenger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 00:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Devils Horn from Dead Space.

BANG BANG! PEW PEW! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 09:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blade Runner, if you have not yet seen it. Rutger Hauer's soliloquy at the end is so short and yet one of the most soul striking lines in movie history. The whole movie is filled with subtle but important imagery that you need to pay close attention to, especially towards the end. Existential crisis fuel.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 00:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To curb all the "we'd all be nuked so it wouldn't matter", just assume that total nuclear annihilation doesn't happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]If WW3 or some other sort of hypothetical conflict between major powers occurs, what do you think it will be like to interact with people from hostile nations online(Reddit, online gaming, etc.)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 00:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
