<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2997</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That isn't deductive reasoning, and it certainly isn't evidence. That's just speculation and appealing to data that you don't have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any evidence that Supergirl isn't getting online viewers like Arrow is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Meanwhile on ABC...](http://cdn.abclocal.go.com/content/ktrk/images/cms/1036198_1280x720.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would explain [in part] why ratings fell after the first two episodes of the season, not why they're fallen in recent weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * [The Grinder](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/the-grinder-season-one-ratings-38238/): permiered to a 1.52 with 4.98 million viewers. Its penultimate episode did a 0.52 with 1.51 million.
* [Grandfathered](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/grandfathered-season-one-ratings-38240/): premiered to a 1.49 and 5.33 million; ended with a 0.65 and 1.64 million.
* [Borderdown](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/bordertown-season-one-ratings/): premiered to a 1.13 and 2.34 million, increased to a 1.48 and 3.58 million in its second episode; ended with a 0.45	and 1.159 million (and went below that a number of times prior)
* [Cooper Barrett](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/cooper-barretts-guide-to-surviving-life-season-one-ratings/): premiered to a 1.139and 2.62 million, increased to a 2.07 and 4.57 million in its second episode; did a 0.44 and 1.037 million before getting pulled.

None of these shows were picking up steam, they all declined severely in viewership over the course of their first season and ended with very poor numbers. I don't see how it's likely that any, let alone all, of them would have dramatically reversed course and risen back to decent numbers had they been renewed.

FX is a cable channel so they have a different business model than Fox's broadcast channel. Anyways FX has shown itself willing to cancel freshman shows that aren't performing well (Bastard Executioner, he Comedians, Saint George, Partners, etc). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pushing Daisies still got renewed even with the strike.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But if you compare Supergirl's 2nd season to Arrow's 2nd season

You can't compare a current season to a season from three years ago without accounting for the overall drop in broadcast ratings that happens every year. Adjusting for that puts Supergirl S2 about on par with Arrow S2.

That said, Supergirl's ratings definitely seem to be declining more than average. For much of the season Supergirl was a clear number 2 on the CW behind only the Flash, but these last two weeks put it at the same level as Arrow and Supernatural (and LoT when it was still airing), even with those shows' ratings also declining over the course of the season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Rating itself stayed the same, viewer count dipped:

The demo rating is down a few hundredths in unrounded numbers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flash and Arrow went on the same hiatus (and there have been plenty of promos for all three during the break). Flash returned up 0.14 from the previous episode, Arrow returned down 0.06 (and only down 0.01 from two episodes prior, which had been the season low). Supergirl returned down 0.18 from its previous episode and didn't rebound at all this week. I don't think we can blame this solely on the hiatus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who says networks are ignoring stuff like online viewership numbers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of people like to blame the strike for Heroes' downfall. Doesn't mean the strike was actually responsible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't legally stream the CW in Europe; the CW only operates in the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heroes lasted for two years after the last strike; it fell apart all on its own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as DVR goes, if you're watching within 3 or 7 days then it matters whether or not you're skipping the commercials. Commercials are sold based on C3 and C7 ratings that count delayed views within 3 or 7 days but only where the commercials weren't skipped; L+3 and L+7 don't matter for commercial prices (however they would for product placement, though I don't know how exactly the pricing for that works). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Just fast forward if you dont wanna see two guys kiss.

It's seemingly always two women when it comes to gay couples actually showing physical affection, I can't recall two guys kissing in any of the CW shows (at least recently).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the CW, most of the drama feels pretty forced, and their DC shows in particular tend to lack subtlety.

Also Gotham isn't a CW show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm pretty sure that's been a thing for a while, at least in Season 2.

It's been a thing since S1E1; the DEO knew who Kara was shortly after she first arrived on Earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if you're part of the very small percentage of the population not reached by a Fox broadcast signal, Fox's website/app is still free to use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 09:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you being intentionally obtuse, or what? 

To say that things always get larger *upon heating* would be incorrect, because negative thermal expansion is possible. However to say that things always get larger when they expand is true *by definition*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't need cable to watch Fox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I will never understand why. 

Ratings. Ratings are why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GoT should be fine unless a strike goes on for quite some time, and even then HBO could just delay it since they're not bound to as rigid a schedule as the broadcast networks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I still saw ads for Pitch back when it was still airing in the fall.

Also Gotham just came back from a three month hiatus, so I would expect it to have been getting more promotion than usual recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't stop promoting it; they did back off its marketing after the premiere but that's the case for pretty much every show. 

Now there's a decent argument that its timeslot was a poor choice, but I doubt changing timeslots would do much at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its ratings weren't particularly promising </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll finish the same week as Flash and Arrow; it started a week later than them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eobard took Time Vault Gideon back towards the end of S1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 22 episodes this season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somehow I doubt that a 67 year old who never played baseball at a high level could pitch in the big leagues.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The strike didn't kill Heroes' ratings; S3 premiered to similar viewership as most of S2. That the show went downhill after that is a separate issue, and from what I can gather it appears there were significant behind-the-scenes issues involving writing/production in season 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. This has been true since S1E1, it's not a new development. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firefly was cancelled 4 years before the last strike happened, and Heroes continued for two more seasons after the strike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supergirl S2E19 "Alex" Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Synopsis:** Alex is kidnapped and the kidnapper threatens to kill her unless Supergirl releases a notorious criminal from prison. Supergirl and Maggie have always had different approaches to apprehending criminals but this time they must work together to save Alex. Meanwhile, Rhea (guest star Teri Hatcher) has an interesting proposal for Lena (Katie McGrath).

Director: Rob Greenlea

Written By: Eric Carrasco   Greg Baldwin

**Main Cast:**

* Melissa Benoist as Kara Zor-El / Kara Danvers / Supergirl
* Mehcad Brooks as James Olsen
* Chyler Leigh as Alex Danvers
* Jeremy Jordan as Winn Schott
* David Harewood as J'onn J'onzz / Hank Henshaw
* Chris Wood as Mon-El
* Floriana Lima as Maggie Sawyer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not like you have to watch it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotham is almost certain to be renewed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Pitch' Cancelled By Fox After One Season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll be Eddie just like Prometheus was Tommy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Savitar will almost certainly be a character that we've already seen a fair amount of this season, so I doubt the opening credits will spoil his identity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You could tell that CBS were in no way sure about how the show would do and spent as little as possible on it.

CBS paid $3 million an episode for the show,  a very high license fee for a freshman broadcast show. CBS also did not produce the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except Jed Whedon is a WGA member so that solves nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They may have already planned out a decent amount of the overall arc for the 5th season but the scripts are absolutely not written at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No one mentioned pacing

The top comment in this chain specifically mentioned pacing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 10:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That article doesn't mention cycling at all, so how exactly is it relevant here? 

Also nowhere did I claim that the NBA is more diverse than MLS, and MLS being more diverse than the NBA doesn't contradict anything I've said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Who the fuck can watch BBall and think 'yea that's diverse'

Anyone watching the Spurs, for starters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at [ESPN's list of the top 100 NBA players of all time](http://www.espn.com/nba/story/_/page/nbarankalltime/greatest-players-ever) I get 71 black, 28 white, 1 asian (could be off slightly, I was counting quickly). I didn't count nationality; they're predominantly American but then the NBA is an American league so that's to be expected, and there are a non-trivial number of non-Americans.

In comparison here's [ProCyclingStats' list of the top 100 cyclists of all time.](https://www.procyclingstats.com/rankings.php?id=4210 page=2 id=4210 nation= team= page=1 prev_entry_id=1346 younger= older= ApplyFilter=Filter) As far as I can tell Quintana is the only rider on that list that isn't white, and the only other non-Europeans on there are three Aussies, two Americans (though for comparison's sake Lance should probably be included making it three), and Vino (if he counts). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yet he's chasing medals under the british flag.

Because riding under the Kenyan flag was a huge headache. Froome has not forgotten the community that he came from, he just understandably isn't particularly loyal to the Kenyan cycling federation that was never particularly supportive of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hawaii Five-0 was recently renewed for an eighth season so it's been pretty successful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 09:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably because the show's been on hiatus since January. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legends finale did [0.56](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/dcs-legends-tomorrow-season-two-ratings/), for a season average of [0.64](http://tvseriesfinale.com/tv-show/cw-2016-17-season-ratings/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please ensure that your comments do not violate the rules of this subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those could arguably be sitcoms but I'd classify them more as dramedies, and notably they're hour-long shows rather than the traditional half-hour sitcom such as Powerless. Granted CEG was originally going to be a half-hour show for Showtime and was then reworked heavily to be an hour-long for the CW, but I don't see something like that working for Powerless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You can't start a sentance with a conjunction.

You can absolutely start a sentence with a conjunction. Per the Chicago Manual of Style:

 There is a widespread beliefone with no historical or grammatical foundationthat it is an error to begin a sentence with a conjunction such as *and*, *but* or *so*. In fact, a substantial percentage (often as many as 10 percent) of the sentences in first-rate writing begin with conjunctions. It has been so for centuries, and even the most conservative grammarians have followed this practice.

[Here's Wikipedia's section on the subject,](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Conjunction_(grammar\)#Starting_a_sentence) and if you search 'conjunction starting sentence' you will find a multitude of other sources saying the same thing.

Perhaps you should make sure your notions of grammatical rules are in fact accurate before you accuse others of having incorrect grammar.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NBC can't sell the rights to the CW. NBC's options are to renew it or not; if they opt not to renew it then WB can shop the show around to other networks such as the CW. 

That said the CW is not likely to pick it up, both since the CW currently doesn't do sitcoms and since Powerless was reportedly very expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well every show takes weeks off, but yeah airing episodes out of order was stupid. However once that was done there was no way to undo it, leaving cancellation as the only reasonable option *at that point*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 08:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A second season is typically when a show finds itself and the audience begins to stablize somewhat.

Changing networks after the first season is going to screw with that. And very few shows change networks after one season, putting Supergirl in a somewhat unique situation.

For recent shows that have similar ratings trajectories to Supergirl, Quantico on ABC is the first that comes to mind: S1 premiered with a 1.93 and 7.142 million, ended with a 1.04 and 3.783 million; S2 premiered with a 0.96 and 3.635 million, most recent episode was 0.5 and 2.592 million. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Pretty sure its still the 2nd highest rated show on the CW this season.

On average, yes. But this 0.5 matches the season lows of Arrow, LoT, and Supernatural (in rounded numbers, as we don't have unrounded finals yet for this episode). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 06:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a perfectly acceptable sentence. Sure, it's not anything particularly elegant, but it's grammatically correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Firefly did terribly and anyone looking at those numbers would have dropped it

As far as I can tell no one on reddit complaining about shows getting cancelled ever actually looks at the numbers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A 0.5 matches the season lows of Arrow, LoT, and Supernatural; earlier in the season Supergirl was a clear-cut second place on the CW behind only The Flash and decently ahead of the rest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet it didn't hurt the Flash's ratings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chuck and Community also never got good ratings (particularly Community) and Chuck wasn't produced by NBC so NBC only made money off it via ad sales, not syndication and DVD sales and whatnot. Harsh treatment of poorly-performing shows, particularly from outside studios, is not Brita-ing them, it's good business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but it's making huge money for The CW overseas (the Netflix deal)

We don't know how much Riverdale's Netflix deal is worth, both in general and compared to the international distribution deals for other CW shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scrubs ran for 7 seasons (on NBC), Community and Chuck for 5, Hannibal for 3 despite poor ratings in S1 and abysmal ratings in S2. Those shows were not Brita'd by NBC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 07:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's been plenty of marketing, and Riverdale may be getting buzz but it's not really translating into ratings. But otherwise, yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The show was dead in the water (in terms of ratings) before any of the schedule and episode order changes happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 7 will be unaffected; season 8 could be affected if a strike happens and goes long enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pushing Daisies survived the last strike, it got cancelled the season after that because (like seemingly every Bryan Fuller show) it couldn't sustain decent viewership numbers.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vixen is just a half-hour per season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What makes you say it would dry up?

Because the people that own the content won't continue licensing it cheaply after they saw Netflix's success with streaming, they'll either greatly increase the license fee or pull it to use on their own streaming service. This is exactly what's happening and it was really easy to foresee, which is why Netflix has pushing to expand their library of originals so that it can survive a massive reduction in licensed content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Netflix wants to do that because they know that their supply of licensed content is going to dry up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> B99 has already been sold to syndication. But its syndication deal includes a fifth season, should it get one, which should help its renewal chances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agents of Shield *is currently in syndication*; it was sold to syndication on MyNetworkTV a year ago and began airing there last September. 

88 episodes is the standard threshold for syndication these days, but it's not a hard limit (for instance ABC cancelled Nashville last year after 4 seasons and 86 episodes, at which point it was already sold to syndication). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The only reason they are keeping it around is to reach syndication next season and also as a lead in for the new inhumans series

It's already reached syndication, and ABC isn't going to use a show getting fractional ratings as a lead-in for something as big as Inhumans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't disagree with what I said. Pushing Daisies got renewed in spite of the first season being shortened by the strike and returned to viewership only slightly lower than its S1 finale. However its viewership continued to decline in S2, as it had in S1, leading to its cancellation. I'm not seeing any strong evidence that the strike killed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SNL is on the list because (as the article said) it would likely have to cancel its last three episodes of this season if a strike started on May 1, since SNL isn't written weeks/months in advance of airing like most scripted shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pushing Daisies survived the last strike. It then died of its own accord, because like Fuller's other shows it had a lot of critical praise but not a lot of actual viewers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think that was the only on screen casuality as well.

Excluding villains I think that might be the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Savitar is voiced by Tobin Bell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the question you should have asked is

 Why should I buy a 60" television?

Adding the "when I don't even have basic cable?" implied that you felt not having cable means you don't need as large of a TV as you would if you had cable, which is foolish since there are a multitude of ways to watch TV and movies without having cable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How was the writers strike responsible for Pushing Daisies getting cancelled? It still got renewed after its strike-shortened first season, and the S2 premiere drew only slightly fewer viewers than the S1 finale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minimally, provided it doesn't last overly long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But a lot of TV shows wrapped up filming for fall premieres.

Just the pilot episodes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you don't need cable to watch TV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most reality shows are unscripted. Sure the directors/producers are often manipulating the participants, and the editing can further distort the 'reality' of what's going on, but that's not the same as having an actual written script. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Netflix doesn't produce most of its Originals, it commissions them from outside studios. So for them to cut out the WGA completely they would have to cancel many of their existing Originals that come from American studios. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unscripted shows don't need writers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, 10 years ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So this has to imply that all of them will survive season 7

Na. Actors signing a contract for X years doesn't mean the show can't drop them before that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supergirl S2E18 "Ace Reporter" Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Synopsis:**  Lenas (guest star Katie McGarth) ex-boyfriend, Jack Spheer (guest star Rahul Kohli), comes to National City to unveil his big breakthrough in nano-technology, which has the potential to eradicate all diseases. Lena asks Kara to attend Jacks conference with her for support. When Kara sees Snapper (guest Star Ian Gomez) in attendance shes inspired to tap back into her reporter skills and questions Jack on his discovery, which ultimately leads to a bigger investigation that puts everyone in danger.

Director: Armen V. Kevorkian

Written By:  Paula Yoo   Caitlin Parrish

**Main Cast:**

* Melissa Benoist as Kara Zor-El / Kara Danvers / Supergirl
* Mehcad Brooks as James Olsen
* Chyler Leigh as Alex Danvers
* Jeremy Jordan as Winn Schott
* David Harewood as J'onn J'onzz / Hank Henshaw
* Chris Wood as Mon-El
* Floriana Lima as Maggie Sawyer
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Lead actors like that will get paid whether they are in the episode or not.

Generally yes, but they are also still in the credits for those episodes. GoT has had episodes where main cast members are absent and not credited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the GoT actors took a lower salary the difference would just go to the studio/network, it wouldn't do anything for all the people who are barely getting by. Wealth inequality is an issue but calling these actors assholes for not taking a lower salary than they could is not the way to address it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least until they get killed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's typically how it works for main cast members, but they're typically also credited in episodes even when they don't appear. For GoT there have been episodes where main cast members don't appear and aren't credited, so it may work differently for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Friends cast only made $1 million an episode in its final seasons.

However they still make a ton from syndication. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Him getting resurrected afterwards won't help your trial by combat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Albasini marked a brief move by Henao at 6 km out but didn't himself attack (or even take a pull in that move). So better than nothing, but still not that much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They wanted to get Albasini to the line.

I think the point is that pulling Albasini to the line with Valverde in tow may not be the best strategy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's made the podium at Amstel Gold before, so there's that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> indicted = impeached </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Networks give no fucks about cancelling shows that have ended on cliffhanger (hell even Netflix has done it), writers often try that to get leverage on the network but it doesn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [A puppet, you say?](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/4a/ce/f3/4acef3bb61f15691e4f3c0aca590f091.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also Legion get good ratings for FX, its situation is nothing like Firefly's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Melissa Benoist Cast in Paramount Networks Waco </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You did the math, but the writers didn't (and rarely do, it seems). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are L+SD numbers since that's what's publicly available. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being terrible at politics is not the same as being insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His family is all kinds of fucked up but not really because of a lack of sanity on his part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "Netflix Original" label just means Netflix has first-run distribution rights, it's never meant that Netflix produced it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
