<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2621</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get along with both of my parents famously. My mother's other husbands and boyfriends even get along with me alright. I'm both ny mother and fathers best friend. When I came out my dad took it in stride. He was surprised but he was good with it. My mother was in denial and then tried to set me back up with every ex girlfriend she knew about. It didn't go great lol
But my father and I are thick as thieves  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have five gay friends. 
1: dilpickle, old roommate and dnd player. Get along great, one of my best friends. We both thing the other is the ugliest piece of shit to walk the earth. 
2: yogi bear, another old fried and I used to live with his brother (my best friend). He had a crush on me for a bit and we stopped talking. When he got over the crush we started hanging out again and we get along great again. 
3: math boy, went on a few dates but he didn't want anything serious so I started seeing my now ex. Math boy wanted to keep the friendship going so we kept hanging out and I just see him as a friend now. He kinda proclaimed his love to me though the last time we hung out. 
4: little joey, really cute guy who I slept with for a bit. We get along really well and have almost dated a couple times but I'm the kinda guy that goes and gets what he wants and he likes the guys who he has to chase to get into a relationship. 
5: art guy, we almost dated. We both think the other is attractive, we have a lot in common and used to talk about art all the time. He lives far away so we didn't date. He got a new boyfriend and doesn't talk to me much at all, think he's keeping me as a back up of things don't work out with his guy lol

I'm still pretty friendly with a bunch of my exes and old hook ups, plus there are the other gay guys that I hang out with from time to time or get a beer with. People tend to get along with me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was pointed out to me that I'm one of these guys, i spent some time think about why I did it. I never really realized I did. The reason was because I felt insecure that the guy I was dating was hotter than me so I though 'hey look at all these pretty people who fuck me' 
Point out the problem to him and he'll try and fix it. It's a little tough getting used to not talking about it though so give him some slack for a bit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I go up to them and say "do you want to be friends in a not me plowing your ass way" it usually gets them to laugh and then I say "see you already think I'm funny"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there ;) http://i.imgur.com/w4SpX6e.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty dom and make them look me in the eye and say "I concede". Only "I concede" works, not "I give up" "I surrender"... 
it gives the sub a chance to fight back by saying "I give" and then I get to break them of that. It's a ton of fun :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 12:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From reading your post it's sounding like you want us to convince you that you should be with James. 

Do what makes you happy, stop fretting about who will be hurt and focus on one thing. Who would make you the most happy. You need to focus on yourself for a bit here and decide what you need. If you focus on them then you'll hurt everyone involved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Message him and let him know you're interested but not out to your brother yet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 11:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much :))))) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends what we're doing but yeah I can get loud lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done that in the past lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you're a troll :/ 
I have a thoughtful reply too. Please stop trolling, you aren't adding anything to the community when you do this. 
I'm sure you have a funny response to this but I'd much rather see a thoughtful one. Even if I disagree with you, I'd rather read what you think than see your trolling. 
Try giving to the community a chance. I think you'll like it. 

Ps if anything is going on I'm your life that you need to talk about, message me and I'll be here to help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol fair point  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Underwhelmed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say it was playful. I'll ask her about it when we hang out tomorrow. It's been a couple years since the event too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Message a few guys on Grindr first and then talk with them at the bar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in the same boat as your guy then I was with a guy who just kept flexing his ass while I was inside of him. I lasted like five minutes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want a boyfriend but apparently I'm just good fuck material :/
I only have myself to blame though, the most common thing I hear on a first date is the other guy saying "I never go this far on a first date" 
I really need to learn to slow down and calm my member down some.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only on my depressed days  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol thanks. You have any pics xD  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never though of it like that. They usually happen in a group setting. Something like 
Friend: "you two used to hook up right?"
Her: "if that's what you want to call rape"
Me: "I have a video of you begging for it"
Her: "I wouldn't call that begging"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's uhauled mean lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol maybe  http://i.imgur.com/BCiPY5F.jpg http://i.imgur.com/V4yv9Y9.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I talked with her ex for awhile before it happened to set the ground rules. She was always a fan of hair pulling but hated choking, she also liked being slapped and biting. She has a safe word, apples (10points if you get the reference). She fought back a bit at first so I slapped her and then I held her down with a bit of choking for a bit. After a few minutes she stopped struggling. One of the rules was that I couldn't cum in her v so we did anal too (something she hates) that's where I came. 

After all that we cuddled for awhile and she kept telling me thank you and that she really wanted it. I called her boyfriend over and we three spent the night together watching doctor who lol

Apparently they did the same thing again with one of her boyfriends friends and it didn't go so well, but yeah she enjoyed it and sometimes she makes jokes about it...those make me feel a bit uncomfortable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a friend that really wanted the rape scenario and I knew that from back when we used to hook up. She (I'm bi) had the same problem of it never being real enough. So she told her boyfriend to get someone to do it, he really liked the idea and asked me to do it. She and I used to hang out three or so days a week and we hadn't hook up for years. Her bf sent me a video of her explaining that she wants someone to rape her and she was giving consent to do this, only reason I went through with it was the video. So the next time she came over I ripped shirt open and pulled down her yoga pants and went to town. It was a little strange tho  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't done that yet lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't...yet ;)
(South bend/Chicago area) lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they have some solid legal footing there, Grindr hasn't been shown to act in good faith and we could really use some court rulings on identity theft in social media.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Move past it or say to them something like "could we hold off on the gay jokes today, it's been a tough one" the guys who make the jokes might not even realize they are being rude  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm bi and was a bit of a slut. On average I'd say anal with guys is better. First off guys moaning is so much hotter than women moaning. Then most of the guys I've been with are way tighter and I don't have to worry as much about sticking the whole thing in. I do find the angles work easier with women and it's nice not having to use lube with women but I produce a ton of precum so I don't need much with guys and often times with a bit of spit after rimming a guy I can go off that and precum. A lot of the guys I've been with are more active than the women  and though I love boobs, there is something about the collarbone of a fit guy that drives me wild. I think the really big thing guys have going for them is that, in my experience, they are more willing to experiment and try new things in the bedroom. 
Hope I answered your question :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Straight forward can often be the best way lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude there are over 330 million Americans. We aren't all bad. Also hearing a British boy say "well are you going to fuck me or what?" Was one of the hottest moments of my life lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call a hospital and speak to a RN, ask the nurse for gay doctor recommendations and I'm sure he/she will have one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say something like "you act a lot like someone who wants to date me for a guy who insists he's only here to hook up"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people will think less of him, you can't help that. He just has to decide if the potential happiness with you is worth the loss of those people's respect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks pretty good. Just watch some YouTube videos on how to style short hair for men. The length suits your head well. If you want a more hands on approach then go on a date with a cosmologist and get their opinion lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God damn there has to be something wrong with me because I find that romantic lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that made my day lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I saw a post from u/chrisnothing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously thank you. I subscribed to the subreddit and I'm reading through it. I will do what it takes to like the way I look in the mirror again. 
Thank you so much. If you think of anymore advice it is all well appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much :) 
I just joined a gym today and I'll be signing up for a trainer tomorrow. You being hot af helped me out dude lol 

This is where I'm starting from http://i.imgur.com/HwPgBO6.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you stay happy single? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I came out as bi I've constantly been dating people or I'm in relationships. I know what I need right now is to focus on improving myself but late nights like tonight make me lonely and miss having a cuddle buddy. 
How can I be happy single again?


Edit: thank you all so much :)
I deleted Grindr, joined a gym today, put in new job applications, took my mother to lunch, got dinner with a friend, cut a toxic "friend" out of my life and made plans with people I haven't seen in awhile. 

I love all of your advice, you are great guys :))) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the same way to be honest, only I'm the more rugged one lol
Don't lower your standards if it will also lower your happiness. 
I'm single right now and am taking my time to choose the right guy who checks the boxes for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get new peers. When people ask about college talk about your academic accomplishments. Find people who genuinely respect you and value you. Quite worrying about a past you can't change  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an outgoing confident guy. I have a friend with social anxiety that has me go out with him and help him get guys. His first dates are always double dates or I've pretended to be his roommate before to excuse my presence there. 
If you have a friend like me then ask him/her to help you out. After a few times it will get easier for you and now my anxious friend is one of my closest friends and I like his boyfriend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm bi and want a son. My ex (guy) wanted me to go father a son so we could raise him together and he'd look like us, my ex looked a lot like me. 
Ps I mostly just posted on here because I'm drunk and miss my ex but I'm not gonna be that guy that desperately drunk texts an ex. Instead I'll be the guy who posts about him on Reddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :))) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a couple years you're going to regret ending the friendship over this. In a couple years you're going to regret waisted so much time obsessing over a guy you never had a chance of a future with. 

Love yourself then your friend, do what you'll regret the least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been told I look good both ways. I like guys both ways lol http://i.imgur.com/HvNkvo4.jpg http://i.imgur.com/NMPXzcW.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do I have to do to look like you lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's weird dude  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try Einstein, now go back to your patent office and do some real work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 13:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mother is a really good judge of character so yeah I'd go with her on that one.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 13:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a box clearly labeled "dildos and such" inside the box have another label saying "why are you looking?" 
Under the toys put a note saying "you touched them!?...there's no sink in this room bro" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 13:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come to Indiana by Chicago. I'm a top in a world of bottoms lol
Though all the people I keep falling for only wanna hook up =\ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 12:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to say it but I don't think he is going to change. It just sounds like that is who he is. You need to detach your success from his. You two need different rides into and from work if you want the relationship to survive. Also it kinda sounds like you both work at a Walmart like job. If that's the case then don't be too concerned about the job. It's easy to find other jobs like this one and you need to decide if being a good worker there is worth tanking your relationship happiness. 
Also if it is this kind of job he might just be lethargic because of the shit quality of the work. If he isn't this way when you do other things then don't paint him by his approach to his job. 
I suggest that you two get jobs at different places and ride separately into work. 
Good luck out there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 12:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fearing it's going to end at any moment is a sure fire way to make it end. 
Make the long term plans but also play it by ear. Don't buy cruise tickets for six months from now but plan to go and put the vacation time in. 
After you've bend together longer this will all become more natural for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do I do to look like you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a bit too long unless he makes a ton of precum  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
