<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1397</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, its berenstain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While not directly religious, the new year is a Christian influenced holiday. Namely, the Jewish new years in in October (or thereabouts) and the Muslim one moves around the year. 

It's essentially a civil calendar simply because the Christian calendar was the tye most dominant, because most western people were Christian. It's why the civil calendar is named for a pope. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or like every American hotel has a Gideon Bible in the drawe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 15:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *JC Penney. 

Berenstain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 06:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One interesting theory is that mammals live about 1.5 billion heartbeats. because of different metabolic rates, different mammals live different lengths.  almost always, bigger animals have slower heart rates. 

http://www.npr.org/templates/story/story.php?storyId=12877984

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 21:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. Just behind this picture is Wacker drive and lower Wacker (below is lower Michigan) that's where part of the dark Knight was filmed in the lower streets. To the left, right behind Wrigley building (in photo) is the ibm building which is where Batman's condo and corporate offices were filmed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 21:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was just there yesterday. I was at an office in the crown of the tribune tower (Gothic tower on the right). Here is one of the views from there: https://imgur.com/0c5FgdQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 15:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so funny (re sad) that for all of the things that people voted him for, far and away number one is his ability to negotiate, however it's been mightily clear that he's an absolute rube, and that he is a pushover to the extreme, and so easily manipulable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 11:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I think China is quite enjoying being the adult in the (global) room. 

This is their opportunity to become a world leader and they are not going to squander it for what is essentially petty fights. By China rising above (for this and for climate change) they are trying to signal to the west that they can be trusted on the world stage to move the world forward, trump provides the perfect contrast, and perfect cover for their way of handling domestic and regional affairs. 

China is going to beat the US, not despite trump, but because of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 10:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBf, the xc90 is the offered alternative (us news always provides 2 alternatives to compare) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 10:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like metacritic, us news is a review aggregator. It averages other reviews, (and adds some of its own details.) If it is missing components such as safety, it means nor enough other reviewers have quantified it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 18:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The governor only signed the law, why didn't the legislature who actually wrote the law not get voted out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 01:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why doesn't California have universal health care already, then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 14:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are more crown family, pritzker family, regenstein family and Lurie family things across Chicago than Richard Daley, though if count other daleys, such as Maggie, it'll even out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 01:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dae notice Gamora's unmakeupped eyelids at the end? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 07:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There aren't nearly that many jewish people there. It's recognized </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 16:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any programming/algorithmic advantages to other languages based upon their unique vocab/syntax/language structure that is lacking in English? 

Or because programming is so specific and technical, programming in alternative languages are simply a 1:1 translation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 15:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to be a hackey sack man like you, but then I took a beanbag to the knee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 14:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pic for those curious:

https://royalexhibitions.files.wordpress.com/2010/05/scottish-crown1.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 14:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4/45 assassinated, but another 4 died from other means, that gives them 8/45 fatality, or 18%  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 14:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally think that they're going after governors as a medium high-profile priority, not that others are ignored. Local elections are typically run out of state level parties, not national ones -which makes a lot of sense - and governors are more important than the house at the moment in a longer term strategy:

A) the house isn't going to flip soon, the majority is too strong, and there aren't enough seats to flip. 

B) the governors (along with local races) will be instrumental in the 2020 gerrymander, so focusing control their is hugely more important than the house at this time. And that gerrymander will also allow for the house to flip in 2020/2022 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Kochs Won 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 13:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats look to 2018 governors races for rebuild: The large, wide-open slate of gubernatorial races will be key for the party over the next two years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 13:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 01:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Electoral college votes for clinton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 01:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course he knows that they won't deliver. Cruz is gearing up for a 2020 primary challenge. 

TBH, I'd take zodiac Cruz over trump every day of the week. His brand is at least within the confines of the "rules" and is predicable and won't destroy the country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 14:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except tesla just posted a profit. 

Anyways, You clearly have no clue how businesses work if you think that reinvesting profit=loss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 05:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a one balled dick in a butt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 21:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'd probably rather not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 21:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't current events specifically part of the genesis of this sub? Like if there are current events going on with complex reasons or outcomes/implications, the this place would serve as a place to explain these difficult things?

Ie middle East entanglements and complex government laws and regulations?

I remember the subs creation, and iirc it was specifically for this express purpose.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 14:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's there just to test you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 14:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would explain his painful social awkwardness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 14:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's done all the time, is it really extraordinary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 13:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The American dental association no longer recommends flossing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 02:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wear my pants right about my belly button. Much more comfortable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 01:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't think he wasn't light-headed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 15:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be pedantic and slightly more precise. It's "beams of light"

Even today, in modern Hebrew, the word for beam (of light and structural) and horn is the same word "keren" or "krn"

Be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 15:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you rather have a soul crushing job you hate, but with a mid-seven figure salary (can't quit) , or a job you love every minute, but only make minimum wage in high-col city? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 15:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Israel-related_animal_conspiracy_theories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 04:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me the example is from the first movie, and it makes a plot hole that no one else seems to notice. 

In the series of games at the end they skip the potions riddle. Not only was that a great scene (and also easily done without much CGI/effects at all), it's integral to showing (early on) where snapes loyalties lie. 

In fact, earlier in the movie, when the kids tell hagrids that they think Snape is the baddie, hagrid tells them it couldn't be, because Snape is one of the teachers who is protecting the mirror. 

If there is no potions game, there is no Snape protection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 03:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Merrick Garland gets recess appointed, GOP challenges or in court, it goes to supreme Court, Garland rules on his own appointment. (SC is not required to recuse) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 03:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like when Congress accidentally passed a law destroying sovreign immunity, then overturned the veto, then blamed Obama for not warning them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 03:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ideally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 03:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot Tom delay  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 18:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the East India Company? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 02:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the'yre trying to fight the urge to becoming mofuckas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 02:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, but the government would still have to pay this money to maintain it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 16:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought this was a silly argument, even if true. 

Because if only one of tens of thousands of food sources is user friendly, then that's just a coincidence. The argument only would work if there were many user friendly foods, not one, ans certainly not one that isn't terribly widely available or central to our nutrition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 02:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, one of the biggest things holding by 5G is vector processing. Ie, funding the direction and location where the device is. 

5G will be run on much, much smaller wave length than previous generations, this efficiency allows more data and better bandwidth sharing/division to allow a much higher capacity data transmission. 

The downside is that smaller waves dissipate much faster. This necessitates a more directionally addressed beam to allow for better transmission. 

One way Qualcomm is trying to overcome this is by sending out a fishing signal, which will tell the antenna where the device is, and then the antenna can beam directly to the device with more amplitude, and allow for better range. 

Beam formation is near the speed of light, so 150 mph is not very fast, and the signal beam will likely be 100s of times per second.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anish Kapoor Coats Cloud Gate in the Darkest Black Known to Humanity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 13:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He sold it long ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think trump and Christie are friends from way back. His ouster is simply because Christie put Kushners father in jail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's party of Jeff Bezos media network. So maybe like WAPO?

It's pretty liberal, with a focus on clickbait </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 14:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, so long as Medicare and Medicaid exist, it prevents it's beneficiaries from supporting single payer. 

As soon as Ryan cuts it out, and at some point Dems are back in power (sooner than later, if Ryan does do this), it will be easier to implement medicare as a single payer for everyone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 05:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's where the Messiah has been waiting on his donkeh the whole time? Someone let the pope know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 04:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I gathered from the article:

Musk is terrible, nothing good. 

Musk isn't so bad, he actually has some good points, isn't the worst, and supports research and advances. 

Is that a correct reading? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 04:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, too, had to cancel mine. 

When I realized that I was making financial contortions to justify it, I had to come to grips. But it will be better in the long run </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 03:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Linky? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 03:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hitler wasnt the model Aryan. Wasnt even Germann, either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 22:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe I'm saying this, but hopefully Jared can contain bannon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 22:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe I'm saying this, but maybe Ivanka and Jared can contain him. They've already knocked out lewendowski and christie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Taps Reince Priebus As Chief Of Staff, Steve Bannon As Chief Strategist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 22:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 21:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh thank goodness we have your dose of logic. My ancestors could have used you in 1942. Surely the optics and cost of killing and deportation of millions of Jews and undesirables make it impossible to happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would Toyota Shift to Electric Cars Mean Death to Fuel Cells? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 21:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 20:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except he went the relief. He was the supporting character. The cab driver was the relief, and he was hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It keeps him from running as a primary challenger in 2020 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course the BinBong scene, but also the whole bus trip.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just throwing a question out there; after 4 years of crazy trump, wouldn't America be hungry for some stability and experience? 

This was a change election, but it brought trump, wouldn't a change election in 2020 be for the establishment?

Just a question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not about Bridgegate. It's because Christie put Jared Kushners father in jail. 

http://m.jpost.com/Us-Elections/Report-Trumps-Jewish-son-in-law-pushed-for-Christies-removal-from-transition-team-472409
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will season 4 be in the spring as usual, or move to summer to coincide with game of thrones? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 04:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need SV to calm down after GoT, but maybe they won't coincide anymore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 03:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm partial to cartoon comic relief.

**Best** Kronk, of course. 

Honorable mentions, pumba and Timon, pill bugs (bugs life), donkeh, scrat (ice age), anger (inside out).

Worst, I didn't like the gargoyles  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 02:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't get too be global pedo conspiracy by *not* placing a pedo symbol in your logo for everyone to see. Marketing is marketing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 02:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're called frits. They assist in reflecting heat. This increases heating efficiency in the oven, and insulating efficiency outside. 

Usually made of ceramic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 01:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sh bbe, it's OK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 01:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jewish food. Not just bagels and Reubens. Granted, none of it is terribly healthy. 

Everything fatty, rich and dark. We have a cheesecake and blintzes holiday, and a jelly donut and potato pancakes one, too. Not to mention the best briskets, kugels and of course bubbes chicken soup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 08:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He won't fit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he will also quietly beef up security protocols for nuclear codes, require more input. Also cede some executive powers, such as the war acts (police action) back to legislative in order to reduce risk, just in case. 

Republicans always claimed to wait a weakened executive branch, and Congress won't refuse more power, so.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a jobs program </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 14:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that what the movie is about, anyways? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT, if you can, bring your kids with you to vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 13:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 08:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sauce? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today is the Day! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 08:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 02:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And after you get it, it'll ream your a**hole dry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 23:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The infrastructure makes sense more when you realize that the name of the bill that authorized the interstate system is "The national interstate and defense highways act."

Seriously. It is defense that gets them all excited, not infrastructure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 14:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You beat Tuco! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 19:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean by "have hate in their DNA"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 19:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll probably bring on the superdelegates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Caregivers take care </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 15:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 02:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this was a Kevin James type movie. I want a refund </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 22:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinkpads are ace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 22:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having a sorting to also be by activity, not just voted popularity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think about it, you'll be featured on the news with all the other geriatric fans about how long you've waited. Then the team will give you a front seat at the WS. It'll be worth it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 15:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are still the party of ideas. Ideas about misogyny, racism,fear and dictatorships. It's an ethos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 14:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or in a few months :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 13:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They only inherit half the drought. Because the cubs were so long, that even getting to the WS was a drought breaker. I think that one belongs to the Expos/Ws </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 13:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was blown up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 05:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rain delay brought to you by T-Mobile is not a great advertising line </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 05:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are plenty. You canGoogle them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 05:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try r/counting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 01:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and right after that fantastic pick off, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 01:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, like Donald Trump. Now I get it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely want to give people in the 808 time zone heartbreak. And want to give people in the 1908 time zone lots of luvin. Go cubs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if (*even if*) you didn't like the past 8 years, cheeto Hitler is not the answer. 

The Germans didn't like their economic situation either, that does not mean that Hitler was the right choice, and they certainly are not absolved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 12:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need to be smart of everyone else is scared of everyone else. He most definitely was manipulated in several ways by his aides. Most notably, he dis not create the Holocaust, he simply created the environment where it became possible. He was not involved in the wansee conference, nor in implementation. He was just the"make Germany great again" guy, while his minions figured out how to do it.

Of course, Hitler had no problem with the Holocaust, and supported it Bigly, but her definitely didn't come up with the idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 12:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think anyone thinks that Donald Trump is an excellent salesman. He has his skills.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something very fishy is going on in Comet's FBI: FBI releases Bill Clinton closed case files days before vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 05:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 05:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're finally waking up those bantz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jake Arrieta is the 1st @Cubs pitcher to win multiple starts in a single World Series since Lon Warneke in 1935 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 04:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 04:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't trademark something that contains someone else's trademark (Indians) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 04:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bite that pillow! We are coming in dry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 04:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **WE GOING TO GAME 7, BABY!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 04:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like these cubs mojos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 04:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ice cream and popsicles all night </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 04:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are required by MLB rules to wear the same uniform as the team </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 04:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice work, I like it. Small suggestion, instead of saying the punchline, show it. Maybe a frame of your mom stammering in a chair across the principal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 04:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 03:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It still doesn't make them deserving of respect. 

To take a conservative talking point. Many complain about liberals caring about criminal's difficult life etc and things that cause and lead to a life of crime and violence. Or like abusers who were abused when they were kids. 

They say that's all BS, and crime needs to punished. 

The same applies to them, then. 

I don't give a rats ass about why they are the way they be, I still don't respect them (for an extreme example, I don't respect people who voted for nazism, even though"it's all the Allies fault because of the treaty of Versailles).

They fundamentally misunderstand why liberals care about background. It's not absolve the perp, it's a way for us to learn and try to prevent others from following in their footsteps, ie stop the cycle.

So, of course i know why West Virginia loves Coal-Trump, but it still doesn't make me respect them. I understand them. Big difference  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 02:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> saltiness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 02:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn straight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 01:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **WE'RE GOING TO GAME 7, BABY!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 00:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also scalia was a radical in his constitutional thinking. Yes, it went on to influence a couple of generations of lawyers, but it was completely new. 

If they wanted to keep it how it was, it would be super liberal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 17:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1st and business class tickets typically make up over 30% airline revenue. Aside from their high prices, those flyers will buy tickets based on scheduling (often last minute) rather than price sensitivity. 

A first class ticket (1 way) for tomorrow morning from LA to London will cost $7k-$12k depending on the airline. Just 3-4 of those tickets, plus 8 business class tickets (6-10k) could be nealry $100,000 for that one flight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wall Street Journal feels the pain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 14:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 13:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's what mine looks like: https://imgur.com/nBq9L3c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 12:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anihydrous butter solids? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 12:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I visited Indonesia, I was surprised by the lack of seatbelts in the back seat of the Toyota I was picked up in. Apparently they're not required by law. 

I was kind of horrified that Toyota would save the couple of bucks and retool an assembly line to remove a few seatbelts for the third world market just because it wasn't legally required </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 05:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Swans can be gay

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 05:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It also looks like someone's crack. The two arrow things are fat peoples dimples of venus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 05:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Donald Trump avoided paying potentially hundreds of millions of dollars in taxes in a way even his own lawyers considered questionable, The New York Times reported Monday.


 The newspaper said the maneuver also may explain how Trump posted a one-year loss of more than $900 million a few years later, enabling him to avoid paying federal income taxes for perhaps 18 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: Trump used dubious tax avoidance scheme in 1990s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 05:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: Trump used dubious tax avoidance scheme in 1990s that his own lawyers say is questionable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 05:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 03:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's gonna be hard for the white house to publicly come out and undermine their FBI, nothing positive will come from that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 03:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here I thought Tim was short for Anthony </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 02:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently looked up knex and was so surprised at how cheap they are. A full motorized rollercoaster for under 20$, if it were Lego that would be 225 minimum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 01:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I hope it didn't come across as belittling the extremely difficult work that she had and the unique issues that she faces, but everyone is working off hard work of the generation prior. We are all standing on shoulders of giants.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 01:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fredge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 01:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the UK, the group puts all their white chanel bags on the dance floor, and kind of dance around them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 01:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Hillary would love to have the admiration and respect that Michelle gets. 

However, it's only because of the extremely hard work and the thankless fighting that people like Hillary have done trailblazing the path for women everywhere that society respects women like Michelle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 01:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HILLARY CLINTON ADVOCATING FOR TERRORIST REFUGEES AND GIVING OUR TAXES TO IMMIGRANTS FOR GOVERNMENT HEALTHCARE AND FREE LIBERAL EDUCATION! CROOKED!

^^^/S ^^^just ^^^in ^^^case ^^^you ^^^thought ^^^otherwise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 00:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww. That's too bad. At least you got to see the cubs make history. Must have been incredible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 23:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does she have an opinion on gay swans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 23:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do none of the other teams have similar stuff? (Sorry lifelong Chicagoan, casual fan) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 23:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were you at the game? I didn't see the "view" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 23:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a lifelong Chicagoan and only casual fan, I have been fascinated by the traditions, the W, the songs, the histories, etc. 

Is this more or less a unique Chicago thing, or do other teams and cities have similar stuff, if so what kind do they have? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 22:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There once was a 3-1 lead... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 16:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 07:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need a new rule, like rule 34, every accusation that trump throws, it's a projection of his own behavior.

Seriously, there isn't one thing he has ever accused anyone of every that he himself had not done, and more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 07:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For better part of a year, and if you count his birthering and history of racism, then decades </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 06:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK. I wonder if mine skipped because reasons or if she had three jewish holiday that day? (50th) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 06:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All that fanciness and he couldn't splurge for an @chaffetz.com or @Utah3rdDistrict.biz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 05:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forget CS running fine, evey AudoDesk product is intended to be on windows, and until this year you couldn't even get rhino3d for Mac. So all my friends have ridiculously expensive Macs and run Windows clunkily on it. It's like what are they even doing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 05:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **HEY STOCKBROKER, CAN I GET 300 ON GOAT FUTURES? AND 500 ON DANK 3-1 MEMES! GOT IT? We going to Cleveland baby!!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 05:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAVE YOU BLOWN YOU'RE LOAD YET? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 05:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kerry Wood! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 05:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be out of bounds to say that the uncle did what your pops would have wanted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 03:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you took a moment to read what you linked you'd find this quote: 

"*Clinton administration attorney Lanny Davis called the decision to indict a week before the election rather than after the election "bizarre."*"

It was wrong then, it is wrong now, as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 02:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nuance and r/politics don't often go well together </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 01:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which 10? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 00:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I'm surprised because Keystone was such a huge deal specifically during review and permitting. You'd think a sister problem would br ripe to attach and ride along on that publicity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 00:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/understanding-controversy-behind-dakota-access-pipeline-180960450/

This says otherwise. It says that originally it was going to cross the river elsewhere, but because of fears of oil spills in the water going to the state capital the rerouted it near the standing rock. But now when crossing near standing rock they claim that there will be less likely to spill because pipeline. 

It sounds to me, and uninformed bystander, that so long as the potential risk is not to state municipalities it's an issue, but when it's someone else's (ie native) then it's all OK. I understand both sides want NIMBY, but somehow when neither side wants something, the native peoples lose out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 00:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm already resigned. 

If the cubs are going to give up the series, then we should lose tonight. Don't give the Indians the satisfaction of winning at home </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 23:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. I have beastly W530. It's a brick on a hippo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 23:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does the land belong to them or not? Your comments seem to vaccilate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 22:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> then why was there a price in the first place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 22:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of Apple's core values is hardware and software that are designed holistically and then work seamlessly together. 

But they certainly don't translate those values to their hardware suites working together. 

I'd much rather have some rough around the edges software-hardware relationships than hardware-hardware. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 20:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except the way you and others above have explained it, its more like McDonald's had burgers at 10, and burger King (army land) had burgers at 15. So the customer says, that price is too high and takes all the burgers at McDonalds for nothing, and then says, that's what you get for charging too much. 

Am I missing a component? No one should be forced to sell burgers for less than they want to, even of the"market won't bear it" it's McDonald's prerogative to sell at whatever price, and the it's also the natives  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 20:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You still don't answer the question why the natives shouldn't get the amount of cash they are asking for? If the market won't bear it, then the oil company shouldn't build. 

It's not hypocritical at all to demand the amount of money you want. No one forces you to sell your stuff to someone else at the price the buyer demands. I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 18:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in a design related profession. Professionals absolutely need to have everything beautiful. If they don't own beautiful things customers might think that they are not good at design. 

(Lol I have a Thinkpad) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 18:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I commented there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 17:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That argument makes no sense what so ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 17:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is it greedy for natives to demand more money? If they don't want to sell, they shouldn't have to. 

Especially, as you continue to write, the company didn't want to do plan B because it's expensive, so clearly that is the "market rate" for land. 

Why should the natives get the short end of the stick because using federal property instead of private property is cheaper?

Even if I were to believe what you are writing, it makes absolutely no sense, and bolsters the native argument, not the oil company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 15:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I better invest in some short term goat belly futures.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 13:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can ELI5 what's going on? Also, why is this an issue during construction and not during planning and permitting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 01:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like your username </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comey wrote bombshell letter to Congress before FBI had reviewed new emails </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 01:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comey wrote bombshell letter to Congress before FBI had reviewed new emails </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 01:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 16:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe we ought to appoint 1-2 alternates to the supreme Court ? Same vetting process as a supreme Court justice, but only sit when a justice recuses themselves? Maybe chief justices of the various circuits? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 22:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. No poopy seeds?

2. No NEON relish? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 22:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why didn't the issue come up in the planning and permitting stages and only during construction? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 14:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's not insult lizards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 14:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly the fact that most billionaires from the 1980s have not worth 20-40 billion now tells me that it's not so straight forward (exceptions apply) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 06:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sticky keys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IS THE IVY RED YET? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 15:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 06:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's the man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 06:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any qualias </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 23:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biopic actors: Streep for now, Anne Hathaway for young. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 23:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ Poe's law hard at work  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 13:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the large size is spacing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 07:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's bringing the power down to lower voltage, wouldn't things that need more power have smaller transformers, as they need less stepdown? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 07:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 06:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Touche </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 06:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brisket: jewish or Texan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 06:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More gazpacho, actually </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 06:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except that the famous Earl of Sandwich story involved a one-sided sandwich </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 06:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst are good people who let evil happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 06:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Classic chauvinist line: women are out of control and oversexed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 05:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess someone called hannity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hannity offers to pay for Obama to go to Kenya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 05:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
