<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2840</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I'm sorry, didn't realize that's what you meant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hit me up on discord, @subject2840 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get around 120$ a month for food and outing. I wouldn't be able to afford something like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White
Yellow
Green
Blue
Red
Orange </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanna learn something new, solving a cube in and of itself is cool, it'll take a shit ton of time where I could be learning something new.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cards are the best. I have a bunch of decks and can shuffle in a few different ways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already play as much as possible  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's kinda expensive and I'm sorta broke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I already know how to  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT Request: What's a skill I can learn with a few minutes practice a day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't matter if it's a social skills or something "useful" it could be entertaining.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Come over to discuss anything you want too. No limits, just whatever's on your mind. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 11:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 09:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luxembourg. 

Most powerful passport in the world. 
I'll know French, German, Luxembourgish, and English. 
EU member state
Good population to surface area
In between France, Germany, and Belgium; cool places to travel close by  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could be from any other country, which country would it be and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 09:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I don't do that. The guy always has his employees do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll either be a pharaoh or some fucked up porn star. Accidentally found this out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> George Washington. He was the only president to ever get a unanimous vote. By approval ratings, he's #1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subject2840

I would send you some awesome landscapes if my country had em  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reinstalled runescape and started dungeoneering 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having a nuclear meltdown will suck. No one wants that, or even wish it on their worst enemies. 

The thorium reactors wouldn't be practical since it's just ramping up costs for the same thing, so companies won't do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the main point for nuclear, there's no byproducts(that'll fuck with the environment). Which is what we really need right now, since we've already fuck with the environment enough. 

Chernobyl shouldn't have even happened. It was just dumbassry that made it blow. We can't have shit like that happen again. Fukushima though that really damaged the reputation of nuclear. I hope that another Fukushima won't happen, but it probably will eventually :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mannnnn the porn thing was the worst. My friends would send hentai In our group chat and always tag me. I would instantly delete that shit because I don't see the appeal of seeing a girl with boobs bigger than watermelons getting raped by an octopus. 

I keep meaning to read light novels but tbh books are what took me away from anime. I've kinda grown out of anime into some more mature media. It's still good, but I'm much less of a fan. I've been reading books like slaughterhouse 5 and 1984, and will buy saddam's book soon to see how his brain works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh I might've confused the numbers. My bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a few flavors that don't have nicotine, those are the best ones to vape. My brother doesn't vape nicotine one, rather the nicotine free one. It's even better than the other vaping flavors since it won't get you hooked like cigarettes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
