<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3835</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like [heather] and [puddingWhispers] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> test for [Heather Feather] channel link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> test for [Heather Feather] channel link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> test for [Heather Feather] channel link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [video] Jet Blue emergency landing September 2005 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I just want to ruin your poll with a pointless answer" because I'm too stubborn about technicalities to tick the correct box even though I know perfectly well what you're asking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally someone in this thread who can tick a box without dragging up the last 1000 years of history and politics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why did you expect an Irish option? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because Ireland isn't part of the United Kingdom so comes under European </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still roughly equal at 13-11, but I'm far more entertained at the fact that 22 people took the time to submit a response to my joke poll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to type out a whole 11 extra characters when I enter the URL. Which is admittedly not that often. But still.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It got requsted [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/unitedkingdom/comments/5qavop/subreddits_have_to_be_at_least_three_characters/) :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Subreddits have to be at least three characters long, but /r/de gets a special exception due to it being a common abbreviation. Why don't we also get an exception for "/r/uk"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The word "british" never appeared once in either my post or my poll. As I've said numerous times ITT, it's a quick, throwaway, just-for-fun poll. It's not the ONS census.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean I'll be a filthy foreigner? Think of the domestic job that I'm taking away from the purebreds! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you won't get accurate results

.

Do you want to know how many people that participate in the uk sub actually live in the UK or do you want to know how many were born in the UK. 

I honestly don't care. **It's a quick, throwaway, just-for-fun poll. It's not the ONS census.** If you want to make a competing survey giving an in-depth profile of the exact heritage and location history of each person who answers then be my guest. But that's not what I was going for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you didn't, because StrawPoll has an option to accept only one answer, which I enabled. As someone with a degree in computer science and a job in the industry, I know perfectly well about radio buttons. But as I've commented numerous times elsewhere, it's a throwaway just-for-fun quick poll. It's not the ONS census. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, it's not really supposed to be taken that seriously. It's a quick, throwaway, just-for-fun poll. It's not the ONS census.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe a Google account is a better option as they're slightly more trustworthy I think, and it also allows me to use my throwaway google account. I think far fewer people have throwaway Facebook accounts. Also I think people are pretty suspicious of signing in with Facebook recently, because so many services ask you to sign in then subsequently make posts and like pages on your behalf etc. Not that you will, but the suspicion exists. And if you're requiring people to have signed up with a third-party service you're necessarily excluding anybody who isn't already on that service, so you should always fall back on a local account. Although I do appreciate that it's far better for security to strongly encourage people to use facebook or google first, then have maybe a semi-hidden option like "don't have a facebook or google account? click here to sign up" or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I could have done a multi-part Google Forms survey with a whole profile for each person, but that wasn't really the aim. It's just a quick out-of-interest thing. I also think that people are willing to spend the time to tick a box but their attention span will soon run after after more than one or two questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the question does ask "Where are you from?".. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it does say "where are you from?" in the question.. I didn't really expect people to take it so seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I could edit the options I'd have fixed the typo I made in "International"! But you're right, maybe the phrasing could be a little clearer. Although the question does ask "Where are you from?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The National Insurance people? I can't think who else you might be talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> see [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/unitedkingdom/comments/5qa2wj/in_the_wake_of_the_150000_subscribers_thread_many/dcxkr7k/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not really the point of the poll. The point is to find out where people are physically located, not what citizenship you feel most closely represents you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't choose the font. But I think it works with the informality of it. And yes, I make a lot of tyops, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet here we are.

https://www.strawpoll.me/12201205 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The welsh seem to be underrepresented at a whopping 0%, even being out-stripped by "I just want to ruin your poll with a pointless answer". Maybe they're all busy with.. erm, something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being English necessarily makes you British and European.^^^for ^^^now ^^^anyway. But the "European" option implies that you're **not** also British by the assumtion that you choose the narrowest demographic that applies to you from the available options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't choose the font. But I think it works with the informality of it. And yes, I make a lot of tyops, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You monster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I made a poll](https://www.reddit.com/r/unitedkingdom/comments/5qa2wj/in_the_wake_of_the_150000_subscribers_thread_many/). It will be intersting to see! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Apparently so](https://www.reddit.com/r/unitedkingdom/comments/5qa2wj/in_the_wake_of_the_150000_subscribers_thread_many/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 16 minutes in and we're currently at 44% European..! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note to anyone who voted in the original - could you please vote again in the updated poll because I had to recreate it to fix a typo. If you saw horrible code like ` quot;this quot;` you voted in the old poll so your vote has been discarded. Sorry about that. There were only ~~three~~ ~~four~~ five of you.

EDIT: GODDAMN IT. I made another typo in "international". Ah fuck it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 09:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I don't use Facebook which excludes me from using the app.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah on closer inspection the details of the shape of the girl's body do line up pretty closely. So yeah maybe it is the same original.

http://www.apple.com/apple-events/october-2016/

starts at 59:15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ahh the gnerd. Wait.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 18:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't this the pic used in Apple's keynote where they demo'd the macbooks with touchbar? And the presenter photoshopped it live on stage. It might not have been this one but if not it was very similar. It took me a sec but I thought I recongised it from somewhere

edit: [Nope I was wrong, it's quite similar though](https://i.imgur.com/0GbtAZQ.jpg). Don't mind me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? Works fine for me. I just linked to the /top so people see the actually good posts if they click it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this. I know it was ages ago but I had the same problem and this utility seems to have fixed it. Thankyou! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reminds me of [/r/SUBREDDITNAME](/r/subredditname/top) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 13:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that low effort posts are pretty tiresome. I like creativity and originality with notinteresting posts, rather than just finding new titles to resubmit a black image or taking a picture of a pencil and captioning it "this is a pencil". 

I think the spirit of the sub is different from just literally submitting things that aren't interesting, and the best posts make me laugh rather than just bore me. 

To that point I've started downvoting comments like "ok" and "yes" because they're so low effort and they stopped being funny about a week after the subreddit was created </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 10:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. It fits fine. The best posts are ones that entice you to click and are anticlimactic and cause you to realise what subreddit you clicked on from the front page, and I think this one does that perfectly. The username honestly just makes it more intersting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 10:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it should be music only. But it should fall back to music when pushing play there won't do anything, for example if it's linked to YouTube or, in your bizarre case, the App Store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 10:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you downvote it at first? It's a perfectly notinteresting post even without the username. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 10:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sharing your positive experience with a religion? LOL NOT IN /R/ATHEISM DOWNVOTES FOR YOU YOU THEIST HEATHEN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for natonstan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 10:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comments solely based on the appearance of the content creator are at best clutter and at worst offensive and creepy. If a commenter has nothing more to comment on than the looks of the person in the video then that doesn't contribute to any discussion so I almost always remove them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was sort of a joke. It honestly wasn't even a good one. I wouldn't take it too seriously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No that'd be 

don't (drive|operate) heavy machinery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 00:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah I see, I misunderstood. Yeah probably, although I wouldn't really know much about the rooting process etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 00:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  almost all android devices are rooted

I don't think that's true at all. I'd be surprised if it's even as high a percentage of android users as iOS users who root their devices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> on my iPad 4th Gen: absolutely. iOS 10 runs like absolute fucking horse shit on the iPad 4. Performance has degraded with each iOS release in the past few years but this takes the piss. It's very nearly unusable. I can't really use it for anything other than streaming video now. Apple shouldn't have allowed it to be upgraded. 

On my iPhone 6: Not so much. I was only really using the jailbreak for the occasional tethering and for snapchat, and I have 4GB of tethering allowance anyway and I can live without the snapchat hacks. And I upgraded to the iPhone 7 anyway so I didn't have a choice but to use iOS 10 after September. I do really miss [[zw1t]] though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for JCCanezo_77 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll give it a go, thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unable to boot into windows 10. Possibly a small amount of corrupted data on boot drive - is it possible to save it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 12:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know much about windows booting with bad data? I've seen "repairing drive C:" a few times recently while trying to boot and it always seems to have successfully repaired any errors. I ordered a new drive anyway because I was worried about my BD failing, but it's not arrived yet and now I can't boot my PC. 

The C: drive is visible, but chkdsk found errors when I ran it from cmd in the repair menu. I ran `chkcsk /f /x /r` and it got stuck and never finished. 

I did a copy-paste of my C: drive into a folder on my D: drive a couple of days ago but I doubt that'll be any help tbh lol.

When I boot it says "Preparing Automatic Repair", then says it failed to repair files. I tried the "Reset PC" option and selected to keep personal files, but that failed too. 

Using Windows 10. The data I care about is backed up twice, including in the cloud, but I really don't want to have to deal with a fresh install. 

Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 21:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda stupid that you're getting downvoted for a correct answer that just happens not to be the other correct answer that everyone else thought of. I like the lateral thinking.

    f(n) = f(n-1) + f(n-3)

It's an altered fibonnacci series. The previous two numbers would be 1 and 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 10:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My entry. Good luck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hit markers weren't "replaced", the "hi there" was just added in over the top

literally unwatchable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to hear her talk more. Her voice/accent is great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is nothing short of criminal that this is not a perfect loop. That stutter when it restarts makes the satisfaction evaporate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this is the kind of submission that gets upvoted around here then I'm not sure I want to be a part of the subreddit any more. Saying that "by every single metric" is extreme hyperbole and has surpassed being "misleading" into being objectively wrong. Yes, you can easily cherry-pick examples in which men are disadvantaged, and there are certainly social pressures which adversely affect men. The point of this subreddit is to fight for **true equality**, and to recognise that although feminism is a great idea, there are issues on both sides that need addressing; not to pretend that men are the oppressed ones and that we "have it worse in every way". 

You know those crazy tumblrinas who complain about manspreading and think they were raped because a guy walked past her in the street? That's what you look like right now. You're taking a valid argument - that there are biases against men that should be discussed in an adult and constructive way - and you're distorting it beyond any reason and making a ridiculous conclusion.

This is what the internet does. People make bad points, have tunnel vision, and get worked up on defending their point so that they make unfair arguments. Other pick up on those unfair arguments and don't bother to research them, and the discussion turns into a round of chinese whispers, each successive post more misleading than the last, until a post like this shows up. From your phrasing, someone who didn't know any better would think that women rule the earth and men are oppressed victims who kill themselves out of shame. I'm not saying that the statistics you quoted aren't right - although as others have said I'd appreciate some reliable sources before I blindly believe them - but throwing them out there in hyperbolic rage like this just doesn't represent the Men's Rights idea at all, and comes across as having a tantrum because not all of the statistics favour you.

Saying that women have it better in every way is just plain and obviously wrong. Even saying that they're mostly better off is ridiculous. They have far more problems than we do, and I'm all for anything that can be done to boost womens' equality with men because that makes for a much better society. But they have a long way to go, and it's obvious to anybody who stops to think for a second that men generally have a better position than women. Again, there are problems on both sides, but please don't parrot these ridiculous strawman arguments and try to disguise it as helping to push the MR agenda.

If you genuinely believe that men are oppressed and have it worse than women *in every single way* then you're delusional and impossible to take seriously.

https://yourlogicalfallacyis.com/the-texas-sharpshooter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [request] per-app do not disturb, and other powerful DND features </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 16:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems a good Do Not Disturb tweak doesn't really exist (or I've not found it - let me know if it's out there!).

Things I'd like to see:

* Per-app DND, to allow silencing of an individual app or all apps except one
* Multiple daily DND profiles. You can currently only set a single start and stop time, but it'd be nice to say DND should be on between 23:00-07:00 AND 12:00-13:00.
* Geofenced DND - switch on when I'm at work, for example.
* Weekly schedule - specify different scheduled on/off times for different days
* Disable when my alarm is switched off (waking up) 
* Block, rather than just silence, notifications. They currently still show on the lockscreen but I'd like the option to disable them entirely (app-by-app?).

Any other ideas? I found most of those ideas while searching the subreddit for similar tweaks, so they've been previously requested but not all in one thread. It seems *some* features *kind of* exist but I'd definitely pay for a powerful tweak which enables full control over DND. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't unsee that. You're cursed for life, every time you read your username. You're welome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sang your username to "wake me up before you go go" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 23:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because saying that adds nothing to the conversation and is just annoying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/comments/5o7fti/milf_reads_your_horoscope_on_skype_roleplay/dcim6lg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obvious trolling is obvious. If you can't see that a milf themed video is inappropriate then I'm wasting my time here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gah you're right you found a loophole. We didn't explicitly state that MILF stuff is inappropriate. Brb, making a list of the 14 billion topics that are inappropriate. Hope you don't mind reading a 19TB wiki page. Should only take you a few weeks. 

In the meantime feel free to post as much porn and beheadings as you like since that's not explicitly disallowed in the rules so you can get away with posting it all. 

Seriously. The rules aren't a contract to find a loophole in. They're more like guidelines than actual rules. If I think a post is inappropriate I'll remove it, whether or not it was explicitly classified in the rules. That's my job. If you have a problem with that feel free to moan about it in a [meta] post. 

Also it is a rule. Rule 2.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 22:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/anticlimax </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 22:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't really appropriate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 21:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really appropriate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \games

\ga

\gay

I officially declare you a phonetic homophobe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 09:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed. Reports bring this stuff to our attention! More reports = better subreddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 12:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what do you do?

Oh I'm in the special response forces

awesome, what does that involve?

Well I hold a plank of wood so that the other guys can walk up it

oh cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 10:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed. Don't repost stuff quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 00:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your opinion on the wave of "sexualised" asmr content? There seems to be an increasingly large market for semi-nsfw asmr content on and off of youtube, and some have discussed being uncomfortable with the erroneous impression this gives of the community. Do you think it's ok? Or would you stop it if you could? What do you see in the future for the asmr community as a whole? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 23:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which was your favourite video to make?

 I personally love your [repeating the word 'Fuck'](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l5F2Vjhy_P4) video. I've listened to that one so many times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 23:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://static.fjcdn.com/pictures/Keanu_887b5b_2304526.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 23:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you get triggered by your own content? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 23:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Pudd! I'm going to ask the same thing that I asked Heather back when she did [her AMA](https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/comments/3p5bvx/my_name_is_heather_feather_i_have_been_creating/), which is perhaps the hardest question you can answer and which will truly define you as a redditor and indeed as a human being.

So..

Would you rather be attacked by 100 duck-sized horses, or 1 horse-sized duck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think of this one? https://i.imgur.com/IQt57mm.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I've watched this guy before, and roleplays don't usually work for me, but this was great!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'm cursed. No matter how closely I check the title when I make a sticky, there's ALWAYS a typo that I only notice after it goes up. the only explanation is the Ghost of ASMR. Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reposts are ok if they're less frequent than 3 months. If you try to post something that's been submitted within the past 3 months the bot will remove it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 13:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries. If you haven't already there's a quick guide to submitting at /r/asmr/wiki. It's just a 2 minute read but it'll help a lot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 23:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FOR EMPHASIS  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 23:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHY DO PEOPLE STILL UPVOTE THESE /r/BADFAKETEXTS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [A] cover for me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 20:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 11:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there's a line to be drawn somewhere though. It's true that"kids will be kids" and their mistakes will help them develop. But passing magazines around isn't remotely the same as posting videos online </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you delete the original you can resubmit it. Reposts only count if the original is live </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 00:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends how well the other 505 turn out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Computer Science  Mathematics (Type Theory) - Computerphile [unintentional] [male] [german accent] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  When you have a subreddit that hides the downvote button 

But we don't hide the downvote button. It's right there under the upvote button for people to use if they see fit. For example, I downvoted your comment just now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should have been submitted as an [intentional] post as a link to the video. I won't remove it but remember for next time :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love iFixit. I'm positive this wasn't an accident. They knew exactly what they were doing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst piece of advice you've ever followed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 11:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 23:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know that existed. Perfect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 23:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand how this is still surprising to people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, oops. I'm not sure why it caught this. It's supposed to allow you to use both [roleplay] and [intentional] together. I'll look into it.

In the meantime I've approved your post. 

Sorry about that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 14:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crappy design doesn't mean every typo or misallignment. It means poorly thought through design, and the choices made when creating something. Mistakes aren't design choices, they're just poor proof reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PuddingWhispers (Formeraly FatFr33Pudding) will be hosting an AMA here this Saturday 14th at 5pm EST / 2pm Pacific / 10pm GMT! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 14:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everyone!

We hope you've had a relaxing couple of weeks after the craziness of the holidays. Today we are very pleased to announce that [PuddingWhispers](https://www.youtube.com/user/FatFr33Pudding) will be hosting an AMA here on Saturday, January 14th! The AMA will start at 5 pm EST, or 10 pm GMT. He'll stick around to answer your questions for a couple of hours, and the thread will be left up as a sticky for a few days afterwards so that anybody who can't make it can still read through. 

Anyone will be welcome to ask questions and interact with him during the AMA, but please remember to adhere to the [**subreddit rules**](https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/wiki/index#wiki_rules). We are very excited to be working with him and hope you guys are too! It'll be a fantastic opportunity to interact with one of the top youtube content creators.

See you there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 12:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As soon as I heard his voice in that movie for the first time I immediately knew it'd be a hit with asmr fans. It's as if it's *designed* to trigger me. Fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 12:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always been in favour of using "see you at 16" in speech rather than "see you at 4pm". I don't, because it sounds odd, but it's a shame it does because I kind of like it as a neater system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 12:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not crappy design. This is a rushed leaflet with a mistake in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 11:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking Commander Keen. Made in 1992 ish and still very enjoyable.

Also Total Annihilation. Late 90's: terrible graphics, questionable pathfinding, pathetic AI, but my god that's a fun game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 11:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/thatHappened 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally someone who understands. Those peasants who only *pretend* to feel it are ruining it for the rest of us superior beings who can actually *appreciate* the subtle science and exact art of asmr. We select few who possess the predisposition can relax our mind and tingle our senses. The other mortals in possession of abilities so formidable to feel confident enough to ruin the subreddit for everyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm OK with naked D.Va 

This is the real issue here. I'm all on board with that train. Blizzard, are you listening?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I ended up doing and it worked fine. Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever heard of PM's? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PRAW3] Why does fetching a comment with r.get_info() not also fetch its replies? Is there a better way to fetch them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 14:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you fetch a comment like this:

    comment = r.get_info(thing_id="t1_abcdef")

Then the replies are always empty, even if the comment has replies on reddit:

    comment.replies
    []

However if you fetch a comment tree from a submission, you get all the replies in the comment object.

    def get_comment_from_submission(comment):
        s = comment.submission
        i = comment.id
        for c in s.comments:
            if c.id == i:
                return c

     comment.replies
    []
     comment = get_comment_from_submission(comment)
     comment.replies
    [comment object at..] #contains all the correct comments

wtf? Surely there must be a better way than this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 11:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you any idea how overpowered that'd be? She fires 20 rounds per second at 8 damage per round for 3 seconds. That's 160 DPS and 480 damage per clip. She could melt through any target in seconds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditor describes how race/racism is perceived in different parts of the US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 09:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 02:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed. I don't think it's really appropriate to require a survey be done before testers apply. It's kind of a given that they have an iOS 10 device with testflight, and you can just state that these are required. People usually just provide a link to sign up and say "oh by the way you'll need iOS 10".

Also the testflight community is pretty great in terms of feedback. They wouldn't be beta testing if they weren't willing to provide feedback. So requiring them to agree to give it comes across as unnecessarily defensive, and saying "congratulations, you qualify to test our app" is very pretentious. 

Feel free to resubmit without the survey link. 

As a side note, although I can't moderate your submission based on the tone of your wording, I'd strongly recommend that you try to drop the marketing. You're not trying to sell it to testers, and when testing people are far more receptive to a human interaction and realistic description as opposed to a PR-approved advert </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 01:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad it did! That's why I posted :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 18:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> secondary joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 18:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> link to /r/subredditname </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 18:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> condescending retaliation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 18:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> joke reply </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 18:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> rude reply </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 18:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> offensive comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> test [intentional] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 18:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also understood the reference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 17:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or ALyssMR. Pronounced A-Liss-M-R </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 11:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obvious troll is obvious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.google.co.uk/search?q=inurl:png biw=2048 bih=1048 tbm=isch source=lnt tbs=isz:ex,iszw:2560,iszh:1440#tbs=isz:ex%2Ciszw:2560%2Ciszh:1440 tbm=isch q=gaming+wallpaper+inurl:png

Finds only png images of the exact size of your monitor. Google is great.

use inurl:query to search exact matches in the URL. Use tools - size - exact size under image search to find images pixel perfect for your monitor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 14:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's very powerful. But you can also nuke your entire system with one false move. So don't muck around in there lightly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 14:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> idk why you'd use jpgs as backgrounds. All of mine are pngs and they look great. Backgrounds are supposed to look nice and if they have compression artifacts all over them, they don't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 10:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say the voice recognition is terrible. That's the one thing siri is actually pretty good at now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of like the text to speech. It's original, and it adds humour, while concealing his voice.

I loved his [every overwatch hero in one sentence](https://youtu.be/K8K80muFdiA) video. Can't wait for more content.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Comprehensive Guide To Oasis || This guy is great, deserves far more subscribers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 00:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean it was alright. I guess it was funny. But you waaaayyyyy over sold it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meta] Subreddit Update - New Mod and More </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everyone!  

I hope you had a wonderful New Year and holiday break. We wanted to quickly give an update on our announcement from last month, including some new additions to the subreddit which you might have seen when we made [our last thread here](https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/comments/5e6zf7/meta_new_shiny_flairs_mod_applications/).

## Roleplay Flair - Trial Results

Again, we want to thank the community for their input on /u/Sopixil's [idea to flair "roleplay" posts with a unique flair](https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/comments/5d5gde/can_we_get_a_new_flair_for_roleplay_videos_meta/) rather than just categorise them as "intentional". 

The Roleplay flair trial was a huge success and seems to be welcomed by everybody, so we'll be keeping the Roleplay flair in its current form permanently. During the trial I set up the bot to attempt to detect roleplay submissions that were not flaired as such, and the detection worked far better than I imagined. The bot has been sending users a PM asking them to re-flair their submission if it detects an incorrectly-flaired roleplay, but after seeing a near-100% detection rate, going forward I'll have this process automated so that any submissions that look like roleplay videos will be given a roleplay flair regardless of whether OP used a [roleplay] tag. This will help the community quickly find the sorts of videos that work best for them. 

In addition, during the trial we were enforcing the "one flair tag per submission" rule, so that submissions that were tagged "[intentional][roleplay]" were being removed. We think this is counter-productive as it's pretty obvious it should be flaired as "roleplay", so going forward we will not remove threads that tag both, but just flair it as a roleplay and condone the submission. 

As always we rely on user reports to help fix incorrectly tagged submissions and remove those that break the rules, so please remember to report anything that shouldn't be there or is flaired incorrectly. If you're not sure about whether something is ok, report it and the mods will review it. Although we do our best, we can't review every comment on the subreddit so the more (genuine) reports the better.

Also as always, if you have any suggestions about how we could run the subreddit differently, we're always open to new ideas and discussions!

## New Moderator

Thank you to everyone for their applications in the previous thread. We hope to still see you all around in the community. We considered every (serious) application and were delighted at the interest shown.

So, please give a warm welcome to /u/underscorewarrior who will be our new mod :) He'll be around in the comments below to introduce himself and have a chat.

## Discord update + Game Nights!

We've seen more activity in Discord lately, it's been great to talk with all of you!

We've added a new role for ASMRtists on the server that will allow you to talk with other content creators privately for advice, tech help, and more. We'll also use it to verify the real deal, to avoid impostors. (there is only one /u/sailorchell!)  

Game nights are also a thing -- we hope that given the new influx of you guys there will be more interest in joining in playing some games with us. /u/NvaderGir and I have been on Overwatch a lot recently, and with the new Oasis map we're hoping more people would be interested too! We will see what most of us have so we can all squad up together online, maybe play some Rocket League for example :) We're open to hosting any game you're interested in, so chat on the discord and mention your favourite game and we'll arrange a session.

Consider joining today and introduce yourself! - [Join here](https://discord.gg/0aPMRwTjjn67GZDz) | A How-To Guide is also [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/comments/3q0bl3/meta_rasmr_discord_server_a_howto_introduction/)

#Happy Tingling :)

#- /r/asmr mod team </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to Amsterdam about a year ago. I saw the three X's EVERYWHERE in the city - on the pavement, in shops, on the sides of buildings or bridges. I really wanted to know what it meant, and for some reason didn't google it. A couple of months later I saw the flag somewhere else and it clicked. It really is a great one, so much so that the residents plastered it all over the city wherever they can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, I was massively overcomplicating this. So:

* The solution X **is representable** as a float afterall, so that whole idea was a red herring. (Or it wasn't close enough to 125 to be indistinguishable, anyway).

* The only thing that confused me here is the console rounding X to 125 for the purpose of displaying it nicely. This explains the apparent inconsistency in the two integers.

* everything else works as I expected

Thank you for your replies :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 15:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to know this too. 

I did a lot of searching when I needed an answer a few months ago but couldn't find anything. If you're just running the .py file, you can rename the file to .pyw and it'll hide the console. But using py2exe this doesn't seem to carry through and the console appears when you run the .exe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 15:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right,

 Python does not do "divide and then discard floating point", it calls fmod() which returns the remainder

So if X and 125.0 are indistinguishable, then it should return a remainder of 0 since the quotient is 125. The quotient can't be 124 because if it was, X and 125 are distinguishable so the floating division result of `125.0` I saw in the console is unexpected.

So what I'm saying is that exactly one of the following has to be true:

* the floating point representation of X is 124.99..
* the floating point representation of X is 125.0

The first being true would not explain the floating result, as I'd expect to see 124.99.. in the console, not 125. But the second being true would not explain the truncated result, as I'd expect to see 125 in the console, not 124. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm I'll try to rephrase what I'm asking, it's kind of hard to explain.

I don't understand why the results I got are consistent with each other, considering the internal method used to calculate the result.

After the calculation, the expected floating point answer should be X = 124.99whatever. However, you said this *isn't representable in binary* because it's too close to 125. I understand that, and this explains why the float answer was displayed in decimal as 125. So internally X=125 because its true value (124.99whatever) is not representable, so it is indistinguishable from 125 for all the computer cares. However when we get X in the truncated calculation, it's still truncated to 124, which we'd expect if X was representable in binary because it does begin with 124. But we know that it isn't representable, because the float result was 125.0; if X was distinguishable from 125 then I'd expect the result to be displayed in the console as "124.99..". So because X and 125 are indistinguishable, there's no way for the computer to know to truncate what it thinks is `125.0` down to 124.0, according to my understanding (which is evidently wrong but I'm trying to learn why I'm wrong).

The alternative explanation is that there *is* a representation for X's true value (i.e. 125.0) internally, in which case I don't understand why the float result is displayed as `125.0`in the console when it knows that the true value of X is 124.99.

So what I'm saying is that exactly one of the following has to be true:

* the floating point representation is 124.99.. 
* the floating point representation is 125.0

The first being true would not explain the floating result, as I'd expect to see 124.99.. in the console, not 125. But the second being true would not explain the truncated result, as I'd expect to see 125 in the console, not 124. 

/u/anossov said somewhere else that the console rounds off if it thinks the answer is close enough to an integer, which would explain the conflicting answers if it's true.

Hopefully that explains my position. I know it's frustrating trying to help someone who's wrong so I appreciate your replies, but I think it'd be very useful for me to understand exactly what's wrong here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. I guess the `12499.999999999998` result just wasn't close enough to the integer for the shell to classify it as a float arithmetic error then?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. So, I happen to have found a case where the error happens twice in different directions and sort of cancels itself out? If I understand correctly, it's something like this:

1/0.008(00..1) = 124.99.. which is represented as 125 

1//0.008(00..1) = 124.99 which is truncated to 124.0

However, why would the 124.99 be truncated to 124? If the internal representation of 124.99.. is equal to 125.0, then why would it truncate to 124? If the floating point representation of 124.99.. is seemingly 125.0 it should truncate to 125 surely.

This is making my brain melt. I hate floating point sometimes :D I mean I studied compsci in college and uni, and both courses covered floating point so I understand how the representation works.. in theory.. but this particular instance just doesn't compute with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does Python round off if there's a float very close to but not quite an integer? That'd explain why the float answer was 125.0 and not 124.999... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, this is what I was thinking. I understand how floating point works but my confusion was more that one operation gave 125.0 and the other gave 124.0. I'd have expected, if there was a floating point error, that I'd have seen 124.999.. and 124.0. Does python round up if it's close enough to an integer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I guessed it'd be something like this. But it doesn't explain why the different orders of magnitude worked differently. The part that especially confused me was 

     1/0.0008
    1250.0
     1/0.00008
    12499.999999999998
     1/0.000008
    125000.0

Where it works, then doesnt, then works again as we add powers of ten. 

Also: how'd you calculate the decimal value for the binary representation like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it might be something like this. Not sure if you caught my edits, but it got weird when I tried different orders of magnitude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I thought I was comfortable with integer and float division, and then python threw this curveball at me. What's going on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 13:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>      1/0.008
    125.0
     1//0.008
    124.0

Wait, *what?* Only thing I can think of is maybe it's a float rounding error, where the binary answer was something like 124.999999.. which got truncated in the integer division version but correctly rounded in the float version. Any ideas? I'm on py3.5

(correct result should be 125)

---

edit: further investigation reveals:

     1//0.0008
    1249.0
     1//0.00008
    12499.0
     1//0.000008
    125000.0
     1//0.0000008
    1250000.0

     1/0.0008
    1250.0
     1/0.00008
    12499.999999999998
     1/0.000008
    125000.0

Now I'm really confused. There's definitely some floating-precision sort of error but it seems inconsistent. An explanation would be appreciated :)

edit2: I understand how floating point arithmetic works, but my confusion isn't that the answers were different. I'm asking how I could have two different integer answers. If it was a simple floating point error then I'd expect the truncated answer to be 124.0 and the float answer to be 124.9999... but that's not what I'm seeing. That'd be explainable: the two integers aren't to me, unless python is sneakily rounding the 124.999.. to 125 for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 13:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed. Solicitation of the subreddit for money is not allowed. Also why would people donate to you when you haven't even set up a channel yet? :\ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 11:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I find it completely hilarious. Although I always recommend reading his full comment because it's really interesting (and he spent like 2 hours writing it and he wouldn't have invested that time if he could have said the same thing in 5 bullet points). I've been on the fence about trying the released beta tool, but reading his comment in full has convinced me not to until it's finished. I'm probably their worst nightmare - someone technically proficient but has no idea what they're doing with jailbreaks or hacking etc, which  puts me somewhere around the top left of the [Dunning-Kruger curve](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dunning%E2%80%93Kruger_effect), the perfect place to accidentally do terrible, unspeakable things to my phone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 11:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most smartphones have fantastic cameras in them. The Pixel, iPhones, and Galaxy line all have particularly good cameras. They'll always be constrained by their physical size, but the camera tech in smartphones has come a very long way and they produce some excellent footage. They're great to get you started with content creation. I'd try to get a different mic if you can, but the camera should be more than sufficient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 10:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The stylesheet tweak works great, thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 10:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> followup: I left it running overnight for around 16 hours and when I interrupted it this morning the resulting textfile is 875MB and won't even open in notepad or wordpad, and Word 2013 won't open it because "it's larger than 512 megabytes". And I tried reading it into a new python script and even that threw a "MemoryError" which I've never seen before (host system has 16GB of RAM; observing Task Manager seems to suggest it throws the errors after the process takes up ~1GB). Now that I think about it maybe a flat text file wasn't the best solution... :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh. I used to like that subreddit but they went on a power trip and started autobanning people just for taking part in other subreddits. It's been a couple of years so I don't remember the details but I remember them making some pretty shitty comments and basically admitting to loving the control it gave them or something. I don't feel good taking part in a community run by those sort of people so I've not been back since. Well, that and I got banned for commenting in some other subreddit. 

So yeah there could be a whole new mod team for all I remember. It's not like I committed their usernames to memory. But the subreddit is stained in my mind, and I've never had any reason to believe they've changed. I think their banning-people-for-partaking-in-other-communities policy is still in full swing? As I said I've not paid attention for years so I wouldn't know, but I see people complain/laugh about it every now and then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No that's not it. Maybe they actually care or maybe they don't, either way they're power-hungry twats and *thats* why I don't like them.

But the funny thing about disabling the links is that it's not stopping anybody from seeing their profiles. If someone wants to look at the mods profile they presumably have a good reason to want to check it out. And it's not like they're just gonna say "huh the link isn't working. Welp, now I'm truly stumped." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes thanks for that ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol they've disabled links to the moderators' profiles in the sidebar with CSS. They're so pathetic haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed - rule 11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you propose enforcing a scroll to the bottom on somebody else's website? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the Moderation Queue, the option should be available to automatically expand all the reports under the submissions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I got to the modqueue I have to press "View Reports" on each submission. I'm only there to view reports so it'd be nice if the reports were already visible. I think this should be an easy thing to do? It'd save a few clicks. Just a thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 12:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked in the royal mail package sorting centre over christmas a few years ago. You just don't want to know how little of a shit they give. Throwing packages across the warehouse, even ones clearly marked FRAGILE. Dropping them from height into containers. Flying off the end of conveyor belts and tumbling across the floor. **Put bubble wrap in your packages ffs** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 12:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still grandfathered into my 15/month truly unlimited data plan on sim-only from Three. 200 minutes which I never use and unlimited texts which I never use. I **love** the unlimited data though. They've long since stopped offering that plan but since I'm on a one-month rolling contract they just keep renewing it until I cancel, and I won't be cancelling any time soon ha. It lasted me 2 years on my iPhone 6 and I got my iPhone 7 (RIPHPJ) on launch day and continue to use the same SIM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 11:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was a *little bit* funny when someone make the same joke last week. But now it's just blatant reposting. If you're going to copy someone's joke *at least* wait a few months first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 01:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fuck. Is it cooled by quantum plasma or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 23:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those cars at [0:32](https://youtu.be/rhVZ-QIu4jk?t=32s) look as if they're up to something very evil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 16:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sigh. What's this a reference to please. My mental meme encyclopedia is out of date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 14:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can use bars (|), dashes (-), full stops (.) ^^^^lol ^^^^boob , and underscores (_). So that's at least 40^20, including alphanumerics and specials. I might have missed a special or two though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 13:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CC:

https://www.reddit.com/r/redditdev/comments/5lqaci/is_it_possible_to_get_the_list_of_all_redditors/dbxw1v2/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 13:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote this very quickly, because I was bored and it was something to do. It is incredibly lazy coding so don't judge me.

https://github.com/Theonefoster/get_all_redditors/blob/master/get_all_redditors.py

It scrapes a load of popular submissions and gathers the names of any users it sees in the submission and its comments, then iteratively scrapes the gathered user profiles for more submissions to gather users from. Should hit a pretty large portion of the userbase who have been active any time recently, or had popular submissions. Not sure how recently counts as recently but probably at least the past few weeks.

You might have to leave it running overnight... or for a few years haha. Don't forget that with praw you have to leave 2 secons per request... and this is making a HUGE number of requests. Add a login to reduce that to 1 second per request. 

Modify it as needed and then run. Or don't. I haven't really tested it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 20:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds as if it'd make for some shitty sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tend to your wounds Roleplay [Close whispers] [personal attention] [binaural] [female] [intentional] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 23:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regarding this, do you think it'd be possible to **add** the mic to Gboard? I like using dictation but I more like using gboard, which doesn't have a dictation key.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 15:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with emojis? I like them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 14:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please don't speculate about stuff like this unless you actually know the answer. This is how false information spreads and people lose jailbreaks or the ability to jailbreak etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 14:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, any consumer purchase, online or in store.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 13:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed - not in testflight beta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 03:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can filter the subreddit to show only unintentional videos using the link in the sidebar if you like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 01:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But why speed up the clip? Just makes it look fake and far less impressive. If you show it at normal speed it'd be actually impressive   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ASMR Ear Tapping and Close Up Words for Sleep and Relaxation [female] [whispered] [long] [binaural] [3dio] [tapping] [blowing] [breathing] [trigger words] [intentional] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 20:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Binaural Audio (3D Audio) Demo | VARIABLY LOUD [male] [unintentional] [scissors] [sparklers] [soft spoken] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 20:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you possibly mean the [Virtual Barbershop?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IUDTlvagjJA ab_channel=LovelyVirus) It's very popular </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed - rule 11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they say something like "hi it's susan" or similar, rather than show "from 07xxx xxxxxx" it says "Maybe: Susan". Apple say it's all done on-device and no info leaves the phone/etc so it's completely private and secure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Side note: I love iOS 10's new feature of suggesting who the contact might be based on the content of their message. At least I think it's new - I'd never seen it before a couple of months ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 16:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ordered the [960 EVO from Novatech](https://www.novatech.co.uk/products/components/harddrives-internal/ssdsolidstate/pciexpress/mz-v6e500bw.html) :D excited! Only 230 too. No delivery until Jan 20th though :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 15:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm honestly more concerned about boot times. My games mostly live on my HDD anyway so I'm not overly fussed about gaming performance. I might move Overwatch to my SSD though since I have the space and I play it a lot. 

Reason I'm looking into it is because my OCZ ARC I bought last summer is giving a lot of worrying drive errors which windows seems to have to fix frequently. My boot has been interrupted 5 times in the past couple of weeks with some text utility which says "repairing C: drive errors". It's always successful and I've not had any other problems but I'm going to replace it anyway just to be sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 15:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I thought something must be up. I'll look into benchmarks for other drives :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
