<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject322</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! We'll try that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A girl and I cannot find each other on Instagram. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, we're trying to add one another on Instagram, but when she searches me, she cannot find my username, and vice versa. We've sent screen shits back and forth too one another of the searches and its so weird.

Because, even as I'm sure some of you are thinking, she blocked me. Searching for me would still have me show up on her list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've gotten to the point where I can play everything. My speciality is specialists. Love those weirdos, and I think that has lent me to being able to play basically all other heroes competently, except for Mages. How in the world do you play mages. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Li Ming on their team, blows me up. Kael tears through our ranks, Chromie pops us like zits from the other side of the obj. But when I play anyone other than Jaina (I am okay with her) My full range orbs as ming feel like ping pong balls, my circles of doom as kael feel like hair dryers. And my raging sandstorms as Chromie more like throwing a scoop of kitty litter. 

What am I missing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 2 I placed in Plat 3. Good times, fin games even when I was loosing.

But I started to loose a lot. Dropped to silver 4.

By the end of the season I was gold, and now I'm back to plat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! Thank you! I know what my new phone background will be. Where did you find this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come outside </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The coolest comic cover I've seen in a long time. The Totally Awesome Hulk 016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Jessica Jones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 23:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you hear that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 23:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems like the obvious fix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you get "YOU HAVE BEEN DROPPED" and have no choice but to exit. (While getting the really condescending "If you leave you'll be a stupid dirty leaver and we'll all hate you" message. I might be paraphrasing.

These particular issues with the Reconnect system started with the Zarya patch as far as I can tell, and you're right. Blizzard has said nothing about this game ruining bug! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of the earliest gifs on the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I think Daredevil I think Bullseye. I've always thought of Kingpin as a Joint custody deal with Spider-man lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those of you who have been around the block awhile, you'll recognize this gif. I want Tom Holland to master this same dance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is your coffee shop in Toronto by chance? I'd be happy to patronize your establishment. So at least you get a tiny win (A new customer) out of this ordeal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reason I posted this, is because I posted a thought I had 

"It would be really interesting if Overwatch added a Heroes of the Storm fan too their roster, and they justified having Overwatch characters in heroes because Blizzard made a historic shooter based on the characters."

And because I didn't have anything in the body. It got removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think the rule that stops us from posting something without having a body too our post is silly. It's easy to start a conversation with a single title of text. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It would be really interesting if Overwatch added a Heroes of the Storm fan too their roster, and they justified having Overwatch characters in heroes because Blizzard made a historic shooter based on the characters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZatP3287-zg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 04:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is CoE? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CoeCoe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> November 11, 2011

It's been out for the better part of a decade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Level 20 Azmodan here. I now only play him on Towers of Doom where W build is super strong. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 04:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 04:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Nioh

Oh shit. This game looks rad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's an old game you wish you had, a current game you want, and a game coming out that you cannot wait for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 04:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine would be Skyrim (I doubt my rig could run the new edition, but old is fine by me.)

Current game... Hmmm... Maybe Final Fantasy XV. I've played all of the other ones.

And New would be Mass Effect. I cannot wait for it to get a sale price. 

EDIT: I'm going to add a fourth, what non existent game do you wish existed? 

Dragon Ball Fusions 2. The first game is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 04:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The video is not available. You just gave me a sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the Bleach one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi guys, I'm looking for thematic music for my Campaign. Please link some great youtube tracks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something like

When the chips are down, and you need to be heroes:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZDdq9UhTD_k

Surreal settings:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9jz644GeAdE

Happy Village:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CfH163Po8GU

It's time for a big bad:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3YNfX1oU2XA


I'll create a bunch of "Sections" like these ones, where I can quickly grab a tune when the setting changes.

Probably attributing a particular song to a particular character or town in my notes, so I can quickly reuse it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was born handsome, charming witty and wise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also a compulsive liar, but I think it evens out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there, Roleplay is the way I play. I almost never min max, unless it fits the character that he or she would be this way. So I'd be thrilled to hear more about the setting you're using, which classes and races are open, etc.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He Transitioned well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  (The kind you earn for playing the game. Not the stupid refer a friend or buy an expensive collectors edition)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want a StarCraft II promo mount, like hearthstone, WoW and Diablo all have. (The kind you earn for playing the game. Not the stupid refer a friend or buy an expensive collectors edition) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan has chosen Goku as Ambassador of the 2020 Tokyo Olypmics  /r/dbz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan has chosen Goku as Ambassador of the 2020 Tokyo Olypmics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My birthday is that month. If anyone wants to get me this game, I'll name my first generated character after you. 

If no one wants to get me this game, I'll get it off humble bundle in eight years, and play through it discovering the source of all the memes I've been seeing for the last seven years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got this prompt from a facebook screenshot of a tumblr post that was probably found on reddit. No idea who the source is, but the concept sounds great for the talented people here on r/WritingPrompts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] A woman makes a deal with a demon to bare it's child, she makes a separate deal with a witch. The witch can have her first born. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the amount of Civ V I play, Donald Trumps desire to build a great wall makes perfect sense too me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, But again. Not too my super rage monster boss on day two of knowing her after she just had a panic attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if you're being sarcastic. But I too like people's diverse sexuality being a selling point. I just like it when it's well written.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it'd be neat if they added two or three talents where when you picked a talent, let's say on tier 10, she got a Blue Bird or a Robin following her depending on her ult. And maybe like a squirrel a mouse or a rabbit on another tier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But where did this image come from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the point of permanent meta then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying its offensive. I'm saying g its poorly written. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All of these "Screenshots" on this sub are just photo shops so you can get free Karma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, obviously you disagree with me and enjoyed Tue scene, and thats good! I'm glad! But I feel very passionate about this, because I cherish these comics, and I want them to be the best they can be. That one line I found took me right out of the comic like none before. Itade me sad, that even if he's joking to make her happy, the reduced his sexuality to a punchline. The best treatment for gay characters in my opinion is no treatment. That is to say, they are just as normal as straight people, and should be treated as such. Thats the only way to normalize it. But every time we draw attention to it in a manner like this, it just screams "this is something different t and exciting/weird/funny/special" and that just helps keep it as an us and them mentality. I just want an us.

I haven't told my parents I'm Bi, because I know it'll cause a thing. Not a bad thing. But a thing. I want my kids to live in a world, where they can bring their boyfriend or girlfriend home or too the dance, and no one even cares what gender they are. That a gay relationship is just as boring as a straight one.

Ik not saying you're wrong for liking the panel, again. I'm Glad you enjoy it. The whole book is great. Just for me, I feel using it like that, in the context they did is a disservice to the character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow this is an amazing list. I especially love the Giant Mimic twist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm all for him sharing that side of himself in the right context. The context of this scene was not a bonding one though, and they don't know one another very well yet. As for "Discoving" he's gay. I think it could be something as simple as he talks about a date he went on the night before, and how great the guy was. Just common back and forth talk, rather than busting out this out of no where. I don't know if you read the issue, but myself and many others seem to feel it was placed after the fact by someone higher up than the writer. Someone just saying "Let's make sure people know we have a gay person in this comic, add this panel." Because the writing for this chracter is top notch otherwise, so that's another thing that makes it weird. He's very professional and like, just two panels before this was asked to call her by her first name. (Because, again. He works for her.)

I've met many gay people who joke around like this with their friends, or in social situations. But not in the office, helping your boss you barely know out of the building, because she just had a panic attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Running a Mercenary guild camagin for a large amount of people, suggestions on missions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, basically I live with 11 people, most of them are playing. We are party of a much larger coop where others from it will be joining in as well. Not everyone will be playing at once. People will be swapping in and out as their characters are sent on missions. 

Tonight I want to run a campaign where many members of a village have been swapped by Fae Changelings. I'll be doing a Vampire plot. An over arching one with a local cartel that will build up over many missions. (The cartel is just a nebulous force, with the main leaders being difficult to find. So they'll be bad guys for much of the filler.)

What are some fun one offs. Serious ones, funny ones, interesting ones. I'm more into story telling and roleplaying and unique battles. Using the environment and the such, rather than straight swinging. Though there will be that too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but that doesn't make the lines okay either. I like good writing, and I especially think that under represented groups need good writing to depict them. Now, the Iceman and Romeo relationship is cringe worthy in XMen, BUT that's because they're teenage boys. So it's cringe worthy in a realistic way and I love it.

THIS on the other hand, is kind of insulting. And not because of WHAT he said, but rather, HOW and WHEN it was said. Ya know? He is a very good character in ever other instance, even those immediately leading up to this point. I honestly feel this was included after the fact by someone other than the writer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god. That's awful. I read that but I didn't remember it. 

I actually like how they did him and Romeo. It's a cute young teen relationship, that just happens to also be a gay one. It really works.

But having another person declare "You're full gay" kinda takes some of the agency out of it. Like, he's his own man. I know she's a mind reader, so she CAN know. But it's shitty she took all the inner conflict and questioning out of him like that.

(Also. We need more Bi Characters. ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. Yeah. My bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 13:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suggest you buy the book. "Hulk #2" it is really good.

But for context she suffered a panic attack, he is walking her out of the building, being a supportive coworker, explaining if she ever needs anything he's here for here. Its all very well written exactly what you'd expect in that kind of delicate situation. Then, they drop this panel in as the last of their interaction. No build up, no nothing. Then nothing afterwards. She's on the street by herself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 13:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats intentional. They made it more of a skill shot to make it harder to poke with, but they buffed it in other waya </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 13:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "YOU HAVE BEEN DROPPED" 

And then being forced to restart the entire client. Whereas when you actually get dropped because of your own connection, it just recconects you like normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 13:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes yes! This is why I posted this. I WANT diversity. Much like ms marvel. I LOVE her character. But I want GOOD diversity. I want the characters treated with the same care and respect as their straight white counter parts. Like they did with Ms.Marvel. You get to see her family and her culture in a context appropriate fashion. Not just like, her declaring in one panel all the things that make her diverse and interesting.

I really love how they did her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 13:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a reference to something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 13:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She doesn't even react with humour. She takes it as a face value comment. If they made Jen laugh, even a single like, the kind of amused sigh you make when someone tells a pun, that would have been better. But the panel just feels out of sync with the rest of the story.

Thanks for bringing up Tracer by the way. Her reveal was perfect. They treated her like a normal human being, as opposed to a token or a joke like souch of media pulls on LGBTQ characters.

Tracer is my favourite modern example. No fan fare. Just her going home to her girlfriend so they can get ready to visit their gorilla buddy.

And the best thing about all of that, is NOTHING in that SENTANCES is weird because of how they treat their characters including Winston. Sure he's an ape. But he's just a nornal dude. Sure she's a lesbian, but she's just a normal lady.

Because being Gay is Normal. I'll always appreciate Blizzard for that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 13:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm... Not sure what side you're taking here.

I'm saying this as a man who enjoys the occasional penis, that I want BETTER inclusion.

This character, is really good. And had they just approached him like a human being, instead of their token gay character, he'd have made an amazing token gay character.  Instead, now he feels like he was put in just to check off a box and that makes me sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 13:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To a boss you barely know, coming down from a panic attack, that you know has super powers based on anger? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think posts about this bug need to make it to the front page every time they come up. Because it's NOT on your end when you get this "You have been dropped" Bug, that only lets you leave and restart the game.

When it's on your end it reconnects like normal. And Blizzard HAS NOT acknowledged this yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amadeus is "The Totally Awesome Hulk" But the "Hulk" on going stars Jennifer Walters, She-Hulk.

HAH I'd love it if he was a Super Gay Symbiote. That'd be awesome.

He's in it before, as a well written character. A Coworker, a subordinate who is professional and cares about his boss. Then the crapped out that panel for some reason. Very out of the blue for his character. I fell like it was less a writer's choice, and more of a "We need Diversity. Make him say he's gay" choice from the higher ups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 20:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think "Super Gay Secretaries" would be the we he was referring too. 

Either that, or he and Jen. The writing for that panel doesn't flow very well with the rest of the issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a Bisexual man, this is NOT how you do inclusive writing (Hulk #2 MINOR Spoilers. One panel. Has literally nothing to do with anything in the story. And that's what makes me so angry.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is a huge bummer. But oh well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Matience is over, you can play now. Also, the two cool mounts are locked into bundles. Again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wanted both the Nimbus and Felsaber, but I don't like any of the heroes or skins included in their bundles. It's a real bummer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Matience is over, you can play again. Also. No way to get Nimbus or Felsaber outside of very expensive bundles. I can't be the only one who wishes Bliz would let us get these rad mounts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had to put down my dog because of how annoying he was </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was on the phone with my mum and he just kept wiggling around and getting in my face, so I needed to put him down on the floor for the rest of the phone call. 

I love my dog but he just doesn't understand phone etiquette.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Exactly! 

And I bet you won that game by a landslide following that. 

Even if you're way behind before that moment. The chance they could come back is so far away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/plumbing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Snoo for r/plumbing tho </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mean that Azmodan is pushing uncontested. But he can beat anyone solo lane if done right, and it's not even strictly Azmo. It's whomever you have as off lane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taking a fort that's almost dead on Towers of Doom, immediately undoes a lot of work your Spec spent setting it up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 19:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. So let's paint a picture here.

Top lane is fine. Full wall, all that noise.

Mid is missing a tower, but other wise good.

Your spec has pushed bottom too within an inch of it's life. Literally one Azmo-dunk could kill it three times over right now.

Azmo, is now in the top lane and asks you not to push bottom.

The reason for this is, if you take bottom lane the enemies can take it back right away. By the time Azmo gets the top wall down, the enemy will have reclaimed their fort. BUT

If you let Azmo take top, then take bottom right away, now you're two forts up, your enemy has a lot less terrain they can use safely when rotating into the Obj, and even if they take an Obj it'll do 2 less damage. 

Now, while they're trying to take back one of the two, you're able to defend it as a team, while Azmo takes mid. Ideally you'll be able to get 2 or 3 damage off from owning all the towers, But more likely than not they'll take the one you're defending, or rotate and take the other one back. 

But that still leaves you 2 forts up, and you can keep this going for a good long while, taking objs in the mean while. 

Bonus: Boss is better for finishing the game, than it is for getting you momentum. Take a fort and continue your winning snowball. Boss completely losses you any forward momentum you had, and even sets you up for a team wipe if done at the wrong team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say she is without a doubt, I'm just curious what hints there have been? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 13:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes you think Vados is evil? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I heard the computer game, Shandalar, was really good. How can I play it in this day and age? Is there a modded version with any more modern cards? (I didn't start playing until Onslaught, so it'd be neat to see some of those cards hanging around.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 14:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 20:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad someone else had fun with the joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah. I love murky. He's one of my favourite, one of the best heroes. Just Terrific. My Murky play is at the top of Grand Master. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I mean, that last bit probably isn't something America would invest in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make Auir Great again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everyone, it is I, Tassadar. 

With my new remake, and all the discussion happening here, I just wanted to take this opportunity to present myself as a new candidate for President of Space.

As a major point for my platform, I want to propose building a Force Wall, and Making Nexico pay for it. These Nexicans, people of the nexus, when they send us their players, they don't send us their best. They send us their Feeders, their Nova mains, and Murky troll picks. Some of whom though, I assume, are support mains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People are always talking about the insane amount of money the US spends on Millitary, if all of that money was instead invested in other things, what reasonable, or ridiculous things could have been done instead? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 01:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not complaining about my win rate, I'm having fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I'm at 200 won 200 lost pergame. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 19:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the Gay Police officers who enjoy participating in this parade to show that there are gay members of the community who also protect the community who are no banned from participating in this celebration as their career?

It's literally telling them to keep quiet about who they are or they'll be excluded and shunned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Mildly interesting] I have a perfect 50/50 winrate for the last 12 games, since I've entered plat 5 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.imgur.com/z7SjKjI.png

I'm thinking I should just not play Melee characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 18:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you having fun/enjoy the content? 

If no it is below your standards, proceed to complain.

If you get upvoted, people agree, if you don't people disagree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if I recall it was really strong with a short range </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's saying devs shouldn't be above scrutiny when something they push out is below standards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to solo lane as him now you need to take the mana ablity so you can self spam shields and storms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Spiderman and Doctor strange in the MCU together, maybe we can get this scene in the last Tom Holland Spiderman movie, or maybe an after credit sting in one of the avengers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 07:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's disgraceful people are downvoting this. This is a persistant bug that has been effecting the community since the Zarya patch and should be on the front page every day, because neither here, in this subreddit, nor in the offical Blizzard forums, has there been a comment on it by one of the blues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 13:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Both exist in the comics and have very different properties. Captain America's shield is one of the few things that's made of a hybrid of the two. (A feat commonly thought impossible.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 13:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This! This is what I mean! 

Sherlock is a damaged man, John is such a close friend, his first since his childhood. When John goes to Mary he thinks he's loosing his friend, but a man cannot be vulnerable without it being gay love. So obviously his relapse is because he's in love with John and not because he's feeling abandoned by a friend starting a new chapter of his life.

That's the one song we know he wrote, and he IS a virgin. 

Yeah, of course the equate it. Because Sherlock is not close to ANYONE until John comes along, and then Sherlock becomes very close to him. 

This is what hurts me about this. This is what I mean by toxic masculinity. Obviously the must be gay because they cannot possibly be emotionally vulnerable. This kind of thing makes me sick, as a man with feelings, who wants to have the kind of close friendship I see in Sherlock. I know I will probably never have it, because of the way our society views Male Vulnerability.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 12:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't remember the girlfriend thing, but I always got from it that Irene was teasing John </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All this talk about how the gay jokes were offensive, offends me as a Bi man. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 11:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I, like many of you just finished Sherlock and I've run straight to this subreddit to to revel in the series. (Surprised to find the ending so reviled, but that's a whole other thing for another thread.)

But one thing that I really dislike, are the people running around saying "The gay jokes wouldn't have been as offensive if they were true in the end" but I honestly think they would have been.

You see, I don't know if this is what the writers intended, but I've always seen those jokes as a way of the writers drawing attention to toxic masculinity. What I mean by that is, any kind of intimacy between two men is immediately open to speculation on whether or not they're gay. 

If you're close, vulnerable, gentle, kind, caring or any number of other things with a close male companion. Obviously you've got to be a fairy, because real men would never behave in such a manner.

But what we're seeing in Sherlock, is two broken men who have a deep fondness for one another. Both strong male characters with many flaws and many more redeeming qualities.  And the people in their community constantly think they're gay. Obviously we all have a laugh at it, because that's the culture we grew up in.(And fuck, it is funny afterall.) But it makes them both uncomfortable. Because they're not. And there is nothing wrong with being uncomfortable with being mistake for the wrong sexuality. 

It's not Homophobic to say, I prefer ladies to gentlemen. But if you insist that a gay man is straight and just going through a phase, that's obviously bigoted and ignorant. 

So, the show plays on the fact that two hetro guys are uncomfortable being confused for homosexual, and it is funny to see people uncomfortable in a T.V show context, but people think the jokes are Homophobic? Instead of drawing attention to the fact that in real life those same conclusions would be drawn? Instead of drawing attention to the fact our society does not allow men to be the kind of friends who "love" each other. Who get on and finish each others sentences? To take it too the extreme, I'd honestly love to just have a platonic guy friend I could cuddle with up on the couch to watch movies. Because it's nice to be close to another human being. But that will almost certainly never happen.

But lady friends and I don't mean of the romantic variety? Oh hell yeah. Let's climb up into each others arms and weep openly when some sad shit happens. (Though I better only allow one or two tears to escape to show that I am vulnerable and human, but not ugly cry because then I'm a little boy and a lesser man.)

So yeah. In conclusion, I always thought the gay jokes were a wonderfully funny shot at Toxic Masculinity and that the show was really doing a service to guys who might desire an intimacy with other men that doesn't lead to a sneaky handjob under the table at a seedy bar.


  
OBVIOUSLY I could be wrong, I'm no Sherlock myself. Maybe I'm reading into these jokes in the wrong way. But goddamn if I'm not glad they exist in this fashion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 08:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vibranium only stops things with energy or momentum. He could easily slowly pull his arms apart.

There's a scene in one of the punisher comics, where a guy uses an energy shield with the same properties as Vibranium and brags that nothing the Punisher hits him with will every be able to penetrate it, so the Punisher "Laments" the fact that he'll need to slowly inch his knife through the shield repeatedly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make Ultralisk great again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 06:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As we all know Ultralisk isn't exactly in a great spot right now. It's stupid squishy, and doesn't do a ton of damage. 

Allow me to suggest some upgrades.

First! When you choose it, and then summon it. It gains a TLV like control scheme. No more needing to manually click on the map in it's location.

NEXT give it a burrow charge, like you can upgrade into in the main starcraft game. This will give it a stun, and a way to chase. (Think Anubarak. Basically the same thing.) 

Now, at level 20, let players choose Tarrasque, which does the same as usual.

OR Noxious. Which basically gives the Ultra a slow/damage over time effect.

Those changes plus a little health buff and maybe Baseline Physical Armour, would make Ultra a great Niche pick truly worth of the Queen of blades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 06:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Tarrasque baseline! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 04:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys, level 17 TLV player here, can flex into any role.

ETC and Diablo for tanks
Sonya, Artanis and Thrall for Brusiers
Kerrigan and Illidan for Melee DPS
Kharazim and Morales for Support
Valla, Raynor, Sylvanas, Lunara, Zul Jin, Tracer for ranged DPS
Zagara and Azmodan for split lanes
Xul and Murky for double soaking on BHB and TOMB
Leoric, Zarya. Butcher, Abathur and Cho for situational flex picks

And of course, TLV for winning on just about every map

https://www.hotslogs.com/Player/HeroOverview?PlayerID=611405
Alabaster#1763 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chair league looking for team thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 04:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're looking for a team, post your info here. If you're looking for players, post your requirements. Let's make this the best season of Chair league yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OR. You could let people complain about things they don't like in an online game that constantly gets updates, so the Devs can see these complaints realize HOW big of an issue it is for the community, and allow it to work for positive change, in that direction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well. That's the real reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I love the AA build. If they have a lot of squishy heroes, I take Banshee, but I usually grab Hyperion for the Zoning potential. If your team is being chased, fire Hyperion down the path you'll be running, that way it follows you and gives you covering fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. I always go with the two Assimilation talents plus the ravage heal, just to feel like I can keep myself alive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She stabs people with them, when she jumps super high, she also uses them to grip walls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's super fulfilling once you nail it.

A tip for the laning phase, never attack enemy minions. Just auto the enemy hero.

If it's Zagara, kill the Hydra, then go back to autoing them but don't chase. 

Just try to zone them out of xp soak range. Like, the furtherst you should ever stand is at the back of their minion wave. Your extra range allows you to dance at the edge of their sanity  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAh yeah she's stressful
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man. Auriel gets me too. Like. I've seen AMAZING auriels, and I just don't... Get it? Like. HOW are you healing that much? 

It's incredible. She's probably my worst support, and that's saying something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah. Anyone's Micro is easy in lane or on camps. But when you're in a 5v5 it's hectic as hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... And how is producing a tank every 15 seconds different from grabbing mercs on re-spawn?

Or efficiently soaking XP or Bribe stacks different from harvesting resources? 

Moving to capture an Altar different than building a vulnerable expansion? 

Or capturing a warhead different than building one?

Macro is a very important part of Heroes of the storm. A purely Micro game would be something like Geometry wars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You DO need to micro them, but I'm talking about knowing when it's best to have Olaf grabbing the siege camp or being in lane, when it's best to have Baelog holding the objective or in the team fight, when you should have Eric in a bush to scout, or gathering globes.

TLV has a lot of Macro knowledge necessary to pull them off. I find their Micro is much easier than Illidan's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the hero that you find most "stressful" to play as? But not necessarily the hardest. Just the one that really winds you up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, it is a tie between Illidan and TLV. Both very different, TLV you need lots of Macro skill to control the three vikings and have them where they need to be, but Illidan is very Micro. If you're not making the most of every single moment of a fight, you're losing sustain and probably dying.

You gotta hit as many people as you can with your W, use your Q to pull yourself out of skill shots instead of moving so you don't waste an Auto attacks (Though knowing when to stutter step is a whole other thing)

I just had a TLV game, followed by an Illidan game and I just want a nice and easy Towers of Doom Azmodan game to help me relax.

EDIT: Just qued into a Garden of Terror. TLV ahoy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 20:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ANAD? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 07:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. 

It's the same with my Wonder Billie. If Blizzard wanted to re-release her I'd be just fine with that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 06:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you had it for two years longer than everyone else who got it. They never said they'd not re-release these things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? Haha

I'd like to think my advice is the advice you'd use MOST of the time on the map. But I know it's not an all the time thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. Everyone seems to be piling in here with their "Umm well actually you're stupid" comments and bringing up the specific scenarios in which it is better to get the boss.

This is obviously not a comprehensive strategy guide for Towers of Doom. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm proud to say I have 100% winrate as Azmodan on that map. I mean, I'm level 20 with him, so I'm probably not an average Azmo player. But I still get excited everytime I see that map. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol again, I think antagonize him was wrong. But fucking savage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously if you cannot see them they are back at Core. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. The two closest looking things are Warcraft mounts. The eyepad for the old gods, and the Legion exclusive donkey demon wolf thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I am u/keypaw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I learned this in customer service </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's usually true. Obviously if he tilts this easily he loses a lot of games, but he's still at your rank? He's doing something right.

I never thought of it like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually a great idea for a new style of mount. Spheres. 

Zagara shoots banelings, btw. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fzMhh8zhTiY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. I often find it turns around if you can convince them to stop, and your way is the best way too. The only problem is, they don't all listen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 14:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you're in the situation that I discuss and there's nothing you can do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 14:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was not expecting any gold, thank you kindly. Truth be told I assumed I'd be downvoted into obscurity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 12:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other three who are hoping that 20% will pay off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 12:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. They can stop the bullshit just by being quiet but they wont silence their own sense of justice. That way they're the "good guy" mean while the other three just lost a game so the other person could feel like he fought the good fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 11:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that your official title? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 11:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, just summed up my entire rant in two lines. Well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 10:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dragonshire is the bomb. I love it. I always take the Eric stealth at level 1, and sit him on the furthermost corner of the dragon shrine. It's hilarious to watch people attempt to capture it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 10:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not what I'm saying at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 10:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is replies like this that make me love posting these kinds of threads. I see people like you and I can just say to myself "This guy gets it" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 09:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Very much so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 09:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I think so too. This post is just going out to those ones that provoke the trolls even further. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 09:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And momentum. That's the key there. You're up a fort, while they're taking it you can take a different fort, they're doing less damage on shrines, they have less room to run away or circle around for attacks. 

It's not so much the damage benefits, as the strategic ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 09:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just my line of trying to convince people that if you need to say it, wait until everything is done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 09:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OR. You can say sorry and not mean it to get on with your life, because taking some righteous stand and losing the game is not worth it. A good skill to have is to learn how to pick your battles. I don't feel like chewing out some random over the internet for a bad choice that he could have made for any number of reasons, making his day worse, leading him to make my day worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 09:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. My advice is obviously not a catchall. No advice is, there'll always be times you need to use critical thinking. But by and large, this is good advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
