<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3318</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When have you ever broken the law/rules, because it was the right thing to do.  What happened?  What would have happened?  
Thank you for what you do!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> who was/ is the lady in front of Sen Danes telling him parliamentary procedure and what to say. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Senator Steve Daines had an altercation with Senator Warren.   The entire time the was a lady in front of Sen Danes telling him parliamentary procedure and what to say.   Who is that lady and what is their position in the Senate?? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a  Casualty Assistance Calls Officer (CACO) assigned to the family whom is contacted and serves as a liaison between the government and the family. The CACO is the official representative of the Secretary of the Navy who provides information, resources, and assistance to the next of kin.  Their full-time responsibility and mission is to assist families during a difficult time and ensure they receive the benefits and entitlements due.  The CACO would have to be contacted to relay the information to the family and respect their wishes.(visit or not)     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How does filibuster work in the United States Congress. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was under the impression that some blowhard talks forever and when he is tired of talking they vote. (Just a waiting game) 
A reporter tried explaining that rule changes can be made and filibusters can be ended or extended.
I sense this is a tall order to fill so I appreciate your attempts.  The Supreme Court Nominee prompted this question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does the bailiff "Byrd" on Judge Judy make the participants leave their paperwork on their podium when they walk out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time the case is over when "Byrd" is escorting the participants out of Judge Judy's court room he tells then to leave all of their paperwork on the table they were standing at.  Anybody know why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All, watch those ridiculously low used prices on Amazon. (Usually say text us for availability) I decided to nibble on the bait and they wanted me to send Apple store cards or the like for payment.  Scam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 06:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boom!  Thank you TubeSteak.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: If gold is more valuable than silver then why are higher ranking U.S. officers collar devices in the military (colonel's generals) silver and lower ranks (major, ensign) gold? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 06:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 00:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, when I read "convicted felon" I thought he spent it with Martha Stewart.  That was close. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 03:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not Masonic -  I am a Master Mason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: When/where do race car drivers practice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 02:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way I see things is there are a lot of cars and only a few race tracks.  So, lets say a race car driver wants to race Le Mans.  Is there time throughout the year the driver gets to practice, or do they get a few practice laps and go for the win? Are the drivers that good that they can jump on a track after a few runs and compete? How do they get that good in general?  What about the next race track in the circuit  is there a race to get to Qatar (for instance) and get some time in?  Is practice time related to how much you pay?
Bonus - if you would please.....How do the track folks know if you warrant time on the track?   If "Billy" thinks he has the "right stuff" can he just walk up and enter a race with the money and a car that meets specs and race.  Is there a certification or something like a permit to race?  

Thank you everyone!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 15:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being big = Being mean.   Think Shreck.  Im a big guy, not fat(well a little belly).  I realize that peple automatically think I am mean and unapproachable when in fact I love having fun, talking to people and joking around.  Im told I am very kind as well.  I will do anything to help someone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was sleep apnea a known health concern in the past. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 14:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that sleep apnea is prevalent today in part due to obesity.  With that said, I see many fit persons with sleep apnea.   How long ago was sleep apnea first diagnosed and written about?  Is sleep apnea genetic?  Is it a flaw in our anatomical design?  In the past have people suffered from and expired from sleep apnea as much as it appears they do now?  Any thoughts on SIDS and a possible relationship to sleep apnea due to infant anatomic flaws that we were not aware of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 03:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CN, ordinary tear gas. The chemical name for CN is chloroacetophenone. Chloroacetophenone (CN), the active ingredient of Mace, is a riot control or tear agent used by the military (military designation CN) and law enforcement. It is also available to the general public. The United States considers agent CN and its mixtures with various chemicals to be obsolete for military deployment. Chloroacetophenone (CN) has a sharp, irritating odor (sometimes described as "apple blossoms" odor). It may be dissolved in a solvent.  
There are two issues, the grenade explosion blast (like a really big big firecracker, ) and the flash that opens it and the release of the Gas.   Your neighbors won't be happy.  In a sealed can shouldn't be that dangerous, keep away from fire/heat.

Google image search "M25A1 CN grenade"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 01:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> purley coincidental </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shelf for inside fridge/freezer  vents go toward the back?  Best Guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 01:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You're worth it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
