<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3232</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But we know a lot about the biology about cancer. We don't a lot about the biology of schizophrenia.

I've been reading a lot of your comments in this post--I'm currently completing the final year of my doctorate in psychology, and I have to say I think you might just not be aware of how much we actually know about schizophrenia. I also think you're confusing schizophrenia with general psychosis--your OP title really should have written "psychosis free" rather than "schizophrenia free."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There needs to be a preliminary diagnosis, which can be a rule out diagnosis (which is not official). If the insurance company wishes, they can request the full report to see how that conclusion was drawn, but they do not refuse to pay for an eval based on the result that was found. 

For example, you might see someone get an "adjustment disorder" diagnosis, or a r/o of generalized anxiety, or something like that. You have to illustrate that you came to a conclusion based on your findings, but that doesn't always mean a major psychiatric diagnosis like bipolar disorder or schizophrenia. And ethically speaking, we as psychologists are not allowed to use managed care to dictate our clinical findings. So if someone literally has nothing wrong with them mentally, we might note a v. code for environmental or familial stressors, and we might list a rule out if we're on the fence about something, but we're never going to diagnose someone with something for "insurance money." We bill for an eval, what the eval finds is neither here nor there. And really, the purpose of an eval is to come up with some kind of diagnostic conclusion and recommendations for treatment, so it's part of the job to come up with a diagnosis *if clinically indicated*. If you work with practitioners who provide diagnoses to make insurance companies happy, you should probably report them because they're not practicing ethically. What's your work setting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be referred to officially as "psychotic disorder due to another medical condition."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the Dr. doesn't get any $$ if they fail to provide a diagnosis. 

Where did you get this information? Because that's not how it's worked any of the places I've worked, including the psychological testing agency that currently employs me. My supervisor, for example, is a licensed psychologist who gets paid whether she provides one of the major diagnoses or not. So I'm curious why you have this belief? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, schizophrenia is one of those diagnoses that should not be applied unless numerous things are ruled out first. CT scans are not standard, but would be recommended in cases of signs of neurological symptoms (severe headaches, dizziness, numbness, balance problems, sudden changes in personality). Schizophrenria is not sudden--its onset is gradual and it is degenerative. A responsible psychologist or psychiatrist wouldn't diagnose it without extensive family, medical, and developmental history. That said, I've definitely seen it misdiagosed, particularly in cases of drug intoxication. 

No responsible professional should see psychosis and jump to diagnosing schizophrenia right away, is what I'm saying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you, but I'm referring to how the diagnostic system is set up now. For better or worse, mental health issues are viewed as distinct from medical conditions. Now IMO, they're all part of the same ball of wax. 

The working theory is that the pathology of schizophrenia is associated with alterations in glutamate, dopamine, GABA, acetylcholine, and serotonin neurotransmitters of the brain, but beyond that there's still a lot to figure out with regards to the etiology of schizophrenia.  

I was speaking to the way the system is set up now--we diagnose using specific criteria, and in order to meet the criteria for a diagnosis of schizophrenia, the clinician must first rule out, to the best of their ability, medical complications that cause psychosis. 

Now the problem with that, of course, is you can't rule out everything  100% of the time. However, a responsible clinician will take family history, and take a full developmental history--I genuinely wonder if that happened with the guy in the OP. Typically schizophrenia will start and progress differently from psychosis due to a brain tumor. He was clearly misdiagnosed--which to me just speaks to how careful people need to be with not casually applying the diagnosis of schizophrenia. I work in the field and while I've seen plenty of cases I would be very hesitant to give that diagnosis without extensive background information.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To get what exactly? Shot up with haldol and held for 23 hours? What, exactly, do you think a person diagnosed with schizophrenia "gets?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How'd you guess? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are missing the point--if someone is diagnosed with schizophrenia and turns out to have a brain tumor, then that diagnosis is *wrong* by definition. It's a misdiagnosis. 

Now, are people misdiagnosed with schizophrenia? Definitely. I've seen it happen, as I work in the field. I see it most often with drug users, and sometimes in cases of PTSD. But that's a different conversation--the person in the OP never had schizophrenia, they had psychotic symptoms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right...and if *they* also have brain tumors or other medical complications, then they're misdiagnosed as well. 

I'm just going based on the DSM 5, which is what we use to diagnose at this point--it's not perfect by any means. In fact, there are numerous flaws with the way diagnoses are assessed and applied, IMO. But that's a different conversation. A person with a brain tumor whose psychosis goes away after surgery did not technically meet the criteria for schizophrenia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, thank you! I haven't cooked a tritip to that temp before, but yours looks great. Do you have any trouble finding that cut in your area? I'm in Texas and it's not nearly as easy to pick up here as it is in CA, for example.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, all that sweet sweet insurance money. 

Trust me, mental health coverage is abysmal. The honey pot dried up years ago, and people with chronic, degenerative mental illnesses like schizophrenia are pretty screwed in this country from the POV of coverage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very nice! Technique? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even better, heat it up and pour it over your ice cream.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's not. One of the diagnostic criteria for schizophrenia is that the psychosis is *not* caused by an organic condition such as a brain tumor, tertiary syphilis, etc. To be more accurate, the OP should write "psychosis free." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the best steaks I've had in a long time was a sirloin at Bohanan's in San Antonio, which is IMO is a very good steakhouse. If it's quality meat that's skillfully prepared, it's going to be good. I hate steak snobs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frozen spinach is a godsend. I add it to meatloaf, meatballs, casseroles, egg dishes, stuffed peppers, stews--it's a great way to pack more vegetables into your meals and it's cheap. My baby is still on the fence about sauteed spinach and will sometimes spit it out, but he has no qualms about eating a turkey meatball with spinach in it, or a risotto with spinach in it, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it on either seeded rye or pumpernickel, 85/15, one thin patty, bread toasted both sides, caramelized onions, cheddar, jack, or hoop cheese, no sauce, and a mix of butter and mayo on the outside when you grill it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pleb meat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, give it a rest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's a question of class. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, are you surprised "xX420GanjaWarlordXx" is acting like a tool? I'm not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it doesn't look like anything I'd want to eat, TBH, and I love sweet potatoes. I'd rather just eat a normal brownie and enjoy that. 

However, I made up a recipe for light blondies made with white bean puree, and they're freaking delicious. Sounds weird, but it's delicious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a snap! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fellow Texan here. Stop it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's a gluten free, vegan thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm all for making fun of food pedantry, it's one of my favorite things--but calling sausage lumps "meatballs" is just inaccurate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC in the movie he talks about making the sauce and then adds the sausage *and* the meatballs. So he has both in the movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. I'm off to go make some budget pizza by melting Kraft singles on some matzoh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that's not how meatballs are usually made. That's like saying you make meatloaf by dumping it into a pan, forming it into a log and baking it. That's a loaf of meat, but it's not how people usually make meatloaf.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also uses actual meatballs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And for anyone interested, you should also check out [Our Man Flint](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lQwJQkEh2QY), a spy parody with James Coburn that Austin Powers already draws a bit of inspiration from.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, why not just buy ground sausage rather than buying it encased and then squeezing it out of the casing? It should actually be cheaper if you buy it loose. Also, I remember the Godfather's dish had sausage *and* meatballs.

Second, these are not meatballs. If anyone is interesting in actually knowing how to make mean meatballs, check out [this recipe for Rao's meatballs](http://www.huffingtonpost.com/food-52/raos-genius-meatballs_b_3497027.html). Nothing beats Rao's for that kind of thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what the commenter means with all the Irish stereotypes, but I also thought it was kind of a cute and I liked all the cameos of famous Irish people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit OP, you can't post drama if you're involved in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Richard_Fist! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* You may only post links if you are not the source of the drama or directly involved in the drama. Do not submit drama you have commented in



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slapfight in /r/PopHeads over Ed Sheeran's new video, and someone starts throwing shade in Gaelic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Green hat yourself, noob.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try cardamom pods, whole cloves, and a bay leaf. I love the aroma of the rice when it's done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can repost it as a self post and then you can provide multiple links in the text.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, I anticipated some backlash--if and when this blows up beyond a handful of comments, it can and should be resubmitted. It's just that, as it stands now, there isn't enough meat on the bone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Blahrgy! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* There is not enough drama to merit an SRD submission.  Please wait and see if things develop further, or look for a subthread with more drama. Make sure you're linking with the proper context.

Events such as "X sub was hacked" or "Y sub was made private" are not drama in and of themselves - do not just link to a subreddit that was taken over. If there are dramatic happenings around the takeover, please make a self post and include links to drama that users can read.



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Capcuck! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* You linked directly to the full comments of a submission.  This  submission actually does merit an exception that rule, but as per the sidebar it must be submitted in a self post.

If you're unsure how this is done, check out our [wiki](/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules#wiki_submitting_self_posts_and_write-ups)



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so easy, he could totally stop his addiction to being an asshole if he wanted to, but he doesn't want to, because he *loves* being an asshole! 

More than a few of the real addicts I treated when I worked in rehab actually used this same logic when they were still struggling with denial. "I love drinking! It's who I am! I'm a party animal! Things are fine!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consistency is, indeed, key. There's a difference between using a spanking as a consequence and abusing a child. I'm not a proponent of spanking specifically because the bulk of the research doesn't back it up as being more effective than behavior training. And while it can be an effective deterrent, it's usually only effective for a very narrow age range. I see too many parents trying to use spanking with older children or even adolescents, and that simply does not work--and it's bad for the parent-child relationship. 

The most effective way to discipline kids is to praise the desired behaviors and ignore or correct the undesired behaviors. Once children get old enough to understand consequences, you can start taking away things they want when they make poor behavior choices. But again, you have to meet the kid where they're at in terms of their development. You can't expect a four-year-old to not behave like a four-year-old. So if you have a kid throwing a tantrum, understand that it happens, but don't reinforce it by giving attention. "Active ignoring" as it's called is *amazingly* effective with younger kids--way more so than spanking their bottoms, IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For ice: Put the ice in a large ziploc bag, then wrap it in towel, then pound away with your mallet. I've done it before and it worked fine. 

For meat, I don't think you have much to worry about, it doesn't take long to pound it. Feel free to make a masturbation joke there if you want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giordano's? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chicago, Illinois, United States.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard that episode but that was one of those tidbits I've known for a while--it's part of the lore of that movie, along with him eating a live roach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's cringeworthy to be sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's right up there with [Anatole Broyard](http://www.frenchcreoles.com/Broyard_Anatole_head_300.jpg).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My god, nice crust. Twice fried?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't remember all the posts made about him, but [this will get you started](https://www.reddit.com/r/SubredditDrama/comments/34e82d/with_great_privilege_comes_great_responsibility/?st=j29r664m sh=fa1da903) plus the related [drama post](https://www.reddit.com/r/Drama/comments/34gogi/so_it_started_when_i_posted_my_daughter_sagan_to/?st=j29r542w sh=ea3ea689).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right--the jerk store called and they said they were out of me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kick to red radishes is not the same as chili peppers--it's a different sort of heat. It's caused by allyl isothiocyanate, a sulfur compound. Think the compounds released when you chop onions. Allyl isothiocyanate is also found in horseradish and spicy mustard, so that's the kind of heat I'm talking about. They definitely have a bite to them--maybe you're just not particularly sensitive to it, but it's there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, it's more of a personal beef. His tendency to post other people's food is actually one of the reasons /r/food started to add the "homemade" tag requirement. He would post pictures he took from other people's blogs and then not answer any of the questions about how it was made or what was in it. So I took issue with that, and I criticized him for it--and then mysteriously I found out that I had been banned from /r/UpliftingNews, a sub I had never commented in or posted in, but a sub that he's a mod of. Hmmm. And my modmails to them were ignored. So I contacted the mod above him on the mod list personally and they unbanned me, stating it must have been a mistake. But I don't think it was. 

Anyway, I think he's a big old obnoxious karma whore, and a defensive one at that. I think he's worse than Gallowboob, actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh it was the "rose in the glass" routine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't grammar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [NSFW](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Penile_fracture). It's a rupture of the blood vessels due to trauma during erection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're creating an imaginary distinction. Gnocchi is very similar to spaetzle--and there are plenty of gnocchi recipes that call for egg. Different cultures have different names for potato dumplings, and there are many iterations of potato dumplings out there. I'm really confused as to what your issue is with this recipe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is some *very* tomato-heavy butter chicken. Naan looks great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if I were making it, I'd throw in some thinly sliced radish as well, because I like the spicy, refreshing radish with the crispy, fatty chicken.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edited.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once saw a mentally ill man put a young woman's *hand in his mouth* on the L. It happened so fast, he came up to her and smiled and she smiled back and I thought "oh shit, no, don't look at the guy, keep your head down" but it was too late--he took her hand and she looked confused and then bam, into his mouth. 

I've also seen people selling crack pipes on the train, which IMO is way more offensive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I know exactly who I'm talking to. Hence my first comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Made from 100% repurposed crash test dummies and recycled medical waste." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I walked through the set of Prison Break when they were shooting downtown by accident once (near the Fannie Mae building), and took a bagel off the Craft table.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you remember this guy--he's the one who posts videos of himself and his wife laughing at Reddit comments, and he made a huge deal about pushing his kid into STEM, and he generally struggles with relating to people in a healthy way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that sub. It really makes me appreciate my MIL.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure why you keep addressing me directly, I'm not obese nor do I have a problem with overeating. 

I was just pointing out that just like you have difficulty with your social behaviors, some people have difficulty with their eating behaviors. They're not stuck like that, they can always work to make positive changes, but these people need empathy, not shaming. Do you respond well to being shamed for your social difficulties? Somehow I doubt it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohh, I see--so when something directly affects you, your behavior is out of your control, but when it's something that doesn't affect you, then it's 100% someone's fault. Got it.

Anyway, I'm sure you're just here to try to bait a dumb argument as you are wont to do, so I won't engage you further.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I mean social ineptitude is also something you can control, in theory, but lots of people still struggle with that, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, you don't want to slide out. Penile fractures are no joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A great example of the urban phenomenon is seen in the film *Vampire's Kiss* with Nicholas Cage. In the scene in which he runs down the street screaming "I'm a Vampire!" at the top of his lungs, there were no hired extras--the people on the street in that scene are just bystanders who didn't know they were in a movie, and who genuinely do not react to Nicholas Cage screaming about being a vampire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He states:

I'm fighting an upper-respiratory infection that keeps me house-bound. No, I don't have anything better to do.

He's got [the consumption](http://looking-for-mabel.webs.com/009%2007%20JUL%20PIXS/fading-away1858.jpg). Lots of brilliant writers had it. Balzac, Chekhov, Camus, Keats--and now DJLinFL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh jeez, I'm sorry, I misread your comment--I thought you wrote " remember my dad smacking me, that's why I do it to my kid." I apologize for misunderstanding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And is there a more pathetic redditor than gallowboob?? Just in general I mean.

Maybe iBleeedorange, or maybe the people who aspire to be like Gallowboob but fail. Other than that, I can't think of any. And ~~Maybe~~ definitely the incel guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, you're right:

"Molded directly from 2007 Penthouse Pet of the Year Heather Vandeven, this Pet Pussy features a sexy doggie-style pose that allows for easy penetration of the vaginal or anal openings. Hand grips ensure security, and the removeable multi-speed bullet provides vibration if desired. The best feature is the Cyberskin Virtual Touch texture, which is amazingly life-like--especially with the hand-painted detail. Requires 2 AA batteries, not included."

Hand-painted detail!  This copy makes *me* want to get one. 

Speaking of which, I'd pay good money to see this kind of thing getting sold on QVC in the middle of the night. "Look at this beautiful hand-painted detail around the asshole, it's just so special and deals like this won't last." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The ass you can really get behind!"

The marketing takes care of itself, really.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your eyelid is overlapping your asshole and giving you a shitty outlook on life. Have the nurse change your diaper.

I feel like his comments were actually written by a random insult generator.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I wanted to look up the product to see how the company describes it, but I'm paranoid about looking that up in my workplace (where we treat victims of child abuse).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree! I think a chipwich is a sandwich, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commenter in /r/PettyRevenge gives a confusing critique of OP's writing clarity, proceeds to argue with anyone who disagrees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you're being facetious, but that really is how this stuff trickles down. There's something fundamentally *wrong* with parents who derive amusement from the suffering of their children--and, at the risk of getting too psychodynamic, I think it betrays some disruption in attachment in the parent's upbringing as well. They weren't nurtured consistently, or supported emotionally--something went wrong. And now their kids are going to deal with their own baggage from it. Here's hoping the bio mother has a more stable head on her shoulders--although I'm not so sure. I've definitely seen custody situations where the bio mom got screwed and an abusive dad got custody, but those are the minority of cases. Chances are if she lost custody in the first place she might have her own issues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calling online leftist communities, or online right wing communities, or any other group, "batshit insane" is not against the rules of our sub. Familiarize yourself with the rules, and don't come in here trying to start a fight. If someone calls you names or otherwise insults you directly in here, that's against the rules. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please report where someone told you to shut the fuck up and those comments will be removed as well. 

Attacking your argument is not against the rules. Directly insulting the person your speaking to is. Attack the argument but not the person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are pissin me off talking about this like they grew up in a bubble. I remember my parents yelling at me - I remember my parents messing with me - I remember fighting with my brother - and yet somehow, not to toot my own horn, I turned out great.

I'm so sick of people bending over backwards to justify the maltreatment of children. The psychological abuse of those kids is *not* justifiable. I see what this kind of treatment does to kids, and guess what? It can lead to emotionally unstable adults who are unable to form healthy relationships later in life. 

Not only did they psychologically torture their kids, they *documented it* for the amusement of others--it's like a gift to CPS in terms of evidence of abuse. For context, CPS rarely removes children from their homes. Those people deserved to have their kids taken away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, I don't particularly care about political opinions stated here one way or the other. Just don't tell people to shut the fuck up and try to maintain respectful discussion and we won't have a problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, they are cookies. Different from pastry. Shortbread, however, is both a cookie and a pastry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knock if off and observe the side bar rules, please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was trying to think of another, more elegant way to describe the thing. Silicone love bucket? Pommel-ass? Vagin de caoutchouc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Debate in /r/pics over the proper etiquette for transporting a big rubber ass on the subway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheese slices? On a sandwich? Heresy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, dude, you should write a new AITA post about *this* conversation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kenji knows a lot more than I do about cooking, I'm certainly not criticizing his method. I just like the texture results I get after a good rest in the fridge--overnight actually works well too. Which is convenient, because you can make your batter, put it in the fridge, clean up the mess, go to bed, and then you wake up with crepe batter that's ready to use with no mess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I initially thought clouds, but I love your reef interpretation. "And here's the bleached coral for a side of moral outrage!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm disappointed in your disappointment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, that's a good point. I actually cook mine in a nonstick omelette pan, anyway, so maybe my advice isn't that helpful... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, dude's also a Holocaust denier, so he's either a troll or he's just full of shit in general.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww, he deleted his comments--good thing there's an archive!

And, for reference, [here were his comments in this thread](http://imgur.com/a/etaSV) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I already have an industry. I also have hobbies, one of which is poking fun at food pedantry and snobbery (of which there is a lot around this site). 

You might not appreciate my behavior, but I appreciate yours, believe me. Thank you for the material.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the time this movie was *not* overlooked. It was heavily promoted and everyone I know saw it in the theater. I still remember the trailer that ran on TV (all the time). It also made 28 million against its 15 million dollar budget, and was widely praised by critics. 

In other words, not overlooked at all. But people should still see it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's falling off the bone and it's a little dry, they're overcooked. Try them at 225, cover them for the first two hours and 15 minutes, and then uncovered for the last 45 minutes (testing them before you get to the end time to make sure they're not getting overcooked). And do the finish for a shorter length of time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a tip if you're using stainless steel: you have to get it just the right temperature, and then things won't stick. You can test it--drop 1/8 of a tsp of water into the pan, and if it balls up and kind of glides/dances along the surface of the pan, it's ready. If it just bubble and steams, it's not hot enough (and your eggs will stick).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Or you could just explain yourself clearly without being so opaque about everything. 

I don't personally see what's "anti-culinary" about serving a sandwich on a board. It's kind of a dumb choice, but it's a trend--one that I enjoy poking fun at, but a trend nonetheless. Plenty of people who went to culinary school are choosing to follow this trend. You were linked here because your comment was both unclear and hyperbolic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know Kenji says to not bother resting the batter, but I have personally found that it makes a difference. 

Have you tried thinning your batter just a little? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I have a job, I don't just sit here reading comments. Sometimes interventions aren't as swift as they should be, but that's life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey good people--please don't recreate the drama from the linked thread here. It's truly upsetting when people get hurt or killed, and I know that makes emotions run high and it makes you want to pick sides, but please remember to be respectful in your discussion. 

Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Archive](http://archive.is/RGttc)

I still don't understand what "anti-culinary" means, but I find it very amusing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "it's extremely anti-culinary..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hallucinations are just unwanted thoughts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nah, that sounds gross.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enjoy your seafood, served on this ipad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, kind of, I'm a therapist so in theory I should understand people.

EDIT: to the person who reported this comment, you have to report comments in order for them to be reviewed when we have a thread that's blowing up like this. Don't report *my* comments to report other people, that's just really confusing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hot sauce on a fry up? That is just fucking stupid.

Why? What if someone just likes to add hot sauce to their eggs? How is that "fucking stupid?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know HP and ketchup are standard, but what if someone *likes* hot sauce? Isn't that allowed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's indispensable to *me* which is why I wrote "IMO." Downvoting people just for liking hot sauce -- Jesus, people are touchy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's interesting! I remember helping my mother at that age but not using the stove. But I was allowed to use the stove independently starting around age 8, so I guess it makes sense that with very close supervision you could start them out practicing at the stove around 5. I never understood easy bake ovens for that reason--just bake a cake with your kid using a real oven. Why pay for the toy?

Still and all, I wouldn't turn a 5-year-old loose to make a grilled cheese unless I was hovering over them constantly. Maybe I'm too much of a worrier! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never eaten blue cheese with breakfast, and I wonder if it would be too overpowering, but I do like it. It would be an interesting compliment to the tomatoes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like hot sauce. Which, IMO, is an indispensable condiment at breakfast time. 

And that does look like blue cheese.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's desserts (with the exception of ice cream). I really enjoy making them--I would rather make a beautiful cake than go out to a pastry shop and eat a fancy slice of cake. If I'm going to eat a big sugary dessert, it's going to be something I lovingly made at home because I enjoy the process so much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sigh...yes. It is a wise person who knows how much they do not know. 

Actually, I do understand it. Free-floating anger and frustration is anxiety-provoking, so people like to find simple targets for it. They channel their outrage and then come up with retroactive rationalizations for why that reaction is justified.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, someone in the comments wrote "Floor it, reverse, then floor it again" and they're at +141. I don't understand people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From a therapeutic perspective, that makes a lot of sense. I use a narrative approach frequently with older kids and teenagers. Sometimes it's easier for them to explore their feelings using characters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did they ban you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It reminds me of Keith Moon accidentally running over his chauffeur.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama over what murder is, exactly, in /r/Whatcouldgowrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a couple of places in the city proper that have kind of a tongue-in-cheek "no ketchup" policy, but it's not like they won't serve you a hot dog with ketchup. The dude is being hyperbolic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Archive](http://archive.is/rkBiV) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I lived in Chicago for years, and while it's a running joke that they won't serve you hot dog with ketchup, it's not all that serious a thing. If you want a hot dog with ketchup in Chicago, you'll get one. You take this stuff too seriously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only children eat ketchup! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, I think five is a little young to use the stove. I'm comfortable with having a 5-year-old prep stuff, though. I guess it's an individual parenting decision. My son's still a baby so I have a few years to figure out how I want to introduce him to cooking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, it's been taken care of. In the future, if you don't mind just send a quick modmail--there's a better chance of us getting to it faster that way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, you shouldn't try to wound them as a general rule--of course, aiming under stress is actually so hard you'll probably just end up wounding them anyway. If you *try* to shoot someone in the knee, you're probably going to miss. Aim for the torso, you have much better odds. It's harder to kill someone with a handgun in that situation than you might think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That reference to Club Skirts Dinah Shore Weekend was so fast I almost missed it, but damn that was funny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god, are you *still* arguing about this? Your obsession with this topic is starting to concern me. Are you okay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Or she's hoping to provide motivation and hope to people who are currently in the same shitty situation she was in. It's hard to leave an abusive relationship--harder than most people realize. She might be an inspiration to lots of people who need that hope.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually know something about this from my work with eating disorders. It depends on what kind of laxative. Overdose of stimulant laxatives like bisocodyl and senna will cause excessive cramping and diarrhea and dehydration, sometimes even bloody stools. A magnesium-based laxative, however (like Milk of Magnesia), can potentially cause coma and death when taken in overdose. Same with sodium phosphate based laxatives, which can throw off your electrolytes and cause major problems. What they're talking about in the post is stimulant laxatives--so generally not that dangerous, but definitely not good for you. That said, any medication that causes massive fluid loss through diarrhea is potentially dangerous, as sudden dehydration can cause cardiac and kidney complications. 

Long story short, it's potentially dangerous, although some are worse for you than others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the Jonathan Swift solution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too matchy-matchy. You want to pick a secondary color--maybe gray to match the powder residue on your hands, or a nice bold black and yellow stripe to echo the crime scene tape.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping to find some nice petty bickering about chinos or boat shoes. Not gun drama! But it was too amusing to pass up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 0/10, looks like dogshit, would not bang </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually not that complicated (seriously). She makes it seem harder than it is. I clean mine with salt and a sponge, and sometimes a small amount of detergent if there's a lot of food stuck. Yes, I said detergent--a well seasoned cast iron pan will survive a little detergent just fine, don't let anyone tell you any different. Then re-oil, back on the heat, and you're good to go. I've had the same skillet for ten years and it's in great shape, has great seasoning, and is useful for a wide range of cooking requirements.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually very beautiful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no explanation other than that sub is populated with teenagers who don't understand how serious poisoning someone is. And really, you can understand why--if you see stuff like *Dumb and Dumber*  and *American Pie* it seems like a funny prank, not a crime. And it's so widely depicted as a "prank" that it has its own entry on [TV Tropes](http://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/Main/LaxativePrank) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oxus always [brings his guns](https://media0.giphy.com/media/a6fOOiiFLZNwk/giphy.gif) to every fight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gah, Gunception! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely--I was just pointing out that it's hard to take the dude seriously when he's jerking off about shooting a mugger in the back. I respect that he's been held at gunpoint three times and has that experience, but c'mon dude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, but I think the part about shooting him in the back is more than a little silly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saying "Maybe I..." isn't a lie and is therefore not perjury.

I don't think this is how testifying works. I've testified a few times, and they don't let you say "maybe _____ happened!" You either say what you witnessed (fact witness) or you offer your opinion/interpretation (expert witness) and that's pretty much it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Archive](http://archive.is/8nwPq) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, if Bruce Wayne had been armed, his parents might have lived and he would never have become Batman. So in a way, not having a gun is a proven method of creating more superheroes. QED mic drop I win the argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took the concealed carry certification course, and the dude reminds me of the teacher I had. He would say things like "if you're going to shoot your gun, shoot to kill, because one story is better than two." And he'd go off on tangents about all the Mexican teenagers in his neighborhood and how he sits around hoping one of them will try to sneak on to his property. Barf.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen so much sauce on poke before. Is that a Foodland thing, or is it just your personal preference or what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely, although it's interesting--I actually already use a little cornmeal in my pte brise for pie crusts. One of Julia Child's recipes recommended it. It gives it a nice texture, IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Officer, that arsenic was for *me!* It's for my tertiary syphilis!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Argument over what to do if you're held at gunpoint in /r/malefashionadvice, of all places </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That...is disgusting. I have no idea how it tastes, but I find it hard to believe you can taste the fish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey 44moon! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* You linked directly to the full comments of a submission.  This  submission actually does merit an exception that rule, but as per the sidebar it must be submitted in a self post.

If you're unsure how this is done, check out our [wiki](/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules#wiki_submitting_self_posts_and_write-ups)



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People in /r/ProRevenge debate the ethics of spiking food with laxatives </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God damn, I saw "crawfish sausage" and immediately thought Hot Doug's...that was the last thing I ever had there before they closed. I am so sad it's gone. Their duck fat fries were preternaturally delicious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you think you're allergic, you should get tested--nightshades are easy enough to avoid, but celery is in a shit tone of stuff at restaurants and onions are as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have not. I've avoided okra on Indian menus because I didn't want to pay for something I would most likely not like, but I will give it a try and order some next time I go to an Indian restaurant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Moshlap! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* You linked directly to the full comments of a submission.  This  submission actually does merit an exception that rule, but as per the sidebar it must be submitted in a self post.

If you're unsure how this is done, check out our [wiki](/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules#wiki_submitting_self_posts_and_write-ups)



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey fpo! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* Surplus Popcorn: Due to a lot of stale politicized drama crowding out niche posts and dominating the front page, certain categories of drama face greater scrutiny and greater rates of removal. Your post fell into one of these categories and was not exceptional enough to be approved. See [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules#wiki_surplus_popcorn) for more information. 

Surplus drama categories include:

* racism drama
* gender wars
* social justice drama
* Trump drama



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey SS_Downboat! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* Surplus Popcorn: Due to a lot of stale politicized drama crowding out niche posts and dominating the front page, certain categories of drama face greater scrutiny and greater rates of removal. Your post fell into one of these categories and was not exceptional enough to be approved. See [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules#wiki_surplus_popcorn) for more information. 

Surplus drama categories include:

* racism drama
* gender wars
* social justice drama
* Trump drama



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People were just trying to explain to you why aluminum + certain dishwasher detergents = gray residue. And you called everyone "nuts" and you've been pretty abrasive. Just say "oh, huh, that's never happened to me, interesting!" and move on like a normal person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mother used to make a very similar dish, but she would add White Wine Worcestershire Sauce to it, which I highly recommend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention, there is *hardly any fondant there*. From the look of it, gold tinted fondant was used for the leaf accents on the sides and corners and that's about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okra--I've tried it a ton of different ways, and I just don't care for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...It's not a debate. It's a joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I have on doubt he's a racist, I've seen some of his previous comments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, OP, but you can't use this sub to advertise. 

Your site, however, is really Bad Psychology.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard you tried to report me for being too devastatingly charming. 

P.S. Please stop telling people that you're reporting them. It's obnoxious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you *seen* Bess Truman? Or for that matter, Caroline Harrison, or Eleanor Roosevelt for crying out loud? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now none of you get any ice cream after dinner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow you are rude. Unnecessarily so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that is a heavy cognitive distortion. 

But regarding you depression, please seek help. Start with seeing what counseling resources your school offers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey MyDaughtersOrgasm! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* Surplus Popcorn: Due to a lot of stale politicized drama crowding out niche posts and dominating the front page, certain categories of drama face greater scrutiny and greater rates of removal. Your post fell into one of these categories and was not exceptional enough to be approved. See [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules#wiki_surplus_popcorn) for more information. 

Surplus drama categories include:

* racism drama
* gender wars
* social justice drama
* Trump drama



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this isn't the pinnacle of sources or anything, but [Good Housekeeping](http://www.goodhousekeeping.com/home/cleaning/a34246/what-not-to-put-in-your-dishwasher/) advises against it for the same reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the dishwasher itself but the detergent used in the dishwasher--it reacts with aluminum that has not been anodized.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rumble in /r/Economics over labor, trade, and manufacturing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ["The US labor force has not been replaced by robots, it's been replaced by cheap overseas labor."](https://www.reddit.com/r/Economics/comments/67t3wv/trump_pledges_to_stay_in_nafta_after_aides_said/dgtqh7t/?context=3 st=j24w9j2u sh=d5750709)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What residue?

The residue on your aluminum pans. It is harmless but it can come off in the food. That's all I was saying. 

My Kitchen aid attachments have a burnished aluminum finish. The website covers how to clean them to prevent oxidation residue. It's a pretty easy problem to fix, but it's even easier to prevent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My advice (take it or leave it) is to not focus on being an INTJ. Being an introvert is not the same thing as being socially anxious. I know that when everything in your life feels like shit, it's comforting to get some kind of answer in the form of a category--but that category doesn't mean too much. 

I don't know if you've ever tried therapy, but it can be very helpful. If you're in college, your school may ever provide a certain number of sessions for free. I worked for a year as a college therapist and we offered 12 a year plus more on a conditional basis if it was needed. It can be very helpful to talk to someone--they can offer you strategies to help fight your depression and anxiety. If you see someone who does CBT, you'll see some progress in as few as four sessions. It's not an instant fix, but it does help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sometimes used as a vocational assessment in certain workplace settings. It's not used by any of the psychologists I know, though. And it was never part of my doctoral training, or my master's training. The only time I learned about it was when I took Personality Psychology as an undergraduate, and while learning about it we also learned about it's stickiness in terms of reliability and construct validity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear, the Myers Briggs has done more harm than it has good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Salmon has to be frozen for sushi to destroy the parasites. Salmon are full of worms. That's nothing against salmon, I love it, it's just a reality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First in his class at Grilled Cheese Technical College </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure your thermometer is a good one? And did you measure at the thickest point in the meat?

As a general rule of thumb (by no means applying to every steak, mind you) I cook my steaks on very high heat for about 4 minutes a side, or when they hit around 125 internally. After you take the steak out of the pan the internal temp will continue to rise a little as it rests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is more of an editing choice I guess, but this scene from [Taken 3](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gCKhktcbfQM app=desktop) is pretty ridiculous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Dean Devlin reboot of Godzilla was pretty terrible. "Hey, let's shoot everything in the dark and the rain so we can spend less on CGI!"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's not for everyone! Pretty classic pairing for venison, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Suischeese! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

Your writeup is super biased--this sub is not a place to soapbox or highlight bad behavior. If you can remove your editorial comments we can review it and possibly re-approve it. 



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's lean, so it gets chewy fast if you overcook it. If you got any backstrap, slice that into medallions and quick sear it. For the roast, I would braise that in a Dutch oven with some red wine, maybe some juniper berries or allspice. If you have thin steaks, you're going to want to be particularly careful to cook them quickly. Venison should be rare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The residue can come off on your food, though. Trust me, I ruined a buttercream once by using a kitchen aid paddle attachment that I had absent-mindedly run through the dishwasher. Not pretty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Footage of one of the tornadoes that his Canton, TX yesterday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a joke. Because people *assume* he is because of his name and appearance, even though he's American.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I do have say. It's called parenting. I'm not my kids friend I am their father. I discipline them and praise them. They aren't gay.

I almost wish that at least one of his kids turn out to be gay in order to teach him some humanity, but I wouldn't want to wish that kind of stress on anyone--it can't be easy to be his kid, let alone his *gay* kid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, i like the shock factor and so do many other people. It would add a lot actually. A really wild monster rape scene to finish the game off.

Gross.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
