<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1271</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big Little Lies is great and I wouldn't mind a 2nd season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 00:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 7 episodes, A-level actors, great production values, great writing and directing; this is the treatment I wish 13 Reasons Why (which is discussed later on in this post), and all other books of this kind had gotten. Big Little Lies, based off the Liane Moriarty novel of the same title, is a slow-burner and an excellent one. Told in flashback via an omniscient perspective but framed by interrogations of otherwise minor characters, Big Little Lies possesses a clever structure and an intricate story-line. Its looming mystery is one many might find weak because it's easily solved within the first 4 or so episodes, but hiding the truth was never its intention. Big Little Lies did mystery in such a uniquely pleasing way, it teases viewers and feeds off our doubts, but concluded with our most obvious guesses. 

Big Little Lies's brilliance wasn't in the mystery itself, but in David E. Kelley's subtle writing for its characters and sharply written dialogue, Jean-Marc Valle's signature directing style commonly featuring flashing sex and surrealism, and of course the flawless acting lead by Academy Award winners Reese Witherspoon and Nicole Kidman. Shailene Woodley, Alexander Skarsgrd, Adam Scott etc. were all so great and so were the child actors we didn't expect too much from. Every character was portrayed so perfectly , some actresses even seemed like they were playing themselves most of the time (Reese Witherspoon for e.g.), and it compels you to get wrapped up in the private despair and public pettiness of these characters. For a drama centered around a bunch of 1st graders and their suburban moms Big Little Lies proved that the key to entertaining television is in its writing, directing and acting, and doesn't have to depend too much on its premise at all. Big Little Lies small town setting made for some very pleasing visuals. The cinematography, multiple ocean-waves shots, astounding soundtrack, and well paced, slow progressing story gave the series a very soothing and atmospheric tone, even among its dark subject matters. It felt like Big Little Lies just did the same brilliant episode over and over again and I can't complain. The ending came swift, didn't leave much room for much of an aftermath, and there were a few conflicts left unresolved. And for those reasons, developing a a second season for Big Little Lies should not be difficult for David E. Kelley though the it was promoted as a miniseries. We are already engrossed into these characters and their lives so a 2nd season wouldn't even need to rely on mysteries to be good. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 00:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just ignore the pussy joke man I was just making an effortless example  but yea, I'd forgotten about this. Still want them to address the issue more tho so viewers don't find it sketchy. I was actually having an argument on twitter no too long ago with a few women calling the show sexist. I was trying to explain to them how the show is just a true representation of the tech industry and didn't intend to be sexist at all. But to avoid more negative reactions like these Silicon Valley should make more effort in addressing this issue.

edit: grammer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 00:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's pretty naive of you to claim women need to be catered to in order to enjoy the quality of something.

you missed my point. let me put it this way. The shows is made for a specific demographic and isn't something *most* females and poc will be intrigued to watched. Is it a coincidence that I've only seen this show talked about on reddit and no where else? no.

For a show to be no. 1 in a specific genre on TV it needs to be made for a wide range audience. it needs to be something everyone will enjoy, something that is diverse and interesting. Like Community, The Good Place, Brooklyn Nine-Nine etc. 

edit: I'm getting downvoted but I think I'm gonna stick to my argument here. As both an active member of the black community and a TV enthusiast I think I'm right here unless someone comes and convince me otherwise. Silicon Valley is not a show you'll find many females and black people watching.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 23:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why though? did u ever continue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
