<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2923</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 09:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 01:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 09:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Idk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 10:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 08:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> the drool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feeling the drool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> weekend plans complete with food stain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 06:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> my weekend plans complete with food stain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 06:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was just gifted this MTI Auto-Orchestra drum machine/bass synth. The owner said it was working last time they tried it,   it powers on but no sound comes out. Any idea where I could get this worked on in LA on the cheap? Also, I'm looking for the pedals that control the chord changes. Thanks! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 05:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody know a good place in LA to get an MTI Auto Orchestra worked on? I'm also in the market for the pedals that work the bass section. Thanks! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 04:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 04:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd look up my bank account. Maybe I would actually have some money from the interest accrued.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 05:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTS/WTT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 07:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alesis Bitrman ModFX bit crusher, distortion, comb filter, ring mod, phaser, a million things - $180

SIB Echodrive tube analog delay (blue) - $650

Roland TR 330 1970s drum machine - $175

Arion SPH-1 Phaser - $50

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 07:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have pro tools I guess the easiest way would be to import the songs and normalize them all... But you're probably dealing with perceived loudness because of more aggressive limiting and compression in modern music too which would mean you would need to squash your old tracks. That's kind of complicated and would probably sound like shit. 

For the non technical approach, you could group them in your playlist according to loudness and just go adjust the volume whenever you know the next group is about to start playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 07:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't call this prog rock... I love ELO, and consider them to be a straight up pop band, just a really really good one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 10:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whammy the shit out of the volca! Make a loop of it with the infinity. Play that backwards (I think it does that?) and move the whammy after the infinity in the chain whereupon that loop will be whammied the shit out of again. Make a loop of that with a ditto, then run that through what I'm hoping (but not sure) is a moog ring mod.  Loop that with another ditto and gently rock yourself to sleep . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 22:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sold it last night. Sorry. I'll take this down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 06:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cr 68 for 300 is INSANE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 22:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's all I ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 22:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking at those! Currently have a TR-66 on the way and thinking about getting a univox sr 55. The TR-606 will probably be acquired pretty soon though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 21:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit! Yeah, that definitely sounds right. They're using that delete knob a lot to pull stuff in and out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 20:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would buy the 32 if you still had it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 02:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The space drum function, that is. The rest of it sounds pretty great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 02:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how I found out about it! Now I'm on a vintage drum machine  kick... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 02:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Standard leaves all of the instruments in, wood block takes out the wood block, so on and so forth... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 01:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like a cartoon version of a rototom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 00:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just heard about it a couple of months ago and was able to find it pretty easily. That may have been luck of the draw though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ceci n'est pas une guitar pedal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 00:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 08:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will do  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 02:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Los Angeles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 23:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's cool! I got a good deal on it so I'm probably going to flip it as I have most of my delay needs in the studio covered by my Meet Maude, space echo, Yamaha e1010 and effectron.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 23:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your top 5 out of the 40 you've owned? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 23:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The blue sounds very nice, but I've never tried the red. I've read a decent amount about both and it seems to be about an equal split as far as people's preferences go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 22:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Diamond as a company. They make great sounding pedals that are really well built (I have the comp and the trem too). The vibrato is one that I've wanted for a while. It has just enough features to be fun and tweakable but not so many that it's overwhelming to use. I'm not sure about alternatives...You can't buy one off of the internet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
