<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3364</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 09:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ben Arfa is a lock to play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 07:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gameplay wise - yes

Everything other than that - no

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Draxler OTW? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thoughts on the chances of him getting a TOTW? Tbh, I don't watch any Ligue 1 at all so I'm not sure how he is doing. I'm a bit put off by the fact that he hasn't been getting to play a lot the past couple off games (as shown on Whoscored). Is there a reason for this? He's going for approximately 280k on PC atm. Buy or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a Reddit kit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ryan Reynolds (Deadpool) argues with Betty White </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ryan Reynolds (Deadpool) fights Betty White </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best teams in Europe? Apparently my team didn't get the memo :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 12:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite artist! Cannot wait for this. Panda Bear, Ohio and Gondry is heaven to my ears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbf, I was laughing. I have lost all feeling. I don't even feel angry with Arsenal anymore. It's more like, oh wow, Bayern are really good. Haha.' 'We are so shit. Hahaha...' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that if you hold onto your pokemon in the pokemon list, you will be able to select multiple pokemon to transfer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The legend Choudhury </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'He started off the game by talking shit right off the bat.'

I totally read that wrong the first time and I thought your friend had tried to start crap with the guy. Kudos to you for helping him out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jamie Carragher on the Mings stamp: He 'deserves a smack for that' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ibrahimovic: 'I can't believe you've done this' probably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time when I posted the OTW cards I had here, OTW Gabbiadini got an IF. Fingers crossed it works again. This time I've got Mustafi, Sane, Niang, Payet and Sansone. Please bless me Fifa gods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have I missed something? Why is Bailly not playing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have his untradeable 86 rated card :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think will be the requirements for the St Patrick's Day SBC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As in what rating for players and will we need players from the Irish league?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SPOILER
Shout out to the young black guy for sharing your ipod. You were a total bro :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually surprised at how much I liked the villain (Donald Pierce) in this movie. Well, I found him to be likeable. But I detested him at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I saw X24 standing over Xavier I genuinely thought he was just having a nightmare. Then the scene continued and I was just like 'fuck.....' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CODE KUNST - Fire Water (Feat. G.Soul, TABLO) [Korean Pop/Rap] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 04:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you want to be playing him with bronze J league players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 11:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He hasn't even been that bad... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By Danny McBride. It's always McBride. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Young Patrick Stewart when he had hair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cinematography in this looks insanely good. Getting pretty hyped now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was kind of hoping Newcastle lost just to see a True Geordie rant. Oh well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 08:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just as the Steve Harvey meme was dying as well. Great to have it back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 02:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it better to have a CM with good longshots? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ben Stiller wtf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xabi Alonso review? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 09:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im thinking of trying him out for the hyperlink with my IF Thiago which will make hybrids easier. However, the pace looks like it might be an issue. For anyone thats tried him, can you just share your thoughts on him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 09:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OTW cards wont get upgraded with the POTM releases, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 07:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone here actually stream? My internet is too slow for that stuff, though I don't think I would want to do it anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 02:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I met someone who was shocked when I told her that I enjoyed both BTS and EXO's music. Rivalries in Kpop are so unnecessary. I'll appreciate whatever music I like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obviously everyone here will like Kpop, but which aspects of it do you hate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 02:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely detest some of the fans that I see online. An example that really annoyed me was the controversy with G - Dragon and Nana Komatsu. So called 'fans' started to raid Komatsu's social accounts and hating on her just because they believed that she was in a relationship with GD. Real fans should let their artists have their own life away from the entertainment industry. Fortunately, most of the fans that I have met are great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 13:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't know what exactly to call this genre. It sounds great anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 12:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should watch this then. I have bawled every time that I've seen it. Though that may be because I'm just an emotional guy.


https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3bdm4NBYxII </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 12:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same! I don't know why, but whenever I have a true heart to heart talk with someone I have the strangest feeling to cry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best time to sell my Bundesliga/La Liga players? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 11:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn.. that gap between TT and Blood Sweat and Tears is insane though. Really puts Twice's success into perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reviewing Cheap Informs #2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 11:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you missed part 1, it's here: 

https://www.reddit.com/r/FIFA/comments/5uxxl1/reviewing_cheap_informs/

Skip over this part if you already know what this series is about.(It's pretty self explanatory but I'll leave this here again anyway)

Some of you guys might be interested in picking up the most expensive informs. Their exorbitant prices may not mean they will perform well though. I've decided to do a quick review of the cheap informs/special cards I'm using or have used. These players definitely have potential to fit into your team if you give them a try. These players are listed from favorite to least favorite. All of them were picked up for under 30k on PC.

1. BALDE DIAO KEITA 25K (83) - I saw a post on this sub recently about someone missing out on Mane's low price before it skyrocketed. I was also pretty annoyed after using my funds for my Bundesliga squad instead of getting the man, but fortunately, I have found a player that feels just as good as him. And for much, much cheaper. Let's take a brief look at MOTM Keita's stats. 93 pace, 89 dribbling and 82 strength. 6ft and double 4 stars. Picking the Lazio winger up for 25k was a no brainer. If you're looking for good value players, seriously, look outside the Premier League. If Keita was in the PL, I'm sure he'd be going for more than double his current price. Now, let's talk about how Keita feels ingame. Keita is currently challenging Keita for my favorite player in this game. (Allow me to gush about Naby for a second. He actually scored 4 goals in 1 game today which I was ecstatic about. You don't care? Oh, ok.) Seriously though, Balde Diao is excellent in front of goal. I haven't even mentioned his work rates yet. He has H/L. I can't stress how good this makes him for my team. He seems always in the right position to make a run on the counter attack. With a hawk chem style, his sprint speed is electric. The only negative aspect about Keita that can come to mind is his curve stat of 75. I'm a player who uses finesse shots for everything, even when it is detrimental. A couple of the times when he had pretty clear chances though, instead of bending it around the keeper,he hit it straight into his hands. Despite these misses, in 18 games, Keita has 16 goals. His ability to hold off defenders combined with his sprint speed means that Keita is a true hidden gem this Fifa. Keita is undoubtedly a 10/10

2. EDIN DZEKO 27K (87) - Honestly, the reason I first got Dzeko was because his card just looked aesthetically pleasing. I was worried about him being a disappointment before using him. I struggle with slower strikers. Harry Kane was one of the most rage inducing players I had ever used. And his normal card had better pace than Dzeko's MOTM. Thankfully, with a catalyst style, Dzeko actually feels fast. His pace reaches 83 with the chem style, but it genuinely feels faster. As a target man, Dzeko feels great. His 92 strength is definitely noticeable. If you've seen Giroud play when he's in form, you would be able to picture how Dzeko felt for me during his short tenure of 15 games. Dzeko is a great passer with the catalyst chem style, able to do the Giroud-esque flicks to the wingers. He has 6 assists for me, which is very good since I usually rely on Pjanic to make the final pass. Dzeko's lob balls work superbly. He holds off defenders with his strength before lobbing it to Salah or Insigne. I expected Dzeko to be a better finisher though. His pace and physical stats are fine, but its finishing for me which is actually the main problem. With 89 shooting I expected better. A couple of times he totally missed the goal and dragged it wide while Martin Tyler cackled saying 'how has he missed that!?' Dzeko's end product is very hot/cold. A brace one game, a couple of misses the next. Despite this problem, he has 10 goals which is very good since he was used as a 45th minute substitute for a third of the games I've used him. Another problem which you may have expected is his poor agility. The 47 balance was not very noticeable for me, but the 66 agility definitely was. Dzeko struggled to make quick turns when needed. Fake shots seemed to take forever as well. Sending Dzeko in a straight line and watching him barrel past defenders seems the most effective method. To conclude, Dzeko's link up play is outstanding, and though his finishing has not been excellent, I've definitely enjoyed using this card. An 8.4/10 for the big lad.

3. AHMED ELMOHAMADY 11K (81) - Elmo is going for discard price at the moment. But buying him may not be the best option, unless you just want a colorful squad. Not because he is a bad card by any means, but because he isn't that good. Elmo looked like it will be a good card, but it turned out to be average. A bit like Jurassic Park 3 or Pirates of the Caribbean 4. I kind of forget about him even existing. In about 20 games for me, Elmo was a decent RB. His card is very well rounded and I remember one stand out moment, in one of his early appearances where he took the ball at the halfway point, dribble past 3 defenders before doing a side pass for the assist. After that though, he faded into obscurity. I'll talk about the positives with this defender. Firstly, his stamina is excellent. Fitness was never an issue since I was rotating teams and in the games he played, I never felt the need to substitute him for low energy reasons. Also, I touched on this before, Elmo's dribbling was surprisingly good. If needed, he was able to go forward a bit and use his 80 dribbling stats to good effect. Unfortunately, M/H workrates meant that this card was rarely able to be in a position to help during the attack.  I noticed that, for me, Elmo would always hang back during an attack unless I actually used him. I prefer a fullback who is able to be of help on the offense, H/M workrates are much more suitable for me, though you may prefer a more defense orientated RB and that's fine as well. Another problem which Elmo's chances of staying in my team was his lack of pace. Although I could have used a pace boost card, I really am a bit of a miser, and would prefer not to spend 5k for that chem style on him. Instead of Elmo, I would recommend Clyne who I thought was much better and the best RB this Fifa for me. However, give Elmo a try if you want since you don't have to worry about his price crashing and you'll lose nothing by using him. You may like him more than I did. I will give Elmo a 7.2/10. He was decent for me, but there are much better options in the EPL.

The thoughts on these players are my own. You may not have the experience as me. However, this guide will hopefully show you what to expect. If you have tried these players already, let me know what you thought. Cheers for reading!

*And I saw some comments asking for a review on Boudebouz. I haven't tried him yet which is why he wasn't in here, but his stats look excellent in a CF position so I will definitely be trying him soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pure talent that I'll never have. Seriously though, he's amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This man's cover of Andrea Bocelli and Celine Dion's song, 'The Prayer,' is unreal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A brief summary of every Youtuber's dog video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 06:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have tried him and will do a review in the next part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually haven't tried Vogt yet since I've been using Toprak to rotate and he's been very good fot me. I've seen rave reviews for Vogt though so I will have to try him out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reviewing Cheap Informs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 12:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of you guys might be interested in picking up the most expensive informs. Their exorbitant prices may not mean they will perform well though. I've decided to do a quick review of the cheap informs/special cards I'm using. These players definitely have potential to fit into your team if you give them a try. These players are listed from favorite to least favorite. All of them were picked up for under 30k on PC.


1. NABY KEITA 16K (84) - This man is one of my favorite players this Fifa. I initially hated him, but that is simply because I was playing him in the wrong position' which was RW. Though Keita is a winger, the position he excels in is the CM spot. His lowest stat is his defence (74). To have over 74 on all stats and high pace means that Keita feels better than Sanches.  Pace and high stamima allows him to catch and break up opposition play before kickstarting attacks. His finishing is no joke either. in 23 games he has 12 goals which is a very good performance since he is usually further back. His H/M workrates are not noticeable at all, he does not go out of position. I highly recommend Keita, for under 20k, he is a bargain. 10/10


2. KYRIAKOS PAPADOPOULOS 13K (83) - I have no idea how or why Papa is going this cheap. His pace is quite low,  but Papa's physical stats are insanely good. Strength and Jumping each in the 90s means that Papa is able to bully attackers. The pace is an issue, though for me I had IF Sokratis to help with his higher pace. I definitely suggest partnering with a fast defender so Papa does not get exposed at the back. Use shadow cards on Papa if you can get them, on PC I wasn't able to get any since our market is relatively poor. However, with a basic chem style, Papadopoulos has still been very solid for me. He has even been able to score a couple of headers with his 91 heading stats. Papa's pace may be not ideal, but for 13k he is an absolute bargain. In terms of value he is a 10/10, for his performances I will give him a 8.7/10


3. IAGO ASPAS 28K (86) - I was very excited when I first got Aspas, however, I can't help but feel disappointed after about 35 games with him. He seemed to disappear after great performances in his first 10 games. With an engine chem style, Aspas reached 91 pace. However he still felt slow. Mike Smalling could keep up with him even without boosted pace. It was infuriating. Aspas had 99 acceleration but just 84 sprint speed. Left backs could easily run him down. I would have added a catalyst or hunter chem style but the second problem with Aspas is his workrates. High defensive workrates meant that Aspas was constantly AWOL when attacking. He was a great finisher when he was in a suitable position, but the problem was that he was rarely in the right position. I will probably be selling him soon. Aspas is a great player on some days, but also one of the most frustrating players during the others. Aspas scored 16 goals in 35 games, most of them came in the first 10 games. I will give Aspas a 6.7/10


The thoughts on these players are my own.  You may not have the experience as me. However, this guide will hopefully show you what to expect. If you have tried these players already, let me know what you thought. Cheers for reading! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 12:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree. Seems that everyone in this sub has him while I'm stuck here with a Hunter chem style on Musa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 12:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A gold Andre Silva IF will be so sick for a Liga NOS squad. Fingers crossed he gets one and its cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calcio A informs that will be upgraded? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 10:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to keep the goalkeeper back during 90th minute corners? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 09:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's insane the amount of times that Fahrmann has, against my will, gone into the box during a corner only to get no contact at all with the ball, then sprint back whilst players like Musa jog past him and score. Has anyone even scored a corner with their keeper? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait. There's going to be a Lion King remake?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 13:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ty. This is exactly what I was looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ricardo Rodriguez with a Catalyst chem style is the best LB I've ever used </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you build a team around TIF Bernardo Silva and IF Jonas? Jonas would be preferable at CF or CAM. Silva can be pushed to CF and maybe ST if it works well. I have a budget of 200k on PC. Any formation is welcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 10:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I got about 20 of them for 150. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass bidding on bronze Bundesliga players? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 09:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a good investment option or would buying Sanches cards be better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 09:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a decent idea actually. Im using him at CM atm but might switch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 09:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a decent idea actually. Im using him at CM atm but might switch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is in an 'All Players Pack'? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 04:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking of doing the Foreign Players SBC but I don't know if the reward will be worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Akdong Musician - 200% [Kpop] (2014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite Will Ferrell quote? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Akdong Musician(AKMU) - 200% [Kpop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good apps for learning japanese? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be preferable if its free and if it coild be used offline that would be great. Im using Memrise atm, but their Pro version costs way too much. Any alternative options? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which IF cards will actually be affected by upgrades? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that some players will be upgraded but their SIF or TIF cards will remain unchanged. Are there any cards that will actually be boosted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IF Fernando Torres is going for 40k on PC now, is it worth investing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone tried 84 Balotelli? If you have, could you do a quick review please? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 11:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His stats look insanely good. The only thing putting me off is his horrible stamina and L/L workrates. If you've tried him, could you just share your thoughts on the guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OTW Berahino or OTW Niang? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 04:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which one should I invest in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> K.A.R.D - Don`t Recall [Korean Pop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://giphy.com/gifs/dollars-amount-sEULHciNa7tUQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think his price will settle at? Might pick him up if its below 40k. If not I'll just get his FIF I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. The thing is though, I'm pretty shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just come off the worst game of my life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IF Kalou or IF Modeste at ST? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hes having a mare </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg Aubameyang </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I be selling my Bayern players in the MM SBC instead of for the WL? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 11:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, when does the Bundesliga WL start? If it starts after the SBC ends, then I may be able to buy the players again when they are cheap and sell them at the WL time. I'm not sure what the date is though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best/most exciting team to use with a max budget of 10 million? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should be. I'm hoping for a Sanchez hattrick to beat Bayern 3-0.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 12:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be as creative as you want. Price of 150k. Really just looking for a fun squad to use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Div 5 I think. Obviously your packs may not be as good as mine, but if you don't mind losing some money, you can just try it to experience it for the first time and see if you enjoy it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Plus the guy who wrote straight out of Compton pretty much threw the original script in the trash and rewrote the entire thing. It'll be well written.

Isn't the writer the guy that did the Transformers movies? That's whats coming up on Wikipedia anyway, though that may not be really reliable. If it is the Transformers writer though... 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did single player since my connection is atrocious. After winning all games, I packed Buffon in my first pack and then MOTM Elmohamedy in my second. Before that, my only good packed player had been Di Maria. Needless to say, I was stoked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 10:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That line was a bit cringey tbh. The movie looks good, its the dialogue I'm worried about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it better to sell OTW players during hype or when their TOTW card comes out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gabbiadini is going for 130k atm. Will he be more expensive after this TOTW? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
