<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2337</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 18:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice work. [Here's](http://i.imgur.com/A3TuOrp.png) a link to the #, Name, and type. For the lazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 21:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confirmed all you need is [chat](http://i.imgur.com/WxEnb0Y.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 05:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happens to me every time I open Google now, though not to the extent you show. Mine acts like I touched outside the search field (right after I touched IN the field) canceling the keyboard from showing, and requiring another touch inside the field. Super annoying, but honestly didn't bother me enough to search/comment on it (since I commonly use voice search anyway) 

My initial guess would be to try a different/fresh keyboard- I use Swype with xposed and Swypetweaks and figured that could have something to do with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 21:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little Johnny was sitting in math class one fine day. Teacher asks, "Okay class, three birds are sitting on a wire, Farmer Dale shoots one off, how many are left?" Johnny thinks for a sec, raises his hand and gets called upon: "None, the first bird gets shot and the other two fly away." 

The teacher chuckles to herself and says, "Well Johnny, I was looking for 3 minus 1 = 2, but I like the way you're thinking."

Little Johnny says, "Alright Teach, I've got one for you: Three blondes are sitting in an ice cream parlor eating ice cream cones. One of them licks from the side, one licks from the top, and the other sticks the whole thing in her mouth and swallows it in one gulp. Which one is married?"

The teacher thinks about it for a few seconds and responds:

"The one that swallows it all in one gulp?"

Little Johnny says, "No Teach, the one with the ring on her finger- but I like the way you're thinking"

I hear it about 5 times a year. Never gets old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 20:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, my hat was also off for myself, but I doubt there will be anything after 5.1 for the 1st gens  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
