<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1499</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that was the minority we wouldn't have a problem with wars and abortion. I think you misread my comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As painful as possible, 3-4 months after fault was determined (that alone took 2 months) they still are not paying out til everyone is settled. Pretty sure I could hound them, report them to the BBB to make it faster but honestly they drain me. If you want to recoup losses beyond what the insurance provides you got to sue. That and you can write it off in your taxes as 'loss not covered by insurance'. /r/insurance taught me that. If you want you can hit my post history to find a post of mine that I made where some answered a few questions of mine or post your own (as your car accident is much smaller there may be better ways to handle it)

While the insurance wants to write it off as a total loss my car does work and drive fine so I am not too affected atm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in the same situation, a 10-car accident was caused by 1 driver with 10k liability... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet the information I wanted. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *sigh* a man is the sum of his works, if your works are lacking, how may I judge that you truly are a man and not a dog on the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a joke, but dangerously believable this day and age... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know but is esquire really a trusted avenue of knowledge? I'll put off reading it until more is linked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would need a closer study. They do have a severe drug and organized crime problem. And an aggressive neighbor (China) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the reference, take my upvote  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly it's bc of the few times I corrected pro-trump posters, they just went unreasonablely hostile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he has attempted to force twitter to reveal personal information of anti-trump posters.

While this is not explicitly an order from trump, it was from White House administration, and I hold the man in charge accountable for his senior staff. (Joke, I have to explicitly say it it's sad) Despite how little time in office they hold before resigning due to scandals and conflicts of interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at his karma, days since account created, and his posts. He is a troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only as much as the poison on her lips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some do... but from my perspective a very small minority  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frank Beaushaw is part of diesel. 916-484-8354
    _   He is generally welcoming of new students and will try to talk you into joining diesel.

John McCormack (spelling his name wrong) is part of the main campus automotive, I don't have his business card in me so I cannot give you his contact details. I do know on fridays many students work on their own cars on campus with the aid of the instructors. You can head on over and ask because they accept students that are not in for an automotive career but just want to maintain their own vehicle l. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try https://np.reddit.com/r/marijuanaenthusiasts/

Yes it's sounds like it's for weed but that's bc 'tree' has been taken already; it's quite strange and amusing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 11:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly why is it called Greek fire, always struck me weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you might just be in luck, talk with the automotive collisions (not the one on main campus) or diesel tech. I know they let the students work on their own cars. Heck talk to the automotive on the main campus bc they have one similar just not as big and good.

I'll come back later after getting contact information. (Say 2 hours) sorry can't today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prob dates back to weeding your crops, you don't want stray plants competing with your crops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 10:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch saint helens eruption. If I am spelling it right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 09:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh I think she is still good for niche fights like Multiplayer Serioth VII. Seriously screw that guy, without reraise good luck, also Kuja ultima  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ARC has something similar on Mather but I don't know if they will let non-students use it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I remember when I was young and thought it was cool and exchanged 40$ into dollar coins... was lugging that around San Fran. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shame I would take some if I had the room, I appreciate that you have Enders game and Dune. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vote them away? Write a sternly worded letter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good points </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I understood the retrieval part, for me it was the satellite itself that arouses curiosity  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last stand keeps buffs... interesting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No that bad breath gives me nightmares. That and Mega cactaur slaying your entire party at once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is lenna burst good for weak vs Holy bosses? Cura lv heal on cast plus moderate reraise. Buffs mind on cast. Command 1 deal 4 wht mag attacks, command 2 small group heal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep he is pretty strong. He takes a lot of time, effort, hair (from you pulling out your hair) motes. But in the end his base states are some of the best and can fit many roles. Especially with his burst he is worth it.

Screw this freakn pathetic jerk son of a gun, can't get any weaker, asshat, squishy, frustrating, kill him in the most painful manner ever, king of bad luck, shank him, weaker than air, this Onion Knight... sorry have to put that in after grinding him from 90 to 99 in dungeons due to a lack of eggs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this rate of global warming and destruction of the environment, we might as well ask if they'll be anyone around to remember (this is a hyperbole) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At one point you have a valid argument asking for scrutiny, on the other hand by completely rejecting a piece of potential historical record without attempting to shed scrutiny on the matter... makes you look like you are just ranting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Logical it is, whether to accept as evidence or reject it as lacking, that is the real decision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem comes from believing no matter how your terrible your actions, the goal (salvation, nirvana, ect) makes it justified. Often in contradiction to their scriptures.

Edit: grammar, a 'how' was missing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I meant in modern times, I should have clarified  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did early satellites, particularly spy satellites operate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It dawned on me that the amount of data a spy satellite would generate would need to be recovered. Now days we have wireless transmitters, but back then it wouldn't seem reliable enough to be used. I understand that they would pop off a film canister to be recovered, but how did they 'order' a satellite to go from its regular orbit to a specific location, take pictures, go to another orbit, time itself to pop off the film canister at a specific time, and go back to normal operations or its next assignment. It would seem with the limitations of early technology it would be difficult to do, but if anyone has explanations that would be awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't say exclusive Jewish, they do permit others as long as those others are not from particular ethnic groups that keep committing terrorist attacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long is the limitations period? My relative's apartment was broken in by police, they literally broke the door... pored out all the household liquids (dishwasher soap, half half, vegetable oil, etc) some other stuff out into the sink like baking soda, caused damage to the carpets, broke some chairs, among other things such as ruined a good portion of clothing. Relative had at worst a DUI for cold medicine as a criminal record. Is it possible to get damages from the police department after 7+ months or so? Because it seemed excessive. The police raid was part of a drug sting in which my relative took the bait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marking this I am interested in this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other guy I think he is more right than you, listen to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds violent, abusive, and most likely you will not be dealing with the most kindest of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh wouldn't repeated and documented offenses be needed to take custody of the dog. (It would be a different story if maltreatment was involved but I don't think that's the case) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marking this to read later </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought, I thought some more, I can't think of a plausible reason if the car in question is a sedan or the like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the game was called 'chicken' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My experiences with Mormons is like Jehovah's witnesses. Somewhat annoying but peaceful. But it's a wide world... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 10:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heard it's great fertilizer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 10:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And capitalism to the Irish famine, no really its humans being unsympathetic jerks to one another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 10:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surrender and die... no but really I heard it was engineered to stifle dissent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 10:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oyo_Empire

Was going to pick up more but I want sleep, pick your favorite https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/African_empires </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 08:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Allah Akbar  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 08:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did but they were more there for riots and big incidents rather than small things like a stray murder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta upvote the pun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if a sequel would deal with the aftermath trawling through bodies bobbing up in a morbid graveyard.

https://www.reddit.com/r/history/comments/656mf9/for_days_after_the_titanic_sinking_ocean_liners/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good third didn't see it coming in my high school class </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, without his notes he is pretty bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah used everything I got but came up short by just a few levels  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could just be irritated at this lovely OK that is still crap at lv 95 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is DeNa clamping down on S/L? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More of a rage post

Was playing orbfest hardest level trying to grind this freaken pathetic onion knight, and last time I grinded a character a few weeks ago S/L was much more lenient while now if the dmg in numbers appeared quiting and loading the app won't save you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia: not really

America: mentioned, but glossed over.

Then again I was mostly in the lower grades, but my older siblings agree it's not mentioned much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it wise to mix magic and physical? I normally either go full blown on one of the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got 10 3 stars on the lucky pull...



... and onion knight burst as the 11th item (not a dupe...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even before the war they were looking inwards. Germanys attack came as a shock to Stalin and he refused to believe the first reports. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would give him another 3 at least. His grip on the military was made out of iron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though the Cuban missile crisis was not Stalin (the Russian premier at the time expected demands for missile removal but did it as a bargaining chip, queer conflict that one with a lot of yelling and quiet condolences.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you cannot say unequivocally good guys if you want to stay unbiased, do not let your standard of 'good' drop either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not like the current Russian or Chinese government would appreciate anyone snooping in their dark history either so that makes getting access to potential documents and sites difficult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guessing turkey will lodge a diplomatic complaint against anyone who dares screen it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one deserves anything, it may be the hardest thing to let go of grievances but it's for the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess that's one good thing out of the cold war </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The current Chinese government heavily discourages this. Beatings and the like. The BBC news team when they were reporting on this they got their cameras smashed and a beating... by the police. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never dawned on me until now why the Russian word for Easter "~Pasca" was so different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read the script and general plot. From that alone I got goosebumps. It must be a gem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aye but it's not a C1 AoE. Can't go full auto </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And 100 of the 4-stars but only ~20 wisdom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah turns out I have more motes than I remember... around 800 each mote... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they still stack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep you have one strong guy with instant attack, Cloud BSB 1 to make it faster, and preferably an AoE (for the mini-cactaur) but not needed. Play on speed 5 to max out on that instant attack)

The other guy? Give him health defense ect cause he won't be doing anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have been doing so buck screw the wind attack from the flower </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zodiac spear isn't a pain in the arse (or a really easy early weapon of you do it right) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have both shout and sheepsong I plan to use onion for both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atm doing lv 93 ramza with Lickity split (instant attack) RW cloud BSB 1

Onion is in the back with Stella's music box defending 

Enigma dungeons? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it... though I am out of eggs so I am suffering a bit

A stray attack in the orb fest dungeons can KO him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Onion knight? Worth it to blow everything you have on him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did the lucky draw and got what was what I first thought was the worst draw, 10 3-stars, but wow OK Burst popped up. I am grinding him (he is 70 now) and I am wondering if I should blow my stock of notes on him. (I have around 100 of each 3 star, 60 vit; and 40 of the 4-star)

Also, screw this freaken weak puny OK; had to S/R so many freaken times! His stats are worth it in the end right?... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but I didn't say a thing about other countries. I kinda only somewhat care about other countries not to the extent of let "mimic them." Each country has its own culture and issues that prevent systems from being 100% transferable. Instead one can only view other systems with a grain of salt. I posted bc I believed you were painting an overly optimistic picture of US healthcare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The popcorn is getting stale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may have insurance but If it's outside the network I may have quite a few troubles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only the best if you have the money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want one to get gravel off my lawn after storing a pile of gravel for concrete work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it that it's his tie. And how it's both showing a 'good' side and a negative. Though mostly negative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't attack others come on, it's a rule of the subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if you can undermine a potential enemy (Russia)... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hearsay and gossip is not evidence of guilt, but if you would cite your sources, if shown to be reliable l, that would be much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you do 10,000 squats a day and are bald </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks I may check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks I may check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
