<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2129</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 15:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gotcha, So I take it then the project is over.

So sad to find out,anyway, sorry for the shitpost :  (  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any info on new episodes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 14:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for this shitpost, I am new too the show and i'm totally addicted.

I looked around for news on new episodes and couldn't find anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 13:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you have here is a very nice Codd bottle,Where are you located?

Here in America Codd bottles are a bit more rare, They where primarily a lemonade soda, Some soda company's kept the design up too around 1915.

They where fazed out for the more popular "crown top" bottles that where cheaper to make and more sanitary.

Sadly that was basically the end of the lemonade soda,however,It wasn't the end of lemonade flavored pop drinks, 7up started selling there lemon/lime soda in 1920.

The Japanese still produce codd top bottles called Ramune and the name "Ramune" harkins back to codds early lemonade sodas...lemonade was poorly translated to Ra-mu-ne hence the similarly in the way it sounds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McDonald's: Ronald McDonald back in time 1982 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 17:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 15:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it comes to dogs I just break down, There love and loyalty to us is outstanding.

I can usually hold back the tears on just about anything, not dogs though, The immense love i feel when my dogs look at me is something I can't compare to that of any other creature.

I am terrible at consoling anybody that lost there dog, I tried once to read this lady a poem called the "Rainbow Bridge" after her dog died, every time I tried to read it I became a blubbering mess.

Here is the poem if anybody is interested https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/564x/21/35/c6/2135c6916dd83661a28d645b7ad52191.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 20:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is the video of the finished house?....all i see are vids of him working on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 19:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great post Hooper732 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 14:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm very impressed with his skill with using the live loops

I think your being fooled a little here "the piano line" your hearing at the beginning of the song was not played on that synth the (MicroKorg) It doesn't produce sounds like that...not to say he can't trigger those sounds via MIDI,however, he has nothing plugged into the MIDI ports.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rothera Point - Transmissions II - Novaya Zemlya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 20:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moth Radio Hour: Veterans Day 2016: Iraq, Aircraft Carriers   Candy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 20:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anthony Griffith: The Best of Times, The Worst of Times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 20:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kevin Wilson: Out of Print </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 20:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good question..perhaps your right.

Maybe if he kept them in a humidor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if he ever used them to commit a crime, It would leave somebody else's fingerprints....Morbidly clever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 20:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks to be a rubber hammer, even the handle is rubber.

You can see it wobble when mr. gold comes back @1:56. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy stumbles across a Kilo of cocaine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 20:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are you a fan of NPR? If the answer is yes then /r/themoth can use your help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All i could think about http://img4.bdbphotos.com/images/230x300/a/v/avyymp22f0n6yvmy.jpg?skj2io4l </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's muddy but I thought what the hay maybe somebody could do something with it if they wanted to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 14:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RemindMe! 48 hours

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moth Radio Hour: Veterans Day 2016: Iraq, Aircraft Carriers   Candy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moth Radio Hour: GrandSLAMs Coast to Coast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moth Radio Hour: One Thing in Common </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bread handed.

FIFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Requesting /r/mydog no mods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 20:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to a 1991 article in the Herald Times Online, it turned out that Susan Miles, the winner of the contest, kept the house long enough to reap some tax advantages from owning a property, and then she sold it to Stephen Wright (not the comedian). She never even lived in the house! She went back home to Bellevue, WA, after the contest was over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if that doesn't pluck the hairs on my dum-didadly nogireeno </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Charles Redheffer was an American inventor who claimed to have invented a perpetual motion machine, He was later exposed when an engineer found a hidden cord that led to an upper floor. Upstairs he found an old man who was turning a hand-crank with one hand and eating bread with the other </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 13:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It lists its principles in a "statement of faith" which declares the belief that the Bible is literally true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 12:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 23:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES!

At /r/TheMothRadioHour I have a script that has been loading " most" of the new podcasts.

I can improve on this.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 23:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  behind dark eyes was done by QHO...I guess it's a remix?

I woke up one day and found it there...as for my works, there made in real time using a MicroKorg and Audacity.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do, just keep in mind most of my work so far is me learning and experimenting on recording..that said i think i have one or two good ideas there.

https://soundcloud.com/user-345283577 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 02:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it!

I make music too, I really like your idea here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agee with /u/MrSmithSmith it looks to me that the teacher had no way of knowing he was going to hug her.....she with her back turned.

It's plausible that the student took advantage of this opportunity to hug her as a way of seeing how far he could push things.

If it where in a different context where she was facing him i think it would show intent on her part for accepting the hug...however, in this case the student seems to have over stepped the boundaries.

I do think the teacher must have warned him before to feel so strongly about it....but who knows that's just my gut feeling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 18:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eighteen gang members who used a takeaway caf to serve up bacon and eggs alongside kilos of cocaine have been jailed.
Avon and Somerset Police said the crime group had supplied drugs with a street value of more than 350,000 and used the Breakfast Box in Bedminster to store, prepare and sell it.
Det Insp Jim Taylor said it had been a "complex" but "well executed operation".
He said: "Once again we have struck at the very heart of a Bristol-based crime group operation, thwarting their efforts to flood the streets of Avon and Somerset with Class A drugs and preying on those who are addicted to and unable to resist the lure of drugs."

Source: http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-bristol-37864218 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 18:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the Premier Supermatic Twin (rolls two at once), When you get the hang of it the thing rolls perfect cigs.

Tips: 1- Clear the machine after every injection 
        2- Don't pack too tightly 
        3- Pull back in a nice steady motion
        4- press down near the tip to hold the tube in place
        5- Don't roll really dry tobacco 

Hope this helps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best combination to make yourself a Marlboro Light clone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 18:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have tried many combinations of tubes and tobacco and I am finally  satisfied ....it took me a long time but my search is over I actually think these are better.

Recipe:

Gold Tin Star Pipe Tobacco with 4 aces Regular King Size Filter Tubes.

I actually tried a Marlboro light from my Wife's pack and quickly handed it back preferring my own....I never thought I would ever say this but in my honest opinion there better.


Let me know what you think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> isopropylalcohol - rose pink sugary drink (track of the week from /r/SoundsLikeBoC) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 17:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 16:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see that too,however, it looks to be a gap in the set design letting a sliver of light through resembling a string.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 16:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wrong, what i thought was a string was just the reflection of the knife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 14:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seen videos like this before, It amazes me how different life is in other parts of the world.

Imagine this conversation "hey honey how was your day?"...husband says "O man I had a horrible train ride home" wife responds "O dear what happened?.....Husband replies "It rained!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 14:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a restaurant for snakes....your the meal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 13:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At 1:13 you see the string. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 13:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does he come up with this stuff...dude is really funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 15:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually think Ethan is a decent reporter, it's refreshing to see somebody speak there mind,make good points about society issues and wrap it up in a positive message.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McDonaldland cookies! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 13:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pete Spara - Cold Blow 02 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RegalMusic - MeercatCrashTest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BeepBoomBap - Death Life Rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 22:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 18:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you Brute_zee, I just get the feeling he didn't fully grasp what he was doing could be potentially fatal for the Pilot.

It was stupid...he really should have known better, now he is facing loosing absolutely everything.

I just can't help but feel bad for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 18:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The TV station let him off the hook after he made a public apology.

The FBI is still going to pursue a case against him,he could get up too 14 years in prison.

Here is his tearful apology....I feel bad for him  http://kdvr.com/2016/11/03/man-admits-to-shining-laser-light-at-skyfox/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 23:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Dad drive me to school" ok, They speed off towards the school, Dad says "You know it's PM don't you?''  /r/expected 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a pic of her real father http://wac.450f.edgecastcdn.net/80450F/1063thebuzz.com/files/2015/10/Steve-Shipman-mailman.jpg?w=600 h=0 zc=1 s=0 a=t q=89 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it is the lope then just bite the bullet and stay sober your almost through it. 

Go for long walks and take plenty of hot baths in the evening to calm your nerves.....and stay far away from alcohol, withdrawal and booze don't mix. 

As far as your feelings, do expect to feel strange for a while, I remember I kicked tram after 2 years it took my brain a while to recover ....I felt happy in some ways and also as if I was living in a day dream...very strange.

Something to know about Tram, Tramadol is a mu-opioid receptor agonist as well as an inhibitor of the reuptake of norepinephrine and serotonin in the central nervous system.

Your recovering from not just opiates ...give it some time, go for long walks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AKtion - SPot ON </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LoveKrafty - Abandon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> isopropylalcohol - rose pink sugary drink by </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Truck driver level 10! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Election Day: Savannah Georgia 1948 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea dude I thought the imagery was awesome, very surreal and thought provoking.

You should do one for my music ; p   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed it is,however, I think it's more likely that Tramadol is the culprit here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear from others to use a blowtorch to heat the carbon and then use an air compressor to blow it out.

try it first on a throwaway saw first.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 15:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the poem represents the idea that we stand on the shoulders of those who came before us....from the cave man till now, our shadow was and is afforded by those who came before us.

So perhaps what OP is saying metaphorically is that our shadow is not solely our own, that we live in between ownership,those who came before us and those we affect now.?    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 12:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tramadol has a long half life and most definitely will give you WD.

How much Tramadol have you been taking?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Without Beat by me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 23:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^^ It's His dick case closed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 17:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or that we know it's a pot, I think therefor I am...the perception of it's  use is what being alive is?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 17:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what your saying, he is merely talking about what existence is.

Perhaps he was also inferring that perception is an integral part of being alive? 

I have been reading this book for over 20 years and I always come away with something different ...Lao Tzu had a knack for writing things that have to separate meanings that also lead to the same outcome....there is something so organic about his writings.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tao Te Ching: Chapter 11 (Lao Tzu had some very deep ideas...what is your take on this?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 17:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tao Te Ching: Chapter 11

Thirty spokes
meet in the hub.
Where the wheel isn't
is where it's useful.

Hollowed out,
clay makes a pot.
Where the pot's not
is where it's useful.

Cut doors and windows
to make a room.
Where the room isn't,
there's room for you.

So the profit in what is
is in the use of what isn't



.








This is so true, it's the empty spaces in life that give us enrichment,death brings life,life itself is just filling up an empty space.

I think what he is saying is we should work hard at being creative void fillers ,search for a way to be useful and apply it?

What do you guys think ?

   

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 13:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems to me the running line had one too many wraps....other things too but that's what i see contributing to this fuck up most of all.

As far as a notch goes (correct me if im wrong) I don't think it was necessary, he could perform a horizontal back cut above or under another horizontal cut depending on what direction he wanted the log to go.


Young Aborist here, I specialize in disease/pest management so i could be wrong.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dan Savage: Not That Kind of Gay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 17:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lt. Dan Choi: Made to be Broken </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 17:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Lombardi: Mission to India </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 17:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jean-Jacques Perrey, electronic musical pioneer, dies at 87, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 16:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 16:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What gets me about Donald Trump is his appeal to this undercurrent of xenophobia, It's startling that there are so many people out there who prescribe to this nonsense.

  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 16:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I like piano work in Philae , It got me to thinking i shoould play my piano more often and blend it with my MicroKorg.

I am still working on my style and getting a better understanding on how to record music...so far so good, I see a lot of progress from my early beginnings.

I will let you know how it turns out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Age changes everything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 14:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Age changes everything, When i was young life to me was being flexible,malleable to bend like a tree to weather the storm.

As i have grown older i find that taking on greater responsibilities is essential, standing your ground and not bending with the wind but striving to push forward even though it's difficult.    

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M E M O R E X = M E M O R I E S - The Minds Eye </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 13:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CIALYN - Secret Garden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 13:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 13:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So glad you posted this, I really like your music and plan on adopting a few of your ideas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Organise - Philae </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 13:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Will Kill Your Computer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 12:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 20:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The message I am getting from this, loosing someone you really loved, making the world you live in without them a kind of purgatory? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surviving The Storm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 15:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [General] Surviving The Storm -by me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 13:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surviving! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 13:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Across the verdant valley, Across the the flowing rill Lay a house perched on top of a hill.

I crawl with wounded knee,Fingers clutched to the tall grass I climb, I climb to seek refuge from the house perched on top of the hill,

In the distance cumulonimbus silhouettes darken the sky, thunder clapping from some far away place, I am seeking shelter from the house perched on top of the hill.

I climb though broken arrows and spent bullets from past wars,I climb in pain, I climb alone though the detritus of forgotten arguments.

At last with the last glint of sun being swallowed by an angry sky i lay a foot on top , on top where the house lay upon the hill.

I take my tinder and light a fire before the storm, I take a burning branch to set fire to the house on top of the hill, I watch it burn too the ground, I sleep in the rain next to the warm embers of the house that once was,The house on top of the hill no more 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 23:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not your fault, shit happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 14:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mycelium is the vegetative part of a fungus.

So yea yo dat wall is crazy jacked up like a crack head who smoked a whole bundle and escaped from the trap house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 14:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's  the chalk or plaster being drawn out of the wall because of a leak and creating a good host for mycelium growth.

You better get that checked asap, this can cause breathing problems and many other illnesses....not to mention damage to your house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Truck hits a tree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 01:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tree surgeon Tom Connelly held own head on while in 7m up a tree after chainsaw accident </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 01:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 23:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mycenas are hard to identify to species and some are distinguishable only by microscopic features such as the shape of the cystidia. Some species are edible, while others contain toxins, but the edibility of most is not known, as they are too small to be useful in cooking. Mycena cyanorrhiza stains blue and contains the hallucinogen psilocybin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japanese Fire Tree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 20:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blue Mycena Mushroom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 20:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An aerial photo of the destruction caused from an exploding warehouse in Tianjin China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 18:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eric Andre - Vomit Scene with Lauren Conrad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 16:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 16:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea man, Mr. Henry is a really intense guy, There just teenager's and it wasn't like it was just him and her...No...he had a full camera crew behind him...in a crowded room.

His logic seems to be  "hey i'm having a private moment you interrupted me" ...Thing is your in a crowded public space with a full camera crew around you surrounded by young teens.....that's not a private moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 15:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did he say?, I barely understood a word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 14:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true, I make music and I'm batshit crazy, At least I know it.

The real cringe is that will.i.am has no idea that he's nuts, he just vomits out words hoping that they will somehow congeal into something solid.

He seems to have no clear vision or final point of what he is going to say.....you know he may very well have severe ADD now that I think about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 14:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get the impression her husband was a police officer?

Very touching in so many ways   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 11:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You showed him love, good on you dude for taking him in.

It's always going to be heartbreaking when we loose a dog, at least for Max he died knowing that you loved him.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  fentanyl

I lost a friend to that shit, People have no clue what's coming there way before it's to late. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, go and tell her how you feel...don't just leave her hanging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 01:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 14:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The harpy is one of the largest species of eagle. As is often the case with birds of prey, females are larger than males. The birds can grow to 36-40 inches. Females weigh between 13 to 20 lbs

I found a pic showing how big they are http://imgur.com/gallery/fuklu/comment/530337729 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This HUGE Harpy eagle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 14:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 02:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every Time you see an electric chainsaw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 23:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When this dickhead falls ill...I fucking bet you, he will have an Indian doctor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 13:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve Irwin did a lot for animals in his short life, that said i never really appreciated his up close and personal stile..."peacefully sleeping is the red back spider till I come up and rattle him by his nest"

David Attenborough in my book is far more informative and less intrusive.

Whatever though Steve Irwin's heart was in the right place, too bad for him he died the way he did.....Steve donated allot of his money to nature conservation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 14:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I where a ghost I would be so bored of the freaking people out game, After the first year of moving chairs and knocking on doors etc...I'd write a letter saying, " hey bro i'm the ghost living here, I sure would mind if you stop masturbating to porn in the living room as i am confined to only a few spaces in this apartment,also can we get HBO i get really bored being here all day long."

PS how about we cook dinner Friday night, You like chicken francese?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 14:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to try making something like this, I like the soft pad as a bass line, interesting idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 22:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ken Bone is a better man then I am, We need more people like Ken in this world.

Ken if your listening I am going to vote, You inspired me not only with your message but with your big heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Matt Mercier, Brian Brown   Joe Charnitski </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 03:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy convinces girlfriend to get his name tattooed on her forehead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 02:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 22:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very interesting, for 1985... this was way ahead of it's time.

I know BoC is heavily inspired by the 70's, 80's ....it makes me wonder what  Doxa Sinistra where inspired by.


I never heard of Doxa Sinistra before this post, however, I bet BoC has and was inspired by these sounds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great post funazza, very inspiring track....love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really think you might enjoy my subreddit /r/SoundsLikeBoC, we have tuns of music that sounds like BoC. ;  ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kevin Wilson: Out of Print </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eve Plumb   The Pittsburgh StorySLAM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 20:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very interesting gem here, I must have missed this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 13:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've got jail

FIFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 23:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was ORKID part of it?

Anyways, I agree Solar Bears will be missed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Solar Bears - Across Yesteryear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 13:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kiteracer 2 (Guitar Cover) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 17:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 16:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BrianPeppersFan this sub is pretty Lighthearted, If there is a chance that some of the content is facetious so be it....so are we.

Making fun of a bad song or a work of art is not that serious, After all i'm a delusional artist myself https://soundcloud.com/user-345283577/without-beat.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 15:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this video implying Racism ?

I just see a bunch of girls fighting over god knows what.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 15:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think what you saw was a newfoundland https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/564x/b5/94/15/b59415fe0eb4908662575c865115db56.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 14:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so surprised he has never denounced his faith after everything he held dear turned out to be a lie and they molested his daughter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 18:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone link to this song I really like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 17:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure why you got downvoted, I think your right.....she is at her wits end trying to support her family i'm guessing alone.

She has never been afforded an education, maybe it's her fault maybe it's not, could even be her upbringing......whatever the case is, we as a people/country need to increase more kinds of help/services to those in need.

It's our only hope for future generations.

If you look at this video and think, wow what bad behavior ...your right.

I am just saying how far can you be Whittled away before you break, we are not all equal in this world, 
. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 15:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is having a mental break down.....never getting ahead can drive you batshit crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 23:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My fairy tail is better than yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 16:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not thrilled to say i have been on food stamps/welfare before, I will tell you it sucks, you can never get ahead or live in any capacity on welfare alone.

It's not a free ride here in the U.S, I had to work for my benefits, I also had a side job and i was still sinking. 

So I actually think we should give out more money, Most families on welfare are way below the poverty line.


Better work programs, livable wages,benefits that work, These things we need for a better future for our poor.


As it stands now, our broken benefits make for broken families, It's a dark and depressing world being on benefits.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 16:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point page_8!

I certainly don't hate gay people of any kind, The last thing on my mind is what other people do with there private parts.....the people who do are assholes.

Basically what i'm seeing here is these SJW's want the government to step in and make assholes speak in a more acceptable way......good luck with that.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 14:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  EDC spinners

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r0OJFyHZ7V8

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=13jScMXI8bg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 13:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the new podcasts will be posted here automatically via rss.

I hope it stays working. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 23:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is were Ethan shines, He is brilliant at picking things apart.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diana Spechler: "Natural Selection" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 21:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 20:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how Reddit works, the discussions,the people and all the small communities that make up Reddit as a whole.

I want Reddit to have r/TheMothRadioHour  .

I'd like to think that Reddit is a great way to find new and interesting content.




r/TheMothRadioHour  is a sub i'd subscribe too, So i made it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 19:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very good question,

In the future i would like to have a expansive collection of all the Moth Radio podcasts,videos ETC, I also want to implement the ability to search by flair with advanced search options... so you can find an episode you missed or find new ways to stumble on interesting content.

I also would like to implement a PlayLister so you can cue a few things up and listen to them on your car ride or at home.

I think that's enough for me to chew on for now : )   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 19:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must be out of the loop, Iv'e heard so many touching stories..some of which... even brought me to tears.

Buy hey if you don't like it, you just don't like it  \_()_/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tracey Segarra: Blame </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 16:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adam Gopnik: LOL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 16:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 16:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything you think will improve this sub can and will be considered.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 16:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :  )

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome to r/TheMothRadioHour, I am hoping to make this place great, Suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 16:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 16:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still a work in progress,however, If I can attract more subscribers that will allow me to Listen to the community and make positive changes.

PS, I am looking for approved submitter's...pm me if your interested.

Thank You   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello from /r/TheMothRadioHour, I made a happy home for all the "Moth" related content, I'm hoping to attract all you Moth fans out there, I left the light on for you ; ) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 15:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tony Birch   Brad Lawrence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 00:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 22:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These people brutally murder people and film it, what kind of religion is this shit!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nothing to see here, Everything is perfect. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 22:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 01:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I too love this song, sad to say video is pure cringe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 13:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 13:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the detuning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 13:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What gets me to is he was about to get barber chaired, he sawed straight into the fracture....lucky guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 13:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So true, also that stress fracture almost barber chaired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 02:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This couple must be doing something right, They had that one bear for more than 20 years...and they still have limbs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deru - 1979 (On a Snowy February Day) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Faex Optim - Winter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 00:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 13:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aaa memories, the old roflcopter https://giphy.com/gifs/landing-irish-attempted-13VnAsKZhLgIbm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tara Clancy   Adrienne Truscott </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 04:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stories in this Episode,

1 - Unicorn Tattoo by Angela Lush

2 - Little Lonely Bird by TJ McDonald </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Podcast Angela Lush   TJ McDonald </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stories in this Episode,

1 - Mission to India by George Lombardi

2 - Catholic School Dropout by Mary Navarre </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Podcast: George Lombardi  amp; Mary Navarre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stories in this Episode: 

1 - Eye of the Beholden by Tracy Rowland

2 - Ready or Not by Carlos Kotkin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Podcast: Tracy Rowland  amp; Carlos Kotkin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 15:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have DM'd the mod 2 weeks ago seems he has been inactive for 4 months.

 I'd like to merge /r/TheMothRadioHour over to /r/themoth if i can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Requesting /r/themoth inactive Mod </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 14:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 14:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everyone, I am trying my best to get everything working.

Be patient, In the end all the new content will be automatically posted and organized.

I hope you all enjoy the work I put in so far.

I absolutely love The Moth and I have high hopes this Sub will be awesome when i'm done.

Thank You too all the new subscribers 

* The Fade </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> noby - Oppenheimer (Compomix) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 03:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 01:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm working on that now.

Trying to get automated feed going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is a real photo,though it looks like something from a TTA book. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 23:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/TheMothRadioHour is looking for someone with good css skills. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 21:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 19:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anybody have talent creating banners?
I think that's what is needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FOX - CANADA DRY TRAX </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> noby - Untitled song snippet (work in progress) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uniserve  amp; Ustice - 2 Pieces In B.O.C.-Style. by Sk'p </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alone In Town - Catch My Dream </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tony Cyprien: Bullshit Repellant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 15:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 14:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also guy airs his dirty laundry all over the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anthony Griffith: The Best of Times, The Worst of Times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 23:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike DeStefano: Franny's Last Ride </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 23:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malcolm Gladwell: Her Way </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 23:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jerry Stahl: Kicking the Horse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 23:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wanda Bullard: The Small Town Prisoner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 23:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stephanie Summerville: Life Support </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 23:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 23:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been only working on it for 2 days.

It will look great when i'm done so be patient, it's a work in progress.

My moderation team will be there for us.

*  subject2129 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 18:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [This](/r/TheMothRadioHour) is what i have started, All i did was so far is create the the sub.

Give me a few days to code the css too make it look nice, if anybody is interested in modding send me a PM and tell me how you can contribute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 03:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's 4chan with a picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 01:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once looked 15 minutes for my car keys, they were in my hand : / </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moth The Past Wasn't Done With Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 22:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 17:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does seem fake, I have to agree with everybody sharing that sentiment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 02:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So true, They need long hikes,and other types of dogs to be around.

They are not a house dog, I walk my buddy 2 hours a day and it's  never enough.

Though i think i'm  doing ok because he is so happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 02:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Pyrenees

I have a great Pyrenees, They are VERY special dogs.

He consonantly checks the perimeter of our property for intruders, they bark at anything they see as a threat.

He is no doubt a killing machine, it's hard to convince anybody of that because on the other hand he is super patient,sweet,understanding and super intelligent.

My big teddy bear can and will cause damage, but a small child can pull on his ears and even cause him pain, he wouldn't harm a single hair on a child or a friend.

I rescued him from a kill shelter,I got him because i love big dogs,I never knew what the breed had to offer....great,loyal,loving,understanding guard dog.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
