<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2519</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ronaldo does quite a lot for charity and does have any tattoos so he can donate blood.

Messi on the other hand is a tax fraud who should be in jail but because he is who he is that never happened-so maybe put him in he story  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sitting alone and doing nothing is probably making it worse. I know it's so hard but maybe try and do something. Like go for a walk everyday just for something to do? Maybe try playing video games online where you could just have some conversation with random people? Just something to take your mind of it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Charlie Cox and the guy who plays Wilson Fisk do a really good job I know u haven't given it a chance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the highest rated comic book shows... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Division and AC Unity... that's just your opinion I doubt you have put much time into either both are solid at the very least and many really like both  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just want to make a quick point a lot of the middle eastern Christians, including the Armenians did welcome the Crusaders as saviours to begin with but later on many found them to be worse than the Seljuks and Arabs in a lot of ways.

But I am definitely up for a First Crusade AC, why don't they make the character a Fatimid Egyptian instead? Someone who could maybe play/help both sides as they try to offer help to the Crusaders  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also RIP to the people killed in London-my home city-scary times  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Daredevil and Iron Fist fight each other in the Defenders - Matt betta kick his ass! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone feels Matt and Claire's relationship was natural but her's and Luke's feels really forced? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just rewatched DD season 1 to get the taste of Iron Fist out of my mouth (not totally bad but wanted to remind myself of how a really good superhero show is done) and I really like Matt and Claire's relationship. How they both want to be together but realise they can't because of him being Daredevil.Then she goes for a guy with bullet proof skin who fights people in the open because that is so much easier!?  Not to mention their relationship didn't even feel like it made sense-when they finally got together I just thought 'wtf!?' Am I the only one.

Also Claire is a way better character in Daredevil. Being really preachy about killing in Iron Fist was annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is part true. They made every Muslim convert to  Christianity or leave in 1492 but many only did it for appearance. Most were still Muslim. In 1536 Philip II tried to make these conversos leave all their customs behind like speaking Arabic and this prompted the revolt in Granada in 1537. Only in 1609 did Philip III finally kick all the Muslims out of the country   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Combined with all the other contextual reasons people have said (war with the Dutch) the Kings that followed Philip II were all pretty bad.

Phillip II would micro manage everything and immersed himself in state affairs. His son and grandson cared way more about leisure activities and left the job of governing to their court favourites and this helped bankrupt the country. Whether it was Portugal leaving the Union or the Catalans revolting all took their toll. The other powers circled round taking territory they're always desired-France did this the most. Philip's great grandson was mentally handicapped and could have children his reign was even worse. He died without an heir and the other powers moved in to put someone they wanted on the thrown.

The Spanish empire never recovers from this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 07:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And all of the other people cut out like Martin Sheen etc loads of famous people had roles cut out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best bolt action rifle? (Without scope) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 06:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I recently been using the scout class and these types of guns and I'm loving it. I started with the Gewehr 95 moved on to the Lebel and now I'm using the Lee Enfield which is beast. But which one really is the best? I feel the Enfield because of its 10 rounds before reload and the simplicity of reloading especially compared to the Lebel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are a lot more out there -personally I feel when he's confined by a story (Thin Red Line and this movie) he's better  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch it - the ending is pretty straight forward as Malick films go  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Accents of who? Colin Farrell had his normal Irish accent - the rest had standard English ones - language wasn't too different  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I was thinking of this scene when I wrote it - those little orphan kids are perfect  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terrence Malick's 'The New World' is an incredible movie everyone should check out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a lot of people hate him but I feel this and The Thin Red Line are two of his best. For me the way the New World has been filmed really adds to the feeling we are seeing what it was really like. The bleakness of it at times really made me realise just how shitty it would be to live in this era. Beautiful soundtrack by James Horner, great visuals and good performances from Farrell and Bale. Movie that will stick with you, especially if you love to visualise old time periods.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The writer of house of cards constantly attacks Trump on twitter so kinda hard - also HoC reflects a lot of elements of real life (Petrov, ICO) so it's not unthinkable some part of season 5 could be influenced by the 2016 election  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he would be bad because he's weak more than having bad ideas  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funnily enough these stats are nearly exactly like me apart form my K/D is 2.03. I've played 74 hrs weird.

What's you main class? I've done most of mine with Lewis Gun optical and support </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had four Scottish guys screaming down their mics in my squad at 4:45am - was a lot of fun was cracking up the whole time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 07:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used the scout class my kd got better and I love the rifles without scopes ! Fit my play style perfectly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 06:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so I've unlocked it and I love playing a scout who gets into the action - can't believe I haven't used these guns before!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game gives you so little achievement I've become obsessed with my K/D and stats  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better than Luke Cage worse than JJ and way worse than DD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes thank you I totally forget this part of the OT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone wish the guns weren't locked behind challenges? Maybe they could give them out later on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've unlocked the two new guns for support, which is my main class. However I want to try the new infantry variant of the new sniper but I don't want to risk my stats and stuff attempting to unlock it with a class I'm not good with. Does anyone think and some point they should auto unlock? We did pay money for new content after all - I get for balancing there needs to be some slowdown on people acquiring them but still.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not unplayable but I'll admit it's too easy for the defence. I've won the first map about 3 times out of 6 plays on attack. Normally you have to get a couple of good squads pushing up the hill while the majority attack the Middle. Needs some adjustments though - still love this map even when I lose! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure it's a mode only for the DLC so while it will eventually be for the general player base it's only on the new maps so you will have to buy They Shall not Pass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 32154  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Luke the Chosen One? I always thought it was Anakin... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 08:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iron fist is... not bad! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 07:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When did she get more Indian ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can do both just play smart. Obviously depends what class if you're playing assault or medic can't fault the low K/D. I feel with support you can enter the objective but hang back abit to suppress and kill without dying too much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hadn't even caught up but watched it immediately when I saw the host of Rebels recon tweeting about it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we get Lenny and Frank into a room!? Surely they could exist in the same universe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 07:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had a really good team and actually won - very hard though but tonnes of fun! Definitely needs to be easier to take the hill  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 00:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's smarter than everyone else so I guess we all think we are Frank-so yeah I am on his team  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never skip it so fuck you netlfix 

Nil nil! Nil nil nil!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah that's amazing wish I could bump into him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does he live in London?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 08:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UNCLE MOE HERE I AM!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's lack of accuracy over long range (and limited bullets) means it will probably be fine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they were dropped on Japan? Just developing a bomb for Germany doesn't mean you defo have to use it for them. And do you develop any other type of weapon just to fight one enemy? Usually, no you don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only in the Trump administration does the mad dog seem like a moderate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So at the time as most of allies saw it, they were dropped to bring a quick end to the war. The Japanese were not big on surrender and would have mostly fought to the death in a mainland invasion of Japan. Allied casualties would be extremely high and since they had the technology why would they waste the lives of their own troops.

As time has gone on it has become more cynical. Revenge for Pearl Harbour is one factor but not the biggest. A massive one was keeping the USSR out of Japan, as they had already taken over the North of Korea and they were currently doing battle with the Japanese in Mongolia. Allowing the war to continue might mean Japan being split into.

Now the most cynical aspect is the racial element. Many have now argued that the US constantly demonised the common 'Jap' as no better than an animal. Many have thought the nuke would have never been used on Germany if the roles were reversed because they were white and had a shared history with the US.

Overall I think many of these factors play a role but I believe that ending the war quickly and not having to lose more US life is the main reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a man in China in about 4th century AD who worked out Pi to a certain number forgot which. There is a constellation named after him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe we are just used to the guy from the other maps ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use the bipod and stay back abit-shoot from a distance, I got the 50 kills in one game this way  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made sure I eased myself back into the game last night after playing Zelda/Horizon for a couple weeks. Did really well today even when using the new guns. Ranked up to 70 and got my K/D to 2.00 you just need to get back into it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50 bucks for premium retards can buy it on its own when it comes out-how can you be in this sub but be so clueless!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not too great in the game. Doing well with it so far but pretty frustrating to use  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently got 1,800 with the Lewis Gun optical finally switched to the new DLC gun feels strange - nice accuracy though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That one looked more annoying so I went for the low weight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What makes Abraham Lincoln one of the best US Presidents (in public opinion and rated by historians) apart from winning the Civil War and ending Slavery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone love he fact Elliot wears his hoodie over a tuxedo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see that, his personality really clashes with the positivity of the rest of them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this because of his 'sexist' comments? 

All that stupid uproar aside I'm glad he's leaving. He turned (maybe always was) a douche after leaving IGN. He thinks he's the shit and somehow thinks his stupid libertarian politics were given to him divinely and no one can criticise them. Anyway I know people like him this is pretty shocking tbh 

Also loving his embracing of Dave Rubin and Glenn Beck (facepalm). Just can't stand people who have politics like these guy but think they have re-invented the wheel by preaching them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When me and little bro kept shouting dogs cunt while playing rocket league  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So an actor who got a golden globe for playing a great character is not good in your opinion because they killed off a character that had come to the end of his arc ? Also the show is about Nucky, not Jimmy. Killing Jimmy is a massively important movement in Nucky turning into a full gangster.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever one of those butt hurt Jimmy fans  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You hated his character? Not surprising because he got found an 'insult in a bed of roses' (as Nucky said) and was extremely violent. You are meant to hate them. And don't tell me you hated the show because a certain character died at the end of season 2...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Django, Frank Underwood, The Punisher and Don Draper make a movie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 06:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doing my history degree covering a lot about Vietnam - at least he wasn't a civilian, happened slot in that war. What are your feelings about the conflict in general? Do you feel the whole theory of Vietnam becoming part of the monolithic Red Bloc to be false since they went to war with China in 1979? Do you feel the country is worse off now for the South not winning the war?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey people can die doing anything and you can't blame yourself. Sure you suggested cycling but if she went on a different day, a different hour,  a different minute she wouldn't be dead. It's not your fault  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Returning players - how long did it take you to find a home planet and build a house/get a car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 23:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going to return to this game and some point (always liked it despite the lack of stuff to do) but realistically how long will it take me to get some of the new things? Currently on my third year of uni and have dissertation and junk-I have time for games. But currently focused on Zelda, Horizon and then Mass Effect in a couple weeks. I want to play some NMS but want to know how much time I will have to dedicate to it-thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man a Fallout type game based on Tatooine would be amazing   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 21:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love expensive healthcare, police brutality, huge amount of gun homicides, bombing innocence in the Middle East every day, completely corrupt politicians, a huge private prison industry, institutional racism, news networks that act as propaganda for the unbreakable two party system. Good portions sizes at restaurants though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game looks beautiful and is extremely detailed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not a true united fan if you don't hate on Chelsea gtfo and support city  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but Chelsea are know for being white skinheads/racists  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simmer down neo-Nazi  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actor who plays him is good watch Boardwalk Empire  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg Chelsea you're so funny and you were fucking shite before Russian oil money  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does the US use the insurance model of healthcare despite being the richest country on Earth? Britain at its lowest point economically (late-40's post WW2) created the NHS. Many poorer European countries have universal health care so why haven't the US adopted it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't talk to her and allow her to get off for abusing her employees. Just don't get involved despite her being your friend  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah yeah sorry I liked your point and wanted to add </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you can't suddenly not be a homosexual anymore. Once you know you are on there is no going back or denying it. Also I love your casual homophobia maybe being brought up religious failed you? Don't seem to be too understanding. The main problem should be that your husband didn't tell you, not that he did some of this stuff and the problem with him being a homosexual is not because it against you bs religion, it is that he might not actually be attracted to you because he's secretly gay  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Not entirely unjustified' how about entirely justified based on nearly 70 years of fucking over the Middle East ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard it is complex and just as much of a mind fuck as Mr Robot but it's execution is a lot worse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In WD1 you literally kill a character from AC4  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happens to me at launch for some reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can think of a lot better women for a 20 year old still in Uni than marrying an escort who is 10 years older, lives in another country and has two kids... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harming animals is not okay and the way you physically abused your dog shows there is something mentally wrong with you. As you said in the past you had PTSD so I assume it may be coming back if you want to hurt an innocent animal (your cat who you describe as being a good pet) just because he is whining like all pets do. Definitely go see another therapist focusing on anger and violent behaviour. 

If you were simply being mean you might tell a pet to go away or try to ignore it - not constantly wanting to harm it. You're lying to yourself if you think your just being mean, if you let your mental health be you could possibly end up being violent to humans  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah! The darknesss and silence in the nightttt - definitely gunna remind me off it too now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Metal Gear Zelda... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so this game is nothing like he MGS series but players of both: do you find all the little secrets and cool methods of doing things feels like a Metal Gear game. Like if you feel like you can do it, you usually can and you can find cool ways of completing objectives that the game never tells you to do. Feels like Kojima has a light touch in this game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 07:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That much drinking is really bad for your health and weight-not too mention all that dope probably makes him lazy and unambitious. If you stay with the him you might end up with a overweight guy who just goes to work comes home and gets stoned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Britain ever come close to war with Franco's Spain after World War 2? Would they have if necessary? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my friends mom grew up in Gibraltar in the 1960's and there was always a fear that Franco would try and take it back for Spain. I think at times he blocked the Countries border with Spain. So my question is was did the UK and Spain ever come close to war after WW2, and if they didn't how likely would it have been to escalate? Would they a have sent a military force to liberate it like they did the Falklands?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are different but do share some quite striking similarities. It's clear Horizon has been influenced by the Witcher  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel a similar way-I think the Witcher 3 does trump it for me but it's still up there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be abit careful since he started seeing you 6 months after she died-really that is no time at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It reminds me of ACIII more than anything - and I think Aloy's vision is done a lot better than eagle vision -you don't need to constantly rely on it and it doesn't change the colours too much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 07:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice how you've ignored what we have done in the Middle East in my other comment, oh you can go on - I wonder how rapes were commuted by white people in those countries? Being a rapist is synonymous with being a Muslim and this stereotype perpetrated by right wingers in America, and Christian apologists who become atheist but still have a bias to their old religion. Fundamentalist Muslim counties treat women like shit. If you don't know Iraq and Syria aren't fundamentalist Muslim countries. The refugee rapists are people who are rapists. Not people who rape because Islam tells them too.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a big problem with Sam Harris. So his argument about Muslims and the A-bomb is quite annoying. He says because they are so fundamentalist and belief in martyrdom they wouldn't hesitate to try and bring the end of the world through using it willy nilly. He says if a 'country' had it rather than a terror group. Newsflash Pakistan has the bomb and its fundamentalist Muslim. Just because you are a Muslim, even a fundamentalist, doesn't mean your whole life is just about Islam. Their is still human nature to take into account. He generalises abit too much for me but he has some good points    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Response so far has been mainly supportive  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you would be more sympathetic if these Muslims we oppressed by a great super power?

Why don't you go look at the history of the British and French Empires in the Middle East and North Africa and then research the history of the US in the Middle East.

Who suppressed Iraq's initial desire for independence after World War One? The British 

Same thing but in Syria? The French 

In Algeria? The French

In Egypt? The British

In Palestine? The British

Who overthrew Iran's democratic government in favour of an absolute dictator to get better oil deals? The US and the UK

Who invaded Iraq based on false evidence creating the huge mess we have today? The UK and the US

See? Muslims alone oppressing eachother? Add a century of western oppression that's created this awful situation.

I am British. I admit what we have done is wrong. We deal with the refugee crisis, we have more Muslims living in Britain than the US has-no mass hysteria, no rapes on every corner, no terror every day-does this happen sometimes? Sure. But being blindly anti-Islam based on racial stereotypes is how your worldview is affected and people like you make sure real criticism of Islam is ignored.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See what you have just done is why we can't have nice things.

Europe isn't in chaos from Muslim culture. Are there bad incidents? Undeniably. Is it an epidemic no. 

This how comment is just generalising massively and I really haven't got time to point out how wrong you. You're pretty delusional and definitely drank the cool aid provided by the likes of Trump and Farage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooo You're hard  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you have done here is just a massive generalisation. Yes true some Muslims from foreign countries don't (if you mean this specify) but personally being from London I know a ton of Muslims who aren't defined by being a Muslims and are perfectly compatible with western society (think of people like Sadie Khan). Also a lot of gulf countries are becoming more westernised (Iraq, Kuwait etc) so you ought to be more specific if you are trying to say Muslims immigrants from fundamentalist countries like Saudi Arabia and Pakistan find it hard to assimilate rather than 'Muslims' in general.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who said I do  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do we 'fear' Islam ? I don't I just think religion is stupid and dangerous I don't fear it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously Islam isn't a race but people generally only hate and mainly discriminate against the Arab/Turk Muslim rather than a white Balkan Muslim.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really the belief that Arab (or middle eastern people in general not just Arab) are all Muslims and of the fundamentalist variety so you should be scared of them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Irrational fear of believing Muslims will conquer you white Christian country and impose sharia is irrational-and yeah I agree but go to Africa to see violent Christianity  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that is really shitty Canada in some instances seems like liberalism gone awry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's trying to not be seen as a racist/bigot 'oh it's just their culture/religion nothing to do with me'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that comes from their discrimination in white countries like the US and France but I see your point  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See that is irrational-if you are living in a white western country or an Asian one why are you scared someone is going to do all of those things solely because they are a Muslim? Now someone might do those things because they are an extremists.

Now if you talking about Sharia law that is a legitimate concern and those thing systematically happen in places like Saudi Arabia but the irrational fear is people in America thinking Muslims will take over and make it look like Saudi Arabia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly Chopper good point!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's basically a fear of Muslims based on racial stereotypes of arabs aswell as believing most support jihadist groups  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone get annoyed that legitimate criticism of Islam has been destroyed by 'Islamophobia' !? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I am in the planning phases of my podcast where I am going to harshly criticise each religion. I've studied Islam a lot at Uni and there are so many things that get lost in the racist stereotype of Muslims sweeping western country. Muslims are basically hated for the colour of their skin and the association with terrorism but rarely do we see a intellectual criticism of Islam without the people doing it being called 'racist'.

Where in the mainstream media or even alternative media do we hear a lot of people say Muhammad was a conquering warlord who killed and enslaved many? Where do people say he knew Jewish and Christian merchants so it's no surprise Angel Gabriel (same one who visited Mary what a coincidence!) visited Muhammad. If you delve into it, it's so clear Muhammad just copied abrahamic religion and added himself to further is own power-but again we don't hear this often. (Much easier to get followers when you take what they know and add yourself as the newest chapter-right Jesus?)

It's all well and good to criticise Christianity (and people do it all the time easily) but does anyone else find it so frustrating that people are afraid to criticise Islam in the same way out of fear of being labelled a racist/bigot? 

All religion is bullshit but I just wished we would criticise each as harshly as the other but in an intellectual way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You fucking stole my strategy/video !!!!!!! https://www.reddit.com/r/horizon/comments/5x9rv3/a_perfect_blend_of_tripwires_and_a_stampede_no/?st=IZXEFP0I sh=e1f4045b </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The original trippy TV dream Sequence... (Recess) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 17:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Map is misleading - Australia, India and China are way bigger than they appear  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
