<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1101</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 00:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he's just referring to his movies like Inferno/The Dilemma simply being lousy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 20:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James is still recovering from what Oswald unleashed on him and deserved absolutely none of it. 

Is he? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 01:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's posted in the_donald a few times, so probably not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 22:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like a lot of CSNY music but David Crosby is an old fart. He's blathered about rap [not being music](https://twitter.com/thedavidcrosby/status/607152874024345600) in the past and this isn't the first time he's taken shots at Kanye (["he can't write, sing, or play, at all ... he is an egomaniac ... he is dumb as a post ... he creates nothing ... helps no one"](https://twitter.com/thedavidcrosby/status/619007384174747648)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HRC supporters might not if this significantly damages her numbers, because she hasn't got a lot of time left to pull them back up and Trump is already proven to be basically indestructible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 02:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm exaggerating, iirc the most conservative county is Placer. Orange County is probably the state's most well-known Republican fortress though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is. Doesn't show if you're viewing a reply I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I live in the most conservative county in the state, where I see support for conservatives! CALIFORNIA CONFIRMED RED!!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 15:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Underneath the "tallies here now" counter, click (edit) where it shows your username. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 04:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm planning to destroy all TVs ever made so Legends of Chamberlain Heights won't get any ratings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 04:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *didn't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 00:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get mentioning it but the way it was made front and center in these obits is ridiculous. From THR:
Michael Massee, the actor who unfortunately will forever be known as the man who accidentally shot and killed Brandon Lee on the set of the 1994 film The Crow, has died. He was 61.

WTF? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 22:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've seen a couple now. I still think what I said stands because most of those aren't upvoted and the top comments (from both people who like/dislike Trump) are all condemning this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally can't find a single "wow this was a great thing to do" comment in this thread, and the general consensus among both sides seems to be that this was boneheaded. Not sure why the "tolerant left" zinger is coming out in such full force. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the thing. I hate Trump, but this was a completely brainless move. If you celebrate this, all you're gonna do is fuel the right and give them more ammo to bash how "tolerant" the left is, as is being done in this thread as I type. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 18:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain why people got so mad about his James Rolfe tweet? His comment was dickish, but I don't really see why it was worth being shredded over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 18:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes you think he's having trouble staying relevant? He's always been a very well-known comedian, his latest standup special dropped the day (or before?) she died. I doubt he really needs this extra push. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 17:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 17:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oof, that dude's an asshole, but that's also crossing the line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 17:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:
Six months later, the coroners office still has not declared a cause of death. I have a feeling it might have been an overdose, [Oswalt] said, citing the Xanax. Thats what the paramedics there were saying while I was screaming and throwing up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Episodes Curran wrote:

* "Treehouse of Horror 13" (segment "Island of Dr. Hibbert") 
* "I'm Spelling as Fast as I Can" 
* "My Big Fat Geek Wedding" 
* "Don't Fear the Roofer" 
* "We're on the Road to D'ohwhere"
* "The Wife Aquatic"
* "Sex, Pies and Idiot Scrapes"
* "Rednecks and Broomsticks"
* "The Greatest Story Ever D'ohed"
* "How Munched is That Birdie in the Window?"
* "The Winter of His Content" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kevin Curran, Writer For The Simpsons, Dead At 59 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 01:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His IMDb says he's 5'2", that's probably why. It's definitely wrong, though. If I had to guess I'd say he's 5'7" based on [this photo](http://static5.imagecollect.com/preview/560/d860ed099a5202b) of him next to Catherine Zeta-Jones and Martin Sheen

I've submitted a correction to IMDb, let's see what happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 21:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a year off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 15:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the cup. It's implying that although lemonade costs like two dollars, Trump is too cheap and asks for one of the free water cups and then swindles 'em by filling it up with a fountain drink anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 03:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because he is dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 23:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of it is crappy. But Blowin' My Stack/Trampoline/I'm a Robot/Autopilot should've made it onto albums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 17:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Really good hook. I'd probably fully embrace it if the lyrics weren't terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be down for another Rentals album. If anyone in here hasn't heard Return of the Rentals, you're missing out, it's a great album, and definitely very Blue Album-y. The other two aren't as good (Seven More Minutes in particular is definitely a hot mess) but still worth hearing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 00:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is their first year eligible. A band's debut album has to be 25 years old before they can be nominated, and Ten came out in 1991. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 21:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After that whole fiasco with him recording ladies using the toilet, I'm just gonna assume he's an asshole in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 20:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lack of Smashing Pumpkins kinda surprises me, and I'm not even really a fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 18:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rivers also followed a few heavy left folk lately in addition to LOLGOP. I think that's just him being weird again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 16:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pat is the most openly political member and he definitely dislikes both Trump and Clinton. He seems like a fairly moderate guy. No clue where the others lean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's sure not conventionally attractive, and gals would flock to most any successful musician. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 22:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Cocks hat revival when?](http://i.imgur.com/nfPCBq3.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Al Jean's executive producer credit was AL "YOU'RE NEXT, GUNSMOKE" JEAN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The latter. Pokmon typically airs roughly one new episode a week for a year as a season, so they have 19 50ish episode seasons compared to The Simpsons with 28 22ish episode seasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ed sheeran. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 03:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing that after being tased + Melissa showing him her fortress he's going evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 23:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Thought these low-effort posts were banned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 23:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kotaku in Action </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 22:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree. Reddit goes nuts for this movie and it just absolutely mystifies me. So much filler, awful pacing and structure, very few memorable characters. It's also just kinda not funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 22:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I missed it when it came out and only saw it like 10 years later, so it might've just been overhype that killed it for me. But I really don't get the love. I just don't think any of the characters were funny or endearing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 19:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The short is fantastic too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 06:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll take users at least trying to be creative over "My Fav Scene from [Show]" any day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 04:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was posted by [Busy Philipps, right](https://twitter.com/ziwe/status/787285456526381057)? She has like 300K. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 22:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should you really have to blur the username if it's a celebrity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 19:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feig declined the opportunity to apologize for his remake which performed well below expectations at the box office, in addition to annoying many devotees of the original and undermining reviewers, and killed Sonys hopes for a brand new Ghostbusters franchise.

Yeah, this is clearly a biased clickbait article trying to manufacture controversy after this film has mostly faded from the public eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 19:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This show is frustrating as hell. It's proven multiple times it can be entertaining but it just doesn't seem to want to be and instead insists on coasting using tandy's one-dimensional character traits of episode after episode. It's also just pretty much stopped being a comedy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 05:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aww yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 05:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Joe Jonas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 03:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, this comment is 17 minutes old and has like 10 upvotes, how did this get gil- ohhhhhhhhh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 23:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This joke is a train wreck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 19:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...what does that have to do with Tumblr or feminism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 19:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boy, that mustache sure was awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 06:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friend of a Friend  Fake Smiles and Nervous Laughter  I Love the USA  Jacked Up (Remix) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 02:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [He got it back.](https://www.facebook.com/deanweengroup/posts/1136057233142478) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 00:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hasn't Rivers said he wants it to come out in 2017? Year's not far off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 23:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, iirc Chris Williams (the guy on the cover of The Pod) is Mean Ween. Unless they swapped the name around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 16:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more interesting here than /r/tall. Only so many shower head photos and "bumped my head!" I can take. There's nothing I can really contribute here but it's still interesting to read people's experiences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 15:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ruling Me is cancerous. How the heck is it still here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 17:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure the average viewer doesn't really care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 01:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never been a great judge of height, but I don't think he's that tall. [Here's a photo](http://i.imgur.com/KALlLyK.png) of him and Rivers next to Robert Kirkman, who's 6'. Brian is a fair bit shorter than him and not that much taller than Rivers who's around 5'6. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 20:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brian is more like 5'8 anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 20:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title track isn't even the worst song on the album. That'd be Motion Picture Soundtrack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 19:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That guy sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 15:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't. Horrible unnecessary noisy production, uninteresting melody, and terrible lyrics. It says a lot about this album that it's not even one of the worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 06:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That video is more like 12 years later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 05:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh, LA Girlz doesn't really seem too much like Blue to me. The production and instrumentation is a lot heavier, it doesn't really have that bright Blue sound. I'd probably nominate Summer Elaine and Drunk Dori as the most Blue-like tune from White, but even then it seems pretty distinctly modern Weezer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, there was proof. /r/weezer/comments/4xc064/a_message_to_rweezer/d6enxak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just type whatever you want to find on a page in the URL bar, and an "on this page" should show up beneath the search suggestions/history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Run Away is one of this album's two passable songs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 15:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All jokes aside Smart Girls is infinitely worse than Where's My Sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 03:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Douglas M. Lackey, the show's music editor: http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0480116/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 22:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with Always Sunny. 

I'll throw out South Park (the last 10 or so seasons). I like (even love) most of the stuff in seasons 1-8, but they haven't been reliably funny in years. I think the storytelling has gotten intensely lazy and they rely on boring running gags too much, and I don't really find their insights on current events particularly clever or thought-provoking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 19:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great song. One of my favorite closers. I think this and Smile are probably tied for my favorite Green song. Still the third best Weez album </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 15:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMDB fought it in the past. Look up Junie Hoang. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 15:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.theonion.com/article/humanity-still-producing-new-art-though-megadeths--50983 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 04:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Protip: don't use "BH" on a subreddit dedicated to a band where two of its biggest hits have those initials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 13:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a great song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 04:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have FXX, the Simpsons World app has every episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FXX to hold second "Simpsons" marathon: every episode will air from Nov. 24 to Dec. 6 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 02:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is this funny? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 06:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 21:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goddamn how is Let It All Hang Out still in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 13:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL. pretty sure he was only ever in their band because they liked his appearance and thought he'd bring the Ladies to concerts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 04:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm honestly baffled, how the fuck did any of the above just happen? Some dude randomly trashing the guy for not being a true auteur? A guy going RIP suddenly agreeing that he sucks? Somehow getting to being happy about McG dying? WTF? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lyrics are kinda stupid but I love the harmonica. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 13:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> from season 11, The Mansion Family </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 03:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> waiting on you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 21:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love KOQ, but a lot of that comes from the supporting cast, which doesn't look nearly as impressive here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 05:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone on /r/adultswim posted a letter by someone who was close to him. Apparently an infection caused by food poisoning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 06:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I - I Just Threw Out the Love of My Dreams

M - Miss Sweeney

U - Undone -- The Sweater Song

G - (Girl We Got a) Good Thing

L - Longtime Sunshine

Y - You Gave Your Love to Me Softly

W - Waiting on You

H - Haunt You Every Day

E - El Scorcho

N - No One Else

I - In the Garage

M - Mykel   Carli

P - Paperface

E - Eulogy for a Rock Band

E - Endless Bummer

I - I've Had It Up to Here

N - No Other One </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 02:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is taller by one inch! He has it in the bag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 14:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From me who didn't see it, it wasn't too great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 15:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that song is way worse than Mall or Partying IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 22:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Snow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 03:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that Hash Pipe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 23:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I Care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 23:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pilot to The Cleveland Show explains it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 17:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Male Applebee's sure was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 16:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True yeah. I've seen a lot of people who don't even know there was a drummer before Travis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 06:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark is the only guy from their first two albums still in the band. For a trio that's pretty significant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 06:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel bad for Matt, honestly. That video [where he butchers](https://youtu.be/3PzsZrGFrAs?t=28) the opening to "What's My Age Again" is super hard to watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 06:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freedom of '76 got over 1500 upvotes there once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
