<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asking some dumb shit about the weather. Works all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but waves don't die </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In your ear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 01:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JIZZAM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one with skull and crossbones. Usually hard to miss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank you oh wise brethren from the east r/GetMotivated. My life has been ever so changed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what's the most awkward thing to say after sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Campers, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But *apple pie,* that's as American as you can get </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The squatty potty. It may seem like a gimmick, but that thing *really* helps you take a good shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Granted, I need more sample size to see if it actually works, but Blackjack. After one time at a table for four hours(counting cards with a strict progressive betting strategy), I turned $100 into $225. Unfortunately, I live in Kansas and I am under the age of 21, so whenever I want to do so I have to go down to one of the 18 and up Indian casinos in Oklahoma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any sense of conceit. If someone thinks they're better than someone else, even if it's note, I immediately have a grudge against that person until their death, and it's their burden to prove me otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 08:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assault is still a civil case and can be used against businesses, such as bars, when a bouncer gets too rough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 22:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brb currently calling a doctor to find a remedy for this irony overdose </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also battery is an offensive touching, such as intentionally blowing smoke in someone's face if you know it will be displeasing to them.

EDIT: I realize this has nothing to do with the conversation, I just figured I would try to have at least one real world application of the knowledge I have accumulated this far in in my business law class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make Hockey Great Again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's probably waiting for him to get home </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/nosneeze </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! Jokes on him, our bridges suck too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These, specifically the batting stances and technology, were explanations as to why OP was like my grandfather, not problems with the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does this mean?

My grandfather, raised a farmer and turned into a union iron worker, loved to work with his hands. Much like many older people who like to do manual labor, he feels uncomfortable around technology, and feels no inclination to learn about it, thus leaving him very unlikely to be on Reddit. I on the other hand, raised around technology and not in the isolated environment of a farm, feel comfortable around technology and have faith that I will be more accepting of further technological advancements.

Further, the comment about my grandfather also implied that he is a baseball traditionalist, which he is. While raised on the farm, he was paid to play on his local Independent League team, where he both pitched and played first base. Nonetheless, he, at his old age, is agitated easily by flashy batting stances, such as that of Mike Aviles or Gary Sheffield. He is also agitated by the long, drawn out tactics that managers use now, much like OP. Further, OP's argumentative style had very little structure and were largely things that caused him to be angry, regardless of how rational or irrational each of those problems may be. Ramblings such as this come from my grandfather as well. 

This is why I made my original comment. Hope this helps you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, sounds like medieval warfare, but entertaining nonetheless  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that American football is different than the traditional football(soccer, in American terminology), I'm just very confused as to how a lawn dart even makes it feasible to play football, and now especially with swords </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I didn't know my grandfather was on Reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And much more shouting of "[WHO DO YOU THINK YOU ARE? I AM](https://www.youtube.com/shared?ci=OCqihdEY9wQ)" or other incoherent bullshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cue: Joel Embiid vs. Isaiah Thomas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition, if they hit the referee with the challenge flag projectile, they receive an extra point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your definition of American Football? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst team in the NFL plays the National Champion in an exhibition game. I swear there were a few years that Bama could've beaten the Browns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't poke the bear r/baseball </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I could get a "fuck off" from a former president, that would still be a successful day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live 3 miles from where this happened. I live 5 miles from the Jewish Community Center that was the victim of the mass shooting in 2014. It's been a rough couple years for high profile hate crime in my area, despite it being consistently rated as one of the nicest places to live in America. I can assure you all, this is not like rural Mississippi, as always, these are isolated nutjobs. These tragedies are horrible to watch right in front of my eyes, and I have no idea why they keep happening right around me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Social Media: Distracting you from the pointless conundrum that our lives really are! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: I once combined both and tweeted at Aramark Sports while at a pro game because I got shitty food and they came and gave me a $20 voucher. Twitter is wondrous! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on the real life story of Jeff Sessions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Your daughters hot and I'd love to get a piece of that ass."

Let's see how much restraint the former most powerful man in the world has when it comes to being a father. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fountains of Wayne. Those dudes were the shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The word "moist." 

I wish I could return to childhood innocence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya no the American ones are terrible and hiss at literally everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next year he can have an underwater welding party, and if he screws anything up, everyone dies! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little long, but bear with me.

On Christmas morning, a kid unwraps his presents to find a new bike. He absolutely loves it, and takes it out for a spin. While out in the park with his brand new bike, a mounted police officer stops him and asks him, "Hey buddy, did you get that bike for Christmas?"

Eager to show off his newest source of pride, the kid answers "Yes, I did," so the cop answers "Next Christmas, you should ask for some reflectors," and hands him a $20 ticket. 

The kid, now very agitated, asks the cop whether he got his horse for Christmas. Playing along, the cop says "Why yes I did."

To that, the kid responds, "Well next Christmas, how about you ask for a horse with the dick on the bottom instead of the top," and rides off.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pregenent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 05:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry that I am not worthy of your presence oh spiciest meme lord </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this what happens when two horses get into cocaine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After turning on my faucet, I was shocked from the static electricity in the water stream. I thought water and electricity don't mix? What gives? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 04:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, you're new here, aren't you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What in tarnation memes on historical rise! Buy now before it's too late! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 03:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what in DEHYDRAATIOOOOOOONNNNNNN </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 03:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 02:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is like a bat-call for u/DoubleDickDude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 02:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if I had sex three times a day, I would allow you to run me around a track an endless amount of times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is this a joke weather channel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is actually incredible how many people don't realize that the AV Club is an Onion affiliate and are legitimately critiquing this article as click bait </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Blart Mall Cop memes making a comeback! Buy now and get rich! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would like to highlight that in just four comments we went from the time it takes to have five people to get AIDS from continual anal sex to a public health announcement on vaginal/anal tears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given the origin of the n-word that it was a derogatory slur made by slave owners, no, I would say that rapping to the Wu Tang Clan is not justification for ignoring hundreds of years of a very ugly chapter of history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this is similar in nature to asking whether it is immoral to be emotionally supportive to a very hot female in a time of emotional distress for her, to try to throw your name in the hat. I tried this(it actually eventually worked), but I felt guilty because I felt the only reason I did it was because she was hot, so I started being emotionally supportive to other people to try to prove to myself that I'm not an ass. I guess I accidentally guilted myself into being a better person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if you're fucking for three days, I feel like your penis would begin to wear down, and begin to bleed, thus creating a quicker cycle because now blood is directly deposited to bloodstreams. I feel like the real question here is, which process would happen quicker: the guy at the back gets AIDS when the guy in front starts with it, or the guy in front gets AIDS because the guy in the back has AIDS. I personally think if the guy in front started with the AIDS, it would be a quicker cycle because of penis bleeding from the sex friction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> go fuck yourself

EDIT: I respect the opinions of all Denzel curry fans, just not this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, obviously they aren't the most comparable in the world because they attack different demographics within Hip-Hop, but I still just wanted to see input outside of me and my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DISCUSSION- RAE SREMMURD VS. DENZEL CURRY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA finds seven earth-like planets that are capable of sustaining life. While this may have nothing to do with Hip-Hop, the sun they rotate around is named TRAPPIST, so looks like we've got some TI and Migos fans in NASA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TRAPPIST

Migos? Gucci Mane? TI? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Supervolcano" scared the shit out of me. I thought the world was going to end the next day for the month after I watched it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freud wins. Anyone else loses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get undressed right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Megan Fox, and, well, the location is on my cock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Betty white. If 2016 couldn't break her, *then I will.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Sacchan?](https://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/5nrazv/japanese_woman_wonders_where_her_dog_sacchan_goes/?st=IZH64OKS sh=8455b537)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a company as large as his, its no wonder that at least one person didn't have a positive experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, after he appeared on WWE, I don't think there were a lot of people collecting memorabilia for him thinking he'd be the president in 7 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, renewables are not pretty much free. Their overhead for the maintenance and overall cost of the solar panels, or wind farms for that matter, were too high to warrant the use of such an inefficient system, especially back in the 80's when renewables were fledgling. If you look at it, minus the pollution argument, foreign oil was vastly cheaper, more efficient(on the dollar), and just more reasonable at the time.

Further, Carter's energy policies totally fucked America, i.e. the energy crisis in he late 70's, when Americans had to wait in line for gas only to have the stations run out, so I think people were pretty sick of the idea that these renewable energies would help bring the exorbitant price of gas down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 07:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I told you Ben! It was all an elaborate trick to embarrass us! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Employees working on a locomotive, Chicago, 1945. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! That happened to me! Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys should date, and if you break up, now you know how to breakup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is a CHAMPION! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was like 5, and I wasn't even feverish or anything, but I was having a nightmare, and I thought I woke up and I looked over at my dresser, and right on my dresser was about a four foot tall dime with FDR staring directly at me, and that scared the everloving shit out of me. Looking back on it, it was probably the worst nightmare I've ever had, and definitely the most bizarre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omg this is literally the third time In the last month this question has made it to the top of this sub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We got Migos on daytime television. Congrats guys, I think it's time to call it a day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read up on it online, it takes about 10 minutes to learn the concept, but it's just about getting quick with it, so I downloaded a Blackjack app and just play that all the time while trying to count. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today is Presidents' Day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However, if all goes according to plan, next year it will be Steve Bannon day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A. Not illegal
B. Not that hard
C. Fun as shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 18, so gambling in my state. Gimme Blackjack, gimme NLH. I would thoroughly enjoy myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Narcos. First episode people are already getting wrecked. It doesn't change over the next 19 episodes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a face tattoo. Try living with that for the rest of your life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obligatory not me, but nonetheless I could not regret this picture more than I do now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure? I've heard he has pretty large hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, if you could have sex with anyone in the world, but they had to be over the age of 60, who would you choose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 06:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And why is Bush's not made out of steel beams? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Historical TV show memes are on the rise! Buy buy buy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 06:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kellyanne Conway debriefing Donald Trump on the Bowling Green massacre (2017) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 06:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the weirdest pickup line you have used that actually succeeded? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> congrats on the sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, *sex* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first thing a science textbook tells you to do is question everything, thus defeating the purpose of the textbook. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 04:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most attractive first baseman available

I actually have no idea in what sense Ken was meaning here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heed peasants, we have a new king now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 03:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey girl, are you a 90 degree angle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cause you looking right.
*silence*
Sorry, was that not acute pickup line?
*silence*
Honestly, I'm very sorry, I'm just being obtuse at this point.
*silence*
But in all reality, I think we'd be complementary together.
*silence*
Just let me supplement that ass.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what are the odds? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 17:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> congrats on the sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 17:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we chat some more, pay the bill

I know this is rather ambiguous, but did you make her pay her part of the bill after all of this too? 

RIP, mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 17:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Winner. Or loser. Whatever you want to call it, this is the most cringeworthy one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 17:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dude took way too long to finish. The computer. 5/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually like to remember you from the journey to the center of the earth. What was the center of the earth like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In On Sight by Kanye, he says, and pardon me if I'm paraphrasing a bit, "First I pull up and park the benz, then I get this bitch shaking like Parkinson's."  Despite being my favorite rap lyric of all time, I would have to conclude that the lyric is indeed cringeworthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Randomly start making out with the girl you have a crush on. I hear that generally weirds people out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I graduated top of my class and with a perfect GPA in high school, and I quickly realized that if a significant source of your pride comes from being at the top, you need to readjust because there is no perceived 'top' in college. The 'top' now consists of the leaders, not just the smart kids.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I think The_Donald is a cesspool of shit, but that doesn't mean this has to become a cesspool of shit on the other end of the political spectrum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, why is the sub even called r/Politics at this point? I was always under the assumption that this was supposed to be a news feed with largely events and few columns, but over the last month there have been more highly speculative articles than I can count. The mods of this sub should honestly be embarrassed as to how out of control this has gotten, as if I wanted to subscribe to something like this I would just subscribe r/democrats. I subscribe here to read the news, not speculation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 01:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro it's been murder and drugs and poverty themes since Lost and Found in '05 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once flipped each shoe off my foot from about five feet away, having both of them land perfectly next to each other and perfectly next to the door. It was potentially the greatest moment of my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMA REQUEST- LIL YACHTY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was riding on a family road trip in early high school at night, and I was texting this girl name Erica that I had this huge crush on and had it for a while before that. It was going too well and I was getting friend-zoned, so I shut my eyes for a good five minutes to just contemplate my young life. As soon as I opened my eyes, I immediately looked out the front window and there was this massive Bank of America building in front of us, except all of the letters had burnt out so that it just read "erica." I was utterly astonished about the odds of that happening, and to this day I am still somewhat astonished. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find comedy series easy to watch consistently, but hard to binge because of their inability to wrap you up into a storyline. With that being said, Narcos gets you so involved in the storyline because there is always an impending death in the chase for Pablo Escobar. This is the only show I have ever binged, and I watched the 10 hours of season 2 content in the 60 immediate hours after it came out. It was incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super crazy travels cut off due to soulmate's AIDS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, as we've all unfortunately learned, there's worse things that can happen to young pitchers... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AYOOOOOOOOOOO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best "Would you rather?" you have ever heard? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still yet to have a really successful post, but my first successful comment was making a joke about capitalism directly after Castro's death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's the father of Trap music and king of the Atlanta rap game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the one story that you always want to tell, but hardly ever get the chance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what is the craziest thing you've done for an SO on a day like today in years past? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the single stupidest thing you have ever seen anyone do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For our Reddit friends who are trapped in the friendzone for Valentine's Day, how did you get there and what are you going to try to do to get our? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
