<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3415</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You actually should be more concerned for the behaviors your child displays in public vs those they do in private. 

It's good for children to learn early that there is a time and a place for everything, for example this kid may rough house with his siblings at home but it doesn't give him lead way to sweep kick another kid on the pitch. 

I'd be super worried about my kids behavior on the pitch...why wouldn't you be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No but I want more than "They are sick." 

That doesn't hook me, there was nothing about this trailer that screamed atmosphere and suspense like the top comments are making it out to be. 

Like I said I don't feel engaged without proper context so maybe once I see this film I'll feel differently about it than I did the trailer. It seems interesting but I'm not interested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an awful lot of stuff to write for someone who can't read

Wow what a turd. You never explained how or why it would benefit you for them to do that and your reason is bull. 

We already have a way to make gold and items...by playing the game. There is no reason to go back to the AH and it would be to your detriment if we did. The billions of gold you have now and the top tier gear would be impossible to get without a hefty grind or shelling out some real dough. 

You're saying if we made the game harder for you it would be better for you because it would be...easier for you to make gold and items by making it harder to get gold and items?

Not only are you pretentious you're apparently retarded too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they don't. 

Standing in the middle of a highway is much different than using a cross walk at a stop light. 

You're just wrong man, admit it and move on. Stop trying, you're not gonna get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you stand somewhere really dangerous that would cause direct harm to you and you do it willingly then you fall under my definition of dumb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would it be a boon for you?

With the normal loot pace (let's assume you're talking about around the time people farmed Arreat Crater for legendaries) you're talking about getting a max of twenty legends an hour, more if you're real lucky. Consider all the legendaries that are now implemented in the game and how they affect many different build s and play styles. Upping the drop rate brought more people to the game the only people who would benefit off an AH by your terms would be hard core dedicated players or people with money. 

And it was bullshit that back in the day I couldn't ever dream of reaching MP10 without either giving up more cash for gear, farming a ton of gold, or farming the gear myself...all these alternatives take tons of time and only benefited those with time and money. 

No, as someone who has been poor and broke and played since the days of the AH I'm going to be rude and say you're very very stupid for thinking the AH would be a good thing ever in any context now for Diablo 3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you don't understand the point of my post. I can't say who deserves what that is a matter of subjective opinion. I was trying to point out to you it's not a matter of whether they deserve it or not but the context in which they got hit...which was being dumb and protesting in the middle of a highway. 

We can argue all day long about whether they deserve it or not but the fact of the matter is they put themselves into a situation to have this happen to them. 

Do they deserve it? I honestly can't say I could see both the yes and no sides of that question. 

But I don't care that they did/didn't deserve it, I care that people are stupid enough to stand in the middle of a busy road and then people want to act all surprised or indignant when someone gets hit. Pointing out how idiotic this is rather than arguing about whether they deserve to be hit is more productive to the actual conversation rather than determining dues. 

If people think they can garner sympathy for doing this then they will keep doing it, we need to let people know we don't care they should follow the rules simply for safety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not misquoting you I was being sarcastic. Maybe not literally surrounded but the dude had 10+ people bearing down towards his car, for all intents and purposes we can say the dude was surrounded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, believe it or not one can have an opinion that someone is dumb and led themselves into a situation but still feel some amount of pity for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it didn't show enough. I get something spooky is going on but I don't feel engaged without proper context and playing the pronoun game just makes me sick. 

"If their sick...I'm sick."

Who's sick? With what? What kind of sickness?

I need a hook and this trailer don't have one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I checked out then. I've seen the "thing that looks human but isn't and has black goo coming out of it" too many times now. 

I'll wait for this production to be finished and judge it by it's merit then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many bed and baths a house has in one of many factors that determine the worth. 

A shitty 3/3 is going to be cheaper than a super nice 2/1.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "NO ONE WAS ATTACKING THE DRIVER GUYS HE WAS JUST SURROUNDED BY AN ANGRY MOB PUSHING AND BEATING ON HIS CAR HE WAS TOTALLY SAY."

You're a fucking trip man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you wait patiently in your car for the police to help you if you were surrounded by an angry mob intent on possibly hurting you or would you fight or flight instinct kick in and nail the gas pedal to get the hell out of there?

You don't have to answer because you and I both know it's the latter. 

Running over and hurting people isn't good but you can't possibly think the people in the high way had any right to be there. There is a reason we don't let people just walk all over high ways and dangerous areas. 

If someone gets hit by the subway for standing on the tracks are you going to be mad at the conductor for not stopping? 

This situation is clear and cut: Don't stand in the middle of the highway and you won't get hit by cars. Bonus points if you can avoid acting like a barbarian and trying to assault people while doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life has consequence. 

If you stand in the middle of the high way you're bound to get hit by a car and the law won't be there to protect you because it's not a pedestrian zone. We can argue over whether they deserve it or not but the objective facts are 

1. you're on a high way 

2. there are cars on the highway

3. cars can hit and seriously hurt/kill people

These factors added together make it more likely they are going to get hit by being in that position and we cannot simply have sympathy for people who purposefully and idiotically get in the way of others and progress. 

It sucks they got run over and I hope they are ok but it's not surprising in the least...what did they think was going to happen?

Play with the bull get the horns as they say.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok well you get out of your car and face the angry crowd, slap some people about.

We have rules and regulations for a reason and one of those is YOU DON'T STAND ON THE HIGHWAY.

You're liable to be hit if you're on the high way and if you're being a cunt and blocking it you're at fault for being hit. 

Pedestrians only have the right of way in pre-determined pedestrian crossing areas. 

If there is no consequence for your action then people are doomed to repeat. I for one and glad that person ran through the crowd because idiots need to learn how to actually protest and not hold up the lives of others in the process. 

Do you think it would be right of them to block the high and an emergency vehicle carrying someone on the brink of death can't get through because a bunch of retards are standing in the middle of the road? 

People who act like cunts and play with guns will get shot, people who act like cunts and drive will get in wrecks, and people who act like cunts and stand in the middle of the high way will get run over.  That's not opinion that is truth. 

It's not a matter of who deserves what it's the logical matter of what will happen if you commit to these actions and in this case standing in the middle of the highway...surprise...gets you run over by angry drivers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude I lose my Money Trough all the time! I use it by picking it up from my inventory and the amount of times I've just dropped it on the ground is un-countable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's cool and all you do you OP.

My personal opinion: That is really tacky and looks gross. It's a mish-mash of nerd culture with no real theme and off looking references. 

Like it's all video games...then Darth Vader? Dr. Eggman?

That's not even a gun in Doom and whoever drew this knew your face better than your wife's. Your character looks fine but her's is straight up ugly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know his motives I want to know the reasoning for him thinking the AH would be terrific for seasons. As it stands now it's super easy to get geared out, especially with Haedrig's gift. At this point the AH would be useless in any meaningful way because of how easy it is to get most gear. 

With gifts and primals being the rarest commodities in game that would probably be a reason but that is hardly even a good reason to bring the AH back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  AH would be terrific for seasons.

Explain your reasoning for this statement. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I need to stop playing solo que. 

I tried my best with this game but I swear it's always my team mates. 


Skyes trying to be damage. 

Seris and pip trying to flank. 

Androxus that will just sit in spawn. 

And if you ask for healing the healers literally tell you no and will ignore you. 

Paladins has the worst community of FPS players I've ever seen and it's the main issue with FTP games, you got to let all the trash in too. So every little kid and dumb ass troll who thinks throwing games is clever gets in while those of us who really want to enjoy the game simply can't. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that where the NPC in the top right housing is from? Thorium mod? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would the Auction House be good for seasons?

As the game stands right now the only two things that escape the grasps of most players are high GR levels and Primal Ancients. 

Everything else can be collected in droves as the game is. Gems, gold, materials...they are all super duper easy to collect, so what are we going to sell on the AH?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know! I'm always accidentally auto-sorting mana potions into my chests.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the wiggly border around some of your items? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a girl asked me to buy her some cheese sticks I'd be in love. Food  alcohol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently passing a kindly Stone for a man is just about as painful as having a baby. None of the gross effects or vag to assist splits though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually wait until I know a person a little better before asking them to play dress up with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it weighs nothing why not just put it up when you need to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm male. No one ever encouraged me to do anything. In fact my grandmother who raised me constantly told me I couldn't do things while giving all the emotional support to my female cousin who she also raised. I liked computers she liked anime. I was a fat loser who was gonna waste away on front of a computer and she was gonna work for Disney one dayear!

Yup I sure was encouraged as a male. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A single player mod for Diablo II that enables instant respecs and infinite storage space as well as an increased inventory size. It's compatible with a few other mods not Median at the moment but the 1.13c version of Median and PlugY can work together.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what the cube is for. You can re-roll an extra legendary of the same kind to get the stats you want before gifting it. 

This is just another way to hold players hands on their way to perfect stats. 

This in my opinion is what set Diablo II apart from Diablo III. In Diablo II when you got your high end gear it felt really special and powerful. In Diablo III everyone gets super high end gear really quick and the game becomes about perfecting that gear. We're losing the lust of the loot hunt and it's turning into more of a numbers game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More often than not the moves aren't choreographed either. Most matches are planned on the fly sometimes five minutes before the match.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the intersection and which way you're turning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PlugY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
