<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject350</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 01:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! Thanks so much for your help. This is amazing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 01:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone please help by removing the man in the middle. This pic would make a great birthday present for my dad. It's his birthday today, and mine too. Thanks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 12:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A friend is lodging my dog whilst I'm on holiday. Got this pic and made me really happy to see her. She's the one in the middle and the other 2 are my friend's dogs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 07:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What makes a bowl or any other utensil microwave safe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 12:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meanwhile at a drug store nearby </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 21:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 16:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an Indian, I can add that most of my patriot friends are zealously patrolling Facebook. Take care out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 12:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's better. You'll make a nice guest in India. Just eat the food, have some chai, repeat all day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 11:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch. How'd that go down? Grew up in North India, rice is sorta special and most homes will have it once a week as a treat, as we mostly eat roti or flat breads. Totally opposite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 11:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope it wasn't a Guinness  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most culturally inappropriate thing you've ever done? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 11:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flying from Copenhagen to Oslo. These mountains remind me of nothing but The North and The Wall *Game of Thrones theme song* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 15:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 19:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, same on ee. Not really very annoying, is it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 19:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Successfully tested Voda, EE and giffgaff last year and then decided to stay with giffgaff. Couple of months in got worse and worse.. Left giffgaff 6 months ago and switched to 3. Sweet sweet unlimited data, tethering, great network coverage and most importantly free roaming in so many countries!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
