<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1143</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I say read it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am holding this as a promise that you're gonna finish the story. There's no backing out now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the whole thing. Took me fifteen minutes. Totally worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know Polandball got rid of x-posting ban right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, don't burn yourself out too fast. I read over your post and I have the impression you go hardball when you start your hobbies, but stop when there's a bottleneck. It's like running, right? You start off nice and breezy, and you will want to go real fast cause you feel great. Then the 5 minute mark hits and you're just dying. You might wonder why you already feel socked 5 minutes in. You will want to quit. Don't. Maybe slow your pace, but push through it. Then you can run for an hour. Same goes for all your hobbies. You gotta push through the bottlenecks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use podcast addict, it's on Google playstore. It lets you skip 15s back and forth. I think you can customise how long you skip too. I use it for all my podcasts, great app.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Female. Medical practitioner. Organized and logical person, an introvert - maybe you don't like big crowds? I think you are in your early to mid twenties, since you are still in school, but you can be older than 22 since medical school lasts longer. A little childlike or dreamy? Probably those people who aces tests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You made me remember the times I was forced to use fountain pens in school to write my homework. Sadly those were not happy times for me. Nobody had an interest in calligraphy so everyone bought those cheap pens that clog and blotch a lot, if you were not careful when writing you get those really thick lines that made words half illegible. Sucking ink from the bottle always made a mess that I had to clean up with tissues, and the absolute worst part is when I leave my pen on the notebook to go do something, and come back with a huge ink blotch on my half done homework... that I need to start over again. I've never bought any fountain pens after school, so I don't know if all pens are like this or I just got really crappy pens. The ink stains are hard to wash off too... Now I think twice before buying anything inky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 14:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we found the Brasilian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 04:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> slipping into an old pair shoes

Old pair of shoes

he would take us back with us

Take us back with him?

Petronus Towers

Think it is the Petronas Towers in Malaysia right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how you never told us how much karma the man had, it's a nice point of imagination for the readers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kept my hands help straight up

held. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it lets you search by subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 01:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would you go about doing that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 01:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Australia's colour. Nice deep indigo purple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are there 'made in xxx' labels on products? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 02:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [here you go](https://www.reddit.com/r/WritingPrompts/comments/4tkprc/wp_you_are_alois_hitler_spending_your_days_trying/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been done before.

Edit: [found it](https://www.reddit.com/r/WritingPrompts/comments/4uyxxp/wp_knock_on_door_sir_have_you_found_jesus_uh_no/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me about the happiest day in your life

I would like to believe it hasn't happened yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> til death do us part? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be a reasonable explanation, because how could google be [evil](https://xkcd.com/792/)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy to have ya! [Here's a comic to get you started!](https://www.reddit.com/r/guyjc/comments/oyk18/reddit_the_basics/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP you're a wonderful person based on these threads I've read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 04:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> amazing art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does that iron cross represent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a very... raw book if you can describe it that way. Full of emotion but not much plot. Also what does your flair mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is your name a reference to Lord of the Flies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this story is incomplete  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll probably poke around a lot more, i.e. explore stuff. Find out what's inside an alleyway, climb a tree and see how high I can go, try to open random doors, recreate the scene of Friends in a fountain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 03:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't change who I am without losing myself in the process

This is a thing a lot of people think, but wouldn't you still be you, whatever you do, because you're...you? "[Be yourself](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fLLz7O9Lf6k)" isn't really great advice, a better version should be "be your best self". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Dan talk about D-day in any of his podcasts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, does he have a series on WWII? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 01:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem, I love history. [Have you seen the video about the fallen of WWII?](https://vimeo.com/128373915) ^hope  ^I'm  ^not  ^boring  ^you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> found the links if you wanna read them :] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They say war changes someone forever, and people have nightmares for the rest of their lives for killing someone. There was this guy that posted in a askreddit thread about his childhood in some war involving Russia(~~I'll find the thread later~~ [found it](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/5knrsf/what_is_the_most_terrifying_thing_youve_ever_seen/dbpl3yd/)), that really makes you think about your privileges in life. Also read a [bestof thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/5p0jjm/til_the_british_submarine_hms_artful_can_stay/dco6lre/) a while ago about why veterans have a hard time readjusting to civilian life~~(will find it later too)~~. Makes you realize how high the price of war is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came from writingprompts. Contrary to what you believe, your story is excellent, although your formatting needs more work. I'm sure that many others, including me, would like you to expand this series. Feel free to PM me stuff if you want an honest opinion, cause I like your writing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Timmy fucking died! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lying cozy in bed while listening to the rain pattering outside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **"End quote."** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #TeamTea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you like history? Try Dan Carlin's hardcore history, its a podcast with two hours or more episodes talking about history events. I find his voice very soothing, and I often fall asleep listening to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminded me of a Holmes story where he deducts the previous owner of Watson's watch just by looking at it:

I have heard you say that it is difficult for a
man to have any object in daily use without leaving
the impress of his individuality upon it in such a
way that a trained observer might read it. Now, I
have here a watch which has recently come into my
possession. Would you have the kindness to let me
have an opinion upon the character or habits of the
late owner?

I handed him over the watch with some slight
feeling of amusement in my heart, for the test was,
as I thought, an impossible one, and I intended it as
a lesson against the somewhat dogmatic tone which
he occasionally assumed. He balanced the watch
in his hand, gazed hard at the dial, opened the
back, and examined the works, first with his naked
eyes and then with a powerful convex lens. I could
hardly keep from smiling at his crestfallen face
when he finally snapped the case to and handed it
back.

There are hardly any data, he remarked. The
watch has been recently cleaned, which robs me of
my most suggestive facts.

You are right, I answered. It was cleaned
before being sent to me. In my heart I accused
my companion of putting forward a most lame and
impotent excuse to cover his failure. What data
could he expect from an uncleaned watch?
Though unsatisfactory, my research has not
been entirely barren, he observed, staring up at
the ceiling with dreamy, lack-lustre eyes. Subject
to your correction, I should judge that the watch
belonged to your elder brother, who inherited it
from your father.

That you gather, no doubt, from the H. W.
upon the back?

Quite so. The W. suggests your own name. The
date of the watch is nearly fifty years back, and the
initials are as old as the watch: so it was made for
the last generation. Jewelry usually descents to the
eldest son, and he is most likely to have the same
name as the father. Your father has, if I remember
right, been dead many years. It has, therefore, been
in the hands of your eldest brother.

Right, so far, said I. Anything else?

He was a man of untidy habits,very untidy
and careless. He was left with good prospects, but
he threw away his chances, lived for some time in
poverty with occasional short intervals of prosperity,
and finally, taking to drink, he died. That is all
I can gather.

I sprang from my chair and limped impatiently
about the room with considerable bitterness in my
heart.

This is unworthy of you, Holmes, I said. I
could not have believed that you would have descended
to this. You have made inquires into the
history of my unhappy brother, and you now pretend
to deduce this knowledge in some fanciful
way. You cannot expect me to believe that you have
read all this from his old watch! It is unkind, and,
to speak plainly, has a touch of charlatanism in it.
My dear doctor, said he, kindly, pray accept
my apologies. Viewing the matter as an abstract
problem, I had forgotten how personal and painful
a thing it might be to you. I assure you, however,
that I never even knew that you had a brother until
you handed me the watch.

Then how in the name of all that is wonderful
did you get these facts? They are absolutely correct
in every particular.

Ah, that is good luck. I could only say what
was the balance of probability. I did not at all expect
to be so accurate.

But it was not mere guess-work?

No, no: I never guess. It is a shocking
habit,destructive to the logical faculty. What
seems strange to you is only so because you do
not follow my train of thought or observe the small
facts upon which large inferences may depend. For
example, I began by stating that your brother was
careless. When you observe the lower part of that
watch-case you notice that it is not only dinted in
two places, but it is cut and marked all over from
the habit of keeping other hard objects, such as
coins or keys, in the same pocket. Surely it is no
great feat to assume that a man who treats a fiftyguinea
watch so cavalierly must be a careless man.
Neither is it a very far-fetched inference that a man
who inherits one article of such value is pretty well
provided for in other respects.

I nodded, to show that I followed his reasoning.

It is very customary for pawnbrokers in England,
when they take a watch, to scratch the number
of the ticket with a pin-point upon the inside of
the case. It is more handy than a label, as there
is no risk of the number being lost or transposed.
There are no less than four such numbers visible to
my lens on the inside of this case. Inference,that
your brother was often at low water. Secondary
inference,that he had occasional bursts of prosperity,
or he could not have redeemed the pledge.
Finally, I ask you to look at the inner plate, which
contains the key-hole. Look at the thousands of
scratches all round the hole,marks where the key
has slipped. What sober mans key could have
scored those grooves? But you will never see a
drunkards watch without them. He winds it at
night, and he leaves these traces of his unsteady
hand. Where is the mystery in all this?

---The sign of Four, Conan Doyle
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TT] Write a story about a child losing their innocence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [this song is better](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hKRUPYrAQoE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Sherlock fan that read all the books, I grudgingly approve. Great writing, but that Holmes made my skin crawl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the children return to Narnia multiple times, every time decades of years had passed, so they return to a different world each time, which kinda relates to retourning after many years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda sorta like Narnia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have similar music taste, can you recommend more songs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Not to Calvin](http://www.gocomics.com/calvinandhobbes/2011/08/01) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Past thieves of Reddit: what made you steal what you stole? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     if germans angry==true;
        give beer.
   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, had some pretty awesome conversations with people on trains and planes. Talked to a professional horse racer on his way to an international tournament on a plane once, and watched a movie with a couple while on a train. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I throw that crumpled paper ball across the room and it lands in the bin, first try. Score! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know life is unfair but why can't it be unfair in my favor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 16:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where can I get a plate like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 16:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In twenty years I will become an inventor. Then I'll invent a time machine, return to yesterday, take myself to tomorrow, and skip this stupid assignment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
