<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3901</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 10:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think ad-based revenue models are toxic to society.

One doesn't have to have read Chomsky's "Manufacturing Consent" (although it certainly helps) to know that it corrupts the very foundations of our information sources.

I've always said that we need to transition away from an internet of ad-based revenue where *we are the product, sold to corporations* and get into the habit of paying for quality content that serves *us as a society* rather than serves corporate interests by exploiting our basest instincts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Medium: "Media is broken. Corporate advertising budgets become the primary funders of our information providers. No matter how skilled or well-intentioned, ad-driven publishers are rewarded on their ability to capture attention and even, at times, to weave a particular corporate-driven narrative." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 10:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 10:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless we can make this publically owned and equally accessible to everyone (and we can't given that we cannot even get our shit together to meet *the most basic needs* of everyone equally), I'm in the **[Purity First](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=elQC62FUgqw)** camp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pierrick Picaut - "BURDDY" Commercial Making Of in Blender </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pierrick Picaut - "BURDDY" Commercial Making Of in Blender </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pierrick Picaut - "BURDDY" Commercial Making Of in Blender </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Blender Foundation organized a 2.8 workflow sprint at the Blender Institute in Amsterdam, 25-27 November 2016.

From the video description. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you **[sure](http://www.moviedeskback.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/The_Jungle_Book_HD_Screencaps-23.png0)** you can tell **[within seconds](http://cdn.highdefdigest.com/uploads/2016/08/19/High-Def_Digest_www.highdefdigest_.com_Blu-ray_Review_The_Jungle_Book_2016_1_.jpg)** what's real and what isn't?

CGI is getting **[pretty good](https://youtu.be/r2SSEaWCAi0?t=27s)**. Just to be clear, *everything* except the kid is **[CGI here](https://www.fxguide.com/featured/out-of-the-pages-and-into-the-jungle-book/)**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it really that inconceivable that someone isn't entertained well by what they perceive to be an extremely formulaic story with uninteresting, shallow characters and uninspiring action scenes?

I'd be a bit more careful than to call someone *dead inside* just because they're not particularly enjoying *Star Wars: Rogue One* - it doesn't reflect well on your judgment, or character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to watch Rogue One the other day... had to turn it off after 90 minutes or so. I was bored to death. :/

Really don't think I'll be following this franchise into the 2030s... or even just to the next film. Neither The Force Awakens nor Rogue One were worth it for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch Part 1 of Andy Goralczyk's "Waking the Forest" tutorial for free on the Blender Cloud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch Part 1 of Andy Goralczyk's "Waking the Forest" tutorial for free on the Blender Cloud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blender 2.8 Workflow Workshop Featurette </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blender 2.8 Workflow Workshop Featurette </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted this also in /r/russia, same title - **[this](https://i.imgur.com/ejFhoJA.jpg)** was the result. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 13:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that in our hyper-complex and interconnected world, with political and economic systems spanning the globe and incomprehensible to anyone in their entirety, judging what one can or cannot control becomes literally impossible.

Or rather, the distinction between what one *controls* versus what one *affects* becomes an easy excuse to claim that just because you feel like you cannot *control* something in its entirety, you can dismiss any responsibility for *affecting* it.

I don't think our world currently is suffering primarily from people feeling *too much* responsibility for things that they don't actually have any influence over at all but rather the opposite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A City Without Gays: The LGBTQ community is almost invisible in provincial Russia. But a small town mayor has declared war on them regardless. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 13:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A City Without Gays: The LGBTQ community is almost invisible in provincial Russia. But a small town mayor has declared war on them regardless. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's the statue of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Official Twitter account of the Democratic Party tweets out picture of protesters, but edits out a socialist sign in it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 11:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Russian friend told me that **Moonlight** is 16+ over there.

Does that mean **Power Rangers** is gayer than **Moonlight**?

But seriously - what criteria is this based on? Beyond being retarded in the first place, it also seems arbitrary as hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 10:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to be clear, this thread here wasn't the AMA. It **linked** to the AMA over in https://www.reddit.com/r/blenderhelp/comments/61a53w/im_a_longtime_blender_trainer_and_cofounder_of_cg/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not the AMA. Go to https://www.reddit.com/r/blenderhelp/comments/61a53w/im_a_longtime_blender_trainer_and_cofounder_of_cg/ to ask in the AMA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Movies use OpenSubdiv and all-quads, and enforce an all-quads policy much more stringently than games. In games, triangles are much more accepted, since all quads get triangulated anyway in the game engine, and don't use OpenSubdiv (which works better with quads).

Compare **[Pixar meshes](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/564x/0e/d0/4c/0ed04cfbfd774a1dfeafe82a52901a47.jpg)** vs. **[Witcher](http://oi50.tinypic.com/2i8i0qq.jpg)**.

Other than that, movie meshes just have a much higher density (i.e. are more *high poly*) whereas games tend to be more *low poly* because the latter have to run in real-time.

However, on AAA games nowadays, poly counts for hero characters can get much closer to those of feature animation characters than in the past. However, especially in VFX, topology can be **[extremely dense on movies](http://www.riggingdojo.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/Rigging-Dojo-Face-Modeling-Topo-3.png)**.

Of course you don't manually retopologise at this density.

You do a low-res topology in which you define edge flow, then subdivide it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a long-time Blender trainer and co-founder of CG Cookie, Ask Me Anything!  r/blenderhelp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a long-time Blender trainer and co-founder of CG Cookie, Ask Me Anything!  r/blenderhelp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a long-time Blender trainer and co-founder of CG Cookie, Ask Me Anything!  r/blenderhelp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Jonathan, thanks for doing this AMA.

What are the plans regarding keymap optimisation and better/easier customisation of the keymap for Blender 2.8?

It's one thing for Blender to have a rather convoluted, inconsistent and complex keymap by default - but this becomes a lot more difficult to work around when Blender has the most unintuitive, opaque and confusing process for redefining one's own keymap. Both because of the shortcut editing UI and because of the fact that many functions don't seem to be accessible in the hotkey editor at all - or are at least difficult to identify.

If you compare this to **[Maya's Hotkey Editor](https://gfycat.com/ImmaterialSoulfulAnkole)**, or MODO's way of setting hotkeys, which is also much more intuitive, this seems like an area that desperately needs improvement if Blender 2.8 is to become **[The Workflow Release](https://code.blender.org/2015/07/blender-2-8-the-workflow-release/)** it has been promised as.

Since I believe you were among the people spearheading the UX and keymapping efforts I was hoping you could shed some light on what the state of things is, and what we can expect from 2.8 in this area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 09:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in the title.

/r/Degrowth  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kenn ich nicht. Sieht fancy teuer aus. ;)

Wo gibt's das denn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insgesamt sollte man den Autoverkehr berhaupt so weit wie mglich unterdrcken und Leute zu den ffentlichen Verkehrsmitteln erziehen. Das ist durchaus auch eine kulturelle Sache - gerade hier in Deutschland, wo das Auto weitlufig auch ein Teil der Identitt ist.

Nur der PKW-Verkehr, der am Ende wirklich noch ntig ist, sollte dann von autonomen Fahrzeugen durchgefhrt werden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, not bad! :) That's pretty cool.

I'm trying to minimise my expenses as well. Sometimes my self-discipline leaves me though. I don't buy *stuff*, I also only drink tap water and tea at home, don't really go clubbing or otherwise partying with alcohol expenses, but I do occasionally spend way too much going out for nice brunches and other meals with friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Na klar ist aggressive Promotion der ffentlichen der beste Weg!

Autos sollten in der Grostadt berhaupt nur in Ausnahmefllen genutzt werden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich nehme es keineswegs persnlich.

Wundert mich lediglich, dass die Votes so ausgeglichen scheinen - das weist ja meist auf ein kontroverses Thema hin. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welchen Teil?

Zur ersten Hlfte des Satzes:

**[Making a new car creates as much carbon pollution as driving it](https://www.theguardian.com/environment/green-living-blog/2010/sep/23/carbon-footprint-new-car)**


Zum zweiten Teil:

Wenn die meisten Autos 95% der Zeit **nicht** benutzt werden (1 Stunde am Tag = 4.167% Nutzungszeit) und wir all diese Autofahrten durch Autos ersetzen, die 95% der Zeit **aktiv** sind (23 Stunden am Tag = 95.8% Nutzungszeit), knnen wir die Zahl der Autos auf ein Dreiundzwanzigstel reduzieren.

23 Autos fahren an einem Tag jeweils 1 Stunde, also insgesamt 24 Stunden lang.

Diese 23 Autos knnen theoretisch durch ein einziges Auto ersetzt werden, das 23 Stunden lang fhrt.

Ist durchaus eine Milchmdchenrechnung, aber nicht komplett daneben - und fr Ineffizienzen habe ich auch 5-10% angegeben, statt eine Reduktion auf 4.35% (1/23). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sicher nicht. Ist fast immer unterwltigend (kann man *underwhelming* bersetzen?) aber ich lerne nicht daraus.

Kaufe selten was zweimal, aber immer wenn ich was neues veganes sehe, das ich noch nicht probiert habe, schpfe ich kurz Hoffnung, dass es vielleicht ganz okay sein knnte. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fr's Protokoll: Ich fotografiere nicht zufllig "anderer Mensche Einkufe" sondern nur diesen hier, weil ich den Einkauf selbst weirder finde als den Akt des Fotografierens unter Achtung der Anonymitt des Kufers. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 13 votes, 1 point (54% upvoted)

Habe ich hier unwissentlich irgendwas kontroverses angesprochen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Das Rudeltier Mensch sollte vielleicht in den nchsten Jahren und Jahrzehnten eine zeitgemere Flexibilisierung der Arbeitszeiten auf breiter Ebene durchfhren und sich mal von der frhindustriellen Fabrikarbeiterkultur emanzipieren.

Und die Verschleigeschichte ist wieder was anderes. Wie viele Leute fahren ein Auto wirklich bis es verschleibedingt ersetzt werden muss? Viel hufiger sind Signalisierungseffekte (Stichwort Statussymbol), Steuerbegnstigungen und vergleichbarer Kram verantwortlich fr die unntig frhzeitige Anschaffung eines Ersatzfahrzeugs.

Eine Kultur, in der ein Auto weniger als persnlicher Marktwertindikator und mehr als utilitaristischer Infrastrukturservice behandelt wird, knnte hier zu deutlich rationalerem and effizienterem Umgang fhren. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ist der mit Hund weniger Ghetto? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alles linksgrnversiffter Abschaum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cool Blender FX loop by Andy Goralczyk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohne Hund. Der deutsche *Netto Marken-Discount* mit dem gelb-roten Logo.

Der mit Hund ist dnisch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interessant. Wieder was gelernt.

Das war brigens in Berlin-Mitte. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> War ziemlich abartig. Nicht weil vegan, sondern weil unguter Tiefkhlfra. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, das ist dann natrlich kontraproduktiv. Ich selbst kann das nur anekdotisch beurteilen - im Fall meines Freundeskreises sind das nur Leute, die selbst kein Auto haben, aber sich kurz ein DriveNow-Fahrzeug nehmen, wenn sie mal was mittelschweres transportieren mssen oder so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Into The Wild 10 years later: Christopher McCandless Is No Longer My Hero </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich finde es schon erstaunlich, dass "Publikationen" wie die *SUPER illu* (nie zuvor gehrt) berhaupt einen Markt haben.

Aber dass jemand zum NETTO geht, um sich *speziell* diese Zeitschrift mit Madame Kepetry zu kaufen - und sonst nichts - das hat mich besonders beeindruckt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Der Herr vor mir an der NETTO-Kasse war wohl ein Fan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 11:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Naja um da mal was gegen zu sagen, der Hauptvorteil eines Autos fr viele ist ja gerade, dass man es jederzeit benutzen knnte. Und wenn es viel rumsteht, dann verbraucht man ja auch keinen Sprit.

Selbstfahrende Autos kann man auch jederzeit benutzen, wenn man sie wie ein Taxi/Uber per Smartphone bestellen kann. Und selbst heute komme ich innerhalb Berlins von nahezu jedem beliebigen Punkt A zu jedem beliebigen Punkt B schneller und gnstiger per ffis als per Auto (wenn man smtliche Kosten des Autos sowie die Parkplatzsuche einrechnet).

Der Ressourcenverbrauch eines Autos entsteht nicht nur beim Fahren, sondern insbesondere in der Herstellung selbst!

**[Making a new car creates as much carbon pollution as driving it](https://www.theguardian.com/environment/green-living-blog/2010/sep/23/carbon-footprint-new-car)**

D.h. je weniger Autos wir **bauen**, desto umweltfreundlicher. Macht viel mehr Sinn, 5 Autos zu bauen, die 23/7 herumfahren als 15 Autos, die vielleicht eine Stunde am Tag genutzt werden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mein Vater liest die BILD (und keine andere Zeitung), mit genau dieser beschissenen Begrndung. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich lebe in Berlin und finde es jeden Tag absurd zu sehen, wie viel Platz und Ressourcen fr Autos verschwendet wird, die an jeder Straenseite sowie auf groflchigen Parkpltzen rumstehen und 95+% der Zeit nicht benutzt werden!

Ich hoffe zutiefst, dass wir mglichst bald in einer Zeit leben, in denen (selbstfahrende) Autos ein Service sind, den man einfach schnell per Smartphone bestellt, wenn man von A nach B muss. Das Auto kommt, man steigt ein, und sobald man am Ziel ist, fhrt das Auto zum nchsten Kunden.

Firmen wie **[Car2Go](https://www.car2go.com/DE/en/berlin/)** und **[DriveNow](https://www.drive-now.com/de#!/carsharing/berlin)** sind schon mal ein guter Anfang.

Stellt Euch vor wie unglaublich viel Platz und Ressourcen das sparen wrde - zumal die Hlfte des Ressourcenverbrauchs eines Autos durch seine Lebenszeit entsteht beim *Bau* des Fahrzeugs, noch bevor es jemals verkauft wird, und wir damit vielleicht 5-10% der Fahrzeuge heute bruchten, wenn diese permanent unterwegs und in Nutzung wren. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $1000 is 926.48, which translates to 463.24 per person per month? That seems extreme even to me.

And you're *not* living in a flatshare? How does that work? You don't each have your own place, do you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comcast is killing off DreamWorks Oriental </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's for the viewport. Doesn't replace Cycles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow... $1200 is my complete cost of living *per month*. Including **everything**.

In Berlin, Germany. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, this is the official Blender Foundation development blog.

Eevee is the viewport that's being worked on for Blender 2.8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed: https://m.imgur.com/4qOED8J </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blender's 2.8 viewport: Eevee Roadmap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blender's 2.8 viewport: Eevee Roadmap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blender's 2.8 viewport: Eevee Roadmap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there needs to be a distinction between *creative* and *artistic*.

Programming doesn't have to be *artistic* but it very often is *creative*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dave Chappelle: "If Martin Luther had a sneaker deal, we'd still be on the back of the bus" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Carlin ~ The American Dream </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angeblich cheaten Telecolumbus mit Ookla (speedtest.net), daher verwende ich meistens https://speedof.me - aber mit beidem ist meine Geschwindigkeit immer weit unter den 200 MBit/s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waking the Forest tutorial by Andy Goralczyk is now available on the Blender Cloud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waking the Forest tutorial by Andy Goralczyk is now available on the Blender Cloud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
