<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1497</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm staying on 8.1. You wouldn't have a link to those registry hacks, would you? I fucking HATE the fact cannot actually delete Internet Explorer and those other fucking gay apps. What a fucking joke.

You really should try Ubuntu. It's piss easy to do whatever you want. No bullshit - you own your OS with Linux. You can do just about everything with the GUI and there's so many places to go for instructions if you want to use the terminal. It literally too me about 15 minutes to work out how to do what I wanted to do - as in browsing the net, making documents, playing music and movie files. Do yourself a favour and make a live disk/USB. You don't have to install to use it. 

Also, if your Windows system shits itself (like mine did) you just boot a live Linux OS and drag all of your files back off your Windows partition. Saved me countless hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait as long as you can but only to the point where you are still the strongest - otherwise, YOU get eaten. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do people bother making or looking at porn where the subject's face is not shown? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No face. Next... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pity you took your head off, too? Who the fuck wants to look at porn without faces? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's almost like American law stops at American borders. Can you believe it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get your fucking arse into gear and lose some weight. You have ample time to do this. It will be hard but scoring that root is totally possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO private schools should receive any funding from the taxpayer. Especially religious ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure Perry's won't go that far... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pathetic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Low brisance - less shattering, more heaving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah,I had a brief look at it. Fuck. That. Shit. I only need Windows for the games I play. And I ain't playing Mircrosoft's games - if you know what I mean.

Been using Ubuntu Linux for quite some time now and never once has it failed me. Never once has it just shit itself for no good reason. I really wish more people would give it a chance. It is NOT hard to use (anymore) and there is plenty of help out there.

The very second that I can run any game on Linux, I get rid of MS crap altogether. Windows is nothing but bloatware, in my opinion.

Just today, I was at a mate's house - he'd "upgraded" to Win 10. And BAM! Guess what? - all your fucking drivers are now generic MS ones! Have fun going and reinstalling all the ones you had before! Isn't that just fucking great! Something we can all look forward to... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it true that some drivers were (or are) good enough to change diff oil pressure as they go through a corner? I assume it would have controlled lock-up as they went around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never, Marge. Never. I can't live the button-down life like you. I want it all: the terrifying lows, the dizzying highs, the creamy middles. Sure, I might offend a few of the bluenoses with my cocky stride and musky odors - oh, I'll never be the darling of the so-called "City Fathers" who cluck their tongues, stroke their beards, and talk about "What's to be done with this Homer Simpson?" 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-pVpCskFBrM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it true you can't bring your own lunch/food? Why the fuck would kids eat the shit I have seen in photos? Some of that shit would have caused a small riot at any high school in Australia. At least at my school, anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No kangaroos, please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we start a collection for some more petrol? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing he's not American. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring back tobacco sponsorship. Don't race in countries that refuse to make exceptions to their lame laws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When's the next best-of? It's been far too long. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents managed to pay a house off at 18% interest. And they certainly aren't rich, in the scheme of things. Now, you have these clowns that borrow way more than they can afford and they seemingly make no effort to take into account any possible interest rises. I find it hard to feel sorry for them. They're half the reason why the market is the way it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not by anyone who could write about it and knew about the rest of the World. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least it wasn't Dr. Robotnik. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see this article on /r/worldnews. Surely, the mods wouldn't be suppressing it...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that because people borrow money and don't budget for increases in interest rates of 0.25%? Jesus christ, I don't know how some people work out what they can 'afford'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like reality TV. FUCK reality TV in all its forms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like shit. Put the front back on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 10:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like you've already got the turkey baster up your arse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 10:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened the last two times Russia tried to assert authority in Chechnya? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 10:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chechnya has little strategic value to them. Crimea most certainly does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 10:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Islam in action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 09:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never used it, in the first place. 10/10  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 09:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gay: Feminine, inferior.

That's what my dictionary says. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 09:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always imagined using something similar as a throttle body for an engine. Possibly less resistance at partial throttle and you could shape the blades/vanes to induce turbulence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why can't they allow the teams a certain budget and let them use it how they see fit? Build what they want, within reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another reason why I absolutely refuse to 'upgrade'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Country? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What currency are you talking about, FFS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NOT the Aboriginals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cunt don't wanna be corded:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1LKx26XAW4g </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No end in sight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will fucking go without, just to hit his bottom line in a case like this. That is straight up fucking highway robbery. And then I'll tell me mates not to go there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you gonna do? Cunts own half the country, anyway... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen that video of the Messerschmitt being flown through the Black Forest at death defying speed and angles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuckin' oath it is - when I was about 7 I was washing my treadly in front of the house. Lightning struck a giant gum tree about 40 m away. Pieces of bark were pelting me as I turned and cowered away from it. Took several seconds to process what the fuck was going on. I have never run so fast in my entire life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When my Dad was a kid him and his brother rigged up an axe that was supposed to cut wood. But when Dad said "when I say now", his brother immediately pulled the string and the axe came down and chopped his big toe in half - length ways. Extremely bad injury - split his big toe in half about four inches into his foot.

40 something years later, he hits a divot in the ground when using this abortion of a ride-on mower he bought off a mate. The blade ended up striking his big toe in exactly the same way the axe did. 

Nearly lost the toe but they somehow saved it. Now, it's just like this pink sausage that doesn't bend at any of where the joints should be.

Also, around the same time they were playing cowboys and indians. And another brother got his eye shot out with a bow and arrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the women are equipped with wet-bulb thermometers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who want to download: Tools -- Page info -- media -- save the pic you want </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a couple who drink at my local pub and we call them "The Metallica People". They're in their 60s and are obsessed with Metallica - to the point where they will randomly break out in song, singing their favourite tracks and lyrics at high volume. You could be playing pool and the bloke will sink a shot and immediately bellow "gimme fuel, gimme fire!!". They wear the shirts and whatever else they can get hold of all the time. They're very nice and polite, though. It's weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hollywood movies and action shows. They are utter garbage. Almost all of them. When are we going to stop seeing people taking 20 punches to the face with no injuries sustained? How many times do we have to see some fuckwit wielding two pistols with deadly accuracy (and unlimited magazines). It's fucking insulting, really.

I had to sit through Suicide Squad the other day (it would have been rude to leave, unfortunately). I honestly do not understand how whoever went to a director with that idea didn't get laughed out of the room. Pure. Fucking. Drivel. From start to finish. Just rubbish.

Why do people watch this crap? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People carry on like stomach acid is everything. It isn't. The enzymes produced are just as important. A little bit of HCl will not dissolve anything and everything.  Stomach acid is only 0.05 - 1 molar concentration, which is nothing in the scheme of things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sugar "absorbs carbon dioxide"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be careful with any sprays. When I was in high school people would lace weed with fly spray. You never knew until you smoked it. Got you really fucking bent but not the ideal thing to smoke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, they were looking into my neighbours' claims that I had somehow sneaked into their house and installed hardware to spy on them. Yes, I am serious. So they sent two plain, uniformed cops to investigate. I actually had to show them how to look through the files on my PC. Internet history was not saved, either. It was pretty funny. They were pissing themselves laughing by the end of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think that would be fair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I never keep my lighter in/with my tobacco. Always in my pocket. You smoke 'em as you roll 'em. No point carrying around of pre-rolled ones, in my experience. Maybe a pocket for papers. Possibly a space for filters - but they can go in with the tobacco, itself I'd say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's fair enough. You are absolutely right. I make no argument against your logic. At the same time, I actually don't have anything to hide and getting the VPN is extra work for me (at the moment). 

I really couldn't give a shit what the cops look at - I have indeed had my home searched for a certain matter. I was only too happy to show them my PC and watch them struggle on how to work out how to use my browser (Opera) and try and work out how the fuck to use Linux. The matter in question wasn't about cybercrime but it was funny as fuck to watch them open my porn folders and endless funny pictures. The pair of them looked like fools. And I wasn't charged with anything, anyway.

If I did have something to hide, I would employ a VPN. And you know what I do have to hide? Browsing history that could be used by advertisers. THAT is where I draw the line. No cunt is making money off me if I don't get a cut. If a law comes into place here such that ISPs can sell my data, I will get a VPN that very week. Fuck advertising companies and the shit they want to put on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's what I sort of thought. Would it effective in this upcoming war over selling browsing histories (like the shit that's started up in America)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem to know about this - what's your opinion on all these people that talk about getting a VPN and it supposedly making them immune to scrutiny or some shit? I see it all the time - VPN this and that, like it's some kind of impenetrable shield. Surely, it can't be that easy. Can it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They know you'll keep buying and using their stuff. When will people learn and give Apple shit up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not where I'm from, here in Australia. The whole system in most places is appalling. And ancient. No planning. No maintenance. Just like the roads. But you better pay those fucking council rates...

Look at London for an example of poor planning and upkeep. They lose a staggering amount of water every single day:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Thames_Water#Leakage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wake up to yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost as bad as when you get charged for a packet of source at the corner shop. Very poor form. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look for a download that says it includes the crack. I used one of the CODEX ones and it worked, immediately. I just go on TPB and download things that have the little skull next to the name. If there is no skull, don't touch it. Read the comments section to see if others had trouble. The description will tell you how to use the crack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had a work mate get bit by a redback - twice within one minute. He was back from hospital within the hour. They're laughable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we get a decent pic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best one is where you build a pile of rocks on the beach and then cover them with sand, to look like a sandcastle. There will always be some fool who will come along and kick it with all their might... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate. Playing a different game while I wait. The download did look legit but I just finished fixing my PC (had to reinstall the OS) and I don't want any more trouble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, that makes sense. Cheers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice work, Sherlock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. Thanks very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate. Makes perfect sense. And yeah, the question certainly did say PF4+.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Utter contempt is no phobia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best mates. Started off getting bullied, before we teamed up. Went to uni together. Gonna hit the cunt up for a high paid job, very soon. He'll be good for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use you fingers. It's not that hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Madison. Fuck I hate that name. Closely followed by any *yden or similar sounding construct. Ayden/Jayden/Brayden/etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the latest RYO pack of tobacco can be fully sealed - with a zip-lock bag type of seal. That's an absolute must. People who take a while to get through a pack depend on proper sealing - otherwise it dries out too much.

Where I live, the packs are sold in 30 g and 50 g pouches. Also, people usually use filters (as well as papers) - so you need somewhere to keep those. Filters are quite bulky and you don't want them squashed.

I'd say you want the leather very soft and thin. And with absolutely no residual tanning products to contaminate the tobacco. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just quietly - get a fucken haircut, cunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it have to be a flat plate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have the belly of a malnourished child. You need more than those protein shakes you dad gives you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did they move heavy items to and from the holds? And why are there what looks like capstans below deck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does not matter. Only the context matters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair play. Gotta check that pooter, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on a PC. They're too stupid to make it cross-platform? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the helmet on, he could cosplay as a fucking gearstick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a brighter note, here's Stephen singing Together in Electric dreams (with Davros):

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BQ8iKccMJA8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That outfit fits you like a condom would fit your dick waaaaay to loose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing, really. Why are so many people playing reddit detective? It's neither clever, nor smart. If they are sticking to the conversation, that's good enough for me.  I don't feel the need to look at their history and bring unrelated stuff up, whether they are an arsehole or not. It's irrelevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll still be hampered by stupid rules. Seriously, one of my major gripes is the fuel consumption rule. Why the fuck can't they use the allocated fuel as they see fit? I don't watch race cars to marvel at their fuel consumption figures. I hate this hybrid shit and rules that are seemingly for the sake of rules. Give the teams a budget and see what they come up with or just go ahead and make it a one-make series. There's no variety anyomore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why is one end a different charge from the other? How can one end be 'more positive' if the bonding is the same? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every single other program opens where I left it. I don't really get why VLC won't. It wouldn't be so much of a problem if I could see both monitors properly at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do they have to micromanage everything? Set the allowable budget and let the teams decide exactly where and how to use that budget. F1 is everything it shouldn't be, these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of rev-limiting system would they be using? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Win 8.1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's what I though. But doesn't selenium have six, too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Witcher 3][PC] Where is the brightness setting? The game is far too dark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is getting annoying. The game is way too dark for my liking and I cannot find a setting to fix it. Anyone know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 11:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck instagram and their no volume control garbage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 11:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Handbags at ten paces! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, thanks. I'll look into that a bit more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> West/LOCTITE/Camozzi FTW! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's also a fish that makes you shit your pants:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Escolar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is part of my practice chem quiz. Would I be right in assuming the   oxygen end would be more positive than the selenium end? The selenium has a lone pair left over but the oxygen has given up all its lone pairs, no? I want to get this right before I do the real quiz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pirates. Nothing but pirates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus fuck, that ring must sting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone ever heard of this molecule: OCSe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two question I am having trouble with - molecular structure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first one asks "which species has more than 8 electrons around the central atom?". The choice are BF3, BF4-, XeF4, PF3 and OF2.

I know the answer is XeF4 but I thought it was PF3 when I did this practice quiz.

I thought P was surrounded by five electron pairs, making 10 electrons. I don't get why XeF4 is the correct answer.

And the second question asks what shape PF4+ is. I cant remember what I said but it was wrong.

Can anyone explain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
