<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1811</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely not this one. The only way to travel interstellar is through higher dimension. buuuuuut we're still too stupid to understand it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 15:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is retarded. Light speed is not the way to travel through space. Aliens are so laughing at our stupid technologies...   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 18:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a shame that $5 office mouse feels more comfortable than a professional gaming one. I now know that it's not me only. After reading some more I found that some people are having the same issues as I do. It really feels that it should be slightly bigger mouse..  
I don't know maybe people who like this mouse either have midget hands or are accustomed to awkward grips..   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 17:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U ain't Chris Smoove babyyy.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 12:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> logitech m100 is perfect grip for me. If it had thumb rest, it would be perfect mouse for me :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 11:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already done so, also made it completely click-proof with little piece of paper haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 07:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing you all hold the mouse like [this](https://i.imgur.com/yVDCg64.jpg) so your palm is a little far back off the mouse. I hold it like [this](https://i.imgur.com/580sUiT.jpg) where I rest almost the center of my palm on the mouse and the center of my thumb rests exactly on that button. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found a solution to my problem I guess.  
http://i.imgur.com/pvqY1rS.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then it will be more confusing hahaha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put the center of the thumb right on the button and lift up the mouse while in palm grip.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it extra soft to click or is it just that that's where your thumb is?  

Both.  

Can you still use the mouse fully fine if you lift your thumb and move the mouse?  

I guess, but who uses a mouse like that?  

Maybe I was just used to the m100 and need some time to adjust to this mouse. btw are you using any pressure at all with your thumb on the side when you're gliding your mouse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have completely disabled the button. I use palm grip and I guess I have big hands and long fingers. I was just gaming recently and there was bunch of accidental click click click click.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I have big hands, so the center of my thumb sits right on the button, so if I lift up the mouse I click the button very easy. It sounds weird, but I have to arch my thumb back to not click the button. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disabling it doesn't make the button dissapear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I'm used to the old logitech m100 so that dpi button is super easy for me to click accidentally. Maybe I just need some time to get used to it, but for now it's really awkward experience for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I regret buying Logitech G502 Proteus Spectrum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 13:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew this was coming, but after reading so many positive reviews about it, I was sure this is the best all around gaming/everyday use mouse.  
The problem is that annoying sniping/dpi button on the side. Everytime I swipe the mouse to the right I accidentally click that button, it is extremely frustrating having spent so much money on a mouse and to have such a silly problem. Everytime I use the mouse I have to make a conscious effort not to hold the mouse too tightly so I wouldn't click that button. I know it can be easily disabled in the software, but it won't solve the problem I'll still be clicking that frickn' button.   
jeez...I should've went with the mx master... What a disapointment...  
I'm thinking of riping it out with a knife.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 17:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's one of the fascinating things I've seen in a while. That's like introducing all of our culture to extraterestrial beings. People please do more of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 17:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I feel you.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 18:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 18:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (   ) Count that as 8th \_()_/. But seriously that's their problem, they're either not serious or just too lazy to be commited to a friendship. You'll eventually find your person if you keep looking. Best of luck to you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 16:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But can it run Crysis @8k? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tyronn Lue says J.R. Smiths behavior in Bucks game was embarrassing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 12:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 17:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also beware of [old lada engine](https://youtu.be/smndCQGZCLk?t=4s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 12:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he has superman durability, I honestly think he could play at 40 like Jordan did, though Jordan only played for 30 days at the age of 40 before his very last game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long do you think Lebron will play? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 10:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you imagine Lebron playing in his 40s like Jordan did? That means he would play for another 9 seasons (including this one). He could easily reach 40k+ points by the end of his career. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 18:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talking to people in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 17:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God daaamn!.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 13:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what if there is no holes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silver surfer in NYC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 19:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 16:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine getting voted most quiet person, then standing up in the middle of the class and shouting YEAAAAAAAAH!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 17:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fake right? RIGHT?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polish preparing for new year's fireworks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 19:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 08:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What most people don't understand is that speed doesn't kill you, it's the acceleration or deceleration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the Cavs wore sleeved jerseys in the 2016 NBA Finals. I actually never knew why and this makes the victory even sweeter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 15:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 08:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Do you love me?](https://youtu.be/6J8lrYFdgi8?t=7s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finnish politician vomits during interview </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 16:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 15:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha.  

Edit: also look [here](https://i.imgur.com/odNuwNs.png), they just photoshop the logo parts out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 07:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love to be reunited with MozGod. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 07:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, they always do that, I once bought ps3 controller with no sony logo on it and when it arrived it had the logo. if you're unsure, you could always talk to the seller and ask for a real photo and when talking use as simple english as you can, they're really tough to communicate with.  

Edit: I think it was [this](https://www.aliexpress.com/item/New-Boston-Adjustable-Flat-Men-Women-Hat-Red-Sock-Letter-B-Snapback-Gorras-Hip-Hop-Baseball/32661351679.html?spm=2114.30010308.3.12.qdLgeb ws_ab_test=searchweb0_0,searchweb201602_5_10065_10068_10069_10084_10083_10017_10080_10082_10081_10060_10061_10062_10056_10055_10054_10059_10078_10079_9915_10073_10070_421_420_10052_10053_10050_10051,searchweb201603_4 btsid=793dc312-7c61-4012-959e-90701caf67c0) one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 16:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, I'll miss him.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's ok not to be ok. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 15:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 11:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for shitty link, I re-submitted here: https://www.reddit.com/r/clevelandcavs/comments/58g0lm/mozgod_doing_some_work_on_durant/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MozGod doing some work on Durant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 11:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 06:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also saw it on aliexpress for $7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 11:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where to buy: http://www.ebay.co.uk/itm/191907569645?_trksid=p2057872.m2749.l2649 var=490967922341 ssPageName=STRK%3AMEBIDX%3AIT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Cavs cap finally arrived! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 11:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 21:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First I want to say that by going to the gym you will experience some failure and the most important thing is to not give up when it happens. My favorite quote is this:  
 Success is not the absence of failure, but the persistance through it.  

Everyone experience failure, it's just a matter of who deals with it better and correct themselves. I had couple of funny things happen to me while in the gym. One time I hadn't properly locked one of the leg machine handles and when I was doing my reps midway through it 100lbs of weight loudly dropped and everyone stared at me haha. It was unpleasant experience, but I told my mind that next time I will know how to use it and just forget what happened. You have to look at everyday as a great opportunity to learn new things and get more experienced.   

When I first started I used any machine that I liked or previously saw people do on YouTube. Over 6 months I gained 12lbs of muscle. Personally I think I did a lot of progress not only physically, but also mentally and increased my self-esteem.  

I would love to make you a week routine plan and explain you various exercises and machines, but I'm going to bed now and I'll contact you tomorrow. I'm also 20M  

Edit: always keep that quote in mind, it helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 18:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone got any helpful tips for me?  

Yes! I was in the exact same situation as you are right now. You are making the right desicion. Gym has helped me so much, I'm so happy that I made the commitment, and you will be too.  

What I suggest you to do first is get to love fitness, get as much information about it as possible, so you are not a total noob at it, watch youtube videos on how to do certain exercises, how to use gym equipment properly, make your week routine plan, find your favorite youtube fitness channel. For me it was Hodgetwins, they were shy and skinny when they started working out and they've grown so much since then, they have funny personalities and are fun to watch and learn from.  

Next thing is getting all that courage you have and going to sign up for the gym. I don't think I can give you any tips for how to do that better, you just have to really commit to it, get all that courage and just go there.  

Fuck everybody else who may think something bad about you, that is their problem, not yours, you are a human being and you learn. Be courageous and DO IT! I'm rooting for you bro!  

Edit: If you have any questions about gym or fitness, I would be happy to help you! AMA

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Benq monitor "Out of range" problem getting really annoying.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 06:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This problem is really strange and happens inconsistently.  
When I turn on my PC, everything goes normal, goes through bios screen, windows logo, then stops and this message appears..  
https://i.imgur.com/vZXphWG.jpg  
This happens once in 10-15 boots. This is really annoying me as I have no clue where is this coming from...
My graphics drivers are updated to the latest version. I didn't set my resolution to be out of range of my 1080p monitor's resolution.   
I tried going to Nvidia control panel to see if changing few settings would do anything, I tried to change "Perform scaling on" to "GPU", didn't do anything, same thing.
To temporarily fix this I just turn off and on the monitor and I'm in desktop.  

My specs:  
Monitor: Benq xl2430t (@144Hz) + Displayport  
GPU: MSI GTX 1070 Gaming X  
CPU: Core i5 6600K  
MB: Gigabyte Z170 Gaming K3  
PSU: Seasonic M12II-EVO620 80 Plus Bronze  
RAM: Kingston Hyper Fury X 2x4Gb 2666MHz  
Windows 10  

As I said above. Why the hell does this happen inconsistently, like once in 10 boots? And what is causing this?  
Please help PCMASTERRACE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My God how much more karma do you need op?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ABBA - Thank you for the music </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 20:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So sad to see the website go... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 13:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Borat at massage therapist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 13:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 07:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder what original resolution and framerate they shot their footage in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 07:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You can finish him?](https://youtu.be/3UsO7HJxTnY?t=1m54s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 20:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She did a hideous tattoo on her arm though.  
Edit: Well, to each his own, I guess.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 20:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I thought we had unfair prices here in Lithuania. Haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 20:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, thanks for great discussion bro.  
Bye.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conan tries to play basketball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 20:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My inspiration to learn french </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [They don't want you to find out the secrets of the trophy](https://youtu.be/EYgf5plDdZM?t=4s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew something was off lol, I'll fix it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm @ 4.4GHz 1.35v full load 72c max, idle 30-35c. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the connectors should be on the other side? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1200 + 300 monitor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing special, usual stuff.  
Fractal Design Core 2500   
Seasonic M12II-EVO620 80 Plus Bronze    
Gigabyte Z170 Gaming K3   
Core i5 6600K  
Cooler Master hyper 212x  
Kingston hyper fury X 2x4gb 2666MHz   
MSI GTX 1070 Gaming X   
WD blue 1TB   
Samsung 850 evo 256Gb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first ever PC build </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Sounds like you're hurt](https://youtu.be/X4Xj_wBcgAM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 16:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/LYYiLiH.jpg  
Also, one exploding phone doesn't define the whole android trololololol.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 08:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://i.imgur.com/8pefakO.jpg)  
And  
[This](https://youtu.be/dQw4w9WgXcQ)  
Tee Hee! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 21:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was my first time visiting here, what a pity.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 21:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> poor 

Literally, the weakest argument you can say when arguing about android vs apple, their prices are about the same and I own Galaxy S6. Also I prefer superior hardware and open source at lower cost over a fashion statement.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 19:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Contrast between South and North Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 19:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 17:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump supporters are like Apple people.. completely clueless, unfortunately...  
Edit: and here come the downvotes...Oh boy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 10:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow..What a contrast between South and North Korea.  
https://i.imgur.com/AAaJaoT.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last Man On Earth. Got more and more frustrating... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 12:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice image quality. What phone is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 08:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's that Hodgetwins mating call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 14:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did it earlier, got no response whatsoever.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stolen content. Removed 3 videos. Channel still up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 14:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've found a guy on youtube who basically has been stealing my whole channel (videos, titles, descriptions, etc..) and I decided to submit a copyright takedown to 3 of my stolen videos. As I've known that 3 copyright strikes on your channel will result in a termination of it, but this guy's channel is still up. It's only been like 30 minutes since those 3 videos were taken down. Does it take time for a channel to get terminated? Need opinions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 18:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The degree of difficulty and preparation is unbelievable. I applaud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 10:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LEL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2 LITER + KNIFE ORIGINAL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 18:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 13:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 10:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I now remember, I got it from ebay for 75 cents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 10:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last Man on Earth. And then it got more and more frustrating to watch.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 10:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 14:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this. Is it worth something?
http://i.imgur.com/FmhAiKI.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 14:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop asking for gold godamnit! it's not gonna happen.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 10:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/KWWQxvl.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 08:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like some burger and fries please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian spiderman [0:07] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 12:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 08:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 17:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hugh mongous what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 16:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pronounced weebor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Matthew Wilder - Break My Stride </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 10:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 10:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 16:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What camera? What lens? Macro tubes used? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 08:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious are there any 16K footage available to see? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best show within a show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 18:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite keyboard key combination and what do you use it most for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 16:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 11:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh sorry, I forgot this was satire comment section, I shouldn't have tried to make any real discussions. Your comment is nice though, I approve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jamie Foxx does Doc Rivers impression </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 10:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Shaquille O'neal is a boxer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 10:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 09:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Realistic curvature from a rectilinear lens: http://www.soarproject.org/photos/sunrisesoar3/2010_08_16_08_20_19_SD800_5012.jpg  
Also a normal Canon lens: http://i.imgur.com/blnbc7o.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 09:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost it at "He's an Astromenor". LMAO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 10:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think that would have been monumental, it would have been like "The Shot" from Michael Jordan, but then again it would just simply add to already unbelievable NBA Finals. If I was told to choose mount rushmore of nba finals, coming back from down 3-1 is going to be my first choice no doubt. Great Finals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 20:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this time I'll set up two lamps facing 45 angle at my face then put the phone on a tripod, connect the phone to laptop to see the screen also use the mouse to navigate the phone and use the rear camera. Should be getting better results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 19:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.imgur.com/fo2rLn0.jpg  
Took me one try before reading your tips, I'm quite satisfied with the face scan, but the quality was only "average" . What are the differences betwen average, above average, great, etc...?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 13:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that's just plain stupidity. These are the people who will buy apple products even if the phone had no charging port. #courage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iPhone users be like </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 12:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 09:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, he was in deep shit, he should be thankful that I saved his life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 21:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well so far no freezes, I think it fixed it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 20:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry for your karma loss.  
Edit: tables have turned, nevermind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is getting out of hand. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 19:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 06:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cough..cough...Galaxy S7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 06:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet people still buy this shit, because they've seen their favorite celebrity have it, so they wanna look cool too, what a shame apple... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Andre Iguodala comments on Channing Fryes Instagram post, but Frye gets him back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 14:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 07:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shipping times can sometimes be more than a month though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 22:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too, so fucking annoying, sometimes it happens, sometimes not. I have to open new chrome to fix it..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 21:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try installing different youtube chrome extensions that does various things like auto hd, auto off comments, etc, there should be an option to auto play I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why sometimes youtube doesn't want to go fullscreen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 17:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 20:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I understand it's gonna be buggy, I like this game, it's a fun apocalyptic world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 17:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 09:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha, good thing I was near NWAF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 08:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God damnit...I had full gear with 300+ akm ammo...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
