<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1369</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 03:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so excited for the first 2/3rds of this!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  maliciously lying

Please show me the evidence of malicious lying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, please show me where the WSJ lied.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not only that the WSJ LIED... LIED about him

Please show me where the WSJ lied.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We just have to wait until 2018.

NO!

There are elections this year! Democracy does not take a break.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw them live in 2011. Their performance of Sprawl II changed my life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is HBOGO down? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 05:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am unable to load any HBOGO content right now. I am getting a sign-in error after the page slowly loads. Is anyone else having this issue or is it just on my end?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is HBOGO down? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 05:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the Civil War count? Probably not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every campaign is flawed. If we can't admit that then we can't learn from it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.tomforvirginia.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it was brown people. Duh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they are experienced professionals. They are not the enemy. 

What alternative would you prefer?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Watered-Down Ethics Rules Let a Lobbyist Help Run an Agency He Lobbied </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhhh, what?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The approval rating polls survey everyone, not just the people who eventually vote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders' national field director is running Tom Perriello's campaign for governor in Virginia. This is the biggest race of 2017 and this sub has ignored it completely. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are only two statewide races this year. In Virginia and in New Jersey. This is the first chance we will get to reject Trumpism in support of Progressivism. 

[So far this](https://www.reddit.com/r/SandersForPresident/comments/5tnt4b/there_are_two_gubernatorial_races_this_year_in/) sub does [not care](https://www.reddit.com/r/SandersForPresident/comments/5monp9/tom_perriello_candidate_for_governor_of_virginia/). If we truly want to make a difference we need to act now. We can not wait for 2018, the people of Virginia and New Jersey need /r/SandersForPresident's support right now! 

I don't know much about New Jersey but I do know that former congressman Tom Perriello is challenging Virginia's democratic establishment to win the Governor's race. He is not a fringe candidate, in fact his statewide appeal may be greater than his party opponent. So far he has filled his campaign with Sanders campaign alums and Clinton advisors. [He wants to bring this party together while pushing it in a new direction. 
](https://www.washingtonpost.com/local/virginia-politics/sanders-alum-to-lead-tom-perriellos-campaign-for-virginia-governor/2017/02/07/d3892150-ed4c-11e6-9973-c5efb7ccfb0d_story.html)
The combination of Sanders activists and some Clinton hands is a pretty fascinating group, said Bob Holsworth, a longtime Virginia political analyst. Hes been able to do that in part because theres not a lot of governors races going on. There was some talent out there, and hes identified it and clearly raised enough money to hire it.

Perriello's victory is key for this movement. Do not ignore 2017.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 15:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this the one near the Verizon Center?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, I'm skeptical that thats the entire reason. 

South Park has always parodied the politically correct and for the past decade or so liberals have dominated politics and culture. Even when Bush was in office they parodied the liberal opposition to Republican policies. Remember, Parker and Stone are 'libertarians.'  

Today right wingers control the government and they are at a loss on how to satirize it because they simply don't have the experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 21:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, you want to just sit around and be wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 21:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try 45 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 21:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Politico is full of it. 

I really hate when people smear an entire news outlet for running an opinion piece.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are two Gubernatorial races this year. In Virginia former congressman Tom Perriello has hired Bernie Sanders' National Field Director to help him challenge the state's Democratic establishment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 21:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 17:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  As for comparable shows, that really dig into their main character's psychology, I would say there is only Breaking Bad. I place those two shows side by side as equally the best I have seen on TV, and much better than most of the movies I've seen as well.

Mad Men is much more the spiritual successor to The Sopranos than Breaking Bad. The parallels between the shows are outstanding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 21:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got downvoted because you posted an ignorant comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 04:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk about a circlejerk. Your comment is just a regurgitation of the_donald taking points and I bet you didn't even realize it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 04:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he is an unhinged strong man who just won the presidency after running the most bigoted campaign since the 1960s.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 04:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is pretty clear that Trump is suffering from some sort of mental ailment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 00:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> quote me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is sad because it is probably FX's best drama right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disturbia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't know the half of it. The Kushners are some fucked up people. 

http://nymag.com/news/features/57891/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 04:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have an .edu email a WaPo digital subscription is free.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buzzfeed and CNN did not report that the information in the dossier is correct, they reported that it exists and is being passed around within high levels of government. 

The dossier was written by an influential British spy, given to Sen. John McCain who then gave it to the FBI. The intelligence community then mentioned it in a briefing with the president and president-elect. 

For a news agency to receive the dossier, learn about the briefing and then choose not to report on it would be an abdication of their journalistic responsibility.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evolution is rude af </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deepthroat wasn't the only anonymous source though, there were dozens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the Washington Post had this mentality Nixon would have gotten away with Watergate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats not how this works though. News sources don't just take the source for their word they confirm the info with other sources. The standard is a three source confirmation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly how racism persists. People deny it despite evidence. You are only empowering and enabling them. 

Please go back to the_donald.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a very clear backlash against Wilmore online because he was black. Reddit hated the Bill Nye appearance and internet racists latched on to it to spread their hate. 

BTW, the idea that Wilmore isn't funny is crazy to me. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1IDFt3BL7FA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone is racist, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit racists also used it to justify hating Larry Wilmore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because you didn't enjoy it doesn't mean everyone agrees with you. This sub is terrible. You people get upset over a new season of a TV show you didn't like. Grow up.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then why are you in this thread?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go back to bed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 05:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sick of people calling me racist that I'm going to vote for that racist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 04:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if Kander could win the nomination without being elected into a higher office than Secretary of State. My hunch is that he could.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's incredible that people believe stuff like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be cool if they would experiment with the style. I can see them using correspondents regularly (kind of like what they've done recently, albeit rarely). 

I don't think the writing is the problem either. Though if they don't hire more people it will mean the current staff will have to take on more. That could lead to quality issues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think if they want this to be something that lasts beyond a limited run, like it has in the past, they will have no choice but to hire more writers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They block Twitter? Its not even blocked at the White House.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I was mad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if you're joking, but I'm confident they are redditors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 23:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You write well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 16:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nixon was the worst president since WW2. Its not even close (yet). 

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/White_House_horrors  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 16:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nixon cared solely about himself and his power. He was nothing more than a political opportunist. 

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/White_House_horrors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I remember correctly Allen is watching the Kerse catch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once again the White working class gives Trump a victory.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brady has played in 7 super bowls. Every single one is a classic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Trump a bigger news story than 9/11? I honestly don't know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There really wasn't though. The defense just manipulated the jury. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump was not aware that appointed Steve Bannon to the National Security Council </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just hit theaters but is only playing in select locations. Closest showing for me is about 80 miles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He isn't up for reelection until 2020. Does no one in this thread no how Senate races work?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 07:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one will remember the vote in 3 and a half years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 07:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol Warner is not up fro reelection until 2020.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 07:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Republican hasn't won a statewide race in VA since '09. 

The legislature is also fairly gerrymandered. Though without that Republicans would still probably have a majority in at least one house.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 07:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That wasn't really the case in 2014. Warner narrowly scraped by, though 2020 is a presidential year and the political climate will be very different.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 07:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perriello 2017!

Or Northam 2017, but preferably Perriello!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 07:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nixon started it in '68. 

http://www.nytimes.com/2008/05/11/books/review/Will-t.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 04:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> delete this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 19:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a fan? There's a lot of overlap between Hokies and Skins fans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 19:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol please keep calling midtown downtown. I'm begging you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol no they do not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 02:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but without the Kardashian - Simpson connection the family never would have had the outlet to use those things to heighten their fame.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But for those aware it was a very shallow

The idea that the 13th amendment was appropriated to continue racial oppression is not one that is taught in many public schools. People have a cursory understanding of what Jim Crow is, I'd argue that much of what is covered in the doc is not known or fully understood by the general public.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is important to understand that the racial resentment in LA goes way back to before the 90s. 

[The Watts riots are a good example](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Watts_riots). The LAPD has been a force of discrimination and oppression for nearly a century.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  they're living in downtown NYC

Trump Tower is in midtown.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder what Nixon would have thought of this plan, if he had won in '60?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but thats kind of a spoiler.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> brit marling's acting was incredible though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thoughts on this?

[SEAL, American Girl Die in First Trump-Era U.S. Military Raid](http://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/seal-american-girl-die-first-trump-era-u-s-military-n714346) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 07:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Killing Caesar got us Augustus

A Roman Civil War got us Augustus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god. If we made the NBA finals I would puke. Im sick thinking about it now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we agree. I spaced and mistakenly worded what I meant. Sorry about that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is an argument to be made that Obama could not have won the presidency with that position.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  MAYBE Trump was the most Liberal Republican to run for office

Wait, do you believe this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it really that difficult to understand that many people have a problem with taking Donald Trump for his word?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you not imagine a scenario in which the ends ever justify the means? 

edit: whoops, swapped my wording.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is incredible that someone can be this stupid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone mentioned VT dining is a guaranteed job (and they're great to work for). 

Blacksburg Transit is also looking for bus drivers. 

There is also a[ general staffing shortage in many Blacksburg small businesses.](http://www.collegiatetimes.com/news/blacksburg-businesses-struggle-to-hire-employees/article_fd421334-9ebf-11e6-ad3f-5bc4a87d1cf7.html) I'd recommend reaching out to owners asking if they are hiring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats. It requires an incredible amount of delusion to believe that. I'm impressed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  both sides have their fair share of lies

This is called false equivalency.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 07:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Breaking Bad is an excellent show, but I'd argue it is in a tier right below the trio I mentioned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 06:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, I'm not really sure what you're asking here. 

Trump's exec order bans all Syrian refugees from the US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 06:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrace Winter was the show runner for BE and Vinyl. Vinyl took years to make so it didn't premier as soon as BE ended.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 06:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Anyone who thinks Breaking Bad is the greatest TV show of all time probably has not seen The Sopranos, The Wire or Mad Men.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An isolationist group that had direct connections to Nazism. They advocated isolationism to assist Hitler.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I think we're just a few cycles away from Republicans openly branding themselves as the party of white nationalistic preservation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of this tweet. 

https://twitter.com/seanmcelwee/status/825023051590881280 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 01:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't answer the question because you know you have nothing of substance to offer. 

Anyone with a cursory understanding of world history would know that to equate George Washington's direct ownership of hundreds of individuals with a person's unavoidable existence in a society which capitalizes on the oppressed is foolish.   

There is not a community on the globe where you can escape those realities. 

You'd rather have me starve in the street than to engage and to work against injustices. You offer nihilism. This approach is self defeating. You are an enemy of your own ideals. 

I'm done here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 01:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Answer the question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 23:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly do you think you've accomplished here?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 23:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you were able to make yourself feel important.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 22:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great. Thank you for solving all of the worlds problems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> America and the wolf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what is your solution? You make it seem like existing is equivalent to being compliant with slavery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And how does that make it ok?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Steph in a vacuum.

We get it, you think he sucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Washington

He owned people. And I do not subscribe to any moral relativism arguments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, I'll grant your premise. But what happens when Donald goes beyond this? What will it take for you to renounce your god emperor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Killing of Americans Deepens Debate Over Use of Drone Strikes](https://www.nytimes.com/2015/04/24/world/asia/killing-of-americans-deepens-debate-over-proper-use-of-drone-strikes.html)

[The Drone That Killed My Grandson](http://www.nytimes.com/2013/07/18/opinion/the-drone-that-killed-my-grandson.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Show Us the Drone Memos](https://www.nytimes.com/2014/05/12/opinion/show-us-the-drone-memos.html?_r=0)

[Secret Kill List Proves a Test of Obamas Principles and Will](http://www.nytimes.com/2012/05/29/world/obamas-leadership-in-war-on-al-qaeda.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of parallels with the original Mac. Cool story! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 04:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the heavy politicized investigations that were stonewalled internally? 

You'd be naive to think Reagan didn't know about the deal, especially given the way he ran the White House. Even North admitted Reagan oversaw the affair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 04:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone who doesn't think he is a criminal has a poor understanding of history. The Iran-Contra affair was literal treason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 04:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OTM is my absolute favorite. [Their series on poverty](http://www.wnyc.org/series/busted-americas-poverty-myths) is excellent reporting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 03:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you get your news?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 03:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a better idea. Don't spreads lie to advance a political agenda.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 03:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes they did, but feel free to stick to your alternative facts.

[Under Obama, a Chill on Press Freedom](https://www.nytimes.com/2014/06/09/us/politics/under-obama-a-chill-on-press-freedom.html)

[Only Nixon Harmed a Free Press More](http://www.nytimes.com/roomfordebate/2013/05/21/obama-the-media-and-national-security/only-nixon-harmed-a-free-press-more)

[Risen: Obama administration is greatest enemy of press freedom](http://www.politico.com/blogs/media/2015/02/risen-obama-administration-is-greatest-enemy-of-press-freedom-202707)

[Was Barack Obama Bad for Democrats?](https://www.nytimes.com/2016/12/23/opinion/was-barack-obama-bad-for-democrats.html?_r=0)

[For Obama, an Unexpected Legacy of Two Full Terms at War](https://www.nytimes.com/2016/05/15/us/politics/obama-as-wartime-president-has-wrestled-with-protecting-nation-and-troops.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 03:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prove it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 03:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe you. You're non-American but speaking with an American accent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 03:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NPR and the BBC are great!

I recommend [PBS NewsHour](https://www.youtube.com/user/PBSNewsHour) (tv show) and [On The Media](http://www.wnyc.org/shows/otm) (WYNC radio show/podcast).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gee why didn't I think of that. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I see. You're just insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is it bad that I don't use facebook anymore?

The truth is that there is no way of knowing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could not agree more! I also think this why the industry is cratering, it relies on an audience who isn't too lazy to think critically.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That shopped picture says otherwise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   when his own party owned both branches for 2 full years and he did nothing

This is a myth. Do an ounce of research next time before you spew bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 03:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Backfired? More like fronthired!

#BRADLEY BEAL IN BLACK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 03:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America wins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
