<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2013</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're thinking of the 2012 Texas Republican platform.  https://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/answer-sheet/post/texas-gop-rejects-critical-thinking-skills-really/2012/07/08/gJQAHNpFXW_blog.html?utm_term=.47cc387005d8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you, stalking them?  How do you know what they drive and how they pay for groceries? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only time it's bothered me was when I getting 8 FPS on XCOM 2 when it first came out.  Thank god that game was turn based. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you get it, don't play on hard.  Bullshit super agents... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure part-time employees exist and are a thing.  Hours worked isn't the difference between an employee and a contractor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh dang... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  I mostly listen to Jedi stories, though.  Is it the kind of story they'd tell me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-mPU_sok_qBc/U7FoSqDcjeI/AAAAAAAAAWE/hKFtwGDF324/s1600/071217_levine_007.jpg  I mean, they had no problem implying white wasn't a color when it came to water fountains... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/books/middleeast#wiki_ancient_near_east  Ask Historians has a book list.  This section might help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, on the bright side you prompted me to Google harder, so I found the source I was thinking of:  http://www.ign.com/articles/2009/08/29/a-space-bounty-hunter-in-texas?page=8  I wasn't trying to imply that Nintendo of Japan had no idea that people could theoretically hunt bounties, just that they thought "bounty hunter" sounded cool but didn't really intend for her to actually hunt bounties.  Like if a Western developer called a character a ninja but didn't have them actually act like one. 

Samus really isn't about the money, a truth that confused the developer -- and me, upon hearing this story -- when it presented Nintendo a gameplay design that appealed to Aran's chosen occupation. "We were looking for something more along the lines of a mission-based game where Samus collected bounties. And for the life of us we couldn't understand why [Nintendo was] being so resistive to that concept. And then over the period of days we came to understand that their definition of a bounty hunter is not a bounty hunter. It is not someone who brings in bad guys for money. That concept was completely outside of their definition," says Walker. Nintendo told Retro that Samus does not actually take bounties for those she hunts. (Someone should tell Nintendo that Aran has officially been labeled a bounty hunter for two decades now, a slight inconsistency.) "So we started joking that Samus was actually a pro-bono hunter. And occasionally we'll run into those nuances of translation and culture that can sometimes derail us for days." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably the same way he feels about actual, real bills: absolutely zero shits.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh.  I literally had no idea he had done anything aside from the salad dressings.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't the Prime developers want to add bounties, but were told not to, and it turns out that Nintendo of Japan didn't really understand was a bounty hunter actually did and just thought it sounded cool?  I can't find it now, but I remember something like that.  That being said, I would love actual bounty hunting.  Star Wars: Bounty Hunter was goddamn amazing.  That kind of bounty system combined with a Breath of the Wild style world/quest system would be so much fun.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only got the best rank in one of the storymode missions because the 1st and 2nd place racers killed each other on a narrow path.  I was so careful the rest of the race because it was my one shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Augustus was right at the turn of the millennium. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://penelope.uchicago.edu/Thayer/E/roman/Texts/Frontinus/Strategemata/home.html  I think you'll like this Roman text.  It's a collection of stratagems.  This one is good, too:  http://www.attalus.org/info/polyaenus.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Territorywise, it's under Trajan, who was also one of the good emperors.  It's usually him or Augustus when people talk about peak Rome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "'When did you have your first sexual fantasy about your sex ed teacher?'  Do we really need to answer this?"

"Yes, it's part of the assignment.  Do it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called "terrorist ass shaking," you commie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then he questioned the election results anyway, saying millions of people voted illegally, without any evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that just buying stocks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The original game is called Doki Doki Panic, which I know off the top of my head because I spend my time wisely.  They changed the main characters, but kept a lot of the other sprites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question came to me while I was watching the Sonic Boom cartoon.  It is a legitimately funny TV show, based off of a game that, so far as I can tell from watching others play it, is awful.  But the show is my favorite American cartoon since Emperor's New School. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's something that's much better than it has any right to be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that'd be better for the chapter titles.  Just every single chapter is "A New Low" until you get to the guillotine one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it true what they say about clowns with big shoes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me neither, my friend.  Me neither... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: /r/bois (NSFW) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Important thing to note: the 13th amendment specifically allows slavery as a punishment for a crime: https://www.law.cornell.edu/constitution/amendmentxiii </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: amethysts used to be very rare and were associated with the papacy.  Then they found shitloads in Brazil and its price went down and never recovered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes I worry, what if all my political views are wrong.  And then I remember that on pretty much every policy that has results that can be quantifiably measured, the Democratic option kicks the shit out of the Republican one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're actually safer getting an abortion than giving birth: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/22270271 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you might be right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the organizer thought that the billionaire who showed up to the donation event was planning to give a donation and wanted to stay on his good side just in case.  I mean, hell, I'd shut up and smile if I thought a good cause was going to get a million dollars out of it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a word for that sharp exhalation when you're annoyed/offended? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sort of like an "ugh" or a slight cough.  It's not a sigh or a gasp.  I'm not sure if it has a specific term.  Does anyone know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nox and Nemesis, from SMITE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spoopy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here, kitty kitty... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black woman in a skull mask </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Ben Hopper's "Naked Girls With Masks" series (X-post from /r/WTF) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cia, from Hyrule Warriors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carnival </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black and White </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Classy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venetian style </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tokyo-Girl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two views of amazing tits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only a mask in public </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Middle Eastern Flavor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who needs a swimsuit when you've got a mask? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Masks and Flip-Flops </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Masked Blowjobs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She earned those beads fair and square </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Masked/Unmasked Avenger (X-post from /r/OnOff) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...is there a subreddit for naked girls wearing masks only?  Asking for my...self.

Edit: there is now /r/NakedMasquerade/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr. Satan actually displayed bravery and good intentions in the Buu Saga, though, and used his fame to help people.  I don't even know who Trump would be in DBZ.  Is there anyone like Frieza, but incredibly weak, and all the planets they try to sell are garish and crappy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were filming near LA in full ape costume.  I can't imagine it was *that* cold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wait until you play XCOM and even a 95% chance to hit is still a big risk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a little like being an old and unloved billionaire in your hospital bed, threatening to blame your sole heir if something goes wrong.  All you're doing is making them wonder whether they could get away with pulling the plug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if the economy after Trump leaves looks like it did when Obama came into office, you'd consider that a great presidency? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank god for Best Of compilations.  There are so few full episodes I can watch, but I love the Best Ofs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They also believed that when Trump said he was going to deport all illegal immigrants, there was an asterisk next to it that said "except for my husband."  http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/trump-voter-husband-deported_us_58d4b262e4b02a2eaab244cd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Senator Whitehouse is pretty cool, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not economically anxious, but... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For comparison:

37% of Americans believe houses can be haunted

25% believe in astrology

21% believe in witches

20% believe in reincarnation

http://www.gallup.com/poll/16915/three-four-americans-believe-paranormal.aspx

You are more likely to find an American who thinks witches are real than to find one who supports TrumpCare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Whatcha doing?  Playing hangman?"

"...something like that..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a counter-counter, isn't SeaTac's biggest employer kind of stuck there?  Not like the airport can pack up and move.  I think a higher minimum wage is needed, but I'm not sure SeaTac is an example that would convince anyone that unilateral minimum wage increases are a good idea.  It's a pretty unique case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z0gGWRnoFDI

"He looked at me!  He looked right at me!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rigor mortis is nature's Viagra. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr Rainman, why are we having clapping competitions in Social Studies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think she's hot...   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My coworker also says "By the time a player becomes a Grandmaster, almost all of his training time is dedicated to work on this first phase. The opening is the only phase that holds out the potential for true creativity and doing something entirely new." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm going to murder you, CountFauxlof!"

"Geez, I don't know what to do in this situation...  [looks away]  Ahhh.  Problem solved." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of notes could they even take?  "Everyone!  Write down "find bacteria faster" in your notebooks!  God, it was so simple!  I can't believe none of you idiots ever thought of that before!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying that he made the wrong call.  I'm just saying that if I had 18,000 cats, I think it'd be fair to claim I wasn't anti-cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hello?  No, the Trump robot isn't malfunctioning, it's supposed to sound like that.  Yes, I know it keeps repeating itself.  Look, it's just playing recordings, we didn't program anything." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For someone so anti-nuclear bomb he built a fucking shitload of them.  https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Historical_nuclear_weapons_stockpiles_and_nuclear_tests_by_country#/media/File:US_and_USSR_nuclear_stockpiles.svg  2,422 in 1955 to 18,638 in 1960. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, what about all those Trump voters for voted for him because they couldn't tolerate him?  Wait... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some Shit is a *terrible* name for an arcade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't that only prove that the royal family were Greek?  That's like saying that Scotland is German because the royal family comes from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you're being too generous.  That's like me saying I don't want people to eat fewer Big Macs, I just want every McDonald's destroyed.  Whether or not I believe that private charities will start making their own Big Macs, it requires willful ignorance on my part to pretend there won't be fewer Big Macs.  I get that you disagree, but some methods have trade-offs, and the only methods they're willing to use *will* help less people.  They're inseparable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ah, I'm such a martyr for speaking the truth."

"Actually, you're just an assho-"

"A martyr..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So 100k at 18 is shit, but 60k at 22 is average? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It *probably* worked out worse for the one who died. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Project Highrise? I don't mind trading multiples. https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/601cw0/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_world_of_goo/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Project Highrise or Star Wolves 3, ? I don't mind trading multiples.
https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/601cw0/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_world_of_goo/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daniel Craig: One, James Bond needs to be louder, angrier, and have access to a time machine. Two, whenever Bond's not on screen, all the other characters should be asking "Where's Bond"? Three-- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're a Texas democrat, vote in the primary against Cruz.  He barely won the primary last time, and he's a lot more vulnerable there than in the statewide election.  Texas has open primaries, too.  You just show up and tell them which primary ballot you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No cow ever tried to oppress the master race!

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They knew they could reach Asia going east.  If Asia could also be reached going west, which is a requirement for being too far away in that direction, then you've got a round earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "But why male models?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was picturing more of an ushanka. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorites.  I think it got me into absurdism back in high school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You know, trump reminds me of an old boss I once had. This guy had no real skill other than hiring people who knew what they were doing

Your boss doesn't remind me of Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What book/movie/game  c. would you show to someone if they wanted to understand your sense of humor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And a partridge in a pear tree! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Project Highrise?  I don't mind trading multiples.

https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/601cw0/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_world_of_goo/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   It's not that people are opposed to equality for all it's that when you try to force someone to accept something instead of letting them take the time to decide for themselves that change isn't really all that bad, you get what you get.

So they're not *opposed* to equality for all, they just haven't decided that they want equality for all yet?  How long do we have to wait?  And what do you say to minorities in the meantime?  "Sorry, we know you want to get married, but Billy Joe hasn't decided he's cool with it yet." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a single issue that most people don't move from the Republican to the Democratic position once they actually know someone personally affected?  I mean, abortion, gay marriage, healthcare.  There *must* be like, one counterexample, right?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wasn't the only one: http://literallyunbelievable.org/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eats gum and hates Dippin' Dots?  Geez.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even stoners' dogs have better finances than me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's probably trying for more of an "imperialism was awful" and less "imperialism got me pho?  Fuck yeah!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not all of them.  The Pope loved him for keeping back Islam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agathocles of Syracuse!  Quick little bit on him: http://www.forumromanum.org/literature/justin/english/trans22.html

Born the son of a potter, he became a prostitute, a bandit, and a general before taking over Syracuse in a coup that saw the elimination of a lot of the senatorial class.  He managed to expand his power across much of Sicily and Italy despite doing honestly kind of crappily in his wars against Carthage, thanks to taking the audacious step of sending an army to attack Carthage directly while Carthage had its armies elsewhere.  (Scipio mentioned him as an inspiration when he was trying to convince Rome to let him do the same thing.)  On his deathbed he made the people of Syracuse the heir to his power rather than continuing the kingship.  His long-term impact was almost nothing, though, because right after him came Pyrrhus and the Punic Wars, but one interesting note is that some of his mercenaries, the Mamertines, took over Messana.  It was they and their descendants who initiated the Punic Wars by asking for protection first from Carthage, and later from Rome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, come on, he grew up to be Paul Ryan.  Wouldn't you want to prevent that from happening again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty well, considering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very fast, very tiny stones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of reading about how during the Cuban Missile Crisis, Krushchev and the Soviet leaders got some message from Castro about how they were willing to die in an atomic war to take out the USA, and they all suddenly realized that they had put nukes in a very charismatic zealot's country who had no objection to using them, MAD or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://articles.latimes.com/1986-01-07/news/mn-13892_1_soviets  Radical Muslims once kidnapped Soviet diplomats.  The KGB sent the leader his nephew's severed dick and then shot the nephew in the head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can false information be classified? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wondering whether something could be known to be completely false by the government, yet still classified, such that someone could get in trouble for leaking it.  Or can only the truth be classified? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how many aspects of sharia you could get majority support for from Evangelicals so long as you didn't mention anything explicitly Muslim about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Project Highrise?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/5wt2cv/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_vvvvvv/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Project Highrise?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/5wt2cv/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_vvvvvv/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard a witch turned him into a newt, as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Project Highrise?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/5wt2cv/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_vvvvvv/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confirmed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 22:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here fore Bastion or Project Highrise?

https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/601cw0/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_world_of_goo/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Project Highrise?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/601cw0/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_world_of_goo/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If liberals got what we want, the Electoral College would be gone and Trump would be a whining pissant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is a pretty good example of what happens without regulations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 15:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traded Day of the Tentacle for Legends of Eisenwald with /u/habilevn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 15:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 03:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confirmed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traded Octodad: Deadliest Catch for AX:EL with /u/Mr_Crocketa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AX:EL - Air: Xenodawn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Freedom Bundle Leftovers, including World of Goo, Octodad: Deadliest Catch, Day of the Tentacle, and others [W] Furi, Inside, Recettear, Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [My IGS Rep page](https://www.reddit.com/r/IGSRep/comments/5wjj8v/saintodhrans_igs_rep_page/)

All games I have are Humble gift links.  I'm really just trying to turn these into things I want, so I'm not gonna be very cut-throat with these.

**Games I Have**

[A Virus Named Tom](http://store.steampowered.com/app/207650/)

[Dangerous High School Girls in Trouble](http://store.steampowered.com/app/27400/)

[Double Fine Adventure Documentary](http://store.steampowered.com/app/402590/)

[Dusty Revenge%3A Co-Op Edition](http://store.steampowered.com/app/252430/)

[GRAV](http://store.steampowered.com/app/408340/)

[JumpJet Rex](http://store.steampowered.com/app/329460/)

[Monster Loves You](http://store.steampowered.com/app/226740/)

[Potatoman Seeks the Troof](http://store.steampowered.com/app/328500/)

[QUBE%3A Director%27s Cut](http://store.steampowered.com/app/239430/)

[Rituals](http://store.steampowered.com/app/359190/)

[Rocketbirds%3A Hardboiled Chicken](http://store.steampowered.com/app/215510/)

[ROCKETSROCKETSROCKETS](http://store.steampowered.com/app/289760/)

[shutshimi](http://store.steampowered.com/app/332530/)

[Streamline](http://store.steampowered.com/app/252850/)

[Super Hexagon](http://store.steampowered.com/app/221640/)

[Super Meat Boy](http://store.steampowered.com/app/40800/)

[System Shock Pack](http://store.steampowered.com/sub/82345/)

[Team Indie](http://store.steampowered.com/app/302850/)

[Thirty Flights of Loving](http://store.steampowered.com/app/214700/)

[Tower of Guns](http://store.steampowered.com/app/266110/)

[World of Goo](http://store.steampowered.com/app/22000/)

**Games I Want**

Axiom Verge

Nobunaga's Ambition: Sphere of Influence

Galactic Civilizations III

Urban Empire

The Magic Circle

Wasteland 2

Furi

Inside

Recettear

Lifeless Planet

Transistor

Endless Legend

The Age of Decadence

Outland

Icey

Europa Universalis 4 DLC

Apotheon

Orwell

Redout

Feel free to offer anything else and I'll see if I like it, but I'm mostly into strategy and management games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not good business if all of your Mexican customers hate you afterwards and refuse to deal with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just makes for more aesthetic sounding, okay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will say that I sincerely enjoy the TV show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "My husband spends all of his time in online chatrooms.  I'm worried he's trying to cheat on me."

"Wow, what an awful guy.  I'm nothing like that, baby, I swear." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You mean Best Korea is...*Second* Best Korea?!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hey, just so you know, if you move your queen there, I'm going to take it."

"Who the fuck do you think you are, Bobby Fischer?  Fuck you! ...  Wait, I didn't think you'd actually take it.  Do over!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only downside is that afterwards I discovered I had somehow misplaced my wallet.  Oh well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, some Googling tells me a Tim Horton's chocolate chunk cookie has 210 calories and costs $.99.  A pound of fat is 3500 calories.  So yeah, they're spending $16.50 *minimum* for her to gain one pound over the course of a little more than three weeks, assuming that the girl makes absolutely no changes to her lifestyle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to love strategy guides, but I never really thought about all the work that must go into them.  I guess as a kid I just sort of thought that Nintendo told them everything.  I've still got my Super Mario 64 strategy guide, even though the cover fell off long ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Average 4 year old is 40 inches tall.  Did she knock down fucking Shaq? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too many survivors.  Not an authentic XCOM experience.

But seriously, this is amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasnt supposed to get 222 [Electoral College votes]. They said theres no way to get 222, 230s impossible  270, which you need, that was laughable. We got 306 because people came out and voted like theyve never seen before, so thats the way it goes, Trump said.

I guess it was the biggest Electoral College win since Ronald Reagan, the president then added. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, right.  

"Hey, it's 1960.  What race of person should we pick for the person we're going to groom for the presidency?"

"Definitely black.  Our country *loves* black people!"

"Great idea, fellow CIA agent!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that's what you meant to say, I'm sorry, but you really need to proofread what you write.  "He shouldn't have too" does not imply "Well, I don't understand what he would gain by blatantly lying."  Trump constantly lies about easily falsifiable stuff.  Have you already forgotten how he said he had the biggest electoral college win since Reagan?  Or the biggest inauguration crowd? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting.  I wonder if they wanted Ted Nugent killed when he said:

Because I'll tell you this right now: If Barack Obama becomes the president in November, again, I will either be dead or in jail by this time next year. Why are you laughing? Do you think that's funny? That's not funny at all. I'm serious as a heart attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Look, buddy, I didn't *maliciously* run over your kid.  I just got my wires crossed with all the information I see while driving.  I shouldn't have to apologize." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell, you don't need to get a single Trump voter to change sides if you can get people who didn't vote last time to show up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But the people conquered by Rome were not fully "Romanized". Latin and Greek were often spoken by elites, but never were the vernacular language.

A lot of languages of Western Europe are descended from Latin.  By the time the empire fell, Latin was very much the vernacular of the Western Roman Empire.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Douglas County went for Clinton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WITNESS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the old Steven Bradbury!  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-2QTcunH2-k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I want someone to make a gif of Immortan Joe from Mad Max, and when it cuts to all of the unwashed masses it has them saying "Four more years!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
