<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3339</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually the putting out of fires have left lots of super dry dead trees to build up resulting in more hot spots waiting to ignite.

Let the forests burn so life can be reborn from the ashes

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 18:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also helps prevent cavities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The wildfires did so much damage because they almost destroyed a whole town not cause climate change </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was supposed to go that far  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know we went through a cold spell their and are models don't work at all but now we are definitely going past the 2c mark  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are looking at you USA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately that is only the case when companies are competing for new market share once everyone claims there spot they price fix to get the maximum amount of profit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if I told you the gas price is made up and barrel prices don't matter. Your paying more now because of the increased tension in the syria conflict.

The fact that in 2013-2014 I was paying 1.10L and oil was $100+ a barrel. so gas companies raise it that high any chance they get because they know you will pay and they have to show their investors profit in industry which is starting to decline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I won one of my predictions thanks mighty mouse  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UFC is where you get to shine and prove that you are great. Lose a couple fights in the UFC you get cut. It's quintessential Darwinism in a fight League and that's why I love it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They shouldn't have joined isis  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another sell out crowd like Budapest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They got taking over by BLM so the black is a show of solidarity I believe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still doesn't make it a good design.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pride Toronto 2017 using a black font with black background </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This belongs on r/crappydesign </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then spent the rest of the round on top of Condit I guess you could give that round but I didnt  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because from UFC 79 to the Hendricks fight he never lost a round  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gsp was more dominant but in the current landscape their is no better fighter  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boredom is the cause  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the problem is solving itself /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup most people settle in to a proper budget really fast  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Canada you just get a cheque once a month so their isn't any stigma and you can buy what you want, the difference being 90% of Canadians have bank accounts and most Americans don't trust banks.

Fun fact: Canadian banks are heavily regulated so they can't go bankrupt and if they do the government act as insurance for its citizens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 09:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's is terrible cause it's either going to cause them to look for wealth somewhere else or create a power vacuum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 06:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately won't be able to go there and test it because doing so would contaminate it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 06:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were afraid it would be tested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 06:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should add that most of the storm missed them lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure which infuriates me more, that nothing is being done or that the public is being left in the dark </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well of you watch the video pretty much American can companies are trafficking people across the border for money 

Making sure border patrol doesn't pick them up and that the RCMP are waiting for them to cross </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the refugees get into Canada. Can we have a real news Network look into this please </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Don't get a tattoo on your butt picked by the internet" -the internet - Micheal Scott- Kenny florian

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ice cores tell a different story  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd need a link to mankind creativity or it's no deal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the polar bears are relocating and thriving  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll take 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The video says it's an  "invaluable resource" We can't put a price on this so let's say it's worth 1 trillion dollars. By the fact that the world's most successful coral reef generates a billion dollars from tourism. So what times that by 1,000. It's using horrible math with no logic. 

What is happening to the reefs is horrible but there is nothing we can do but build new artificial reefs and create a new home for the displaced fish.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you familiar with the little ice age </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry guys once we fix global warming we will have lots of ice to drill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully we can get speeds closer to 800 mph  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean the cost of the plant plus storage is the only deterrent but as the cost of storage collapsed it is feasible to use most new renewable power installation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we fix climate change then are planet decides it wants to go back to an ice age......Do we fight that climate change?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that's a false figure  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To clarify he said it's not obsolete if everyone pays there 2% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From 1 billion to a trillion ......Math adds up /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And when you found out you broke two bones so she wouldn't forget  you ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely american we are the 51st state  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty big  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flying cars are already dead of anything is flying in cities it will be drone.

I'm curious to why we don't have drone jet packs yet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inertia dampners! that's so fucking cool. I'm sure I'm missing more uses of this tech but omg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did some research 

1.19 pounds for gas in the UK 
1.14 dollars for gas in Canada 

57 pence tax for uk 
35 cents tax for Canada  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry but everyone  on the planet could live in one city the size of Spain and be perfectly cared for it just comes down to engineering.

Seeing as most Americans eat 70% corn I don't get your grain issue  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 10:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two concepts that are actually viable 

Vertical farms and condensation farms  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would the discovery of aliens and or life on other planets change your religious views? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One buzz can confirm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5.6 billion people having an identity crisis isn't something I want to see </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You weave a powerful tale my friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aliens dont fit the Bible story we don't want are aliens being worshiped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uae is doing it for their citizens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone else find it retarded that we have the technology to make almost every city on this planet self sustaining but dont do it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baby steps they can't just lift off the veil it will take 10-50 more years  

First they confirm water is more common then previous thought.

We go to Mars we find microorganisms then we dig and find fossils

Then we receive what we think are messages 

We figure out how to decode them 

Says "send nudes" 

I joke but seriously I figured the realization that's we are not alone in the universe is only going to come when the majority of people are atheist and educated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google is one of the companies doing it so I think it's safe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A currently a dealer buys a pound for 1500-2300 depending on the quality, Growing to industrial scale the cost will plummet

If they price it at black market rates $10 a gram, The black market would most likely undercut.

My prediction is $5-$7 a gram.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No matter what stance you take if you put your self in the spot light on the internet your going to get hate no matter what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something something White privilege  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To better balance all the government bureaucrats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Good release is usually done at the beginning of the week to maximize the effect on the market. They were calling for Monday to be the day but then changed it to thrusday.

Bad release are done on Fridays when the markets are closed and people can forget or not panic as much on Monday  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens if they oversell stock?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it will be back up in a few weeks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just watched a dude jump to his death a little bit of humor goes a long way  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didnt want to burden tax payers with an unnecessary trial.

Jumps to his death before he gets to jury selection

Good guy murder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to shabby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean that what most of mankinds mythology was all about titans---gods---Demi-gods---- humans-----genetically modified humans-----cyborgs-------singularity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg how dare he ...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do I search for my results </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes restructuring city's would be ideal but you are being short-sighted if you don't think that Renewables wont cover the Gap coal is leaving  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's enabling us to push towards electric with out it there would be no Tesla. Besides Elon said it best your paying for the future price of Tesla.

If Tesla could produce 10 million cars they most likely would sell 10 million cars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck yes! Let's fix aging and give my kids super  powers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can't fix it, most of the damage is from warmer waters so unless you want to add ice cubes there isn't much we can do  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At one point those rainforest we're all the Earth had for a long time but unless an ice age happens we will still have oxygen. 

But total destruction of the rainforest would be bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of the reason it's dying is cause people are going down and disturbing it that and warming waters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The EPA has nothing to do with the rainforest or reef </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but he sounds like he is getting paid to do whatever it is and he isnt an actor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a scale of one to mount shitolympus how full of shit are you. China was ready to sign the tpp  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot Frankie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Show the friendly fire deaths </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To an extent the worst damage is done.

Everyone is moving to renewable energy.

Demand of fossil fuel is peaking and then going to fall rapidly.

Astroid mining is coming.

There are so many things coming together at the same time that it's not worth the worrying

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That the planet will make more trees as the planet warms  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It worked very successfully but farmers there are old school rape the land of it's nutrients then move on. I think they changed a law that had been made so now it's okay to rape the forest again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not surprised when it comes to doomsday you can never paint with to broad a brush </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work in newspapers and it's funny how people think that cutting down a tree in Canada is the same as the rainforest. Brilliant marketing for the win </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're complaining about something that is damn near impossible to fix besides building new ones are making sure no one goes near a reef there's not much we can do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well seeing as the planet warms more trees will grow north don't forget at one time most of north America and Russia was under 2 miles of ice that's every tree in Canada, half the us and Russia gone non existent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ummm seems like a flawed study. I'd like to see the difference in each country please 

I mean if a rich person in America is only living 10-14 years longer then someone from the slums in India then science needs to step it's game up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really no you're bound by their laws and have none of their rights although if a country does do anything drastic it might cause a diplomatic issue between the two countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember when we tried to save the rainforest and it worked for a couple years ..... 

Edit: this was unexpected </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> History does tend to repeat it's self  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Back up your phone 
2. delete all your apps 
3. Factory reset your phone
4. Reinstall all the vital apps, contacts 
5. Cross border
6. Restore phone 

PS enjoy your phone working like new for a few weeks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your Constitution has no power here.

Besides all they're going to do is search your phone for keywords. I should know it happened to me last time I visited.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is going to wrestling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else disappointed in last night's co-main and main event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a nutshell friction  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be too hard when they can find the headline they like on r/politics and just go with that. 

I mean if it stops Assad from killing another 87 people with sarin gas it will be money well spent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 05:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apr 10 you will have most of the details according to a few newspapers, cbc, global, google, the internet, I mean it's hard to find </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In some countries it's illegal to be gay clowns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you suffer from a bad concussion your memory is depleted makes sense  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would they write a story about this? I'm guessing it's to keep people in India </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeker and futurism are pretty good. In a nutshell you already have </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we all just agree that your government is broken and instead of fighting on who is more corrupt you should be trying to fix it.

The probe isn't going to find wrong doing directly related to trump just like they didn't do anything with Hillary rigging the dnc.

4 years from now vote smarter and in large groups </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if i identify as a troll or a goblin?

Cromwell high is the school in Halloween town </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Erie slience of the roads is going to be amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We know the age it was buried over grown over but not how long it's been there.

Their should be more villages the thing about mother nature is it likes to come in and bury everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 15:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing as we have a over a million Muslim in Canada I can say with confidence it's more then Sweden  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
