<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1120</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 00:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/8a9wof46OwI

Here you go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cozy Island in Beautiful Garden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 20:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 20:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Art of the Deal....I kid, I kid.

Stories normally don't "scare me" per se, but some stick with me. **You** by Kepnes stuck with me because I know there are people like that (psychopaths) out there. From **World War Z** the chapter on North Korea just haunted me. I don't know why but the possibilities of what could have happened really made me think and ponder for ages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 19:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just hope it's soon to bring closure to everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 19:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That one just weirds me out. Especially their actions before leaving and then the whole black magic thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 19:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was expelled from Umass? I thought that was West Point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh lol...um

Zodiac (but honestly, let's face it, we're not going to figure it out)

Almost every single missing child including Asha and the kid in Minnesota who ran away to kill himself (there's a bit of Occam's razor to that one, but there is some weird stuff)

Joan Risch

The family with the SUV and the dog and all the money in their truck that all turned up dead (I can't seem to find this one, but most people think it was Meth related, I am not sure)

There's also another one with a boy who goes missing while camping http://www.insideedition.com/headlines/17295-mystery-deepens-over-2-year-old-boy-who-vanished-in-the-woods (most likely the parents, but there's a lot going on there)

The Oh Shit case

The guy who goes into the bar and never comes out.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does The_Donald feel about Jews? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 15:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 15:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this pet theory that Nick and Eddie (from The Dark Tower) are one in the same. Just thought I'd share.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 15:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maura Murray got drunk, got into a caar accident and died in the woods.

The rest of my favorite cases are not so easily solved, I don't think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has an American president ever cancelled press briefings before? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 06:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 04:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sexy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
