<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1989</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Status Bar Icon Glossary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 20:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 09:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well for those of us that like to be courteous without falling into the trap of being overly so and waiting and awkwardly long amount of time, it might be a public service to remind people where that cutoff could exist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is everyone (jokingly?) asking Phil Knight to pay a $25,000 fine that he didn't incur? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 08:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doors that don't have sensors should have radar so you know weather or not they are close enough for you to bother holding it open. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 08:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I go about securing my home network as suggested in the video linked below </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 06:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/UrG7RTWIJak?t=2m56s 

I am having speed problems and I think my neighbors are on my network. This might be the technique I want to employ to boot them off and actually get what I am paying for...correct?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who here has experience having to go back and forth between a gym and home workout routine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 06:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When deciding which pre-evolution Pokemon to transfer and which to keep, should I prefer the one with higher CP or with more powerful attacks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 21:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that confetto is the singular of confetti. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 07:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When are extras in movies paid and when does the production crew just rely on genuine passersby? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 07:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 09:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: 18 Tricks With Which to Impress Your Friends - u/nerf9631
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 04:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James Spader  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think we need a season that's at least partially dedicated to Reddington's past life and all the stories he tells. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 03:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marrakesh sounds like it would make a good 2- or 3-parter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do companies consciously make the decision to play Christmas themed ads so much earlier in the year than for any other holiday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 06:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 03:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for that suggestion. I found the post where someone has all gold and the tiny Rattata gold medal is reportedly the hardest.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 21:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does that bodily reaction not qualify itself as getting sick from the cold?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Subs that heavily rely on a robust wiki should be tagged as such. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 21:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are subscribed to any 18+ subs, private subs, are a moderator, or are an approved submitter, you will see those tags on your 'edit subscriptions' page by the name of each subreddit you follow where the tag is appropriate. This designation should just be added to the list by the discretion of the mods.  

Edit: Examples would include r/fitness and r/personalfinance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If you are cold but not dangerously so, 15 minutes of shivering can burn 100 calories. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 18:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> videos* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What part of a stereotypically female beauty regiment could men stand to start? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 17:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: makeup has been brought up a few times. My only interaction with makeup in the past (besides holidays and the occasional lost bet) is the scene from Full House when aunt Becky was telling one of the girls that the key to wearing any was to make it look like you weren't. That said, two steps forward, one step back. Any advice going forward? Good tutorials? Product suggestions?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 18 tricks to impress your friends with </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 08:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On one hand, I'm really happy that I can just sit and work while simultaneously earning candies for my buddy, on the other hand, where is our 'I'm not actually moving at all' button for when PoGo things we're moving too fast? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 07:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A lethal dose is also a lifetime supply. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 07:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 06:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but what are the exact numbers?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is everyone's medal progress going? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 06:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm finding the hardest ones to gain any progress with are the ones that pertain to specific pokemon like tiny rattata and big magikarp. Am I the only one? How tiny is tiny and how big is big?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 19:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I mean city cops. They'll answer the phone if you wanna call a complaint in on your neighbor not doing anything illegal, they'll happily let you off with warnings if you aren't giving them a hard time, they might shut a party down if they have to but not necessarily hand out MIPs at the door, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 11:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corvallis is a college town like no other and that's a sustantiated bias. You don't have to have run-ins with the police to hear good things about them (so long as you are a reasonable human being), the symbiosis between the town and the school is stellar, you are almost guaranteed to be in the delivery radius of any food place that delivers (have yet to fact check but that's been my experience), the programs are great, there are nearly endless resources for you to do whatever you might want to. The only downside I can think of is apparently our lab on the coast made seaweed that tastes like bacon and is for some blastphamous reason, not served for breakfast anywhere on the Corvallis campus. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What cool thing does your college do for students that you really appreciate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 11:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't have to be something super inovative and unique but that would be a plus. For example, giving students a printing allowance or offering free coffee from certain resource centers during dead week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are those medals coming? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 05:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 05:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What school do you teach at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do brands charge you more on their own website than they would through a retailer or e-commerce site? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 22:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't they want to pass on the reduced costs to the consumer to attract people directly to them, cutting out the middleman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Visualize The Fortune 500 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 08:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm not ready to be a dad quite yet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 08:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 friends and I were having dinner today. A Christian, Jew, Muslim, Buddhist and Hindu all literally walked into a bar today **and I couldn't think of a single goddamn punchline!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 09:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've found that, for better or worse, the amount of cleavage some woman can get away with in the workplace seems to be proportional to how professional, ambitious, friendly, etc. they are. It seems to be one of those terrible double-edged swords.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the secret to 'grace under pressure'? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: I found something.   
   
Due Date  
Released in 2010  
Underwhelming ratings  
Staring Robert Downey Jr. and Zach Galifianakis  
  
Downey's character throughout most of the movie is exemplary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why was this marked NSFW?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is the ASL gesture for 'please turn your blinker on' so similar to giving someone the bird? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why, of all the veggies out there, are onions, tomato, pickles, and lettuce the de facto burger toppings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey PokemonGo players, what are some good spots around campus? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 07:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preferably a somewhere indoors and Wi-Fi enabled where I could set up shop by a pokestop and leave my phone on idle while I study. I'm also noticing that some places are definitely better than others for spawning good pokemon. What are some of the good spots you have found?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] An expression akin to 'no chill' that suggests someone is very energetic and productive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 09:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is every Mile Snow album the same jackolope with a different color scheme? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 18:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is every Mike Snow album cover the same jackalope with a different color scheme? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 07:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 07:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Message the mods. I don't know what to tell you. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 07:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was the default option...on the first link - in the approved list - on the sidebar that actually generated a list of templates for me to choose from. I didn't like it either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Probably just a symptom of how divided we've become. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 06:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE wish that we were given enough characters to give our Pokemon the names from the Honest Game Trailers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 17:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xMq-FyDBeBA  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What type of business makes for a good educational model for accounting students? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 17:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am taking an accounting class right now and want to review the material from the context of a single business dealing with all the document types, transactions, GAAP principles, etc. What about the business should I have made up in my head before pursuing this thought experiment? Are there any products/services that are more or less conducive to this idea? What other factors should I consider?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 09:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *snaps Yes*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time management will forever be a skill worth mastering and college has taught me that better than another other phase of life thus far. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 08:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are the first 100 days so important to a presidency? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moreover, what have the last 44 presidents done in their first 100 days? And if it hasn't been all 44 that have focused on that number (as I assume), then when and why was that precedent set?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE feel both gross and responsible at the same time for having voted? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 00:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What activity or exercis3 can I take on to get rid of shaky-hand? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 21:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What place it is that serves food in the orange plastic to-go containers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see the containers all over campus but never see anyone actually eating the food, let alone, where it's all coming from. I wanna try this place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most impressive part of this picture is that his hat grew up to be a full sized doormat.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do spiders hide when they're not on their webs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 19:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This morning was a cold and foggy one. You could see every spiderweb in the area from all the dew that had collected on it. It occurred to me that I was seeing dozens of webs and no spiders. Where do they go? The cold couldn't have killed them all, could it? Even then, I imagine some would be left on their webs or somewhere nearby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best fresource for briefs on a wide array of topics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 06:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #longlivepluto
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 02:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who comprises the electoral college though? How are they selected?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who comprises the electoral college? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 01:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In what ways have you used the student card to get something that you otherwise wouldn't have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 22:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you do this just for the sake of wanting to hold onto your starter?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does the human body devolve so much over the course of one lifetime that jump rope evolves from a playground activity to an exercise routine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 10:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I reproduce a trademarked logo as a gift? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 22:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am part of both an organization with a trademarked logo and a company that can turn that logo into a large piece of metal wall-art. I want that piece of wall art to be a surprise gift to my local chapter of the organization but I don't want to get myself or my company in legal trouble because of any lack of consent.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do earthquakes shake things instead of move them in one direction? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 20:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't see the jack under the Mustang. I just thought it was really excited to be in the same frame as a Porsche.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 02:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] a prestigious award where the awarded person is not allowed to speak during the ceremony. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 01:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think either Tom Hanks or Bill Murray won it recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst thing to respond to with 'Not with that attitude!'? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 07:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 23:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair, and I get that. I just mindlessly posted without reading submission rules or checking the wiki like I normally would. Desparate times, it wasn't a Desparate measure, just a bad one. Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 23:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate the sarcasm. Unsarcastically, thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 23:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help me and my friends get as ripped as possible as quickly as possible. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 23:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 01:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/x6Ml4AEt0kk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 04:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I don't think they're hitting a nerve. (Call me deffensive) but I just thought that they were flat out wrong in their assesment. Or at the very least, I was genuinely surprised and caught off guard that they were correcting a part of me that I thought I already went out of my way to be good about. I'm more confused than hurt, and a little scared about the authority this particular person has over me and how they might exercise it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 04:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which I absolutely agree with but how should you react? Because my gut reaction would have been to let my blood boil a bit and become defensive, which I know is bad, but what SHOULD I do?... In the moment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the proper reaction when someone points out a character flaw of yours seemingly out of nowhere? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 01:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: A lot of the comments are mentioning that a 'thank you' could be a good response. Well, this is where things become almost comically ironic. The thing that was pointed out to me was that I don't say 'please' and 'thank you' enough. I was honestly set back because I thought that I was really courteous with this person but apparently not courteous enough. It was pointed out to me toward the beginning of an interaction in the day that went on for another 30 minutes or so and a lot of that was sheer silence because my behavior immediately transitioned from normal to walking on egg shells. This post came after that because I've been looking for some ideas for how to continue interacting with this person. It's just an inevitability. 

Edit 2: I've become really self conscious about how courteous I am and have started inserting please and thank you in as often as possible. So, appropriately, a thank you is in order for all the commenters. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 01:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think I could extrapolate your example and settle on cues being a good compromise for any lack of consistency with any number of behaviors? I can imagine a potential point of there being too much for the dog to keep track of but I can also reasonably see a dog being smart enough to handle it very well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 18:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is splitting the training between 3 people difficult because you see potential scheduling problems or are we doing a disservice to the dog by not having a single 'pack leader' as it were?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Survey] What topic, unsolicited, comes up the most in casual conversation for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 07:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help me and my friend plan for ownership. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 23:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are looking at a 3 roommate living situation next year and want a puppy. One of us (me) has never been a dog owner before. I really want one though and am probably not going to be talked out of it. And I know that in the long run when we aren't living together anymore, ownership of the dog has already been conceeded to them. Now, we are all going to be students and have full plates as is, but are determined to raise the dog well. What advice can you give us (me) to help us prepare for this and make it more managable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE 'trace their steps' by going back to an app on your phone that you were just on before you lost your train of thought? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does hiding posts do if it effectively just saves them under a separate tab? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 07:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I started actually exploiting this with no unintended consequence ( that I've noticed so far). I save all the good SFW content and hide all the good NSFW content to compartmentalize the two apart from one another. Is this a bad idea? Will I eventually stop seeing NSFW content on my from page entirely? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where is the line between a friendly reminder and micromanaging someone or being repetitive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 06:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because on one hand, I get that busieness can be a legitimate excuse, but on the other hand, so can forgetfulness. Rather than having this conversation every time, I'd rather find that perfect balance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 22:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A certain amount of different words only makes sense. Are eight lions lounging under an acacia tree the same kind of group as a quarter million starlings that blot out the sun?  

Well, despite the other response, I don't think any word is definitionally tied to a number in the same way it's tied to a particular animal. If we had one word for it (Like they apparently do in Turkish), then all you have to grow up knowing (I'm assuming anyway) is the approximate sizes for different groups. Like, it's just assumed knowledge that a colony of ants is hundreds of times greater in numbers than a pack of wolves. Am I getting that right u/dewainarfala ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do we have different names for groups of different animals? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 10:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to contest that it's fun to say "hey look at that murder of crows swarming above the Congress of baboons!" but... Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 03:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm being taught that stuff, poorly, but the examples are very disjointedly jotted down on the whiteboard and if the professor could at least do us the favor of keeping it neat, then I think I could save myself the headache of the transition to computerized accounting in later courses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 00:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will definitely try those out, thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHY ISN'T THIS MARKED NSFW? IM IN PU- oh wait.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 22:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not OHP but yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any free Flu shot clinics still up and running in the area? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 22:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help me teach myself accounting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 22:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in a 200 level accounting class and not using excel. I'd be kind of infuriated if that was the only problem I had with this class and professor. Maybe it's part of the course description, maybe the professor is just that bad, I'm doing my digging, but I want to learn how to do *actual* accounting, not just what the prof says we need for the exams. What free resources/tools are you using to teach yourself?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst flavor to combine with coffee? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 21:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: As in actualy syrup flavors that could realistically end up in your coffee that you just don't thing are good. I've never seen Monin put out Poutine or horse meat.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This might be especially relevant in light of the lifted embargo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 00:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FCw58FDw9Zg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In preparation for this kind of feat, what essentials did you have on you at all times, what was dead weight, and how did that change over the course of your trip?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 08:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. I needed somewhere to practice posting links like [this](https://www.reddit.com/r/OutOfTheLoop/comments/2v93u7/who_is_this_guy_that_just_bought_a_new/) and I decided to do that by replying to your comment and instead of discarding, I deleted the comment. Sorry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to Acknowledge a really great thing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 08:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So in a Vlogbrothers video that is as of now, over 5 years old (link in the doobly doo), John talks about getting a mentor and all the good that that will do for you. I, being a college student, took this message in wholeheartedly. But not just from taking John's word for it. Let me tell you a story.  

I started my college career at a community college right out of high school. I stayed at home, commuted to class daily, saw a lot of familiar faces from high school, made some friends, and did some soul searching via taking classes from several departments to hone in on a major I'd be happy with. Well last year, one of those familiar faces runs into me, we catch up, and he tells me that he is doing some sort of work/mentor/understudy program that he had a really hard time describing for me. I was intrigued but brushed it off and the conversation organically moved on. In a follow up, he invites me to meet his mentor and I did. I got the hunch that there was a catch but upon first impressions, he said nothing disagreeable. Then began a long cat and mouse game of what I eventually realized was an attempt to recruit me into what some people would call a pyramid scheme. (My mother was some people. Mother is always right. I'm glad I listened to mother.) 

Anyway, the friend's mentor called himself just that and suggested that it was the key to success. I didn't disagree but I also didn't feel like taking the bait. (It's at this point I wanna pause and iterate that I'm not going to hate on the friend or his mentor or the company. Every person I met in that organization was genuine and good. I just didn't feel like it was for me.)  Well fast forward a couple months and [Tai Lopez](https://www.reddit.com/r/OutOfTheLoop/comments/2v93u7/who_is_this_guy_that_just_bought_a_new/) started making his rounds in front of YouTube videos and, I gotta admit, I took the bait once or twice and heard him out through to the end of the ad. It sounded kind of like the same, inflated, too-good-to-be-true story telling and I was waiting for the pitch. Well, if you listen to Tai's speeches (in particular, I just watched his TedTalk), he also brings up that a mentor is key to success. 

Now, I'm not one to believe in coincidences like that. Maybe mentors are a common denominator for successful people, maybe telling people to go get mentors is the key. I don't know yet, I'm not successful by most metrics. But there is a pattern cropping up here. And here is the kicker. Here is the great thing.  

The great thing is that John and Hank built a community. They do what they do because they want to be doing it. Nerdfighteria isn't a sales pitch. Crash Course is practically a high school education for free. I didn't recognize it at the time but the Green brothers are some wonderful people with a lot to offer the world. 

 https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UBKKcxCuH-g 

TL;DR : John is the great thing. (And Hank) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 08:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At what age do kids start remembering? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 07:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your go-to coffee drink? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 02:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 'daily driver' so to speak is simple black coffee. I have syrups and a milk frother but I usually don't put the effort in for myself. If I order from a coffee shop, my default choice is a cappuccino.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is Tai Lopez and whats the catch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 02:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 23:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful picture but I thought there were only 5 BA pilots...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] The word for replacing a product name with a brand synonymous with that product. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 23:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Examples include brands like Lego, Kleenex and Styrofoam not being the generic product bame, but just brand names that are heavily associated with their product.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 08:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only done 10 prestiges, my most powerful hero is Flavius (level 286) and I haven't competed in a tournament in a while because I am stuck in the low 400s trying to earn my trophy for reaching stage 500.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 07:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought your singing it was the actual thing that you found and I was really confused for a minute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 07:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know there was a guild but congrats!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 07:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! It's more of plug-n-chug that I want to do with it. I just want to be able to plan accordingly and know exactly how much I have to save up before my most powerful hero can start demolishing monsters with one hit. It'd be especially helpful to save up because I don't let this game take too much of my time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 04:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5 is arbitrary. Any number really.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 23:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hey! Pervert! My eyes are up here!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 23:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can OP replace the check boxes with numbers? The chart gives a *decent* idea of chronology but it's not always super clear.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it is convenient to assume the worst in strangers. I'm a lazy, socially awkward freshman, and you are a know it all that has to prove it to everyone, cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 19:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If some app did exist, it wouldn't have been 14 hours. This is just you being sadistic and trying to prove something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 19:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I think asking around on here like this might qualify as a type of exploring in more people's books than whining. In any case, I have been asking around and it's not a sociability issue, it's a time and convenience issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at the DPS of each hero and the cost to upgrade. Those numbers go up every time you make a purchase and I want to know exactly how much I am going to spend on exactly how much DPS if I upgrade the same hero 5 consecutive times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mario might have a point but a non-answer is just that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone publish either a formula or chart to keep track of both DPS cost and upgrades beyond just the displayed numbers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 10:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to view the all time top posts of all the subreddits I'm subscribed to on one page? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 09:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my workaround for this was actually visiting each sub, finding the top post, hiding it, and using my 'hidden' tab to view all of them in one place. Kind of crude but it worked. Here is also some interesting stuff that I might put together more formally later for r/dataisbeautiful  

Of the 120 subs I'm subscribed to... 

6 top posts across all of those subs are marked NSFW  
29 posts were awarded Reddit Gold  
189 Gold awarded in total  
1 top post belongs to a Mod of that sub  
2 top posts belong to Reddit Admins  
619288 upvotes in all  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 08:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Respectfully, the world doesn't need to be my oyster when I find myself both needing to pee and on a floor with no bathrooms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is one uncompromising promise you made yourself that is a part of your daily life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 07:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does something exist that maps out the amenities around campus? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 04:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking of things like bathrooms, drinking fountains, atms, and coffee shops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if time wasn't a factor and, all else being equal, we only look at the 'quality' of code, you would probably build your own library, opt for algorithm X, go for 100% coverage, and not mash. But doing all of the above in a program that increasingly demands more infrastructure is the bottleneck that I am thinking of. How did some of the larger programs out there grow to be so big in the first place?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There seems to be a general trend that is never spelled out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have dabbled in a couple languages for a little bit but don't know much about coding. What I did notice however was that, the more things you wanted your code to do, the less ways there were to do it. That sort of sobered me up to the idea of doing things the 'right' way all the time, but I never got close to understanding where that bottleneck is, if it exists. So, my question is... Does it exist? Is this a trend I have made up in my head? What are some of the better programmers doing to work around this problem?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much merch is too much when it comes to buying things up for the sake of school pride? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 20:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit 1: I'm at a pac-12 school.  
Edit 2: Clothes are not the only thing I'm referring to. There is also stuff like decal stickers, lanyards, bottles, notebooks, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 06:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have ever driven down a bumpy road long enough to get used to the sound of your keys smacking up against the steering collumn, you should have a pretty good idea of why the ball hang doesn't bother us all day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What thing, person, idea, etc. can be sexy without being nsfw? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 06:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 23:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have. And we've replaced routers. Roommate has a bunch that our neighbor is using our network to torent stuff because he is getting the Notifications from Comcast and none of us torent. Could Comcast be throtteling us? That just doesn't make sense that two devices (phone and latop of roommate who has the router in his room) wouldn't be effected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 08:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am and didn't want to carry that bad habit over to other settings like my professional vocabulary... or talking to cuties. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 06:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In place of 'anywho'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is 'anywhom' an okay word to use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 06:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take it by the fact that it's underlined in red as I type and that Urban Dictionary is the top hit when you google the word by itself that the answer is no but it seems to me that it aught to be a real word so I am just looking for confirmation either way. 

P.s. - Context is chatting with a cutie and self-proclaimed nerd so not making a grammatical error in the chatting would be really cool and the sooner the better.  Please and thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 23:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reason I upvoted was because the regions were labled. I can never keep them straight and just refer to the generation. Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 21:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] What's the OTC go-to hangover cure that some people swear by? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 20:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a powder that disolves in water and is not Alkaseltzer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is it called when a company that for all intents and purposes is jointly run by more than one person, but is legally a sole proprietorship? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 01:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you call the business  in this case? What about the head of that company who has it in their name? What about that person's partners? Is there a short hand in the business world for the terminology?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] What's that little saying about whe, guys are in the urinal and inevitably drip on their pants? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 19:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 19:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or siren sounds in music </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 19:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the two guys join hands above you, it's called an Eifel Tower.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What earworm do you get a lot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 19:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 10:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Something more western than Chinese. Not quite western Europe western though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A language with a comprehensive alphabet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 08:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And when I say comprehensive, I mean that, to the best of my knowledge, if the human mouth is capable of making the sound, there is a good chance that sound has it's own letter in this alphabet. I think native speakers need to spend a significantly longer amount of their childhood learning how to read.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are the resources of colleges outside my declared major available to me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 03:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that last move... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internet around the house. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 00:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my roommate and I are having internet issues. Correction, I am having internet issues. It is very frequently very slow for me while the router and all of that is in his room and it's not an issue for him. I am currently on my laptop in his room (where I can see *some* improvement but not anywhere close to his performance levels) and we are trying to do troubleshooting. We don't want to blow money on something that won't fix the problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 21:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More importantly, what started did she start with and what one did she catch?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a BA 211 (financial accounting) tutor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 20:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My professor for this class is among the least help fill I professors I have ever encountered, full stop and I want an A in the class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 10:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my experience of transferring from a state-run two year school to a state-run four year school, the bigger school was so compartmentalized that the main admissions office cared less about transferring with a degree or credits than they did about anything else (gpa, essays, application, etc). Basically, an associated degree may or may not be benificial depending more on your career trajectory and less on your academic trajectory. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 21:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Million dollar idea - Lego licences all of their hat, hair, and helmet pieces to a helmet manufacturer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are mason jars so popular? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 21:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 09:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It tracks in kilometers but OP is probably American. The unit conversion snubs you all the damn time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 09:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OVER halfway there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it just me or were the first three kilometers the shortest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 04:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like it's taking longer to earn candies the more I try to earn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 03:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he wall off competitors from other planets?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 00:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firstly, it's spelled Butterfingers.  
 Secondly, yes, it's quite a popular candy bar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Miss Universe always from earth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 23:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 20:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That depends. Is mayonnaise an instrument?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 20:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilary Clinton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What might some of the subject matter be in a class designed to prepare it's students for adulthood? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 20:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 07:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have multitools around the house and in the car but I could stand to add one to this collection of things! haha. Thanks for the idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 06:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I give the collection a quick glance and quick thought to think of what I couldn't do without for the evening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 06:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically yeah. So I am currently a student, most of what I could conceivably need with me throughout the day has a home in my backpack. This little collection was started on the premise that there are occasions where formal dress kind of calls for minimalism. So yeah, depending on if it is a professional event, family get together, date, evening with friends, or what have you, I have a quick place to go and know that I can grab what I need and nothing more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here is a list of things that I don't EDC but have all sitting together in a spot that I inventory before leaving the house. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 06:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reason I do this is because I found that this is a good system that lies in the Goldielocks zone between Boyscout level preparedness and not carrying so much on myself that it becomes cumbersome. Suggestions welcome. 

A pocket pack of tissues  
A small bottle of Purell  
A 5x3 spiral memobook  
A matching pen/pencil set (complete with leather carry case)  
A card holder (complete with business cards)  
A fine cigar (perishable)  
A small knife  
A torch lighter  
A zippo lighter  
A tube of chap stick  
A small (powerful) flashlight  
A small pack of mints (like tic tacs or altoids smalls)  
A pack of gum  
A flashdrive  
A small external phone battery    
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 16:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fast and furious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 11:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the same reason we capitalize proper names, days of the week, months of the year, holidays, institutions, structures, nationalities, religions, streets and planets to name a few. 

Source: http://www.grammarbook.com/punctuation/capital.asp  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 10:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You is kind. You is smart. You is important.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 05:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I first read 'proper husky' before opening the gif, let it play, and thought to myself "Yep. that is one correct husky. They definitely do that." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are large companies like Trump and Luxotica able to sustain themselves as a single economic and legal entity and still be made up of many smaller brands? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 05:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What news outlets have good reputations for neither having left nor right political leanings and biases? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 20:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get a good vibe from the members. People are people and I've met some good ones. Haha. I just don't have the slightest clue how they compare to the other frats in any way. The house is on Greek row so I'm not blind to the living conditions of other frats but the physical house itself is only one consideration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What due diligence do I need to do before joining a fraternity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 19:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a transfer student to my state university and dove head first into a lot of extracurricular. I am trying to be careful to not let things get in the way of academics but that's not what I am mainly concerned about. There is one frat that I have been introduced to and want to join but what are some questions I need to ask them or myself before I commit to that kind of decision? Questions I have already asked involve things like the time commitment, financial obligation, weather or not the house is a dry house, a party house, etc., weather the cook can accommodate my dietary needs, and weather or not living in would be required. What are some of your experiences? Anything you wish you would have known before signing up? Do I need to shop around?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 08:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is 15/15/15, 0/0/0, and IVs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is DI water not safe to drink? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was walking through a hallway in a chemistry building when I saw a water fountain warning passers by that it wasnt drinking water. So, I guess, on top of the title question, brownie points for any guesses as to why it was set up to look like I could too my water bottle off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "To err is human; to really foul things up requires a computer."  BILL VAUGHAN </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 20:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the story of the happiest you've ever been? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 07:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] An app that gives each and every 3x3 plot of land on earth a unique 3-word long address. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 05:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the deal with limiting CP? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 23:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I noticed that, even though I have plenty candies and stardust, I max out at a number well below 9999 CP and it tells me that 'Trainer level is too low to power up' Why does this restriction exist and what else do I need to know about it?  Also, I have seen cp calculators that max out the
 pokemon's potential cp based on what level of was caught at and I am just look9ng for verification on that because that almost sounds like bull. Especially if your level has something to do with it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you address your professor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 23:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First name, last name, Mr./Ms./Mrs. Last name, 'professor', or something else entirely?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What quiz, when complete, deserves it's own post on r/coolguides? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 23:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'm thinking of entrapment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A movie where Sean Connery's character assults the female lead by dunking her head into water. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 08:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about applying that formula to a much greater distance? Say the actual diameter of the observable universe?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens in this theoretical universe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 22:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for confirmation of a thought experiment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 22:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What's the difference between different burnt things? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 20:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More specifically, I know that wood and foodstuff are both made of hydrocarbons and when you burn them to a crisp, any high school science teacher would remind you that you are basically left with carbon at that point. But there is still a discernible difference between a burnt log and burnt piece of steak. Or even burnt steak vs burnt vegetables that the more daring of us could still taste. Does that just mean that it wasn't burned away *enough* or what?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you have to close your eyes and go to your happy place, where do you go? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 18:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 08:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *can* knot but I choose to not knot until you ask if I *may* knot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 08:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why you save the nsfw posts to view then later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need help with adopting cycling as a form of transportation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I wasn't too skeptical of if at first. Just to clarify a couple things off the bat, school and home are 2 mines apart and I have a road bike. I got it, bought a bunch of gear, planned out my commuting times, the whole shebang. Then I go from using a car to using a bike and I kinda realized that I hated it. Its not the same as riding my bike for fine run I was a kid. My legs and lungs start burning, I'm constantly worrying about something breaking on the thing, it's harder to justify lugging around water and coffee and that's a tough choose to make for me honestly,  and being in a college town, I have the other constant fear of it being stolen. I bought 2 locks and that's not too much of a burden but it does kinda suck when I'm in a hurry. Oh, and winter is coming so I get the burden of coming home in the evening in the blistering cold. Any advice would be welcome because I have already commited to this.  

Edit: Alright, I was kind of being a bitch about it when I was complaining about everything and blew every tiny thing out of proportion. No pain, no gain, fine. I'm not in terrible shape, I am just used to using my car all the time so stopping cold turkey is a change. Again, sorry for my attitude problem above. I have a bottle cage and a backpack with side pockets. One for coffee and one for water, problem solved. I guess I was just hoping to fish a golden nugget out of you guys but 'Suck it up buttercup' took silver so we're good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 09:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Final Fantasy  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 08:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well we can just wait a couple months to find out because I didn't take summer classes so we will just have to see come winter term.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 07:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But do you believe there is a balance to be found or do we have to pick the lesser of two evils? Because snake oil sounds pretty cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 07:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. Whadaya know. It worked that second time. Thanks for all the help!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 05:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with that analogy though is that pharmaceuticals are not apples. And the health care industry, (among a couple others) are distinctly different from ones where a simple example can illustrate a principle. The end user has to rely on a gargantuan network of care providers, researchers, legislators, regulators, and businesses to access the thing that will keep them alive. Somewhere along that long line, the customer loses their opportunity to shop around for alternatives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 04:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One time at band camp, my bunk mates and I learned a couple things.  
IcyHot is a *DEFINITE* no.  
Toothpaste is a bad idea but not as bad as Icy Hot.  
GoldBond actually feels good down there. (I use the powder)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 02:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I followed similar instructions from a YouTube video that seemed like they should have worked. I'll follow your instructions to the T and get back to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 23:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tried that without success. I'll give it another shot though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 19:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> followed those instructions and got a file type that won't play with my calendar app very well and hon't attach into an email from my desktop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best way to integrate my class schedule with calendar apps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a shortcut? The calendar app I already use integrates all the email accounts I sign into but my class schedule isn't showing up. Is there some tool or trick I'm not aware of ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
