<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2159</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 16:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were sittin on this one, weren't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 16:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You birches should be at work anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 03:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 23:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big boats make me feel funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good sarcasm takes a minute to kick in  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone verify what happens if you get a premium from the crate that you already own? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 03:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's difficult, but the enemy teams still has the same amount of low tiers. If you contribute more than them, you'll win games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 22:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah I remember that... shame shame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's some poor logic. If he backs up his opinions properly, that should let you know if his review is accurate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 18:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most are the 180 degree videos, so if supports that, sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 16:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy birthday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 13:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't remember this change either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 01:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Less than some. I spend a lot though too and am good enough to lots of avg exp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 22:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other cruisers are at 33% citadel damage and the British heal is way faster  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 21:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 21:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point I have like 6 or 7 T10s and 50+ ships in my port but I still have 200 days of premium. 

*shrugs* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, at this point they look like they'll be pretty good at least. Especially with that OP heal. I'm not sure I like how they are breaking the rules of AP to MAKE them good, but I'm willing to wait and see. At least they'll play a lot different than other cruisers we have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good change but 35k HP is still very difficult to work with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 05:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be real though, potatoes are delicious and I have nothing against them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May the flames guide thee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I think someone is botting, I call it out in all chat and if they don't respond, that's good enough for me to report. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to say maybe it's just a little kid, but goodness me 6000 is a lot of matches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 17:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U a boss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 17:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pro tip, run the turret traverse mod that gives 15% faster traverse for only a 5% reload reduction (.25 seconds). After EM, the 180 is down to 18 seconds which isn't bad at all. And BFT brings the reload back down under 5 seconds.

Edit - just saw OP is already on top of things. Good on you OP. Carry on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 15:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone confirm if I can just play the game story only while skipping most mundane content? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 23:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I told my clan mates, "there's no way this fragile piece of trash is a competitive ship" when I first played the Kutuzov. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 19:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dat booty can't hide  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 18:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exterior is also nearly identical, paint job notwithstanding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 18:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I thought they were waiting on improving it before putting it in the base game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 15:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was my thought too but Prinz Eugen was a carbon copy Hipper and it was $50. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 14:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they just consider it for ease of play.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 14:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah I see that as the trend, but I just don't get why ship size should affect prices. Maybe I just need more coffee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 14:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder what the rational is for DDs to be cheaper than BBs and cruisers for premiums.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 14:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $25 for a T7?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 16:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's very few instances where it's even possible to purposefully run into allied torps. And most would still try to avoid because it's more fun to play and win. I'm not a fan of neglecting something that could benefit many users because a terribly small percentage may abuse it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 15:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a zao with worse HE but also like half the reload and way better traverse. It evens out. Hindenberg is godlike imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 16:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More definitely is better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 16:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Benson has better torps, more maneuverability and speed, and 20 minute duration smoke. Benson will be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 21:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen it yet, so I hope not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 20:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god two brothers is in the queue?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 14:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have games all the time in the Atago where I go through all the 60-65k potential HP. Don't know what you're on about. Assuming you don't just get instantly deleted, you should be using those heals well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you have to look at the average damage per ship as compared to others. Just like any stat, really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is also not a reliable way of measuring effectiveness. For example, as a cruiser, if you focus on killing DDs, your damage will be lower than someone that burns BBs all day, but you may be helping your team win more. 

It's best to look at all the stats, which is where something like WTR comes in handy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://m.imgur.com/CoWZ05t?r </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 19:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything about them is so ridiculous it's hard to take them seriously. It's like, come on, these guys couldnt possibly belive they are in the right. But then they keep on going. I dunno man. Something funny going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 19:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember my first ever Bismarck game I got a devastating strike on an Amagi with a quad citadel. Was from about 8-10km iirc.

Have never really had an issue citadel'ing anything other than dispersion, but that's any BB. Have even gotten cits on other Bismarck from long range.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 04:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 04:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Learn to chapy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 03:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you get to high enough rank, I'd expect more from teammates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 03:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teamwork goes a long way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 22:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally, if you know there's a DD around you don't try and smoke up until they're neutralized. But there's basically always a situation in battle (either ranked or random) where being smoked up is very useful. My div mates and I do this regularly in randoms and my 80% winrate over the past month speaks for itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 21:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I just said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 19:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, there's certainly good times for it and bad times. Luckily Bismarcks have hydro so it's less of an issue for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: DDs smoking up their allies is a game winning strategy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 19:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Often there is a single BB that gets focused first, if you can smoke them up when they're under heavy fire, that's a huge swing. I know it can be difficult to coordinate with randoms, but just something to keep in mind/look out for. Using your smoke screens for more than just yourself is a huge advantage and something that is often utilized in clan vs clan battles.

Just look out for torps. 

That is all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 19:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, it's been a year already.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 00:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't feel right comin' back here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 19:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amagi's speed and ability to kite while keeping all guns on target makes very good vs Bismarck. Something to keep in mind for ranked since I imagine Tirpitz/Bismarck will be popular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 17:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *BRING ME ANOTHA* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 13:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's MAD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 11:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome back!

Are there any plans to raise the captain point cap to realistically get 19 points? I have several 18 point captains, and most of them finished their main build with 1 or 2 or 3 left over points that weren't really that useful. I've done theory crafting and have seen that having 19 points would open up new build opportunities that 18 does not.

Thanks for you time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 00:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A highly successful disaster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 00:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give me back Yams. :(((( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that MM isn't rough right now for T5/6, but each team should have the same tiering of ships. Meaning if you're contributing as much as the enemy's low tiers, your chance to win should be 50%. Barring just really unluckily bad teams all night long, if you're losing more games than not you aren't contributing enough. 

Like I said, T5/6 MM is rough right now, but just because you're low tier, doesn't mean you chance to win is any less than the other team. Get some div mates to make it less painful. There's still ways to contribute as lowest tier. Good play goes a long way and most T6s have stuff to bring to th4 table. This is not WoT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 18:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just thinking about how nice it must be to sell digital things that have literally zero cost. 

*busts out wallet* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 18:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people are rather amazed with how nimble I am.. ;,) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 18:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only been a day. I imagine the majority of random pubbies don't even know about the changes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 17:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bow before my agile Hindenberg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 16:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'm starting to understand this weird arousal thing people seem to have for IJN boats...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 16:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my favorite thread ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 19:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 17:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice review, I like how thorough it is and the little segments on how it compares directly with its competition.

Sooooo when is the release? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 15:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will PayPal you $1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 15:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! Thanks for taking your time to answer questions, I have 2!

Firstly, are there any plans to rework captain retraining? As it is, I feel it's the only "unfair" element to the free to play model in the game as with high tier captains, it's completely unrealistic to retrain a captain to a new ship without forking over money. I know WG is a business, but as someone who is willing to spend good money on this game  (I have so many premium ships) it still doesn't feel good.

Speaking of high tier captains, is there a plan to raise the cap on captain points? I have several 18 point captains and I often find myself with like 1 or 2 points left over that go to waste. Raising the cap to19 would open several new build opportunities that I have seen . Since 19 is currently kind of a joke to get to currently. 

Thanks for your time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 15:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would pay real money for this tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 14:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand not wanting smoke to be everywhere, but with radar just being buffed, it seems there are hard counters in place to keep a smoke meta from happening. Not to mention it would help fight vs all the BBs in MM right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 20:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I see are my PayPal receipts... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 19:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing about ranked?

I'm getting feisty for it here... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is WG kill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 15:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Captain XP is gonna be bangin this week with them dragon flags too. Gonna get 15 pointers on my T2s cuz fuck it
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 13:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An actual toaster? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 23:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pretty much only play in divs. T7 sees T8 a lot, but that's not too much of an issue usually. I agree with the title that T6 is shit right now but I don't think any other tier is suffering.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 22:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe not, but all I play these days is T7 and 8 and I get highest tier the majority of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 21:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're exaggerating because MM is set up so that you're guaranteed to be top tier every 4 matches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 07:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Kutuzov is loving all these BBs. So many Witherer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 21:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wooooooo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 17:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never doubted Wargaming. Okay maybe a little bit, but times are hard. It's not personal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 21:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DD armor nerf also is a buff so BB AP won't full pen much anymore though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 18:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure the devs confirmed you could not overpen the citadel.

Edit - it appears I am mistaken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes when I play a certain game a lot, I kinda fall into bad habits that are hard to notice until I just get too frustrated with the game and quit (temporarily). Have a nice break, friend. We'll need you when you get back because this really is an awesome game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 16:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I like the guns. Similar accuracy to most BBS I dind, but the shell speed is solid. I use AP 95% of the time. My hit ratio is like 36% with the ship, so about even with my other German BBs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 16:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play hyper aggressive and just be a badass. I usually run in divs though with other good players. 

Here's a video of me playing Bismarck with a couple div mates if you're interested. Teamwork goes a long way to winning a lot.

https://youtu.be/VAcoWhZKcTI

I pretty much maintain 75% win rates these days just with good Teamwork and teammates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 16:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play a lot, but not nearly that much. It's about 50% time played, 50% money spent. I don't even like playing T10 that much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 14:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And my one solo match was confederate, high caliber, kraken, dreadnought  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fr Deutschland! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 01:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 00:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys enjoying that solo league this season? Must be tons of fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 19:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on what all you need I guess. If you need a mouse keyboard monitor etc, yeah it can run you a little more than a console. And of course the transition will probably hurt a little, but it's an investment. If you're not happy with Sony's product and services then what can you do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 18:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sell all PS4 stuff, sell a kidney if you still need funds. PC isn't as expensive to get into as people think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 18:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to jump on that PC train, my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 21:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should have a realtime weekend event. Play one game a day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MM guarantees your are top tier every 4th match. Unless this has changed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 16:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're thinking into it too much and you're jinxing yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 16:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's just contradicting to your problem then. I'm sensing confirmation bias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 16:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My average damage is better when I play solo because pesky div mates putting in work. But overall winrate is better in a div. Don't know about sinking early, maybe you're just overconfident and overextended. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 16:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell yeah this will help me get that 19th point on my Bismarck captain! 

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 14:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The current state of balance for the IJN DDs leaves a lot to be desired, and this addresses that. I'm all for fixing and balancing current ships before adding more. That being said, German BBs just came out and RN cruisers are literally right around the corner so I don't know what you're complaining about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bismarck in the Mist (Full Game with Div Chat) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 06:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 21:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I bought the print a couple months ago and then I emailed you about if you would make more god of war prints. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 05:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought this print from your website! It's amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 04:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it's not something that plays a big role too often  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 22:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The singing at the end was my fav part </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 02:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks badass. I wonder why there isn't too much hype for it. Maybe people don't see all the intricacies at face value.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 01:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thisismylifenow.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
