<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same thing I've done for the last 18 years. Duh, I mean I'm getting pretty good at this by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's okay to have one STD? Better get my money's worth and go get AIDS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sudafed. One or two and you just have a cold, but if you buy 10 packs then all of a sudden you're a meth dealer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Narcos. Shit got crazy, and real fast. That show, to date, is my favorite show of all time. When seasons 2 came out, I watched the 10 hours of content over a 48 hour period. Only show I've ever come remotely close to doing that with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I'm Tom Shane, and now you have a friend in the diamond business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shrek memes are high! Invest now! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump memes are high! Buy buy buy! However, the market for Anime memes is crashing quickly! Sell sell sell! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edgy memes are on the rise! Buy, buy, buy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 15:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kansan here, can confirm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 15:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A local jewelers' ad used a gaming console as an example of a terrible gift, but here on Reddit, I feel there may be some disagreement with that assessment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically everyone in the Saint Clare's clan in Uncle Tom's Cabin. The symbol of purity, his daughter, Evangeline, dies of tuberculosis, Augustine dies despite being a profound opposer of slavery, and then every slave he owned(and treated very, very, well) gets fucked because now they lose their magnanimous owner and get transferred to his bitch wife. Most of all, Uncle Tom gets totally fucked because Augustine was about to sign his freedom papers, and then he dies and Uncle Tom gets sold to Satan himself and is worked to death. I realize they were all pawns in a fictional didactic novel against slavery, but still, they didn't deserve that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To you, what is the sexiest accent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's like 7 different theories, but I think the KKK should be added as an 8th possibility </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a history in injustice and throughout the late 1800's we inserted ourselves in many countries and made a lot of people suffer because of it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A penis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something that you used to find stupid but now you find amazing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wtf are you talking about that shits crazy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there is a connection that suggest the KKK killed JFK, but no one wants to investigate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was working at a frozen yogurt store, a store that typically parents come in with their young children, and sure enough an all-black biker gang of 30 comes in and gets frozen yogurt. Incredibly nice people, it was a fun time.

EDIT: As I see a mini "Is froyo a shitty version of ice cream?" debate unfold in the comments, I feel obligated to weigh in. We had this debate many times on our shifts, and after getting a free cup of froyo with every shift, we determined yes, it was a shitty version of ice cream. The free cup was still much appreciated though.

EDIT 2: We had some pretty weird people come in sometimes. There was a dude who came in literally every weeknight and then save some froyo and take it out to his dog in his truck, there was someone who walked there, tied up their dog to the front bench, which then jumped on top of the bench, peed on it, and splatter it's piss all over the front window. Lastly, we had some dudes in a Motorsport club come in occasionally, so they'd roll up in two ferraris, a lambo, a viper, and like 3 BMW's, and then all come in dressed like they were college frat boys despite being 50. It was a fun high school job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Holy shit, what's that thing moving off in the distance?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You watch too much porn, young man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I see plenty of 5'5" and 5'6" dudes with like 5'1" females. Their market is just smaller(hah, get it?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> f
r
i
e
n
d

z
o
n
e </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was having a really rough time and I saw her crying one day at lunch, so I reached out to her, talked a little, but it was clear she wasn't interested. Just gave up.

8 months later, I get a text from her asking what my snapchat is, with a smiley face, and we ended up going on a date.

The key, just be a nice person, and don't try to force anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comment is 10/10, but then again, so am I on the hotness scale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Instead of building a wall out of concrete, what is a better material to build the wall out of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what is your worst friendzone story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 07:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 07:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boston
guitar

Say, isn't that a band? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 07:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if you moved back and died, does that mean that *he died a virgin* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 07:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really late to the party, but this one reminds me of my favorite,[Existentialist Firefighter Delays 3 Deaths](https://www.google.com/amp/www.theonion.com/amp/17500)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 07:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you ask a 5 year old girl what she thinks about spankings, and then ask her again in 30 years, I can assure you the answers will be *very* different </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 06:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have so many dollar moneys then will you give me some gold moneys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I wasn't the oldest child like you were, my father has a very similar story. He had a child his junior of high school and had to drop out. He worked 3 jobs, 80 hours a week for his new wife and two(he had another child two years later). He ended up getting divorced, but while that was happening, he got a job at QuikTrip. He quickly worked his way up, was promoted to store manager, worked his way through stores, each one being higher volume than the previous one. He learned rudimentary programming while in the stores, and then got promoted further to corporate, where he met my mother. From there, he moved on to another job as a programmer, moved up to manager at a different job, had me, moved to a different managerial position, and sure enough, now he's a CIO at a middleman insurance firm, all with just a GED. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do I sometimes have difficulty deciphering between real and manufactured memories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And a timeshare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, so you're telling me that you can consciously say that liberal bring their hatred to a certain place and then *in the same comment* make a blatantly xenophobic statement? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy being a guy, and I have no transgender motives, but I definitely would just like to see what it would be like to have nothing dangling between my legs for a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The recovery was relatively slow, and even though we are now officially out of the recession, our GDP growth rate is still only a mediocre 1.9%. Further, many people believe that because the labor participation rate decreased, this caused many to retire early, causing them to essentially be permanently out of the workforce, when they could really still be working today had jobs been saved quicker. While I don't necessarily agree with this last point, I'm just telling it how it is. Another thing, he's a democrat and party lines are drawn so staunchly that no one admits the opposing parties' successes anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That Donald Trump would appear on WWE, make over 200 million dollars from the Celebrity Apprentice, quit the celebrity apprentice, and then run for president months after quitting the apprentice, and proceed to become the president of the United States.

You can't make this shit up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jazz Cartier has officially agreed to take steps toward an AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello Mods of Hip Hop Heads, we have confirmation from Jazz Cartier that he would be down for an AMA. When can we get this set up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah hell yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 24:20 is when the freestyle starts for anyone wondering. Also, this is good enough to where I'm questioning as to whether this is an actual freestyle or he wrote it earlier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. He may well have done one, I just still feel another one would be fun with his album coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No albums, he's dropped 4 or 5 singles since then tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMA REQUEST-VINCE STAPLES </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most absurd part about this is that the first 5 years of Mike Trout's career has translated into the 5th best WAR peak of all-time.  I  realize he is only five years into his career, but if you put him on an average career longevity with ideal health, this man *will* be the greatest player of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As we've seen with the Astros and Twins, it seems as if teams on the rise achieve success before they were expected to.  With that being said, I feel like the Phillies are at that same stage, and with their showing of promise last year, I bet they will outdo expectations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does gravity work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMA REQUEST-JAZZ CARTIER </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, this is why I meant by mainstream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMA REQUEST-MIGOS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They just keep coming! Brutal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does gravity exist? What causes the forces? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 04:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't the first time they've done something like his. I swear the cardinals promotions department is the worst in all of baseball </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simple: pink genitals. No one fucks with bright pink genitals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what about blue crocs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not even 12 hours after the Super Bowl and we're already going meta! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 14:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure this is the plot of an [Ace Hood music video](https://www.youtube.com/shared?ci=v5zqVa8u_5Q)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George made it into the Super Bowl! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many times did you actually think you loved someone before you met your spouse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Germans, Japanese, and any other nationalities with a (relatively) recent history of war atrocities, how are these chapters of history addressed in your societies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 07:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a college freshman, 'taking me back to high school' isn't really a thing, but undoubtedly 'Magic' by B.o.b. And then any song by Taio Cruz, Akon, or Jay Sean are the songs that take me back to middle school. Those guys were the shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 00:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok Mr. Madison Bumgarner singlehandedly wins me the World Series every other year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I mean, they love each other so much that they both times their medical emergencies right so they went to the hospital together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk if I'm the only one to think this, but I totally expected him to spurn Michelle and go over and give a big fat kiss to Joe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parents of Reddit, what's the most embarrassing moment for your children spurring from something that you did? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snap. I've never been able to figure it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cum quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alternatively, in states with a consent age: When is her 16th birthday? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Morticians. People will keep dyin', man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EL BJ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was gold detecting on Oak Island, and I got a pretty strong hit. It ended up being a foot down, and there was the holy grail, the ark of the covenant, and Shakespeare's original manuscripts! I figured someone hid them here in purpose, so I reburied them, and now it's fun to watch the idiots on history channel dig 180 feet down for something that's a foot below then surface. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it really ironic how this post has a ton of upvotes, but none of these answers have very many upvotes because no one has heard of any of these songs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This means if you took off 16 months straight, you could essentially start a 'baby farm,' getting paid full salary to have a baby every 15 months, and let's say get paid for a good 10 years to have 8 children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also go see [3005](https://www.youtube.com/shared?ci=6AV4uouy4nA) , [The Worst Guys](https://www.youtube.com/shared?ci=cxmPwpDl3So) , and [Sober](https://www.youtube.com/shared?ci=h2_oTTKDmpg) , all of some of his earlier stuff. It's completely different than his new stuff, he's actually a rather upbeat rapper in all of these songs with great rhythm and great music production. Also, if you're looking to test the speakers on your car, Go check out [Zealots of Stockholm.](https://www.youtube.com/shared?ci=HJI-fKJ2Isc). Another very quality song not many know about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Jazz](https://www.youtube.com/shared?ci=ARoBjwcDEOo) -Mick Jenkins

Very good, even if you don't like rap/hip-hop, it's very mellow so I think you'll like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! 6.5/7!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely thought this was some photo explaining the birds and the bees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ya but as soon as she told me I was outta there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so you wish my parents tried to abort me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow you went out of the way for that one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got 5/7. Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judging by his name BigIndianJoe, probably just be Indian. American Indians' treatment by the government here in the states is rather suboptimal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 22:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just pro-me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it will. Everyone's does. Duh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd win, and trust me, the fight would probably go something like [this](https://www.youtube.com/shared?ci=56EswfP7xUE)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the single stupidest thing you have ever seen anyone do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do have nice buttocks tho if you were wondering </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shit u right  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife was brutally murdered in front of me during our wedding ceremony.

I was the product of an aborted abortion.

I have gonorrhea and I came in my eye, so now I have perennial pink eye.

EDIT: I frankly thought the majority of these answers on this post were fairly boring so I'm glad I brought an element of suspense to this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Swaziland? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm only going to use two words:

Flat, farms.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beluga whales. Shits crazy dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 7 questions:

1. What is the best way to launch a 90 kg projectile over 300 meters?

2. Do you know what a potato is?

3. Who is the dumbest person you can possibly think of?

4. What's in the safe?

5. If someone says "Thank you kind stranger," what just happened?

6. What is the best food to serve over rice?

7.  If you're talking dirty to your partner, what is the one thing you can say that will totally turn them on?

If you get 5/7 questions right, congratulations, you did very good and you are now a citizen of Reddit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About half of the world likes dongs.

A lot do people like danishes.

Most people support renewable energy.

This is a good deal. 5/7.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello, I could tell you something cool about myself, but my life will inevitably end with a dark, painful, lonely death just like yours will. AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 12:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, fuck Australia, amirite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to my local Chinese places and it's by far my favorite restaurant, and found about a 2 inch long, 1/8th inch wide metal shaving in my food. Needless to say, it was my favorite restaurant, so I didn't say anything about it and I've been back countless times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *New research shows that there is a more efficient way than previously thought to launch a 90 kg projectile 300 meters* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truly next level thinking would be displaying that he coast is clear just to have a car coming so you can reprieve the world of one less asshole who has tailed your ass for the last mile and a half. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After seeing multiple posts about related topics, is anyone else wondering why Turks are so nice to stray dogs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hey girl, you ever tried ass play?"

"Well, this one time..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to see a gif of a ball hitting stuff, you should've seen me and your mum last night </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That bloody asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you explain the tall people who looks like midgets? Are there tall midgets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who else do you think submitted this question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So for you, all the way in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Germans complained that poisoning wells was a war crime

Yes, because they were so concerned with fighting that war the right way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your freezer isn't working if they're rotting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, how long does it usually take you to lose interest in someone you had a crush on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true, in high school I thought there was a girl that liked me who laughed at everything I said, and occasionally I'd throw a test ballon out there that just wasn't funny, but I'd act like it should be, and sure enough she'd be laughing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he was using Crest Whitening Toothpaste, then he was bleaching his asshole, cleaning his asshole, and pleasuring himself all at the same time. Efficient! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if it makes him feel better you should tell him about the thousands of karma you're receiving off of this experience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, to say this would vastly oversimplify evolution. Instead the ancestors of the charmin bears, *ursus lessismoreidae*, were the ones that wiped their asses on the trees, eventually causing those tree to turn brown. However, this process is due to continue, thus turning trees black eventually. While seemingly harmless, this presents a major problem to humanity, as these new black trees will be able to absorb all sunlight, thus making these new trees very, very powerful. Please contact your local congressperson to let them know about this concerning ecological phenomenon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> False, it is actually rather easy to create a square jerk, as most likely all those in the square will have equal length arms. With equal length arms, they will be equally spaced from each other. However, under the circumstance that one person has longer arms than the rest, we are dealing with a "kite-jerk" and if two people have longer arms than the other two, then we are dealing with a "trapezoid-jerk." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because identical twins are the same sex, the twins that procreate must be fraternal. Because they are fraternal, the baby will probably come out of the womb with a polo shirt, nice khaki's, and some boat shoes, just like any frat lord would. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a thought, but how about we humans try this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, so where are the dogs supposed to shit then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That dress is overrated! Sad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article is based on fact, but there's still a lot of assumption in it. There are a few pretty broad jumps in logic, so I would necessarily say there is a "strong" chance by any means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, jokes on Bernie. His names Steve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
