<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2013</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did Spoony do something?  His twitter looks pretty anti-Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you telling me that not only does the electoral process of the USA determine who the brightest person is, but that is also takes into account the fact that we use the Electoral College rather than popular vote? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spracism.  Truly our galaxy's greatest issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, looks like they're discussing McDonalds and JonTron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing "used engagement rings" don't sell very well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not an athlete, but before the Polgar sisters were even born, their father claimed that with the right education, he could turn any healthy child into a genius.  https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/L%C3%A1szl%C3%B3_Polg%C3%A1r#Education_and_career  He and his wife chose chess to train their kids in, and their three daughters all became top chess players.  It could be natural talent, but two of the sisters became the top two female chess players, so that's a mighty big coincidence.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to disregard anything you're saying, but are there any "Healthcare towns" out there?  I think one reason why stuff like coal and steel are so devastating when they go out of business is that they were usually the town's company and employed a lot of the people.  But in my experience, health insurance companies have their big offices in big cities or just outside them.  I don't think you'd have any poor areas created, even though you would see an overall loss of jobs, just because they'd be in areas able to better absorb the impact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the EPA complained about being forced to spend hundreds of millions of dollars on stuff they don't need, I would feel that it does.  http://www.military.com/daily-news/2015/01/28/pentagon-tells-congress-to-stop-buying-equipment-it-doesnt-need.html   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Master was at least able to run something successfully.  I'm pretty sure any significant Mad Max character would make a better leader than Trump.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know how Orthodox Jews have those little wires that trick God into thinking they're still in their house so they can do whatever they want on the Sabbath?  Can we get something like that so the GOP thinks we're all still in the womb so they'll give a shit about us? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One explanation I've read is that the goal is to be so overwhelming, no one else even bothers to try to build up their military to compete, which helps maintain peace in the long-term, but like, we're past that point.  We can reduce a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yzma 2020 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you're party platform becomes "Piss off liberals because fuck liberals," it's hard for something not to become partisan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd think Trump would be more supportive of Jupiter, since they both have the same attitude towards women and consent and all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2010 is when they visit Europa, though.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why leave Earth if things are good here?  Do you quit a job you enjoy?  Trump will make the planet *so* awful, people will be launching themselves from trebuchets if it means leaving it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make X-COM mandatory in schools until America understands probability! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's X-COM, baby! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rio Grande valley is actually pretty reliably blue.  http://www.politico.com/2016-election/results/map/president/texas/  I *wish* it were only Trump voters affected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted something to go with Barack, and the only bad guy I could think of was Hannibal Barca. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, in his will he gave away all his money to the common people of Rome.  That's gotta count for something.  I'm pretty sure Trump's will says all of his money has to be buried with him in a golden pyramid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Millions go hungry in America?  I just ate a sandwich!  What nonsense!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And I *really* didn't like the way Barack Hussein Obama brought elephants over the Alps, ruled Iraq as a dictator, and then flew planes into the World Trade Center." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I guess it depends on what sort of life actions you think are meaningful.  Personally, I feel like the late Republic was already corrupt and broken.  Caesar certainly wasn't altruistic, (he once observed he'd rather be the first man in a small, Alpine village than the second man in Rome) but I think if he hadn't destroyed the Republic, it just would have been someone else.  There was no going back to the days of Camillus and such.  

Machiavelli observed that sometimes trying to be nice causes more harm than being cruel.  Caesar's wars killed millions.  But afterwards, Gaul was part of the Roman Empire.  Do we know how many Gauls died in petty squabbles before Caesar, or what happened to quality of life?  If there had been no Roman Civil War, how many would have died in riots and uprisings?  It's hard to say.  

I also think it's possible to be great without being good.  But even then, Caesar died because he was too merciful and pardoned too many Romans.  Caesar was perfectly willing to pardon the leaders of the war against him.  Would Pompey have been so merciful had he won?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Misleading as fuck URL, there, geez.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like oatmeal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I would like to dictate how you live your life."

"No."

"Help!  Help!  I'm being persecuted!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cotton Mather called Rhode Island, "a colluvies [a cesspool] of Antonomians, Familists, Anabaptists, Anti-sabbatarians, Arminians, Socinians, Quakers, Ranters, every thing in the world but Roman Catholicks and *real* Christians." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep.  If you want the guy who *actually* wanted religious freedom, you want Roger Williams.  https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Roger_Williams </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not just have a suggestion box outside the police station? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, I forgot about how much he hated his wife.  I read that one time he came back from a campaign and his first words to her were "Madam has grown fatter." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, try not to make any phone calls on your way through the parking lot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree!  Why does Disney have to have all these movies with sexual preferences, like heterosexuality?  All these men and women falling in love all the time.  I hate it!  All kids movies should have friendships only! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, what do you dislike about Frederick the Great?  I still like him but I'm open to being disappointed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When, in honour of his defeat of the Sabines, the Senate offered Manius Curius a larger amount of ground than the discharged troops were receiving, he was content with the allotment of ordinary soldiers, declaring that that man was a bad citizen who was not satisfied with what the rest received.

-Frontinus: The Strategemata </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you find out about someone famous that made you no longer like them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what sort of argument you're trying to make.  That sounds like a good thing that Clinton finds it easy to be transparent and accountable.  Shouldn't we be concerned that Trump finds it so difficult to reach others' standards?  This is the presidency.  You're not supposed to be graded on a curve that was made just for you because you couldn't do well enough to pass otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you buy the spicy mayo that goes on sushi? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 00:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if so, does anyone have recommendations?  I love that stuff but I never see anything at the grocery store that looks like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, you just *know* that once she gits that deductible she's gonna be in the hospital every day, taking advantage of all that free medical care for giggles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask him to throw a ball up while in the back seat of a car going 60 mph and prove to him that movement is impossible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before, they at least saved some seed grain for next year's harvest.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should post this to /r/chess.  You'll probably get more detailed answers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just so you know, there's a demo on Steam that has the entire first mission and part of the second, if you want to try it out.  It's personally one of my favorites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hook up the gun to a random number generator.  Then it's not murder, just God's will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50 years of full civil rights? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you've got a source that says 73% or less of media time spent discussing missing women focuses on white women, you don't really have a point either.  Or you could read this study: http://www.academia.edu/857391/Missing_Children_in_National_News_Coverage_Racial_and_Gender_Representations_of_Missing_Children_Cases  It found that black children were 33.2% of missing children, yet only 19.5% of missing children cases covered in the news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your hobby is killing foreigners and your country enters a world war, that's gotta be like Christmas for you.  "You mean you'll *pay* me to do this?!  Hot dog!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it is the fastest selling Nintendo console: http://www.gamespot.com/articles/nintendo-switch-is-nintendos-fastest-selling-conso/1100-6448486/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 1971...  I'd rather have a judge tell me I can vote than wait 50 years for a vote to let me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, homeless people have to exist somewhere.  I wouldn't consider the law to be a good ideal.  If they were so concerned about it maybe they should have tried to actually help the homeless rather than trying to make their existence illegal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hint: racists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd probably help if you took a screenshot of an island you've been playing for a bit.  Income will always be your lifeblood, though.  In Tropico 4, I'd start with some cash crops in good soil and lumber mills if you've got good soil.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they should do it like that Blind Date TV show and have little thought bubbles and captions the entire interview. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Footage of OP: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R15LkyO8gq8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't name most of them... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 21:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am C-3PO, human-cyborg relations, and I myself will carry you to the gates of Valhalla. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess would be that symmetry is a large part of being generally attractive, and when you average everyone out, you tend to get more symmetry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something something broken paws </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't it be great if only people who voted for Republicans had to live with Republican policies?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that called Yeshuism.  Basically, accepted Jesus's (Yeshua's) teachings but not his divinity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worth adding that it's an amazing sub that /u/LockeProposal is primarily responsible for and frequently posts to.  Don't let him be modest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sega wouldn't have given them the money to add in Chaos at all (gotta pay developers) unless they did it as additional DLC, so it's not like the choices were free Chaos or paid Chaos.  It was paid Chaos or nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qkwFa1E4t_c  Where Did We Go Right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally, schools charge tuition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless, of course, you're pre-destined to live in a little bubble for the rest of your life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if the common folk are racist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See: the metric system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hm, my Scrooge McDuck money pool is overflowing.  Guess I need to give the extra to the poor now..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geez, just take a break from jacking off.  No need to do a marathon.  You need your strength. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which huge problems, and how is it worse than pre-ACA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you took advantage of all that free, hot air to get rid of the need for a heating system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is now banned from /r/conservative, as is tradition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.aclu.org/news/aclu-tells-high-school-allow-students-protest-aclu-football-game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, so long as it was done before quickening, that is, when you could feel the baby moving, abortion was legal at the time the Bill of Rights was ratified. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you want to encourage avoiding healthcare?  What do you mean by unnecessary care?  If someone's sick, I don't want them to not see a doctor because of money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if you started with a barium swallow to make it white, and then started on the dye? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh my god that's so much better than I had any idea of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Spartans have a *lot* of great sayings: http://penelope.uchicago.edu/Thayer/e/roman/texts/plutarch/moralia/sayings_of_spartans*/main.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't he say that he didn't make Gordon cry, Gordon *chose* to cry?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't that make it better suited for /r/news or /r/worldnews, then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We once had a customer physically mail us screenshots of a call center agent's Facebook because she didn't like the content, and wanted us to know about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turns out Two-Face is in charge of the CIA.  "Should I hack the DNC?   Tails!  Damnit!  What about the RNC?  Heads?!  Oh, come on!  This sucks!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why she had to play sick, so he couldn't eat too much before the threesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caligula's uncle, actually.  He became the emperor Claudius. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> balanced a national budget for the only time ever

Didn't Andrew Jackson get rid of the national debt and Bill Clinton achieve a surplus?  Or is Nixon's accomplishment somehow different from theirs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't remember the source, but a description I liked was that Ben Carson is what happens when God makes an RPG character and puts every single point into brain surgery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The right people will get it."-MST3K </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd take Lord Humongous over Trump.  He was perfectly willing to let the people with the oil just walk away.  Trump would probably bomb their families. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then left another country to preserve slavery, too.  Leaving two different countries to keep slavery is a record, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His comment seemed off, so I did research.  Lots of Trump support for a liberal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   When he did show up to class he always had on a wrinkled Homer Simpson shirt on. 

I think that was just an Abe Simpson shirt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really disliked how the advertising was misleading.  All this stuff about how we built monsters to fight monsters.  I kept waiting for the horrible dark secret about the Jaegers, about how we had sacrificed some part of our humanity for the sake of clutching to life just a bit longer...

And then fucking nothing.  They're just big mechsuits.  That's it.  Nothing special.  Not monsters.  https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/cb/79/cf/cb79cf8137ca714b2533592cc61f5239.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally thought it was a pretty good Metal Gear Solid 2 film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try, Grease Monkey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The story I heard was that the French tried to do it and instead created a gun that shot into the propeller.  The plane crashed, Fokker found it, realized what they were *trying* to do, and made it correctly for the Germans.  https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anthony_Fokker#The_interrupter_gear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you don't go through the entire case and lose it.  If Trump had leaked memos of what the executive order might contain, and then had brought out this EO, then yeah, maybe, but he went through the entire process when it wasn't necessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it would have swung two states to Clinton.  Pennsylvania wouldn't have switched, which was the third one needed, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "He just showed up and volunteered to make floppy penises for us.  We didn't even tell him we made video games!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume Donald Trump's vision is like the Ice King with his wizard eyes, only he's constantly seeing Muslims and Mexicans everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is someone famous that you think does have thin skin, and how do they show it?  I'd like a comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why even ask these questions?  You're acting like we're talking about a novel or a TV show and someone called your favorite character unrealistic.  It doesn't have to be *plausible* that someone can become president and have thin skin.  We can look at his tweets that every day prove he has thin skin based on how easily and quickly he lashes out at everyone and everything that goes against him.  We can look at news stories about him.  We can listen to his own speeches.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In what ways are you a liberal, out of curiosity?  Because looking at your history, I really doubt you are, and I think you're just saying you're a liberal to make your position seem more reasonable.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's idiotic in this situation, though.  He's not negotiating with anyone.  His last order was blocked by a judge.  You don't bring a murder case against someone just so you can lose and then bring your real larceny case against them.  It may be his business strategy, but it's a stupid executive order strategy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only that, but he didn't even do *that* much!  He won and *still* questioned the results of the election, saying there were millions of illegal votes.  Can you imagine setting such a low bar for yourself and then still failing?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See also: walking over hot coals, and putting out candle wicks with your fingers.  Go fast enough and the heat doesn't transfer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The source of that Kennedy quote is an anonymous source in a NY Times article: https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4tjcz7/did_jfk_actually_say_he_wanted_to_shatter_the_cia/  Out of curiosity, do you trust anonymous newspaper sources without any other evidence? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Of Orcs and Men and/or Project Highrise?

https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/5wt2cv/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_vvvvvv/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 15:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Project Highrise?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/5wt2cv/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_vvvvvv/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 05:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Project Highrise?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/5wt2cv/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_vvvvvv/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure if soldiers fired on a crowd, regardless of which side was at fault, and killed five people it would be a big deal even today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlike those fucking june people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have medicated me with some Euphoria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's just say I'm no longer alive ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love them, but then again, I love /r/iamverysmart, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So your claim is that it would be impossible for me to find something that is untrue, yet a large number of Republicans believe while very few Democrats believe, or vice-versa.  Is that correct? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...because McConnell told him he would call out the Democrats for "partisan politics?"     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/obama-orders-review-of-russian-hacking-during-presidential-campaign/2016/12/09/31d6b300-be2a-11e6-94ac-3d324840106c_story.html?utm_term=.697f0308690f

According to several officials, McConnell raised doubts about the underlying intelligence and made clear to the administration that he would consider any effort by the White House to challenge the Russians publicly an act of partisan politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mitch McConnell told Obama that if he made public Russia's interference before the election he'd treat it as a partisan attack, that's why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sources for those claims? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Project Highrise?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/5wt2cv/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_vvvvvv/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just out of curiosity, what are the worst things that Trump has done so far in your opinion, and do you think Clinton would have done them, too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but then what do you do?  Democrats aren't gonna vote for you if they've got a real Democrat to vote for, Republicans are gonna primary you, and they're not gonna work with you after you retired because you just tried to screw them over.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's the day we changed the name of the subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Anyways, that's what this turkey reminded me of, Sarah.  You always burn it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] [H] Freedom Bundle Leftovers, including VVVVVV, Guacamelee, World of Goo, and others [W] Paypal/Offers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [My IGS Rep page](https://www.reddit.com/r/IGSRep/comments/5wjj8v/saintodhrans_igs_rep_page/)

All games I have are Humble Gift links.  Just trying to get something for these, so make an offer.

**Games I Have**

[A Virus Named Tom](http://store.steampowered.com/app/207650/)

[Ballistick](http://store.steampowered.com/app/518620/)

[Beat Hazard Ultra](http://store.steampowered.com/app/49604/)
[Chroma Squad](http://store.steampowered.com/app/251130/)

[Dangerous High School Girls in Trouble](http://store.steampowered.com/app/27400/)

[Day of the Tentacle](http://store.steampowered.com/app/388210/)

[Double Fine Adventure Documentary](http://store.steampowered.com/app/402590/)

[Dusty Revenge%3A Co-Op Edition](http://store.steampowered.com/app/252430/)

[Ellipsis](http://store.steampowered.com/app/514620/)

[Girls Like Robots](http://store.steampowered.com/app/263460/)

[GRAV](http://store.steampowered.com/app/408340/)

[Guacamelee Gold Edition](http://store.steampowered.com/app/214770/)

[Guns of Icarus Online](http://store.steampowered.com/app/209080/)

[Hot Tin Roof%3A The Cat That Wore A Fedora Deluxe](http://store.steampowered.com/app/253390/)

[Human Resource Machine](http://store.steampowered.com/app/375820/)

[JumpJet Rex](http://store.steampowered.com/app/329460/)

[Luna%27s Wandering Stars](http://store.steampowered.com/app/330660/)

[Monster Loves You](http://store.steampowered.com/app/226740/)

[Mushroom 11](http://store.steampowered.com/app/243160/)

[Ninja Pizza Girl](http://store.steampowered.com/app/319470/)

[No Time to Explain](http://store.steampowered.com/app/368730/)

[Octodad%3A Deadliest Catch](http://store.steampowered.com/app/224480/)

[Potatoman Seeks the Troof](http://store.steampowered.com/app/328500/)

[QUBE%3A Director%27s Cut](http://store.steampowered.com/app/239430/)

[Retro Game Crunch](http://store.steampowered.com/app/290040/)

[Rituals](http://store.steampowered.com/app/359190/)

[Robot Roller-Derby Disco Dodgeball](http://store.steampowered.com/app/270450/)

[Rocketbirds%3A Hardboiled Chicken](http://store.steampowered.com/app/215510/)

[ROCKETSROCKETSROCKETS](http://store.steampowered.com/app/289760/)

[shutshimi](http://store.steampowered.com/app/332530/)

[Spirits](http://store.steampowered.com/app/402620/)

[Streamline](http://store.steampowered.com/app/252850/)

[Superbrothers%3A Sword %26 Sworcery EP](http://store.steampowered.com/app/204060/)

[Super Galaxy Squadron EX](http://store.steampowered.com/app/345860/)

[Super Hexagon](http://store.steampowered.com/app/221640/)

[Super Meat Boy](http://store.steampowered.com/app/40800/)

[Superbrothers%3A Sword and Sworcery](http://store.steampowered.com/app/204060/)

[System Shock Pack](http://store.steampowered.com/sub/82345/)

[Team Indie](http://store.steampowered.com/app/302850/)

[Thirty Flights of Loving](http://store.steampowered.com/app/214700/)

[TIMEframe](http://store.steampowered.com/app/340270/)

[Tower of Guns](http://store.steampowered.com/app/266110/)

[VVVVVV](http://store.steampowered.com/app/70300/)

[World of Goo](http://store.steampowered.com/app/22000/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Project Highrise or Caesar in Gaul DLC?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/5wt2cv/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_vvvvvv/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Project Highrise?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/5wt2cv/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_vvvvvv/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Project Highrise?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/5wt2cv/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_vvvvvv/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  Thanks, anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have several fetishes based on what AOL's filter did and didn't block. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Project Highrise?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/5wt2cv/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_vvvvvv/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you consider substantial evidence, and if you did believe it, what would you consider an appropriate punishment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that's called a Japanese office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I tell *everyone* I got gang banged.  Totally normal.  You guys are the weird ones." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought you could just provide electric stimulation to the prostate to get a sample? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yours is entirely pointless.  You spend your time criticizing illegal immigration.  Are you against Sessions's perjury that's recently been uncovered?  Do you think he should be punished? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Planetary Annihiliation: Titans?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/5wt2cv/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_vvvvvv/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Portal 2 and Project Highrise?

https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/5wt2cv/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_vvvvvv/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone knows family dinners are important for bonding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but James Clapper!  Stop talking about Sessions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that one issue Democrats have with messaging is that when people are told what the actual Republican plan is, they assume it's hyperbole because they don't believe they could be serious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traded Sproggiwood and Nuclear Throne for Elegy of a Dead World and Neon Chrome with /u/Nooghri </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confirmed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep!  I'll message you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What the-?!  Are they *not* cursing fig trees down there?  Jesus!  Go fix their shit right now!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Neon Chrome?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/5wt2cv/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_vvvvvv/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your thoughts on ILLEGAL perjury? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elegy for a Dead World?  I am also interested in Neon Chrome if I have any other games you want, but I want Elegy more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 06:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything here for Neon Chrome and/or Project Highrise?  https://www.reddit.com/r/indiegameswap/comments/5wt2cv/h_freedom_bundle_leftovers_including_vvvvvv/  I don't mind trading multiples, either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
