<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3428</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Just Master Race Things"-Geralt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 09:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 08:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it seems to much like unnecessary fan-service.  There is always a very contrived reason to bring on Oliver in the crossover, and it doesn't seem like this episode has anything to do with the main stories of any of the shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't access my PowerUpRewards. It says "Sorry, we couldn't validate your information. Please try again." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 23:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I went into trade in a game I was able to get points on my account, but when I went in two days later they said that account didn't exist.


PS: I hadn't linked it with my Gamestop account yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take that EA, Todd Howard, Bethesda, Ubisoft, etc... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 11:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 12:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is practically on death's door. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "My CircleJerk has never been stronger"-r/gaming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 11:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking to get an External Hard Drive on black friday(4tb), and need to know which one to get. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 03:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Resistance 3 buying questions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 09:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently Gamestop raised the price of Resistance 3 from $3 to $10 and I was wondering what you guys think I should do?  My local pawn shop has really good deals on games, but I haven't seen a copy of Resistance 3 there for over a year.  I was wondering if I should just spring for it on ebay, buy the collection(brother has 1 and 2 but I may want to have my own copy), buy it from gamestop when they have buy 2 get 1 free, or wait for my pawn shop to get it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 21:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya, I am from the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 12:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three words....Gaara...vs....Toph

That battle made me the saltiest man alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know if Gears of War 3 ever goes on sale? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 11:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have every gears game besides 3 and I can't seem to find it anywhere for a reasonable price(missed one at my pawn shop so I am pretty salty).  Do you guys know how much it normally goes for on sale, and how often? Thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 09:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same, I was playing mass effect and then the next day I couldn't update my dishonored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 09:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man I have had to do the exact same thing when my games update.  I also checked my brothers xbox and his is having the same problem, so it must be server side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Persona games are on sale and I was wondering if I should get Persona 3 and 4 or wait for a possible portable version sale next week(3 for psp and 4 for Vita)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reason I ask, is that I don't know if the portable ones usually go on sale, or how much they will be.  I am also kind of limited on space on my memory card for psp and vita. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 12:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering why the price would be so high if it didn't include the dlc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having slow down, freezing, load noises, and updating problems on 360. Should I buy a new one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 12:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 360 has gotten loader over the past weekend, with some other problems.  I don't know if the update problems are because of my Xbox or Xbox live(others on this sub were posting about the same issue),but it has been running slower(15 seconds to go to game details, when it would normally have taken less than 3) and freezing(when I click back during a loading screen on the dashboard it will freeze for 14 second).  I have tried removing my hard drive to see if that was the problem, but it still freezes up when just using my 4gb internal.  I was wondering if I should get a new Xbox 360? 

TLDR:  Xbox is running slow(not sure why) and I want to know if I should get a new one for $50-80. PS: I need a new controller as well and that would be included in the 360 I am looking to buy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know if this comes with the DLC when bought used? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 11:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 20:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I eventually solved by just trying again and again, probably something to do with xbox live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 10:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the same problem, and microsoft support said it might be my hard drive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dishonored won't update. 360 also running slowly. Anyone else have this problem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 08:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first my 360 was loading really slowly on any page I tried to go to, and when I tried to back out it would freeze for a few seconds.  After clearing the cache, deleting 50 gb worth of games, and re downloading my profile, Dishonored wouldn't update, but instead give me the error message "445E 0000 D080 0200 8007 2741".  After unplugging my hard drive, re plugging it in, and clearing my cache 5 times, it doesn't show a download bar when it has to update.  It just gives me the spinning circle loading screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kind of stand would you guys recommend for the Ps3 slim? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 00:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the nyko brand any good, or should I try to find an official one?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 21:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It didn't run that great on 360, but it ran worse on One when backwards compatibility was first launched, but had better loading times, at least according to Digital Foundry. I am only asking because I know some games got patched to make it play like the 360 version, but have the faster loading times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that they smoothed out some of the FPS drop problems on some of the Gears of War games and Halo reach, but I didn't know if they ever patched Mass Effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Their video](https://youtu.be/_5VYl0pKbDU?t=445) shows it performing worse on the One. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have both a 360 and an Xbox One, but I don't know which version is worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Digital Foundry's video](https://youtu.be/_5VYl0pKbDU?t=445) shows lower fps, but better load times and no screen tearing.  I am more concerned with fps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only asked because back in 2015 Digital Foundry said it ran worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, but according to Digital Foundry's tests it was under performing on Xbox One compared to 360.  I just wanted to know if it plays as well as it did on 360. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How well do the Mass Effect games play on Xbox One? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has the game been optimized from when it was first made backwards compatible, and how well do the other Mass Effects play?

Ps: I haven't played through the games, so no spoilers please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How well does Mass Effect currently run on Xbox One? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has the game been optimized from when it was first made backwards compatible, and how well do the other Mass Effects play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 22:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me to thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 22:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me to thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 02:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I paid $100 for the vita, and I don't know if I should drop another $100 to get a 64gb memory card? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you buy physical or digital games, and if you buy digitally what size is your memory card? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 18:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering if it would be better to purchase game physically or digitally, because some games have better prices digitally, but have a big download size.  I only have an 8gb card, but I can transfer it to my ps3 for storage. Would it be better to just upgrade my card size? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about Gears of War 3 and Gears of War 2 backwards compatibility performance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 03:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How well does Gears of War 3 and 2 play on Xbox one, because according to the Digital Foundry video there are performance issues on Gears 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 23:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also is the mod playing emulators or from the actual game disc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 23:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never modded the Xbox before, so this might be tricky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any games known to have problems with the 1.6? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 06:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have already run into trouble with Mortal Kombat Armageddon and Fable.  Are there any other games I should know about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 08:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know if you can use the 16% coupon and the 25 free shipping coupon in the same order? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 07:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got an original xbox with a 3rd party controller from craigslist and I need an official one, so if what you say is true then I will get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
