<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3313</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-21 19:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is CRAZY you posted this, because her nutritionist wants to get her eating 2500 calories a day. i mean, how is she supposed to take our word over a "professional"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, one of my friends has been diagnosed with anorexia. I need your advice on how I can help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-21 18:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little background story: This is an old coworker of mine, and for as long as I've known her, she's always been petite (I'm a size 4 and she's smaller than I am), but toned and a little curvy. 


When I saw her for the first time in 6+ months, she is just skin and bones; blamed it on working out too much. Apparently, her heart rate is down to 40 beats per minute when she's awake. Her mom has arranged for her to see a therapist and a nutritionist, but apparently, she's not cooperating so much mentally.


All of her friends won't talk to her or hang out with her because of this, and she told a mutual friend of ours about it, asking her to help her get better. She doesn't know I know, so I can't really get further information, but our friend is stressing out big time about helping her. Obviously, to us the solution seems simple, but I know our thought processes are so different from hers right now. What can we do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-20 23:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so, my dad only has one eye due to some accident with another kid and a stick when he was little (i never felt comfortable asking for details). he has a fake eye now, and someone probably already asked this, but why will you have to wear an eyepatch? is it due to the infection (which i believe my dad didn't have, since it was removed right away)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-18 02:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that looks awkwardly like my psy395 professor... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 05:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> his excuse was lack of opposable thumbs. can't believe i fell for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
