<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3269</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 15:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man thx so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Broke my elbow riding freelines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 16:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone,

So I've had my skates for about 6 months and I'm pretty good at them.  I can get pretty much anywhere I want even up some hills.  Anyways,  I was riding them and I attempted to go over an area with about an inch and a half drop.  I go over it, the skates come out from under me, I put my arm out to brace myself and I ended up fracturing my elbow.  I really like the skates but I'm gonna take a break for now.  Anyone else have any injuries from them?  Honestly I think they're pretty safe as long as you don't try anything stupid.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 06:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My roommate always played world of Warcraft and other video games while voice chatting with his friends.   I can still hear his mechanical keyboard clacking away into the night while I was trying to sleep... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 22:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost as great as the revered AALewis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 21:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These type of guys don't know how to be single.  You have to have more to yourself than being in a relationship  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 18:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I respect and pedstalize women?"  What?!  Why would you say something like that. It's weird and creepy.  All these guy say how they're nice but they're actually not.  Just act normal and stop talking about how nice you are and you'll be fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This bathroom stall door </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 20:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 06:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DOOT DOOT MR SKELTAL NEEDS HIS CALCIUM but there is NO CALCIUM IN THE EU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 03:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1152010 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Self-filling water bottle busted! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 05:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do we have fingernails? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 02:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 04:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 01:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a freshman studying computer science right now.  Hopefully I get to learn about all of that stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 09:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> College swimmer here.  100% true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 17:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you not swimming 2 hours a day for 5-6 days a week?   I feel like that would help you more than lifting at this point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 12:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scanner input = new Scanner(new File(paper)); </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] [book] A children's book where there is a big spaceship and people come back to look at the earth and it is all polluted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 18:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember reading this book a long time ago.  It was a children's picture book and there were all these people that left earth and came back way later to find that it had been polluted badly.  They came in big spaceships and there were thousands of people i think.  There were around like 20 rocket spaceship looking things.  Thanks for helping! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 03:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look up "The Paper Trip" if you wanna actually disappear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 07:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a freshman in college, and one thing I learned is that while I used to equate those scores with intelligence, they don't mean anything to me anymore.  Sure, they help with admissions, but after that no one cares nor does it matter.  College is a different world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
