<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3183</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I dont think that's so bad. Very well could be a thing where he's from or some shit. It's also pretty common for people, as a species, to not respect or keep nature in mind. 
   
That's where I'd fault him. Not recognizing the tide.  
  
That might be too horrible a death to award anything for though. Some shit out of a horror movie. Pinned until the tide drowned him. 
   
I'm sure he didn't have much time but imagine if he had a hope of digging himself out too?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading this makes me think of all the shit people will find in 100 years, or won't depending on how much water rises. 
   
But I shit you not I left my cell phone out fishing once, tide came in like a good 60 feet, next day retrieved it. Dried it out. It worked for a few weeks till  I grabbed a new one knowing it's days were numbered w/ the salt. 
   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all know the only part of Ct that matters is the SW part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i bet the first one or two you guys probably picked up like does it still blow up? yeah probably, let's call the cops... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sometimes, the internet surprises you... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 07:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, These groups do trade oil. Smuggled sometimes, sometimes straight to refineries. For embargoes to work you need to actually enforce them. 
   
If you don't think people in Iraq and Iran aren't taking advantage of the cheaper oil yall are crazy.  
   
And as long as it's delivered I don't think anyone really cares where it's coming from. After it's refined, in country, it's not hard to ship papers with it next to a batch of Iraqi oil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 07:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> edit: nevermind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How far would you be able to see from the top of the Empire State building on a clear day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this actually helped me kind of get that whole light speed travel a bit better. i feel like people casually throw it out there like time dilation and it kind of blows my mind everytime i hear it.   
   
edit: how long does it take a neutrino to get here? lol i'm almost nervous to google shit like that. it's 1:21...cut to 4am.
   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man this post applies to me. Breeders ehhh. #AntiBreeder4Lyfe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> making it rain on those babies.  
  
i got you for like 15k bro. white, good genes, smart. blue eyes. 15k mister. no mommy, no daddy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm not entirely sure to be honest but you can find em i think in common store like home depot or lowes and they're pretty good. 
   
honestly, and this one doesn't look like it has options but i imagine the settings come more from increasing the water flow maybe? If that's even reasonable way to do it.  
  
But the dribble out 'rain' like that real rain that's in the advertisements and pictures like this isn't that good. Mostly because unlike real rain it's only falling from one spot over your head like a comic book and not really enough. 
   
The one I like is more of a kind of slightly firmer rain feeling. So it's a mix between what is sort of 'normal shower' with 'normal rain' rather than like afternoon sun shower sprinkles or a dribbling brook/stream.   
  
edit: And by better I mean it actually feels more like actual rain. Mine isn't directly overhead so that might make a difference. But even when I set it up directly overhead I prefer something with jsut a touch of uumph to it rather than just gravity. In hindsight I think there's a reason we like our water pressure lol. And while this seems like a great idea, reality lands somewhere in between. Like most things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's fucking wild bro. man, still doing work in chiraq?  
   
Funeral business has to be pretty good there. From a market share perspective.  
   
edit: and from my time as a paramedic, ladies and gentleman, inappropriate gallows humor.  
  
edit2: ur username too...lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and my buddy ahve kind of been talking a bout this a bit. I'm pretty...right leaning center left sorta conservative. 
   
Why is it educated people feel so strongly about liberal ideas? And why is it that they are able to express them clearly? I'm all for reduced spending in the government. And a smaller fed. We all can agree on term limits for congress to inhibit special interests and prevent the creation of relationships to for re-election financing. And we all can agree on caps for campaign finance reform.   
  
If we're being serious about reforming our government. That said, how come when I walk into a room of educated people they're mostly liberal.  
  
I like to lean conservative. But i"m not going to take food away from people on SNAP because someone might be cheating it. I think free school lunches are a great idea but i'd also consider cutting that baseball team if they haven't won shit in 50 years. Put some new computers in that school and train these kids for the jobs we do have. Instead of actually giving them to people on H1B visas. With a salary base of 60k.  
   
When Trump won I didn't have time to really get how I felt until I saw his interview with Barbara Walters. I watched it and thought, man, if this guy did this once on the campaign trail I would have voted for him. To him though, and often in business, the ends justify the means. And I'll even concede that to him. 
   
But if you shit where you eat, eventually you got to clean it up. He gets into office and what's the first thing he does? A divisive travel ban that pisses people off and divides them further. 
   
My beef isn't with the ban itself. Or rather, the hold on immigration and review process of screening, call it what it is.  
  
But as a "CEO" the first thing I wouldn't do with my company is release something that might, except in the farthest reaches of imagination, be called a muslim ban. But you know what? Let's give him that too, and blame it on the Media.  
  
What's really infuriating. Anyone who knows anything about foreign policy, like any foreign adviser to Bush or Obama would have told him to include Pakistan on that list. Tunisia and Morocco possibly too.  
  
But what kind of gets me is, our program probably stopped some terrorists up until now. The refugee screening process is pretty strict. You could have reviewed all of this behind closed doors, released this behind closed doors, and maybe caught more terrorists. Now, a terrorist who already thought the refugee program was a last resort, is certainly going to avoid using that program to get into the country. It's like do you send a plain clothes cop to buy the drugs in the crack house or park a RNP out front and 2 patrol guys in uniform to knock on the door?   
  
And it's jsut disappointing, that's not how you run a country. On top of the whole notion that, deep down, it feels anti american. We've been accepting these people for years. 4 in the recent crisis in country and nothing has happened.   
  
No one asked for a ban on Irish Catholics when the IRA was waging war in Northern Ireland. I can't help but feel it comes from a deep place of insecurity and racism. But more importantly, to the uneducated, it furthers a narrative that is based on how people feel, rather than what our government knows. And now, all they see in their feeds are "Muslim Ban." Honestly, I'm not sure if it's the journalist in me, the PR guy in me, the copywriter in me, or the American that's flabbergasted more.  
  
And furthermore Seymore, I think he's smoking marijuana cigarettes, reefers!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, clearly, *Run All Night*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, for me, it was mostly the social context. 
  
a gang member's funeral is going to be filled with *gang* despite family objection. they're not exactly considerate people. 
  
and whether the murder set it off or was just another body dropped on the way, no rivals are going near that place. or they'll prolly be shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that was tough to read. lol the last edit kind of made up for it and glad i got a laugh out of it. but the whole time i'm thinking, maybe i should buy earplugs. 
   
what a horrible experience glad you're alright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to some extent makes me wonder why people don't adopt more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there's a lot of smaller subs you can still find some decent conversation/discussion on.  
   
avoid the politics though. no one wants to actually talk about an issue rather than its talking points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> unfortunately, i think, the people considering it and not having children, very well are the same people who would be considerate parents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honestly the 'rain' showerhead i have isn't expensive and it feels like rain. 
  
the reality is rain doesn't fall the same way everytime, and as long as it comes pretty close to a random falling of water lightly onto you you can exactly feel a difference. at least in the different 'rain' showers i've tried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 02:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for sure, most Indians I know, and many are immigrants both legal/illegal, are caring nice people. Except when Pakistan and Muslims come up lol. And appropriately so in a large degree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 02:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's actually a pretty cool picture. 
  
can i ask you what you're doing that you're taking your attention off the blown glass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol they are well done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure how accurate that would be.  
  
 To be fair, the Air Force never loses. They fly in, drop bombs on targets, fly close air support, and to them, it's generally a success. 
   
To some dude sitting in a FOB in the Afghani mountains wondering what the fuck he's doing there since we haven't built shit and aren't having any progress by the end of his 18 month tour, it's probably a bit of a different story. 
   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> got'em </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't disagreeing with you? It is a sad song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you lack a serious understanding of the radicalization process, radical Islam, and the nature of terrorism today. 
  
If their goal was to kill 350 million people...That'd be pretty lofty. Let's throw in the other infidel populations of Europe and we're probably at a pretty staggering number.  
  
It'd be good on you to read some history of the region and our current history with the wars there. How many of the insurgents were locals we turned against us after we arrived. THe most dangerous year in Afghanistan wasn't until 2006? or 2005? With Pakistani ISI support for the Taliban. 
   
Yall are complaining about the list of countries Trump made and our government is buddy buddy with the very country that caused most of the deaths in Afghanistan.   
  
And it's the very fact you won't take the time to understand the problem that plants you firmly in a camp of racism. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Culturally it's different. That's really it all it comes down to. Something like Animal Aid is a learned western aid organization. They probably still get looks from people like, what are you doing? It's a dog.  
  
Besides being a nuisance and spreading Rabies, they're just not looked at highly nor are those countries budgets included to worry about strays. Some absurd number of people in India sitll burn cow dung cakes for fuel and don't have electricity. Imagine you set up a shelter in an area like that. We don't have electricity, my well floods, and you put 500k into a *dog* shelter. In China they eat dog meat. North Korea too but the food situation is different there. Indonesia is Muslim, so dogs are Haram, along with the meat. Looked at as filthy and unclean things.   
  
Things are just different. Suffering sucks, and seeing some shit like that is fucked up. And I'm glad there's somebody doing something like they are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 06:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ghost War's is on my to read list. 
  
I think we have to take this as a whole though. Because there is equally a sentiment of wanting to not stop our government's foreign policy because we don't just arms. We export as much culture as anything else.  
  
And to an extent, I don't want to say they hate freedom but they do enjoy their way of life. And it isn't always the most 21st century way of doing things. It's very hard to say, 'oh but we like freedom. except letting our women vote.' I also think it's tough to take quotes from his videos where it really was one of the best propaganda campaigns in recent history.  
  
They also knew attacking America would elicit a massive response. I'm not entirely sure how I feel about the whole thing. 
   
Globalization is the way of the future. It's going to be hard to resist that much longer. And OBL's philosophy is as much anti-globalization as it is anti-American. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, to be honest while his motives for starting his terrorist career seem quite clear the attack on the Twin Towers I don't think really falls quite into the same bucket. 
   
It's also been noted that it seemed pretty clear that they knew such a grand attack would incite a response and appropriately America's response would be massive.  
  
And I also think it's important, you really have to, include Pakistan's anti-Americanism within this too. So even if OBL had this well thought out the average, poor, illiterate jihadi straight out of the madrassa who was listening to a virulent cleric probably doesn't. 
   
I think the average American who doesn't understand it was related to our ME Foreign Policy is as uneducated as we think they are. I mean we are truly an uninformed democracy. 
   
It just seems like AMerica was the easiest cop out for him to rally around. Why? Because Britain had already stopped it's own influence it gets forgiven for 200+ years of war in the ME and fucking it up?  
   
You could probably look at OBL's philosophy, not unlike the populist segment in AMerica today, rather than making it a defensive one for America's aggressive ME foreign policy but one of anti-globalization.  
  
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when delivering it to the media, most major news journalist will go to jail before giving up a source. 
   
that said, if he's going through all these steps on a company computer it's all for naught.    
  
edit: 
  
i'd consider dead dropping with gmail drafts and copy and paste what he wants. plus you have some plausible deniability that you were looking for clarification on something/working. to contribute rather than just criticizing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Afraid of exploding? Get a grip dude. If you're going to live your life in fear and commit to this kneejerk reaction then yes, they've already won.  
  
We do discriminate against people coming from those countries. Their process is so scrutinized to get into this country it isn't funny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get your facts straight man.  
  
The reality is of the terror attacks you listed above in you other post only two were committed by refugees and they both came from Tunisia, which isn't on Trump's list of banned countries.
  
 Why is not accepting refugees "xenophobic"? Can you tell me why you think it's irrational to not accept refugees from countries in which a large segment of the population wants us exterminated? 

That's just not true. You should read about the British occupation of the Helmand province in Afghanistan. Actually the whole invasion of  Afghanistan, and Iraq too to a lesser degree. 
   
There's certainly a radicalization process. But your presumption that vast swaths of countries are radicalized just isn't the reality from people who ahve been there.   
  
I also don't think you really understand radicalization. Terrorism isn't defined by its religious movements but by its political goals. It's as much a socioeconomic problem as anything else. Young men don't have jobs, young men don't have food, and then your mother/sister/father/brother gets killed. You've got nothing else, you're kind of angry and someone offers you an Ak-47 and $10/day.   
  
At least that's currently the situation in Syria, give or take. Most other radicalization takes the form of Madrassas where poor families send their sons to study because they have no other opportunities.   
 
What troubles me the most is 150 years ago my people were relegated to the 5 points area of NYC. The poorest, dirtiest, most dangerous area. We weren't allowed jobs and the ones we did get were often in household's as servants. Basically an almost indentured servitude. Or you were shipped down south to fight.  
  
We denied Anne Frank a visa in the 1930's. As well as a ton of other Jews coming from Europe.   
 
In the last 30 years or so we've taken a ton of refugees from a lot of war torn countries. In those same thirty years crime has gone down consistently. Most of these people resettle and receive some backlash for being different but ultimately assimilate and most town are better off for it.   
   
No one arguing against the refugee crisis seems to be talking from their personal experience of how their town went to shit or how their lazy neighbor is a refugee. Not that those arguments are very good either. 3 refugee's have been accused of terrorism. That's it. And they were radicalized after coming to the U.S.  
  
Here's an infographic, for when Obama was in the White House of the process to be a Syrian refugee. https://obamawhitehouse.archives.gov/blog/2015/11/20/infographic-screening-process-refugee-entry-united-states   
    
Terrorists usually have financial backing and come under the guise of anything else but a refugee, particularly because of the scrutiny the process has on it. The 9/11 hijackers, one came on a student visa and the rest on tourist and business visas.  
  
To get a visa, especially from a poor country, you need to show you have ties to that country, usually own property, and that you won't stay past your day you're supposed to leave.  
  
The most convincing way to show this is with money. If you have a lot of money in a bank account in your home country you won't leave that behind. So terrorists, in order to pull off these operations tend to have financial backing.    
  
One of the larger things to note of the recent attacks we've had are that they were home grown, legal U.S. citizens who bought their guns legally. Unlike France and Germany sneaking an AK-47 into this country is difficult. Or, again, expensive.  
    
edit: plus Pakistan, the most anti-american country in the world and home to the Taliban isn't on the list. Like man yall really just don't read do you? Or you only read what you agree with rather than asking questions about situations and methodically figuring them out.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah to be clear, I don't mean to minimize the horror of war in that theater or make it a pissing match between who was more atrocious.   
  
It feels like it depended if you were on the advancing or retreating side and had the chance to exercise that muscle.  
  
I think to some extent though, Russia had already gone through a famine twenty years before Barbarossa that included cannibalism. Then the horror of the Eastern Front hardened an already tough people.  
  
And worth adding the famine in Soviet Ukraine ~8 years before it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> escalated quickly a bit there... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, not my generation i think...  
  
but that's kind of hysterical. i'll have to find something else, i don't think that'll do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, teh refugee process into AMerica is a bit different than everyone else.  
  
It takes 9 months - 2 years to get into this country as a refugee. And it involve biometric screening and multiple background checks.   
  
The point isn't that the ban is bad. It's that it hurts good people too. 
  
Like the two guys stuck at JFK. One has ten years of work with the U.S. as a translator and both ahve their lives and their families lives for helping us while we were in their countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 11:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as someone who is a fan of classical music and a lot of electronic stuff...  
  
gonna have some weird music at my wedding. i'm already trying to convince my girl for barber's adagio as her song to walk down whatever she'll be walking down.   
  
she likes the planets tho! which is cool. def a lot to work with there, and some funky parts too.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 11:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh, from what it sounds like, especially reading that article, he knew he was dead no matter what.  
  
the red army seems to be particularly horrid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 11:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh you can know what someone's thinking. you see it in people's eyes all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 10:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha you know man, as soon as i finished looking at it i went back to them and as soon as I saw the first one  I was like awwww i'm a dick.  
  
got caught up in the actually good design.    
    
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 10:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you know that second can confirm is never the OP! haha so glad it was. 
   
that said, how yall feel bout revealing the username's to one another....lol reddit's a weird place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 10:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah it's the eccentricity thing i think combined with a sense of open mindedness and too much creativity, both in output and input. it leads to some troubling, and sometimes flat out criminal/wrong behavior. 
  
that last bit i mean in the sense of reading stories/plays where things happen. Having heard stories of other people or knowing other people that have pulled shit like that. 
  
 Also, probably should have put this first but I would expand it to all arts. As a writer, I know some professors and shit and students. Mentors, editors, and of course successes/career writers to hopefuls.     
  
I don't know if it's because things like Lolita and Roman Polanski are celebrated within the arts, and it's that to a degree that certianly plants a 'this is okay' notion in someones head, or what it is exactly but, yeah it's there. 
  
And maybe not in any more of a degree than a boss/secretary relationship? The only thing that  gets written about that is in the divorce papers. Instead of De Beauvoir's memos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 06:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm not a big dreamer, I tend to dream it feels like earlier in the night, I'll wake to piss and just it's al lgone. I guess I don't care enough either to leave a book next to me to write them down.  
   
But i've had some of the strangest, and I mean fucking weird dreams lately. The baseline we're starting with is it's weird I'm remembering them and dreaming at all. The content though? Some other fucking level.  
  
One was regarding being trapped in what was a complex. It was a Radical Mosque and the people there weren't quite terrorists in the typical sense we think of them but the people who have run the Madrassa and teaching people to become terrorists for years. So like a step up in the evil category. 
  
The back area had a pool area that was charred and there were bodies in it. A guy stepped out and say hey! It was someone I was familiar with, maybe he brought me there, and he was white like me. At that moment I looked at my girl and said, You got to get over the fence. But she didn't act fast enough and I remember thinking, fuck that was our shot to get one of us out of here. *We're dead.* 
  
Cut to them giving us a tour of the whole facility. And noting these sci-fi esque brazier's with glass tops. As we're giving the tour I keep looking at them like wtf? The white dude is giving the tour with 2 more American, rich, men of Arab descent. They sum it all up with all the good work they've done here changing the world. I look at my girl like, yo these guys are some fucking bad news. Then the white dude walks over to brazier like, you know what these are for?   
  
I go to answer and it sort of looks like a gas or vapor it forming inside it. He pushes it over and calmly walks away. It's VX, you know, like Sarin. He stepped through a glass door/screen/divider. And stood on the other side waiting for us to die.  
  
It's not an easy death, nerve agents, So I'm pretty terrified. But through the dream I've been trying to pin who exactly this guy was to me. I had to know him. Now though, that's out the window and that sense I had of trying to save me girl earlier, that had hope alive to maybe pull it off, quickly flipped to abject failure and despair.  
  
But you know, fuck that, gonna try.   
  
At some point around now, that you're gonna die thing kind of set off an alarm that said, but it's a dream too. I don't know it was weird. 
   
So, I press against teh wall as the glass on brazier breaks. Immediately to my right is a window. One that's floor to ceiling almost but doesn't open. It isn't really a moment to worry about safely evacuating the premises and i kick it to break it. We get through the window and out the back. The area that had those charred bodies is now a pool. I hop down into it with her, holding her hand a step behind me the whole time. We get shot at a couple times as someone shouts at us. At the bottom of the pool there's this vent/grate. I swim down to push it out and get it undone. I quickly realize it's way too small. I'm not sure I might be able to get her through it though. I turn around to surface and in that out of focus looking up through water kind of vision see multiple people standing around the pool and realize, no I'm not getting out of here. And where is she?   
 
And right at that moment where I'd surface to die, I go wake the fuck up man.  
  
And it's over.  
   
I've had nightmare's my owl life. Some really fucking weird and bad ones. I guess that's maybe why i stopped remember my dreams and pushing them out of my head and shit. VX poisoning is a horrible death, like who has that in a dream? **What The Fuck?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm pretty convinced that i'm just going to get skin cancer at some point. lol last thing ever consider to fall into this category. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 02:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know you see some pseudo old school style, faux art deco wanna-be hipster style logos that probably could be done with a filter or lightroom setting.  
 
and then you see some original quality work like this :P.  
  
Great idea, and great execution.  
   
Glad too see it turned into something too. Also props on the shots, I don't know if that was you/a friend or a pro photographer but they're well framed and everything. Really add to the effect of framed images rather than just posting the jpegs.   
  
Of course with any product, it helps to show it 'in use.' Still really added to the overall effect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reducing any funding for schools probably isn't a good idea. 
  
And Charter schools aren't a bad idea either. They pop up in bad neighborhoods, show good results, everyone then wants to get into the charter school or at a minimum out of the shitty school and eventually the shitty school closes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think there's a stern difference between an opinion/perspective and how you feel about something vs proven methods for improvement and improvements on society.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 08:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think unfortunately though, and this is where my conservatism waivers, is that benefiting people directly, as generally been shown, but will yield better results more than anything.  
  
Direct welfare isn't really that big of a part of the budget. It mostly goes to Social Security and Medicare/Medicaid. Medicare mostly iirc. The old and the sick eat up our tax dollars.  
  
A big part of that is teh rising cost of healthcare. That's the thing with the ACA. The problem isn't to insure the uninsured. It's to slow down the rising cost of healthcare. People who get sick cost more. People who are poor cost more.   
   
These are all things in one way or another other places, in varied degrees, have addressed in different ways with generally positive results. There's no reason as a developed nation to not learn things from their examples. 
   
And that's what kills me. Any and all government moves in that direction by republicans is instantly squashed as a bad/terrible idea. And I don't know. It jsut doesn't seem healthy. 
   
A big part of it too is that the change in our economy. The reality manufacturing isn't going to look the same ever again. Especially with robotics. Regardless of how you feel about climate change, green energy could actually be a big production boon for us. Factories for solar panels and windmills. Installation for those things, management of them. Instead it's like oh no! Back to Oil and Coal! Like, come on! Car factories in Korea are all robotics. It's crazy. Like that's only a matter of time because it effects the bottom line when one or two people can manage a whole factory floor rather than the ten we have now. ANd 50 years ago it was 100.   
  
And there are jobs there. We're just not trained for engineering and programming and information technologies and science. It's a shame. The country is headed in a bad direction. I Don't know what the solution is. What I do know is that there are thigns to be learned out there and we're not making any attempts to do so. 
   
And in the meantime we're punishing citizens in certain ways. With girls having to drive 6 hours to get an abortion. With a minimum of 3 visits. Tenn pregnancy is a leading cause of poverty. Long commute times contribute to poverty (and make it hard to hold two jobs).  
  
The facts are out there. Shit has been around long enough to say hey, this works, her this doesn't! Unions, I'm not the biggest fan but that's because AMerica shit the bed with their Unions. Unlike Germany which did it right. You hear things like Amazon choosing to keep an ambulance outside their warehouse because they didn't install AC in the summer because they didn't want to spend the money.  
  
I don't know man, that to me, just seems like not the kind of people that you need in your country to make it better. That's people who aren't just out for their own and their family, those are people who really don't give a fuck about anyone else. And that just isn't how we'll move forward as a country. It perturbs me deeply.  
  
Woha, sorry that got ranty and looooooooooong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 08:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Religion brings out the best in people and the worst in people, and most people fall somewhere in the middle.  
  
Reality is, religion lost its gumption and influence. People don't follow like they used to and faith is a barely tackled with notion, let alone doubt. 
  
In fact you could probably argue that a bit of doubt would be a good thing. Nowadays people's convictions are driven toward politiefs that aren't taken on faith, they're just taken. Or faith that it's what's right because of how they feel. 
   
God and religion often challenged people to question if how they felt was right in his eyes. Not just blind acceptance. 
  
I also have this theory that based on a group of 20 people, 5 are jihadist, 5 are mother Theresa like nuns and ten are just regular religious types, some slightly more devout some totally lapsed but generally jsut regular people.   
  
If we took god out of the equation, the good people would probably devote themselves to other, maybe not equally good, but good none the less causes. The ten regular people's lives won't change much. The 5 jihadists though, especially in regards to Islam, may find a difficult venue and outlet to dedicate their lives to in the name of violence. It's important to note that bad people will be bad but we're talking about fanaticism or radicalization.   
  
Generally though, it's a complex issue. Throwing out some bland statement, to make a point simplifying something so complex, is just silly. Especially when your comment seems contradictory. Catholic clergy advocating a movie that tackles tough philosophical questions? Doesn't seem to be too numbing and a blind faith approach there.  
  
Also, Catholicism is far from the superpower it used to be. At least most Catholics I know are pretty much lapsed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in some regards, this works because there's 1-2 cameras in the net as well. if we can't see it a camera can't either. 
   
this isn't some gps in the ball technology is that's what was perceived here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to be fair, because he made the point using plain, arguably crass, language doesn't really diminish it. fluffing it up with more academic names doesn't really change it at it's base. especially when you consider the context of what he was saying, the point was clearly made. 
   
that said the Right has turned into an individualist ideology but it's become manipulated unfortunately. particularly in regards to the individual in relation to big and small business. That by benefitting the business' we'll benefit the average worker. It's proven now it simply isn't the case. In the past it was referred to as trickle down economics in some regards. That's what kills me as a conservative. I'm pretty moderate now a days after a libertarian streak.    
    
From the National Bureau of Economics study released in December: 

Approximately a hundred and seventeen million people earn, on average, the same income that they did in 1980, while the typical income for the top one per cent has nearly tripled. That gap is comparable to the gap between average incomes in the U.S. and the Democratic Republic of Congo, the authors wrote.
    
And the place we've arrived is federal subsidies for states. So we're not actually reducing the federal government. And no one wants to talk about making a technologically smart military that's cheaper. Or raising taxes on estates, money leaving the country, and to some degree certain investments.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you watch football the channel will pull up the yellow lin for first down and stuff all the time. I imagine in the box they have somewhat similar technology. 
   
Plus a major difference is that only the tip of the ball has tocross the goaline or the first down line making it a lot easier to judge. Harder in some ways but technology isn't as needed, because of the chains.   
  
I'm not 100% sure how much something like this would help in catches/completions though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually they tend to have it for first downs in American football. The difference being in American football only the front of the ball has to cross the line in both a touchdown and first down. So it's a lot easier to tell and aren't going to need such a detailed display to the audience.  
  
If you watch a game of American football they'll show you all the time the first down line and where the ball stopped, and they have the chains too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 02:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> try heroes of the storm. 
  
games only last 20 min on average. it's a lot of fun, still is a moba, and just overall is a lot of fun. 
  
it also splits up quick match, unranked draft, and then ranked solo q/team league. 
   
plus it has a brawl mode and recently introduced sandbox too. 
   
def recommend it if you haven't given it a go. the one hour and one game you'd get in LoL you'll get 3 in heroes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah man, sounds like ya do. keep at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> generalizing a bit there. 
  
most addicts aren't going to be able to afford soda beer candy and all that other shit, let alone a rake or be in a condition togo out there all day to rake. 
   
get a grip, just because someone is a piece of shit who doesn't take care of the area around them doesn't mean they're doing drugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah for sure. His one appointment to the Budget cabinet seat is someone who stands for defense cuts and stuff. Pivoting to a smaller more technology inclined military, for lower cost would be the intelligent thing to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See did he deserve to be punished under the law? Absolutely.  
  
Doesn't mean he deserves his family to be assassinated like they were and for him to live in terror.   
  
In no way are the equally interchangeable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Train is really nice. I did almost 24 hours (looks like it is 30 hours there, I think the way home was closer to 24 flat) or maybe a little over actually from NYC to NOLA. It was beautiful and awesome.   
  
I didn't get a sleeper but that's fine because you go to the restaurant or cafe to kill a few hours here or there and the seats are like big and spacey and easy to fall asleep in imo.   
  
If I was doing this length again I probably would consider a sleeper car instead. Timing worked out for me too. We left NYC at like 6 or 7 pm so got on the train, ate food we brought, had a glass of wine and went to sleep to wake up in the morning.   
  
And then we did breakfast at the food car, a couple hours in the bar car and then dinner at our seats iirc with sandwiches from the bar/cafe car thing.  
  
I think I fell asleep again around 7 or 8 and woke up around Midnight/1 AM in New Orleans. 
   
Either way it was an awesome experience, I absolutely loved it. That length is right on the borderline for a sleeper car. We got away with it and in hindsight said we probably should have taken one.   
  
The train is great for short trips too. I've done the bus for around 6 hours Boston to NYC and it wasn't really that bad. Any longer though and I could see it sucking. The bus is claustrophobic in a lot of ways and doesn't make travelling pleasurable.    
  
The train I also did from NYC to Philadelphia then Philly to Baltimore over a few days. That's kind of the beauty of it. You can book within a few days and be on your way or even the day before and not get charged an arm and a leg. It's a lot of fun and overall a nice trip. Highly recommend it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did Trump run on that a bit? Limiting the influence of money in politics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah sure, and a lot of it came down to her campaigning. Or lack of it.  
   
He needs  all those states to win, she doesn't. Florida is kind of the key turning point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just had a similar conversation yesterday. 
  
Let's jsut talk about schooling in general. New York City has some failing schools. This is actually one area where private industry, aka charter schools, might actually help and fill the gap. That's obviously going to take federal money. Charter schools are a good solution. 
   
But part of it also is that NYC schools are highly segregated. And when alternative solutions, because one answer is never the best answer, like shipping children out of their currently assigned districts to other, better performing ones, are met with resistance. This what people talk about when they use the term institutional racism. 
   
It isn't that the kid is black, of course that's not it directly but indirectly it certainly plays a role that the more impovershed areas are black. So the I pay my taxes, my child deserves this school argument is a selfish one and along the lines of other standard republican thinking. 
  
Is shipping one or two or ten kids from one school into another going to disrupt it that much? Absolutely not. Is it going to open opportunities to those kids, potentially end the cycle of poverty, get them out of a bad neighborhood, and most importantly, get them an education that'll get them to graduate high school and go to college/ Of course it is. 
   
It's a reality that people in America are out to get their share. Whether it's a republican claiming that people abuse the welfare system (which is often most abused by the people who don't need welfare, like wealthy people who separate to file taxes as single mom and the husband files as still married w/ dependents). or democrats arguing for programs to help the poor. There's a fundamental divide individually among us in America.   
  
We don't look at the bigger picture or being part of something greater. We look at me and mine. And that's the reality of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I commented how your news gets gerrymandered too. It's pretty interesting and a 21st century phenomenon. As we continue to get more information from the internet it keeps delivering more like minded and agreeable links to you.    
   
here's a link to an article about it: http://www.nytimes.com/2013/10/12/business/media/when-our-news-is-gerrymandered-too.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To add to this an interesting phenomenon of the 21st century is that your news gets gerrymandered as well.  
  
With all this tracking as you continue to look at conservative leaning sites google and search engines will bring you more like minded stuff. So the thought never occurs to you to click a link to see the other side of it. You only get the info that will continually drive you in teh direction you were going. 
   
It's actually super interesting. I kind of glanced over the post so maybe it was mentioned after the Stanford study or in it.  
  
http://www.nytimes.com/2013/10/12/business/media/when-our-news-is-gerrymandered-too.html  
  
Is an interesting article on it.   
  
And this is just Gerrymandering in general: https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/wonk/wp/2015/03/01/this-is-the-best-explanation-of-gerrymandering-you-will-ever-see/?utm_term=.ac8382788092 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol something like that i think. for those not noticing the human as a dagger or sword into the orc's chest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buddy, you may have seen one or two posts and assumed bias!  
  
The reality is the press was kind on Trump a bit harsh on CLinton, for a long time, before being more equally critical of both. 
   
I recommend not getting your news from any of the major American Networks. Consider reading/watching the Wall Street Journal and the New York Times (for your newspapers, one left leaning one right leaning but both willing to throw punches) and the get the rest of your news from Reuters, the BBC, Associated Press, and Al-Jazeera America.  
  
Generally talk shows and shit like that or prime time news even isn't the place to get your news from. They need viewership and conflict brings that in. So things get hyped up more. 
   
A strong reality is that Trump was treated kindly with tons of airtime without question for a while before people started fact checking and contesting what he was saying.  
  
And you need to understand what it's like to be a journalist when someone makes up blatant lies to you. If you tell me the sky is purple and say, yep that's it that's all i'm saying, you know it, I know it, the sky's purple. I'm going to say of course it's not look at this picture, it's blue!   
  
The next time you claim something I have to think to myself, is this true? Or is this made up? And when you make claims several times that are just factually incorrect you're going to really put yourself under a microscope. You're inviting that scrutiny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, listen I'm a Conservative at heart and believe in scrutinizing the money the federal government spends. A bigger government doesn't necessarily mean things will be better.  
  
Unfortunately in order for Trump to do the things he said he's going to do, he's going to have to spend money. Particularly on infrastructure. And maybe that will turn out to be a good thing. Still I'm skeptical. I also am frustrated by his lack of removal from his business on ethics guidelines. A lot of big construction happens with tax break, he's going to be jeopardizing a lot of stuff by not removing himself from his business when taking some hardline approach toward other countries. 
   
You're absolutely right though. Companies that pay well already due so. And sure it comes at a hit in profits but most notably when you ahve compensation and bonus packages that are valued in the multi millions it doesn't seem like a bad place to tax from. The points about estate tax that forced aggressive philanthropy were goo d too, made by another commenter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not entirely true. there were a lot of people thought he had a shot and it wasn't that far off for him to win, florida which has always been back and forth was teh a tipping point.  
   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 07:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's hysterical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 07:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah generally. I think there's a big distinction between today's new wealth and wealth of the past. 
   
Andrew Carnagie and John Rockefeller, and I'm absolutely mixing up the two, but respectively one opened like 1,000 libraries in AMerica and the other founded a University (of Chicago?).  
   
While there's certainly philanthropy today, and it does some great stuff there's too many causes, especially foreign ones to take money for. We're just not revitalizing and bringing up people from poverty like we used to. 
   
 In December, the National Bureau of Economic Research published a new analysis, by the economists Thomas Piketty, Emmanuel Saez, and Gabriel Zucman, which found that half of American adults have been completely shut off from economic growth since the 1970s. Approximately a hundred and seventeen million people earn, on average, the same income that they did in 1980, while the typical income for the top one per cent has nearly tripled. That gap is comparable to the gap between average incomes in the U.S. and the Democratic Republic of Congo, the authors wrote.  
  
From the [New Yorker Doomsday Prep for the Super Rich](http://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2017/01/30/doomsday-prep-for-the-super-rich) article in the recent issue.  
  
One thing people also miss is that small business is the backbone to the economy as much as larger corporations. Having the owner be a multi millionaire though and the workers earn $12/hr is going to have poor results after 50 years.  
   
Jobs that were supposed to be stepping stones or have upward mobility don't have it. With further mechanization and robotics we're really going to be on thin ice in another 20 years.  
   
And the reality is the jobs are there. The industry is there in a big regard. People are trained for it. People aren't learning to program or build computers or work as engineers. We need a push to modernize our workforce and truly be a leader in the 21st century. I'm 100% on board for investing in infrastructure but we need to do that smart. We need to invest in better public transportation to reduce commute times (leading contributor of poverty and economic mobility). Not continue to pursue a car culture, which in an of itself, is creating the next economic bubble with auto loans for everyone.  
   
The country is in bad shape. And I'm worried that the deregulation will be in the direction of benefiting the top 1-2% rather than the average worker. We could have factories building solar panels and wind farms and exporting that technology but instead we're chanting for coal and oil like that's the future.  
  
It's sad, we're turning into an uneducated nation of people. When instead we could be this technology driven cutting edge workforce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 05:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I get that. That's why I mention it's a necessary distinction jsut to be careful doing so.  
  
It did have its own gas chamber and crematorium too as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The brits also got a tad bit lucky with Hitler ordering to not proceed to capture the british soldiers evacuating during the initial blitz. I believe he was having a pissing match with his generals and wanted to 'win' something to show he was the boss. Up until then it was his and generals and the guys on the ground that just kept rolling forward despite initial orders to only go so far here or there. When they went to march on Dunkirk Hitler wanted to assert his control and ordered them to stop a couple days outside the town rather than continuing on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I think that's what people miss. While to some extent there was a time when reposts were upvoted by the same people again because it was cute/funny/awesome/cool I think reddit's population and user base has grown enough that reposts are often new content for the people seeing it.    
  
There's some presumption that something should only be posted once, is seen by everyone who is on the sight, and anything reposted is upvoted again by the same folks. It's a fallacy and kind of crazy.
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and it a lot of ways it contributes to the conversation. I'm not sure it's worth critiquing at all really. Grateful he posted those links. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR:  Dachau was as fucked up as any of them. While a necessary distinction in some regards, be cautious in doing so. Some horrible, torturous things went on that are potentially being overlooked by simply calling it a 'work' camp.
  
weird things? Don't minimize it.  
  
I don't know if kill orders were given at Dachau  at the end but it was a concentration camp, the first one made so thus the longest one running by the end of the war. 
   
To give you an idea, because, unfortunately, while we all know the horror of these camps, it feels like saying it was a "work camp" kind of defends it a bit. To an extent the distinction is necessary but shouldn't minimize some of the criminally inhuman treatment that went on there.    
   
Rascher experimented with the effects of Polygal, a substance made from beet and apple pectin, which aided blood clotting. He predicted that the preventive use of Polygal tablets would reduce bleeding from gunshot wounds sustained during combat or during surgery. Subjects were given a Polygal tablet, and shot through the neck or chest, or their limbs amputated without anaesthesia. Rascher published an article on his experience of using Polygal, without detailing the nature of the human trials and also set up a company to manufacture the substance, staffed by prisoners.[17]
   
Forgive the sourcing but Wikipedia is convenient. Dachau did a bunch of medical torture there and tests. Some really fucked up shit. Cold water and hypothermia experiments, the blood clotting experiments and if I recall correctly several of the doctors, mostly SS, from the camp were executed by the Allies after the Nuremberg trials. The Subsequent Nuremberg trials that put the doctors and three members of the SS on trial.  
   
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nazi_human_experimentation   
  
That lists Dachau as participating in  a large amount of the human experiments. Another troubling account: 
   
From about July 1944 to about September 1944, experiments were conducted at the Dachau concentration camp to study various methods of making sea water drinkable. At one point, a group of roughly 90 Roma were deprived of food and given nothing but sea water to drink by Dr. Hans Eppinger, leaving them gravely injured.[12] They were so dehydrated that others observed them licking freshly mopped floors in an attempt to get drinkable water.[21]    
   
I used those two particularly because there's citations in Wikipedia for additional research which I'll list at the end.  
  
One more troubling account is the high altitude experiments:  
   
In early 1942, prisoners at Dachau concentration camp were used by Sigmund Rascher in experiments to aid German pilots who had to eject at high altitudes. A low-pressure chamber containing these prisoners was used to simulate conditions at altitudes of up to 20,000 m (66,000 ft). It was rumored that Rascher performed vivisections on the brains of victims who survived the initial experiment.[27] Of the 200 subjects, 80 died outright, and the others were executed.[12]  
   
[12] -  Tyson, Peter. "[Holocaust on Trial: The Experiments](http://www.pbs.org/wgbh/nova/holocaust/experiside.html)". NOVA Online.     Retrieved 23 March 2008.  
  
[17] -  "[Introduction to NMT Case 1: U.S.A. v. Karl Brandt et al.](http://nuremberg.law.harvard.edu/nmt_1_intro)". Harvard Law Library, Nuremberg Trials Project: A Digital Document Collection. Retrieved 23 March 2008.  
  
[21] - Cohen, Baruch C. "[The Ethics Of Using Medical Data From Nazi Experiments](http://www.jlaw.com/Articles/NaziMedEx.html)". Jewish Law: Articles. Retrieved 23 March 2008.  
   
[27] -  Cockburn, Alexander (1998). [Whiteout:The CIA, Drugs, and the Press](https://books.google.com/books?id=s5qIj_h_PtkC pg=PA149 dq=%22sigmund+rascher%22+brain sig=hik0GQjMaPj9LF-YDkYdp0S9Otc#v=onepage q=%22sigmund%20rascher%22%20brain f=false). Verso. ISBN 1-85984-139-2.  
  
Not the most academic but I'm sure someone more well versed on the topic might put together something that will hold up to detailed scrutiny a bit better. I'm sure these are documented elsewhere and particularly the Harvard Law Library's Nuremberg Trials Project probably as it all.  
   
Still, work camp or death camp, avoid using language that minimizes how horrible and truly inhuman the conditions and events taht went on were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 03:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's really boggling my mind is that damn radiator. Those things are ridiculously heavy and are made of iron.   
  
Like what is holding it there and when will it fall!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 03:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's not a special thing. It's more like, technically from the city everything else is up from us. 
   
Also taxes. We support most of the rest of the state. So, to an extent, there is a bit of center-of-the-state (and world to a degree).  
  
Generally Hudson Valley tends to start to be upstate. And it's clear from the change in how shit is laid out. Westchester resembles the less dense parts of Long Island and NJ. North of that though, it's different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 03:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when people warn of a not going into a place because of structural hazard of collapse...this place is long past the 'caution' phase.  
  
But what the hell is holding that radiator up? 
   
Those tended to be iron and is probably a few hundred pounds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No diplomacy is not a place to bully people in. Absolutely not. Very well put. And I agree entirely, I've done plenty of public speaking. Even a half filled auditorium can seemed filled, until you've stood in front of a standing room only one and actually see what it looks like filled. He's seen how packed his rallies were he probably assumed this would be the same way.  
  
And from his place maybe it looked that way too. It is kind of weird that no one would be like no, look at this picture and this tweet says it was taken at 12:01 PM so that's what the crowd was. And he says oh that's not right it was more than Obama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not true. He's alienated women too much by now, especially with this movement that's started. He won't carry 2020, not by al ong shot and not without some hard reforms moving ahead.  
   
The reality is the president doesn't have as much power as people are investing into him. To also be fair, the executive branch has never been more powerful, particularly over the last 15 years, give or take a couple.   
  
Most of the legislation will come out of congress. What he tries to originate from his own office very well may not make it through congress at all. Despite promises to 'drain the swamp' and I'm not bullshitting when he finally won, I was hopeful I pivoted and said, fuck it, lets see what he brings to the table moving ahead. Maybe he will be different. He hasn't though. He picked a pretty shitty cabinet. For all their faults Clinton and Bush Jr. picked some pretty sharp cabinets. Some of their choices obviously weren't the brightest but for the most part they were a colelction, at the time, of some of the best and brightest. All Trump's is lean further right. And I think, to a big extent, without understanding the issues he's appointing these people to (to some extent the people themselves as well, see Rick Perry).  
  
I'm curious what corporate tax breaks will actually do. I really don't think we'll see wages go up much and the talk of a weaker dolalr seems, crazy imo.   
   
I mean we have a president that said "I have good words. I have the best words!" when talking about his vocabulary. So I really question his ability or willingness to understand complex issues. The wall is another one. The cost we could save doing it smart, with technology, is cheaper. We have walls on the border. It's a 14th century solution to a problem that isn't...ah fuck it man, it jsut seems crazy when you think about it too much. And the worst part is you'd find few people who actually disagree with securing our borders.  
   
Part of me hopes that maybe he'll jsut do showey shit, deregulate a few industries, maybe bring a few jobs here or there and that's it. His business acumen may lend itself to some domestic policy but it won't to foreign policy. I mean his 'Art of the Deal' if you've read it was a lot of bullying to make deals and jsut swinging the bigger dick to get shit done. And really he's only grown one brand in one field of business. A field that has continually grown over the years. Real Estate. Not really exactly started all these companies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah for sure, that's with a 14 point spread that puts it more in line with the other poll they show there. 
    
So sure, it's above 50% but they're also the only one. I think to some extent they may have been more accurate in their election polling but still most approval rating are showing around the ~44% mark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so we're agreeing then. Even the Rasmussen is a 54% approval with a 14 point spread.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to piggy back on this a bit, if ya don't mind.  
  
to be fair they weren't critical of him for a long time on the campaign trail. it was kind of like oh look what he said, again! It was a disservice to our population and resulted in this election. By the time they did start calling him out people were saying things like "Oh he doesn't really mean that" or "I don't believe everything he says!"  
  
The reality is Trump benefited more from the media *not* calling him on his shit. For someone to expect him not to be held accountable for telling falsehoods *while in office* is odd. Every administration is going to be held accountable and called on their shit at some point or another. That's kind of why Trump fucked up here.
  
The White House missed a big opportunity by lying about the inauguration numbers. It was a weird thing to lie about to begin with because there's photographic evidence of the crowd. At least the Press Secretary could have came out and just told the truth? No one gives a shit about how many people were at his swearing in. It's just an odd thing to come out and lie about when there's photo's of the crowd. When he could have done is come out telling the truth and established a fair and even shot in the public's and the media's eye. Like yeah sure, Trump tweets and says some crazy things, but **officially** as an Administration, we're not crazy. We got it together.   
  
Instead Spicer sounded *just* like Trump in the sense that he needed to stroke some sense of ego that, no! *of course* we had more people here than Obama, silly! Like duh! It's Trump! Of course it's the biggest Swearing In Ever!!! #IWasThere #Trump2017   
 
It's a weird thing to lie about and it continues on a trend that Trump has established long before he was elected. Fortunately, now, when the White House makes a statement to a room full of journalists, they're going to ask questions about it. Claiming it's "Alternative Facts" is a desperate, at best, and laughable ,at worst, attempt to save face of a *nonsensical* thing to lie about.   
  
That's what you need to understand. The administration set the standard for what the media needs to question. When you're refuting what people saw when they were there and the photos of the event that show something completely different you've now created a universal doubt in everything that will be said by the administration. Considering it is a clear continuation of Trump's previous comments and behaviors it doesn't come as a surprise. But it is a missed opportunity to establish a connection with media outlets.   
   
So when out elected officials are acting like that, and saving face by using the term "alternative facts" in a way they've created a bias against themselves. Because now, as a reporter, I need to question everything and be dubious of everything you do. You've tried to refute photographic evidence of something, that I was *present* for! Don't you see how this is going to turn the media against you? How this breaks a bond of trust usually held between the Press Secretary and some journalists?   
   
That's disturbing. That they went out of their way to lie and lost the opportunity to establish themselves with a sense of trust with the media(1st press conference!). I'm sorry you'll only pull the wool over the eyes of people for so long ( I was kind of hopeful for a couple months when he got elected). Someone who needs the validation to believe he had that largest Inauguration probably shouldn't be our president. The man not smart enough to realize that he needs that validation and choose to lie about it anyway, in the face of a picture, is...I don't know what to say about that. 
  
And that's why people are scared for the country.   
   
My baaad   
  
edit: and just a slight bit of clarification, first off thanks for the gold!   
  
PR, Public Relations has always been to some extent, presenting 'alternative facts' without ever calling it that. Once you do, to an extent, you kind of concede the point. Obviously it's not perceived this way by most because of how information is ingested in this country. The point is, I understand that's what PR does. The move here would have been to ignore it altogether and concentrate on others thing, as some here claimed his staff wanted to do.  
  
What's frightening about that is either no one is willing to confront him on his own bullshit and insanity within the administration or he's able to convince them that his view is right and the way to go. It's kind of scary, at best, and certainly insane, or borderline fanatical, at worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 20:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I plunged my lance into his stomach; nevertheless, the Makassar, as if he had no sense of feeling, advanced upon the weapon which I held fast in his body, and made incredible efforts to come at me in order to run me through; and he would infallibly have done it, if the hilt of the blade had not hindered him.

whaaat!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 10:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah you're good man. I guess my point is while a place like Hofstra isn't Trump University or a purely For-Profit university, people for a while were getting hit hard with income requirements for true financial aid and the reality.   
  
And again, coming out of college without a degree to match isn't going to do you shit really. Like liberal arts degrees are big risks and you need to do the work/intern to make something happen. The biggest thing you could do really is look at college programs, like you said, with specific hook ups within industries you want to work in.   
  
While it is manageable, to a degree, I think there's just too much debt in justifying it. Is 30k debt manageable? One year of NYU that you can't afford puts you in 60k debt, private loans interest rate at 6-8%.  
   
That's *fucking insane.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh man you're initial claim is kind of bullshit. Financial Aid really doesn't come through like that and Hofstra, ten years ago, was almost 50k a year with housing. I want to say it was 36k without housing.  
   
As for financial Aid, it wasn't shit. Sure maybe a place like Harvard that can hit up some alumni for the tuition costs of a student or create some unique scholarship on the spot, there's probably a trust for it, as those machinations in place but you're defending what ahs essentially become a big business subsidized bythe federal government and really taken a turn for the worst. 
   
A lot of people are getting screwed by it. The private universities that don't rank well are just essentially a big gamble. Not going to school for something STEM is just a waste of time and money. What they'll make sure is you get set up with loans, and get saddled with debt. NYU isn't the only school that's bipolar about aid. FAFSA is generally where most aid comes from, not the school itself. It's a criminally expensive, bloated big business that has gotten out of hand due in part to the loan system and federal government.    
  
Not that I'm against a big federal government or anything but college in the U.S. is outrageously priced for the 2nd and 3rd teir schools that aren't state tuition prices. Like Hofstra or Scranton and shit like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> these kind of waves tend to form on reefs, offshore, under particular  conditions.   
  
surfing is more like...not going to a particularly difficult mountain because you can't ski it or sticking to a ski resort in the sense that when we decide to go surfing we know the waves are only 5-8 feet today or 3-5. I'm not going to go jump into the water somewhere that is breaking a 50 foot wave unless i can surf it. And a 50 foot wave isn't going to jsut 'appear' while i'm surfing 5-7 footers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the movie was so cringey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i believe it's actually fruit strips now, not gum. at least the couple gas stations by me that carry it, it's fruit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hopefully hijacking so this gets seen, they actually still make but it's fruit strips now. like real fruit from my understanding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i don't know why i had that reaction, probably just projecting some shittiness i was feeling. 
   
absolutely loooooooove those two though. and equally the type of person who hangs them up, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i agree entirely bout archon. i'm just putting forward the argument of lore vs practicality, you know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol nooooo 
   
u get a new hero ~3-4 weeks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i dont know. keep your eye on the mini map, move the map fast, and yeah...do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 03:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah to some extent you're right. but really what made it difficult was how sporadic the events were and you couldn't necessarilly identify wwith the team to keep rooting for them. 
   
with a league now there's a good chance he'll end up popping on HGC once in a while and just like regular sports find a team  to root for now that they are playing every week.  
  
the reality is while people do root for their citie's team it isn't like there are a ton of other people rooting for other teams in those cities too. regularly seeing them play though, so that you can grow and learn to identify them is what helps it grow. 
   
eventually people will learn about the other players and stuff and find someone they want to root for or another team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 10:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't tell me, no! noooo! you're taking a bit of a practical approach toward all this! you lore-traitor! 
  
seriously, his kit isn't that far off, it still feels like a protoss high templar in a lot of ways. And Tass is unique in his shielding and force wall abilities. Plus from a lore perspective we're forgetting that they were back line, pseudo support casters. That were really easy to kill if you got to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 10:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did you see the D3 mod they released. It made D3 with D2 graphics and only 8 movement directions and shit. Looking at it I was like wow that was a bit rough around the edges, eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 10:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because there's a level of practicality. i'm sure they try out lore based ideas and stuff. it has to be practical and it has to be fun.  
  
edit: it's a totally different game environment than any of these heroes/characters have been in. it's almost like oh, no shit they don't port over exactly the same. shocker! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 10:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i thought something like per target in psi storm it increases dmg 20% or when psi storm hits 3 targets or more dmg increases 50 or 100% or something. And that palys into the HT nuking zerg swarms and shit. 
   
That said, the original post about tass the guy referenced a lot of cinematics and stuff. Of course they make them look super bad ass in cinematics. Ht's were always pseudo support backline characters (that were super fragile!!).  
   
He really isn't that far off from his lore.  
  
And if we did add feedback as a heroic we'd probably replace Archon, moving further away from the lore aspect. Because force wall is super unique and awesome. Part of this is downpalying 1. how unique and cool tass is 2. the impact he does have when played correctly.  
  
part of that is it's tough to enjoy tass when you're not playing in a coordinated team environment or solo q/qm/ud.  So you odn't feel as strong as you might be. It kind of falls back to the healbot/healing is boring argument. That critically downplays how important a good ancestral or palm or whatever is to a teamfight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 10:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> part of the problem here is, and I know his kit isn't super cool now, it was super unique and useful when HotS hero pool wasn't so deep.    
  
People who are hardcore about lore will never really be satisfied and always will be loud about their concerns. What is conveiently being left out of the 'lore' of high templars is that they were fragile, always needed to be protected, didn't have an auto attack (in sc1), and are, lore-wise, backline pseudo support casters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 10:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or everyone could just sort of get a grip and be a bit more practical about all of it. plus we're downplaying how unique his kit actually is in heroes.  
   
HT's are backline casters though. always needed protection because they're easy to kill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 10:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right? but what would you get rid of? Not force wall. Probably archon, and now we're moving away from the lore because of practical application within the game. There's a give and take there. Force Wall is super unique and pretty damn strong. 
   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 10:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh I read that post I get where he's coming from but they choose to take a more supporty form and that's what it is. And the reality is HT's were psuedo support, back line, casters in SC. They always had to be protected too because they were fragile. Didn't even have an AA in SC1, not sure about SC2. Tass fills a super unique one of a kind role in the game.  
  
 More damage to the psi storm def would work. Something that scales with increased targets to emphasize its group effect. You could consider a feedback heroic that drain the mana of a hero to 10% dealing it as damage maybe or 50% as damage maybe. And get rid of force wall. But the reality is you'd want to get rid of Archon really. Because Force Wall is so unique and awesome.  
  
Cinematics always make things look crazy badass. Those were also Zealots in those cinematics. We all know they aren't exactly super badass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 10:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they were also fragile as shit and super easy to kill if they weren't protected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 10:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's kind of what i don't get. plus they were always super fragile easy to kill/needed to be protected units. Getting anything onto the HT's usually meant they died unless he pulled off archon's as soon as they were attacked. And then you still lost some. 
   
Very glass cannon on MOBA terms. I think the call for lore is a valid one, and I get it. Plus if they announced this it wouldn't be for a year at least till something happened. If their new hero cycle takes 9-12 months that's exactly how long it would be. Plus it wouldn't be easy to implement. 
   
What kind of bothers me is that HT's are these powerful cool units. Tass is this unique powerful cool unit in HotS. I get the call for more damage for sure to fit more in lin with lore and something like is Psi storm is hitting 3+ targets it does more damage or for every target it hits it does 30% more damage would be awesome. It would also keep it in line with the hard hitting Psi storm used on grouped up zerg.  
  
That said, he's one of the most unique heroes in the game and stands alone in that regard. Kind of wish people were a bit mroe practical in their considerations. 
   
Then again, from a lore perspective, you'll always have someone saying something and never satisfy everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 10:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah and maybe this could be a thing in a year or two... 
  
Because that's not a solution that's just whipped up. Nor would it be easy to implement. People are kind of insatiable. And I get the ire but because he isn't true to his lore...or rather not true *enough* seems like we're stretching.  
  
Especially when his functionality in game is unique and cool. And it uses elements from his lore and the idea of protoss shielding. 
  
Also, I don't know entirely what people want either. A feedback like mana drain/damage dealt ability? The original HT were also glass dolls and needed to be protected like crazy. Almost glass cannon like comparison if comparing it in a moba setting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 09:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THere's kind of this juxtaposition, maybe justi n my feelings, regarding putting 4k years of history into a simple bar chart like this. On one hand, it's amazing we can quantify all that so simply and it is neat and cute. On the other hand it's a lot of history reduced to 20-something lines, give or take. 
   
I'm not knocking it guy/gal! Great job and it is awesome. There's beauty in the simplicity of it. I'm not sure why my gut reaction felt that way and felt strongly enough to post. Thought it was interesting enough to share, I suppose.  
  
I have studied, in comparison, a tiny little bit of that and a tiny little bit of a bunch of that chart (in depth more recent and briefly studied over a longer period of time). Maybe it always felt like there was so much going on with China when I studied it that I had the reaction I did. 
   
I do wish I recalled more about it outside of the most recent 1k-1.5k (maybe 2k) years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 09:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there's some truth in how the media and, generally, peopel treated trump. to a lesser degree his supporters. it's dangerous to generalize so touching his 'supporters' is difficult. it still doesn't mean we should have let slip and not pressed him on the insanity that was his campaign. the general calls to action, the turning around on issues or statements he made ("I didn't say that."), and shit like that. The media put him in the big top, center ring, and never reminded everyone that we were at the circus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 09:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as a writer it's third consecutive year that paper book sales risen.  
  
that said, these grants and institutions for the arts are a huge part of keeping them relevant and around. the national endowment for arts is a biggy. and it may be a pain i nthe ass to get it to come back. 
   
and it's stuff like the grant search and the network this provides to toung artists trying to connect with different people and funding that makes it so valuable. not because this institution itself is funding everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 05:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there's certain things you eyes do, i can't recall but up and to the left might be recalling something you actually did see but up and to the right is more being creative/making something up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 04:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i dont think the playerbase is as small as people imply. the game has been consistently growing and there's definitely enough people playing. 
   
the skill difference between silver and low plat isn't that big of a difference solo q in a lot of ways. but in many other ways it really is pretty big. i get waht your saying as far as teh average game experience. and I agree with you for the most part. THe more I think about it though the more i do see the differences.  
  
I don't know if it's small playerbase as much it's a combination of being a newr game to some extent and a still growing game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 04:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and carrying in hots is tough. knowing when you need to be with your team to fix what is about to be a mistake or prevent a 4v5 or give up a fort to minions or choose to give up an obj jsut to duo soak lanes because you need xp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 10:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol wait till he gets into HL. 
  
"I placed Gold 5 and deranked to Silver 3! wtf heroes!?!" 
   
lol just kidding.  def take your time going over into ranked though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 10:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is role in the game as a shielder though is kind of needed/critical now as it is.  
  
he needs to be a bit more and i haven't the rework yet but he is a support too. lol can't have it all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol true that. and i know, from a scientific perspective, what you're saying makes sense. i guess my point was that it struck me more, and you did admit you were nitpicking, but really an issue of semantics. even though it technically isn't.   
  
and within the context of speaking to a bunch of random lay people, even more so.   
   
edit: and just so i'm not a total idiot here. white noise contains all frequencies, rather than just the high ones but it's the high ones that dominate that sound to us because of our sensitivity to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 22:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> compared to how the car looks restored i think i'd go along with leaving it somewhat beat up.  
  
then again there's the after restoration feeling of i'm in a DB4, bitch! as a motivator. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 22:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he's an audio engineer. also the way we perceive things is how they are.   
  
it's like language in a way. words we use a certain way, even if it's not their definition become the definition they were used for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 08:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's important to note workplace plans are trending toward high deductible and/or high premiums with the rising cost of healthcare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 04:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It never occurred to me but this seems to be slightly influenced by a Kierkegaard quote.  
  
How did I get into the world? Why was I not asked about it and why was I not informed of the rules and regulations but just thrust into the ranks as if I had been bought by a peddling shanghaier of human beings? How did I get involved in this big enterprise called actuality? Why should I be involved? Isn't it a matter of choice? And if I am compelled to be involved, where is the managerI have something to say about this. Is there no manager? To whom shall I make my complaint? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
