<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3750</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, thats exactly what I was reffering to thanks for clearing that up. I thought I was a dickhead, but I play with even worse scrubs than me, so check-raising, and only calling bets works wonders for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New to poker, is slowrolling frowned upon? 
Its my favourite thing to do when I flop a set, or better, though I never do it with a pocket pair.
EDIT: Confused slow roll with slow play, just to clarify that I am not a twat, atleast not because of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all you shouldnt quote stats over their career since Sanchez spent a significant ammount of time being second to third to even fourth fiddle in Udineze and Barcelona as opposed to Cavani career in Palermo and Napoli where he was absolutely the first choice. And nothing I said was contradicting, it means saying two things opposite to eachother, stop using big words to make you feel smart because you dont know what they mean. Juventus is better than PSG but I understand your subjectivity, Napoli is probably on par with Monaco since Monaco is truly incredible this season. Fiorentina, Milan, Inter and Roma are definitely better than the rest of your league apart from Lyon, but I definitely reckon Roma could beat them. Back to my point, French league is definitely by a mile weaker than the PL, they let in more goals, so its pretty easier to make assumptions you are making based solely on stats. PL is a lot tougher league, harder to play, harder to score, but I reccomend watching a few Arsenal matches just to see what an impact he has.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 14:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forwards considers wingers aswell, and Cavanis playmaking is a lot worse compared to Alexis than is Alexis scoring compared to Cavani. Dont need to quote my words in a sarcastic manner i suppose, since you arent better than Seria A,BPL, Primera or Bundesliga and thats a fact. And you can disregard ranking when all it matters are rankings, and you are third in your own league. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 14:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China and the second best basketball league in the world have absolutely no correlation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 14:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao, "Its about winning" when his team is sitting in the third place of the weakest top 5 league. Sanchez is by far the better playmaker, not as consistent scorer cause he plays on the wing mostly, but all in all a tier above Cavani.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sleeping face </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 11:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, what he did to the kid is harsh. But I would just like to say, when I first heard it I couldnt believe all the fuss that had come out of it. It is probably cause I live in the Balkans and beating your kids is pretty much regular, but everyone I know has had marks like that atleast two or three times. Not saying it isnt wrong, just that cultures differ so much, that it would be considered meaningless here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 11:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id kill for Rondo back to the Celtics but it just wouldnt work. Apart from pick and pop/roll with Horford he would be useless in our constantly flowing offense. However if he decided to become playoff-Rondo, triple-double-Rondo, diving-between the-opponents-leg-for a-steal-Rondo, we would be able to use him, but not to his potential, and sticking Rondo in the second unit hurts my soul.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just finished watching it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 05:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watched three season in two and a half days, slept for a total of 5 hours cause I had to balance school and stuff and I am completely mesmerised. I cant remember when a character dying hit me more than the death of Charlie Skinner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My post was especially against the Wizard, no one is expecting us to beat the reigning champs in a seven game series, unles The Clinic goes on a shoulder dislocating rampage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean yeah, playoffs are a completely different ball game but if you arent afraid of team with a guy who can drop 40 on you almost any given night,  you either are stupid or have LeBron. I mean Smart/Bradley backcourt is ridicoulos(spellcheck hlp, not my first language) defensive-wise, so you can hide with switches ITs weakness especially when you have other fast and long defenders on the rest of the team such as Crowder and Brown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I get that is your list and im biased, but AB healthy means a stronger bench unit for us, which would run over the Wizards bench </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fight with dog checks out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im guessing this first quarter is a tribute to Pat McAfee with all the punting that has been happening so far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah we know, when someone isn't invisible its pretty fucking hard to not notice it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Three team trade, Carroll to the Cavs, Love to Boston and Canadas national treasure Kelly "The Clinic" Olynik goes back to his home country of Canada.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 07:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey its me ur charlotte </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess Johnny Mac really knows everything mate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesnt count, they have to be bros, these two are not supposed to be, yet they are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 12:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No he wont. Im praying with all i got, but no he fucking wont </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 12:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we please call it a draw and give the trophy to charity or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 11:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took his phone and laptop battery and charger, but I have to threathen him whenever he tries to come in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 11:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The key to Rafa winning is my brother watching the match with me. So obviously he has been banished to the bedroom, awaiting further commands.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 11:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roger surprises Rafa with his patented forehand whip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 11:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean "when he retires" you pagan???  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 10:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im fine with that exact outcome right here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 09:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cause you get more power on a 1HBH if you go cross-court cause that lets you get a full swing. He would have to shorten it and graze the ball to go down the line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 09:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the key to winnin a slam is a shit uniform? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How do video game makers emulate movements of three-dimensional geometric shapes such as cubes, balls, cones etc. in video games like minigolf, rocket league and such? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 23:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Federer. His odds are 2.00 as opposed to Rafas 1.8.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I'll be damned then, he is finally living up to his potential. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im guessing its his contract year?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 12:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if he retires after two?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do we always have to make a shitshow to find out who's the best even though it makes no virtual significance what so ever. Most of this sub will say Roger cause he is a religion, some will say Rafa, a few will say Djokovic, Judy Murray will say Andy, and the normal and objective people will say Gulbis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its 5 betwen Rog and Rafa, and 6 between Rog and Murray/Djokovic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rafa winning a long 5 setter in the semis, and going on to play Fed in the final. I feel like I have seen this before since my PTSD is kicking in again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because of Roger Federer. And Roger Federer isnt the GOAT because of Rafael Nadal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nadal playing a long 5 setter semi-final and Federer waiting in the final? This feels too much like '09 and I dont like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
