<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject163</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 06:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Join the military, no one will care about you then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Psychics of Reddit, how accurate are your readings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 06:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Psychics of Reddit, does this question catch you by surprise or did you see it coming? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 06:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does it hurt when you bite your tongue by accident but it doesn't hurt when you bite it on purpose? Now you're biting your tongue too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 05:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you're rich you can go from not shiny to shiny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 04:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly what I'm saying. Awesome. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pretty sure I know we can all figure out when rick and morty season 3 premieres. Right now they are airing rick and morty weekly starting from season 1 in consecutive order. Whenever season 2 ends later this year that's when season 3 will premiere. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm too lazy to do the episode count but if any of you want to do it go ahead and let's wait for greatness together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The drop in homicides is mainly accredited to former Mayor Rudy Giuliani. I personally got to witness how he cleaned up New York City first hand. That sudden drop in the 90s was all him. This also sent a lot of people to prison and made a lot of people in power rich.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I a bad parent or is my kid just a piece of shit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I'm 70 I want heroin in my life not out my life. Ok maybe 70 is too young. Maybe 80. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go vegan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My reaction just now. 
My wife's: "yea they have a baby together, you didn't know that?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 21:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly one year? She looks like she aged 12 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you close your eyes while listening to Oprah Winfrey talk she almost sounds like Whoopi Goldberg. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 06:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 19:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how the image it shows right now is a still from the video of Donald trump outside of Geno's steaks which is next to a Harley Davidson store which is a known hangout for KKK members and other white supremacists. Oh not too mention the sign that says "if you speak any other language other than English while on line, you will not be served." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 08:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Que? No English, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 08:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a slap in the face to the practicality of the scientific method because there's no way to tell if that rock is even 10 days old let alone whatever OP claims </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 06:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guys legs are so skinny I thought he was missing one but it's behind the bag he's holding. I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 06:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just keep smiling at them. They don't deserve negative energy. Let them keep being negative. God's sense of humor will take care of it all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should've died in 2012 when we had the chance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 20:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People call cops pigs but I think a more suitable name would be "insect" or "mosquito" because they are pesky as hell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 20:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 20:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shit you not I wanted to post something similar to this last night. If I post it now it will definitely seem like I'm copying smh. Hate when that happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 08:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the bike is...the silver surfer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix and chill isn't working as a pick up line? Be straight forward and tell her it's time for firestick and dick. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 08:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
