<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2991</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But where is my entertainment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chiron </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing! You offended me on seven different levels! 5/7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Run shirtless through a park singing cowboy songs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd be surprised on how many people don't know their basic rights.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true, thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kelvin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not answer the questions of police officers, unless you are being detained for something you did wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! Jokes on you I read it before checking my thumb! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The black parade up my ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think as long as you're learning, whatever works, works </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand how all my classmates run in three hours or so throughout the semester  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said college, not middle school... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Highly unusual indeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> College students, what unusual things have you done in order to keep your grades up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The new officer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One day the police dispatch received a phone call. On the phone was a lady who was screaming that an officer had just broken into their house and searched around. Confused by this the dispatcher tried to calm the lady down, which was unsuccessful, and she eventually hung up the phone. Not sure what to do they disregarded the call as either a prank or someone with a prejudice. 

However, as the weeks continued, they received more and more calls from various homes and companies all saying the same thing. An officer came in and searched the premise without any justification. 

Finally, they managed to ID this officer and sat him down to ask him some questions. First they asked him if he had been breaking into these different places, to which the officer replied, "Yes."

Aghast and confused by this they asked him why. The officer looked back and forth at them, then said, "Well I read it in the training manual. It said I had the ability to search any premise just 'cause." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good idea. Thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is appreciated  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ginger the baker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Once upon a time, in a very, very small town, there was a baker who was named Ginger. She was a very modest person, and not only was she humble, but also very soft spoken and kind. She was famous in the town for her baked goods, especially her cakes. 

One day she was experimenting and created a new cookie. So far, everyone loved it. Deciding that she wanted to add the cookie to her common sale items, she needed to name it. So she called the town together and had everyone try it.

Once everyone had sampled the delicious cookies and helped themselves to some complimentary  cake, Ginger walked up onto the stage and said, "I have asked you all to come here today to help me name this cookie. Any ideas?"

Someone called out, "What's in them?" 

She replied, "There is just the usual stuff, flour sugar and the likes and also some ginger, which is what gives it that special flavor!"

"So," the person continued, "there's ginger in it, and your name is Ginger, so we should recognize you on your creation and call them Ginger Cookies!"

Ginger was appalled by this notion and tried to fight against this idea saying, "I don't want my name anywhere in the title of the cookies!" 

However, the people were entrenched with this name and after a bit more of Ginger fighting against it, the crowd began to chant, "Ginger Cookies! Ginger Cookies! Ginger Cookies!"

Finally, enough was enough and, Ginger began to scream at the crowd angrily, while flipping tables everywhere!

The next morning, the headlines in the local paper read, "Ginger Snaps!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you find the spark in a relationship again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But there is snake in someone's boot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may have just started a war </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long have you waited for this moment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the dino might not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took me a second, but still Gross </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fred and Dory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two archeologists named Fred and Dory were down on the jungles of South America searching for ruins. Along with them they had eight laborers to help them with all of there equipment. 

One night the laborers were all around a campfire telling the legends of the jungles. One of these legends was the cannibals that would cut your feet off and save them to eat later as snacks. Later that night one of the laborers disappeared. 

As the the nights rolled on the laborers continued to disappear one by one. 

When there were only two laborers left Fred and Dory decided they needed to flee for their lives, but on their way back they stumbled onto a village. 

The village seemed normal enough. The natives were just going about there business. Fred and Dory were approached by one why gruffly said, "what name?"

In reply both Fred and Dory told them their names, as did the two remaining laborers. Then without hesitation the native struck down both of the laborers killing them instantly. Fred and Dory backed away with fear in their eyes, but they were soon surrounded and locked in cages. 

They both watched horrified as the natives cut off both of the laborers feet and then hung them to drain the blood out of their bodies. Then it was their turn. Fred and Dory were both killed and had their feet cut off. 

Later in the week, the natives were holding a celebratory feast, and each had their own pair of feet for a snack. One cannibal looks at another and says, "what you eat?" 

The other cannibal looks at him and says, "Dory toes."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But did we get all the letters right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a life-hack that you use commonly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who have pet squirrels?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So cats are evolving into white girls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: wonderbar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be your friend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That kid is like, I'm out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
