<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do Santa and Donald Trump have in common? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 05:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well whatever it is it doesn't matter because Santa doesn't actually exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 05:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got the joke, I just wanted to post a pun, regarding his incorrect spelling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 01:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of the star wars physics phrase, "Use the Mass Times Acceleration!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 22:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it, I guess I'll have to to wait untell the joke is reposted better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three men find themselves in heaven </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 09:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were all faithful/devoted Christians who donated large portions of their wealth's to charities, so they deserved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My wife is like the square root of pi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 06:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking hate her </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I went skydiving recently </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 05:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it was bundled with the Malaysia airlines ticket I bought.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm scared of ripped paper. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 07:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean tearrified  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 23:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deadpool joke theif, how dare you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The PC Genie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 10:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three travelers stumble upon a magically genie willing to grant them each one wish, but are warned there may be a catch if they don't wish carefully.

The first traveler, a middle-aged man walks up to the genie and says, "I wish for a beautiful wife who would love me for eternity." The man's wish is granted and a woman appears, the man runs off with his wish and starts making out with his new girlfriend. An hour passes and as the other two travelers think of their wishes, the man returns in an angrily fashion.

"WHAT GIVES, WHY'D YOU RUIN A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN YOU TWISTED FUCK?!?!"

"What's wrong?" replies the second traveler.

"My girlfriend, is actually a transgender boyfriend!"

The genie responds with a disappointed look, "look bro, you could've been more specific on your wish, it's 2016 and anyone can identify as a woman."

Using this new knowledge of wishes; the second traveler, a young woman in her 30s, asks for a white, strong, republican male, with the most beautiful glare. She's given a Jar of Mayonaise, and stares at the genie in confusion. "Pretty sure Mayonaise isn't a gender".

"Yeah but Tumblr says otherwise," replied the genie.

The last traveler, a young-man in his 20s, thinks carefully. He walks up to the genie and says, "I wish for a tall beautiful woman, she has to be born as 100% female, has to find me extremely attractive, and is not a jar of mayonaise. I wish to find her in my bed, waiting to make love to me tonight".

The next day and the traveler angrily runs up to the genie and screams at him. The two travelers ask the genie what the catch to his wish was, and the genie rolls his eyes and sighs. "I followed his wish entirely, it's not my fault he's racist and doesn't like African American women!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever tried eating a clock? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 03:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't, you're look very stupid trying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tonight I'm going with some KKK members, for a sacrifice ritual. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 20:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stalin and Hitler walk into a bar. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was a horrible thesis statement for my seven page research paper on WW2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow, this fucking troll joke XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did the black guy fail his math test? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 01:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 00:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horrible repost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 06:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/antijokes

this actually sounds funny from an antijoke perspective </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 06:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there should just be a *thud* after they ask, "what door?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did the duck cross the road? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 06:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waiter:"I don't know and I don't care, how exactly do you plan to pay for the meal you just bought Mr.Chicken?" 

Chicken:"Just put it on my bill."

Waiter:"You don't have a bill..."

Chicken:"No bill? oh you shouldn't have, I'll see myself out!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A good antijoke I read here once </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 05:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shit I forgot what it was... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 08:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buzz Lightyear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Trump as president, women may have to wait for equal rights... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 08:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but look on the upside women, you won't have to enter the next US draft for WW3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 07:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy shit, this is just genius </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A man walks into a bar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 05:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He leaves because it's very busy due to the fucking election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 07:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No fucking way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 07:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this isn't an antijoke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 07:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd expect her to be screaming instead of just pounding a door. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girl, you gotta be tired coz you been runnin through my mind all day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 07:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note to self, stop saying that pickup lines to the girls in wheelchairs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I farted in an apple store once </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 18:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was one of those loud farts, I think I sharted a bit, but I know for sure it smelled. Anyways my manager gave me a suspension.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 18:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then your title should say Virginity not virginity  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did you hear the man who got his left arm and left leg cutoff? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 05:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, you didn't hear? He was screaming from the pain for four hours straight at 2 a.m. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did you hear about Donald Trump's new book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 03:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called Mein Kampf is bigger than your Kampf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did the black guy say to the other black guy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 08:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey jim </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've lost interest in dating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 08:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I decided to tell my therapist that archaeology just wasn't my thing anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many mathematicians does it take to change a lightbulb? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 07:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see there's a lot of them changing it currently, but I don't know how to count. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favorite Vampire Joke from this thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 05:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 vampires are having a competition to prove who's the most vicious vampire among them.
The strongest one started 1st, "watch this," He said as he flies so fast, about 100 miles/hour. After only 10 minutes, he comes back with blood all over his mouth. "what happened?" they asked. "did you see that house over there?" "yes?" "well.. I killed the entire family and sucked the blood dry!" "wow!? fascinating, as expected from the strongest vampire" Then the eldest one takes the next turn "watch and learn," he said as he flies even faster, about 120 miles/hour. After only 5 minutes, he comes back with blood all over his mouth and his neck. "what happened??" they asked. "did you see that village over there?" "ye..yes?" "well.. I killed every last person on that village and sucked the blood dry!" "wow!? magnificent! truly amazing, we can expect no less from the eldest one!" Finally the last turn belongs to the fastest one, "don't blink or you'll miss it" he said as he flies really fast, even faster than the other two, about 140 miles/hour. After only a mere 30 seconds, he comes back with blood all over his mouth, his neck, and his nose. "wh..what happened???" they asked. "did you see that big ass tree over there?" "ye..yes?!" "well.. I didn't" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My ex-girlfriend is like pi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 06:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking hate my ex-girlfriend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's these two clowns that just keep popping up on the television. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 02:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit that's not a television it's my window! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you call a ghost without any feet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 08:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lost sole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the key to a woman's heart? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 07:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sharp flesh cutting knives </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Jews walk into a bank </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 08:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oops wrong bank," said the Two Jews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girl I think you really have a career as a makeup artist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 07:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> said the Abusive Father </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I decided to ask a girl out with a carrier pigeon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 06:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She said no, then her pigeon pooped on my shoulder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
