<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2482</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Average pay for an engraver is $62,011...not awful.

In the D.C. area?  That's near poverty level.  Seriously.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Protip: Call Centurylink and ask to speak to littlebabykush </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy sarcasms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flat soda!  I purposely take the carbonation out of my soda...and I've never found anyone that doesn't think that's disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something you enjoy that you noticed no one else seems to enjoy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy Sciences! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that even legal? 

Have you checked with a Bird Lawyer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is the lighting on people's faces in their helmets!

Gah, drives me crazy.  I get it...it's a movie and we need to see the actor's faces....but seeing the *inside* of someone's helmet lit up like car headlights just breaks my immersion immediately.  How do they even see outside the helmet, the inside is lit up so much!  (example would be how hard it is to see outside your car if the dome light is on while you're driving)

Very rarely, a movie gets this right, and the inside of the helmet is dark or very modestly lit.

Bonus non-subject pet peeve:
When it's dark....shining flashlights in people's faces as they deliver their line in any movie whatsoever. 
No one would put up with that in real life.  Especially the movies where the actor just keeps their eyes wide open as they speak with a flashlight on their face. Ummm, no.  You'd be "Get that out of my face!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your biggest pet peeve in sci-fi movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be amazing if Tim Curry had a cameo in this movie.  Anything really....even just a passing shot of him as a janitor mopping a floor.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's the thing...even after you cut some of the finger off, it kept coming out.  

That story messed me up too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm, no.  

[http://www.scottaaronson.com/blog/?p=1858](http://www.scottaaronson.com/blog/?p=1858)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's Turing when you need him? Watch out folks, we've got an AI here!

You had one job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 01:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found G.R.R.M.'s Reddit handle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to type these exact words.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wondered, since I have always said "I feel like a million bucks!" whenever I feel great...

Do billionaires say that when they are feeling super bad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would take them nearly 32 thousand years to count to a trillion, if they said one number every second without a break.

Heck, even to count to just 1 billion with that same method, it would take nearly 32 years.

Factoring one third of your life sleeping and one third of your life doing other things, if you counted for 8 hours a day, it would take you nearly 96 years to count to a billion in that way. 

So, pretty safe to say you'll never say all the numbers to a billion, much less a trillion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As opposed to.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean...homeless and valedictorian are not mutually exclusive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're doing thrusting wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indecent exposure seems like a slam dunk in that case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found Shel Silverstein. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You act like people would still be going to work to produce all this food, and distribute it...while the world goes to hell everywhere else?  

It would only take the first few lootings of grocery stores...murders over food...people would turtle up in their homes, not go to work...no ones out making your Big Mac then, are they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an absolutely horrible question to ask, and I can guarantee you won't get the job.

Source: I'm HR, and sit in on dozens of interviews a week.  

You might think this is a clever question to ask, and it might be, but the interview panel looks at this question as you bullying them.  It's a VERY passive-aggressive way of putting the panel on the spot and basically saying "Tell me right now why you're not going to hire me...and if you don't have an answer, I've obviously got the job already"

We get this question once or twice a week from a candidate...and every single time we get it, the interview panel (always different people) takes tremendous umbrage with it.  The discussions after the interviews ALWAYS include how that specific follow-up question really put them off the candidate.

It's not a good idea, just don't do it.

A MUCH better alternative would be to confident statement as to how you think that you would be a perfect fit for the position, and that you think you fulfill all the qualifications, and leave it at that.  But don't put the panel on-the-spot by asking for interview feedback during the interview like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would want the power to know where anything is, just by concentrating on it.

This could be as mundane as "Where is Mike's remote control right now."...oh, it's behind his dresser.

...or as profitable as "Where is the closest cache of unclaimed cash of least $50 to me?"...oh, there's an altoids tin of $80 buried 2 feet underground a few blocks over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What obscure   not common Super Power would you want the most? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh sure, no argument here, always go to court.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an amazing picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is completely false.  Any traffic cop that is issuing tickets has 1 or 2 days set aside in their schedule per month to simply attend court for the tickets they have written.

You think the date that you are assigned to show up in court from the ticket you got is random?  Nope...that's the date that the cop already has scheduled to be in court already.

Granted, the cop MAY miss the day in court due to something unforeseen (like being sick, or a family emergency)...but the odds of that are of course very low.

Rest assured, the cop will be in court on the same day you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are duck sized horses, not duck sized pegasi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a police cruiser is speeding on the highway without their lights on, could I keep pace with them at a respectable distance and be immune from speeding, since they would have to admit they broke speeding laws too? (Assuming I had a dash cam to capture their actions) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be doubly fair...bigly is an adverb, and Trump uses it almost exclusively as an adjective.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, he does have the authority.  
A simple google search shows that it's pretty unprecedented, but not outside the realm of what he could do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep waiting to hear the news...
"Trump fires FBI Director."

It makes me LOL, because only Trump would think that would be a good idea.

"No person, no problem." - Stalin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Co-worker supports Trump.  I made a joke a couple months ago mocking the word "bigly", and he jumped all over me saying Trump said "Big league", not Bigly.

I told him, actually, no, it's in the White House transcripts themselves, that Trump said Bigly, not Big League.

It was pretty fascinating watching in almost slow motion as my co-worker pivoted to then DEFEND the word Bigly.  

I understand now how cults are a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I'd feel bad for him, if he hadn't already sold his soul for the job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...as his blind son replied, "Still not funny, Dad." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Millions of people would die in SK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Alternative Fact](https://www.reddit.com/r/Jokes/comments/3ynope/my_4_year_old_son_just_got_me_with_a_dad_joke_i/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Soviet Russia, Mars Missions volunteer you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Reindeer are the Drow of the real world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a lot less dark than I was expecting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but is this article Deputy Director Bullocks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy studies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to your profile when I looked you up, you two have been broken up for 2.5324 years.  But, who's counting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  e request to any 3rd parties that they have passed the data to. The fines for non-compliance are rather large.

Yeah...because the average citizen is able to afford representation to actually research and file suit against large organizations making sure they follow the rules. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that my confusion lie in the way he stated it.

If he'd said "The Air Force is the smallest it's been during it's entire existence."...that would make sense and be instantly understandable.

But the way he said it, by saying it's the smallest it's been since 1947...really makes it sound like he (or whomever gave him the information) looked at a graph and saw only lower numbers prior to 1947...not realizing that the AF wasn't even established then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, that makes a ton of sense to me.  

Even when the pres talked about the Navy not having this few of ships since WWI....Ummm, you mean when we were pumping them out of the shipyards as fast as the rivets could cool down, because we were having ships sunk DAILY?  

That was an Age of Attrition.  You counted engagements in terms of tons of steel sunk.  I mean, my god, TON OF STEEL sunk.  It was purely attrition.  

A single (prepared) ship from today's era could probably destroy an entire fleet from the WWII days...all without the enemy fleet even knowing where the ship was.  

Technology and advancements mean that Numbers such that the President fear-mongers upon are not as relevant a metric as they once were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: The U.S. President just said in his Weekly Address that the U.S. Air Force is the smallest it's been since 1947. How is that possible since the AF was established in 1947? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes sense!  Wow!  No wonder Trump is taking credit for things that he couldn't have had any influence over.  It all makes sense now...time travel... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa, that was an Inception level diversion. Well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deleted
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...meanwhile, studies show that men have never received a compliment from a woman, ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Someone just watched Sci Show in the shower, apparently.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9aoTr9CbHew app) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This so much.

That video did nothing to help me understand how big space is...and everything to help me understand how slow the speed of light is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if it was no coincidence that Obama relaxed wiretapping rules from U.S. Intel agencies right before he left office...
...like, he set the Intel agencies up to be able to catch  the Trump administration in its selling out of America.

If so, Former President Obama, you are the mf-ing man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sort of the same either way, no?

Knowingly, then the current cabinet knows about the Russians interference.

Unknowingly, then the current cabinet didn't know about Russian interference.

Either way....Russian interference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 03:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not, since the next episode isn't until 4 March, and there will be much more material to pull from by then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you paid for something like that...it's what they used to put the body in when it went in for incineration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you take the Dam Tour? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All mental illness is not created equally.

Often, especially do to prolonged alcohol use, mental illness can affect the addict.  That's sort of a "self-caused" mental illness...was completely preventable, and can be a source of bitterness for the addicts' family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Severe alcoholism isn't much different from person to person.  

Different songs, but the beat remains the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
