<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a study found that the costs of switching to clean energy from fossil fuels would be more than offset by the savings in reduced premature deaths from reduced air pollution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 13:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MA House approves bill limiting non-compete agreements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 13:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 13:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fact, Fusion  one of the media companies that had access to [the leaked Panama Papers] documents  demonstrated on video that one of its collaborators was able to form a Delaware shell company for her cat. This took only a few minutes, US$249 (via credit card) and required no identification documents at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL you can create a shell company for your cat in Delaware </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 13:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 20:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I think the point of the article is that it would be better to have a middle-class in academia instead of aristocracy and serfs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 20:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did keep files on just about anyone who was at all involved in civil rights activism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it time to eliminate tenure for professors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 13:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 18:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point.  Mea culpa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 13:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Combining the National Labor Surveys IQ data with the hair color information from the same group of teenagers provides the ability to answer the question: are blondes actually dumb?
The surprising answer  at least given the prevalent stereotype  is that among white women, those reporting having blonde hair have the highest average IQ and the second-highest median, or midpoint, IQ. Plus both the mean and median are above 100, which is the value given to a person who has exactly average intelligence.

And before you mock the government for asking about hair color:
The NLS asks questions that, when taken out of context, may seem extremely strange. For instance, in one multiyear survey, the NLS repeatedly asks about a persons weight and height. Given that most people dont grow in height after their teenage years, asking respondents to state their height well into their late 20s is unusual.
Why does the government need to know this kind of information? Since the survey goes back to reinterview the same people over and over again, it is important to make sure the right person is interviewed. Many respondents are provided with a stipend to provide an incentive to answer the survey for the 10th or 20th time. To ensure the correct respondent participates, instead of a brother, sister or roommate, it is very helpful if the interviewer knows someones height, weight, eye or hair color.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL government data proves blondes are slightly smarter than average </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 13:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why it's easier to be prescribed opioids than suboxonoe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 21:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 13:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in 1240, Robert Grosseteste, the bishop of Lincoln, used Oxford University money to launch the first documented student loan system. He named it St. Frideswides Chest. St. Frideswides Chest was literally a chest. Bound by two different locks, with each key held by a different college magister, or faculty member, it resided at St. Frideswides Priory, a religious house in central Oxford, amid the citys colleges, academic halls and student apartments.


For 300 years, the loan chest system thrived. Then, one evening in early March of 1544, two men  Robert Raunce and John Stanshaw  armed with an iron bar and hammer, broke into the congregation house and smashed all of the loan chests. Although Raunce and Stanshaw were eventually tried and sentenced, their burglary still managed to wipe out much of the chests' wealth.

Edit: rereading my post, I meant that the books were stored in the chest, not the loans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL in the Middle Ages, student loans used books as collateral and they were stored in a chest; the system worked for 300 years until thieves broke into the chest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 13:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The backwards history of attitudes toward public breastfeeding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 23:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 19:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The author shouts out to this sub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meta] Why some people get frissons and some don't </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 19:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Long History Behind the Reburial of Kennewick Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 19:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An app originally for the blind could get you more precisely to a bus stop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 17:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 03:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I counted the number on this disambiguation page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
