<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2519</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a Soviet dragunov sniper used by the guy who killed the Crown Prince-wasn't made until the early 1960's in real life  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calling all gaming Youtubers! Is TGN offering to partner with me a scam!? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 07:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I recently received a post on my channel from some guy on TGN asking to email about signing up with them. Now I started my YouTube channel on Monday and have 198 subs. One video has 9k views and the other has 1k. (The 9000 one is giving to be featured on Kotaku but I digress). One of my videos is actually a podcast that has a tiny bit about gaming but is mostly about politics. This is the video he left the comment on (why I am skeptical) 

Anyway is this guy trying to scam me? If anyone has partnered with TGN can you tell me what it was like?

Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 07:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do the 2nd day thing too-sometimes I'm basically falling asleep but a couple km in and by the last couple I feel good-tiredness hits me like a train when I get out of the shower though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that could be it. Since I've got it I find the newer the game the better it looked (e.g. BF1 looks 10x better than BF4 and not because it's newer) a shame because the art style is great on this game and some of the scenery is great. Oh well it's the gameplay that matters most </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breath of the Wild on Wii U not looking great in my 32 inch smart television (sitting about 1.5m away) anyone else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 04:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So up close the models look good and everything but often texture look fuzzy and ugly during the day. Lines on ladders blur and fuzz as does the outline around grass. Now my TV is good an Horizon Zero Dawn has looked incredible on it. Parts of the graphics look like how my TV display PS3 games - should I just put it down to the Wii U being an old system? Anyone else having this problem ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hitler didn't place an emphasis on the A-bomb. I remember listened to the head nuclear scientist working on the Nazi bomb who said they didn't really have adequate resources and were nowhere near actually creating their own bomb  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually love seeing the Witcher's little influences throughout the game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For weights I'd say weight till they feel better-if this were running I'd say not fine to go back as long as it's just an ache  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 07:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me it's nothing like Just Cause. I've played it you haven't take it from me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a hunting game and it's pretty dark in a lot of places. The gadgets are futuristic but in no way does it resemble ratchet and clank.

Think Witcher, Farcry and Tomb Raider mash up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah but he's a watcher they are loners by nature. The others are part of a herd  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Perfect Hunt in Horizon: Zero Dawn (using tripwires-best thing I've done in the game) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahaha omg amazing!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A war criminal in any other country but let's make jokes with him! Only doomed the Middle East for the next few decades!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched it about 5 times when I did it felt so awesome  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am Rost and you are child Aloy-one day you'll be the master  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bomb behind them in the centre-try not to hit them with it just scare them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I not merciful!!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A perfect blend of tripwires and a stampede (no spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am really enjoying Horizon why does this have to come out this week!?

I am gunna buy Ghost Recon and Mass Effect too, open world overload. Shame my dissertation is in for the start of May no time to play all these  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Mercy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 09:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not going down without a fight! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 06:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's totally fine don't worry about it-pretty much everyone does this but they just don't say it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 21:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel this type of opening has been lost in games. Reminds me of AC 3-slow build up for character development is always okay in my book  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 13:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How bad is it? My girlfriend is pretty messy but her room is dirty if you get my meaning. It's just clothes and books rather than dirty plates and shit - how bad are you? 

Like your boyfriend I'm pretty tidy but it doesn't always bother me when someone isn't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cod 3 has a quite substantial section for the Canadians in the campaign  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tommy gun please! I mean it's not secret but was created for the war but never used  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calm your tits you can buy it whenever you want crybaby, season pass just means you get it earlier and he overall price is less  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since we get Gallipoli hopefully getting a d-day type/beachhead assault variant on a game mode! Disappointed we aren't getting any maps in central/west/east Africa though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 07:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know why you moved in together after 4 months </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I know 5 people who have gotten pregnant while on the pill in the last year (not using a condom) but you didn't do it properly in her so you should be fine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thumbnail sort of says it all 

-Trying to put Pewdiepie comments in a broader context and why it is genuinely bad he said what he did.

-Talking about the history of Iraq and how it led to the rise or ISIS

-Comparing Saudi Arabia and Iran and debating which one is really worse than the other  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Politics) (SFW) The Kavernacle episode one! Generally talking about all these things in a historical context-first episode so feedback appreciated! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure Bosnians would disagree  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking psychos both of you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping they ditch the Arkham-ness and go for a Witcher style full open world Middle Earth - I can only dream  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but come on Platoon came out in 1986 and was hardly a glowing portrayal of US troops - rape, murder, racism all were in the film. Vietnam started 61 and a bit years ago surely they could tackle it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say they felt robotic I really enjoyed the NPC convos and stuff and the detail in workplaces was great but I agree due to the city nature not as much room for randomness that's found in the woods  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think its just meant to be a funny play on words  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'So far, weve just seen Chloe as this attractive lady and femme fatale that doesnt need more than a couple minutes alone with Nathan to seduce him.'

So for the one and a half games of the two games she is in she isn't fawning after Drake (she basically says fuck you in the middle of 2 and doesn't care in 3) but we still describe as a femme fatale because they have one seen of intimacy? Too me she has always come across as funny and witty with way more drive for the criminal life than people like Drake    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^this is a dangerous way to think. Although there were many who didn't agree with it but just tried to survive, painting all of them as ignorant to what was going on is wrong. And 'fascism thing to blow over' you know they called it the '1000 year Reich' and if the war was handled better by the Nazi's it could have lasted way longer than it did. People not rebelling is how you get fascism in the first place and being a willing part of the machine helps them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I wasn't saying that. Just your first paragraph where you talk about how great your dad is too you is kinda undone by how racist and horrible he is in general. I was just trying to make the point even Nazi's loved their families doesn't mean they were good  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad is a Nazi but he still is a great guy because he loves his family... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it was just the nudes fair enough but being concerned about an adult having sex before marriage is fucking ridiculous  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone has premarital sex now, and nearly everyone sends nudes.

Fuck your upbringing and fuck your conservative beliefs she is 25 she can do what the hell she likes with her boyfriend. She isn't a child you shouldn't have any say on how she lives her life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MGS6-I think they could make a really interesting game set in the Vietnam War... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've read the lore of MGS and apparently Big Boss did multiple missions in Vietnam but wasn't this stated on the box art/guide of the original? Which said a number of things that were ret-conned? Anyway doesn't matter.

You could set in in Summer 1968 (think that fits in well between 1964 and Portable ops in 1970) and Snake is convinced by the CIA to rejoin the military in some capacity under his old boss the Major. It could be some sort of mechanised nuclear launch is being tested in Vietnam (or border territories) and Snake has to investigate.

I think they could do something really cool with the open world here. You could have Army bases stand in for 'Mother Base' and maybe carry out certain upgrades. You could drive vehicles from the base and generally interact with the people stationed there. From here you could go out into the world and you could come across civilians, GI's and VC. There could be sporadic battles between the US and NVA/VC that occur when your roaming the countryside. 

I think they could show something that really puts Snake at odds with the US military-maybe he's sees an event similar to the My Lai massacre that further cements his distaste for the US. Maybe their could be a brutal group of US soldiers he could go up against? 

For characters I'd like to see the return of the MGS3 cast, with EVA making a return especially. I am not sure who the villain but they could delve into Vietnamese mysticism to invent some cool bosses.

What do you guys think? A setting that would suit a new MGS?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fine, don't get hung up on it but don't put her through that. She was willing to let you mourn your old relationship-trust me most girls would never do that-but if for some reason you get annoyed by little things don't stay with her   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see your point but sometimes you have to take the good with the bad. Churchill inspired the British to fight on and never give up - if they had the whole of western Europe would have been conquered and America may have never entered the war with the Nazi's. so in a way he could have saved us all from Nazism  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Debatable. He didn't fire on Russian soldiers but whether that would have started a new world war is unlikely  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is saying fictional Jesus from the bible didn't 'save the world' because he 'died for our sins'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would they not be people ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah Persia never invaded Spain and 'saved' is a weird word here. Also the Ottomans did eventually invade Europe - wasn't the end of the world  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big Boss saves the world about 3 times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay how about someone says-'kid come to my car there is candy there' walks off with him instead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thing happened to me when I was 16. Been going out a year and a half. Suddenly we go on a break-6 months later we need to talk, she ends with me because she feels too young to be in a serious relationship:

2 months later she's going out with my best mate. Sometimes it you feel the reason is bullshit there is something else hidden behind it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound like an asshole judging by what your 'concerns' are. Break it off with her she can do better  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It genuinely sounds like she might have a mental problem. The one you said about milk is a massive red flag-it's a basic task I'd expect my 12 year old cousin to be able to do. Maybe she has anxiety at the very least?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about if the kids goes up to someone mentally unstable and they run off with him!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when people used to say it without meaning sex  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PlayStation just gets it-look at the last 3 E3 conferences (especially 2016) just reveal amazing games without all the sponsored bullcrap or cringey sequences. Xbox is irrelevant as a console - why would you even buy one anymore? You can play all the exclusives on PC anyway.

When anyone asked me which console to buy (I own both) not question in my mind PS4 is the only one worth buying.

Games coming out for PS4 not for Xbox 

Horizon
Spider-Man 
God of War
Uncharted Lost Legacy 
Nier
The Last of Us 2 

Not to mention all the games that have come out only for PlayStation in the last 3 years  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In your title you say you want to increase 'running stamina' - best way to do this is from running I'm afraid. If you just want to look good leg weights and cycling are good  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 08:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Battlefield one is simpler, leads annoying and more fun-having experienced any glitches on PS4. New DLC adds four more maps, new mode, new vehicles, new weapons, a new faction and two new operations  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 01:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not ever stretching my hamstring and it getting destroyed playing soccer - out for 3 months feels like it'll never be the same.

If you do a lot of cardio and a sport make sure to stretch it properly ! Don't do what I did  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 05:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the end of the day he wants to talk to you so don't feel like your being a pain or an annoyance. Just play it cool and casual and don't be scared to approach him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just remember you still very young and she has matured quick having two 20 year + kids probably makes her way more mature than you. I'd say find someone your own age and experience a good relationship from the start together - otherwise you might end up being unhappy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girls birthdays normally last a week anyway just do something special on another day it's not a big problem hate people who think their bdays mean you should drop everything to be with them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel your pain hopefully he becomes an atheist someday - it so much better when you can all laugh at religion together  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a similar thing when I was like 13 just tell yourself your being stupid worked for me eventually  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have mates who are way younger and have had way more don't feel too bad - that being said they always lie when someone asks haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some straight Hindu magic from the medic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they could do it with a couple people but depends if you want to incorporate Frank Underwood and Urquhart together - Colin Firth could be okay I guess, Damian Lewis could be another one? If you want the same powerful performance as Spacey and not a more devious once then perhaps Christian Bale? I think Jude Law would make a really good FU after seeing the Young Pope  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree Corbyn is more of a socialist and their is still a huge Blairite faction in the party-Corbyn has welcomed back in the far left elements but all I'm saying is that Corbyn and Cameron wouldn't be in the same party in England and Centre-left Labour MP's are still way more left than most Democrats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game isn't bad - it's a 7/10 - fun shooting, fun driving, great music and great setting-abit repetitive but if you can move past it it's good. If you love the 60's it's a must buy tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> M1 Garand is a beastly weapon on hard difficulty - will even put down most heavy's in a single shot.

The game isn't perfect but there is something about the fun shooting, great music and really cool setting that makes it addicting. If you ever get bored take a break for a week and come back-I'm so glad I did this when it released because I loved it when I returned  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Started new game for the first time since October... have patches made the game look better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So everyone knows this games looks pretty nice at night but lately I've been finding really nice graphics and sunsets in the day - have they added a patch that improves the graphics or am I wrong and it looks the same?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^or play it for fun? Don't people do that with every nerds wet dream Overwatch?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 00:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actors from three great shows: Fargo, Narcos and American Crime Story!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 07:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting to hear your opinions on religion as a man made thing? Do you not believe in any of them? You have renounced Christianity but could you believe in Judaism? 

Anyway good on you for realising hope it's not too hard to tell people ! Come to England where every young person is basically and atheist or agnostic!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 07:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's okay unless for special circumstances.

I've supported United forever but I always used to go and watch Brentford locally. They used to be in the old Division 3 (now League 2) so I though it was fine. In 2015 they were in the Championship play offs and are still in the Championship. One day they might play United but can't help I support both now and I never thought they could play eachother when I began supporting. 

I think if you support top European teams that compete with eachother (Bayern, Barca,Juve, Madrid etc) I find that a bit strange since you don't have any real attachment to them and they compete with eachother for the Champions League. You can defo like different teams a lot (I really admire Athelitco) but don't feel you can properly support multiple teams with good reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 07:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because if you were alive in the 1940's there was no way in hell you could be good looking! And if you were English it made far more unlikey! 

And the lead is at least in his last twenties  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 07:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that the Conservatives of the 90's were extremely similar to the Democrats of today, the two parties have more in common than one might think. The ideas of the Labour Party especially today do not see eye to eye with the Democrats of today. The Conservative Party in Britain right now is the closest thing to the American democrats.

In my opinion Democrats have too many ideologies under one roof - can't have basically Republicans posing as Democrats and people like Bernie Sanders in one party. In Britain you don't get that problem as much because of multiple prominent parties so people like Corbyn don't end up in the same party as Boris Johnson    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you do a lot of exercise then you might be okay for now but I'd think seriously about cutting down. I too drink soft drinks often but trust me add more water or squash and stuff and your body feels a lot better plus you must be spending a tonne of money if soft drinks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 17:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5 litres of soda a day!? Seriously you should definitely stop and switch to Zero/Diet while your at it-are you overweight by any chance?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 08:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know going to parties when your 17/18 is part of growing up. He's seems like a good guy learning a trade and saving up money. You being way too protective and if she loves him why would she care what you think? Trust me I'm in my last year of uni and have had a gf since he start of year 12 it hasn't affected my studies one bit. And I hardly think anyone feels they are a big shot when wearing a high-vis jacket!? Just back off.

And 5'3 and 5'7 is this a family of dwarf men lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have been a irresponsible parent in this case. Accept and learn from it your wife has very right to be mad at you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this thread your saving is more predatory than anything else. You are targeting young vulnerable girls and making them way worse of. I'm sorry but you really have to re-evaluate who you treat women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your ex is Ross Gellar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would Spain have been ethnically cleansed in general? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have been doing 1500's Spain at university. They have their own ethnic cleansing programs in regard to 'converso's', descendants of Jews and Muslims who converted to Christianity. While a final solution was considered for both (and the Moriscos were expelled in 1609) I was generally thinking about the way the rest of Europe view Spain in this period. A lot of them didn't actually consider them to be white. They thought they definitely had Jewish and Muslim 'blood' and that's why they had darker hair and were more coloured than the rest of Europe. Weirdly in a lot of Protestant propaganda they were pretty racist to the Spanish. I know Franco and Hitler were somewhat allied, but does anyone think the Nazi's would ethnically cleanse Spanish people in general? Or would they just accept they were white like people in South America?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AC3 had a bad ending!? Have you played Unity and Syndicate!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah it's a tough one-one of my ex gf's did that to me-I guess if you want to be happy do it. But be honest with ur bf don't give him some bullshit excuse and tell him you fallen for someone else because that's what I wish my ex said to me when she ended it. It will hurt him but honesty is better  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you guys done anything and taking it further or you just like him?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Owned bitch! You deserved it !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have the stigmata!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Become atheist and accept the inevitability of death and then you will not worry about the future anymore  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long have you known the other guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Childish' you are 20 years older than her you know?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound like a bit of a cunt tbf  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Magic mods crash the game a lot more on Xbox One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wanted to tell people if they are having problems with the game crashing on Xbox One-I used to use all these new modded spells and the game would crash every 40 mins-recently uninstalled them and game never crashes, just thought I point it out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a bit more hung up on Platoon as I feel FMJ doesn't really convey the horror of war as well. I liked the characters but they were quite one dimensional. Platoon really made you think how scary and hard it must have been to fight in Vietnam and I like that it conveys the 1 year tour of duty where everyone is counting down the days until they can leave. Both are good but Platoon captures the humanity, or lack of it, in war. FMJ is pretty surreal in comparison I think it's trying to show the madness of war more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you see ArsenalFanTv have uploaded a new video after losing 5-1... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 01:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else find it pretty amazing the US entered World War 1? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 01:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've in the past studied 19th century America and Great Britain and if you look about 15 years before the war you would never think the USA would intervene directly in a largely European war. I know the Zimmerman telegram urged Mexico to invade the US and open up a new front but other than this was there any direct threat to the US? Is it true they largely fought to preserve foreign democracies? Was American exceptionalism most prevalent in this war? As on the surface it seems they are doing what they always said/have said since, they are fighting to maintain foreign democracies (literally fight for freedom)-is there any cynical view to their role in the war like there sometimes is with when they joined WW2?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a very hard question to answer but in short: guerillas were hard to defeat, will of Hanoi was unbreakable and as it was a totalitarian state it didn't have any pressure on it to stop the war. The revisionist view is that politicians didn't do what was necessary and a lot of US generals belief they weren't allowed to do what was necessary and popular pressure forced them to back off-all of these are debatable.

The South Vietnamese Army didn't perform very well overall throughout the war and its government was extremely corrupt. Many Vietnamese just never wanted to go back to being controlled by another country from China, the French, the Japanese then back to the French then a US backed southern state. It's really complex so you probably have to read a couple book and stuff but hope this points you in the right direction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would David Cameron be as welcoming to Donald Trump as Theresa May if he was still PM? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do Rebels say to each other 'may the force be with you' ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was re-watching Rogue One a couple of weeks ago and Jynn said it as they were about to depart for Scariff. Now I can understand this because of her mother believing in the Force. But I'm pretty sure people like Mon Motha and others say it in the original movies. The same Mom Motha who doesn't really know who Obi-Wan is when she speaks to Bail on Yavin 4. Now the Republic didn't explicitly believe in the Force or the Jedi. The Jedi protected the Republic but were shrouded in secrecy-it is probably doubtful a lot of the rebel leaders believed in it before the Empire-so why does the rebellion begin to symbolise believing in the Force and resisting the Empire ? Even if you could say they started when Luke joined them, wouldn't a lot still be skeptics like Han was? Is there any books or something I can check out?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I guess but a lot of the time Disney cartoons satirised the Nazi's-making someone hold a sign saying death to all Jews isn't satire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it was just UK countries like India had their own stats-yeah I know that but it's just I didn't think the home islands played as big a role as they did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After finding out he fought in the Solomon Islands and saw the A-bomb go off I really hated him. Kinda liked him before but cannot forgive a guy who turned on his country after seeing what both of its enemies were capable of  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original had a better score  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people that do weights are pretty vain  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disney cuts ties with pewdiepie after videos containing Nazi slogans and imagery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 05:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The core of the UK army was well trained professionals. As an island they didn't really need a massive army and across their empire they recruited locally  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep that's it^

And ah that bad, but yeah I guess they were lead by the white British but supplemented by the Indians, Gurka's etc  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the order would go AmericaBritainCanada. I'm English but I know we couldn't have won the war with the Americans - couldn't have invaded France without them, and probably couldn't have put enough pressure on Japan to stop advancing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> US had two didn't they? Omaha and Utah. But yeah I forgot Britain had another. Yeah the British did fight the Japanese but they used a lot of their Indian and Asian troops too who are out in different countries for casualties that's why I was surprised  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm English too and that's why I find it so surprising although I shouldn't. I live in London and go uni in Southampton, there are so many war memorials literally everywhere - I guess it took most of the fit young men away from each town in a way that probably didn't happen in the States </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British casualties in WW2 were way closer to the US than I thought! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So just looked up the casualties figures for WW2 by country. I cannot believe the British nearly had the same number of deaths and more injured than the Americans - considering the larger scale of American engagements particularly later in the war- (two beaches on D-Day, Iwo Jima, Peleliu, Okinawa). Am I a noob for not knowing this or is this surprising to anyone else? I know the British lost a lot in 1940 during the Battle of Britain and retreat from France, and they lost a lot in Market Garden but didn't think it was on this scale.

^This Isn't the British Empire it's just for the UK.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I totally see your point and you make a good argument about the way the American tanks were easier to make and maintain. My point really was that the Nazi's created stuff that was ahead of heir time and the best in certain respects - but this didn't translate to success on the battlefield  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the best answer I've seen so thanks a lot ! Some of the stuff you said I did know (probably should have included) - I knew the Americans were generally the most advanced but I was citing the examples I believe the Nazi's were more advanced although this isn't to say I think their inventions made a difference. My point with things like the V2 were that they were the first to make a working rocket/ground based missile regardless if it was effective or not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
