<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject381</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I tag switched to Japan.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well Russia, if you want to. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does this keep happening? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crimea is rightful Russian land </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like you sit in a room fapping all day by the way you said it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

Do you like history? Because that's pretty much the only thing I have an interest in.

 I am an avid collector of  music by the Red Army Choir or other music preferably made by some authoritarian state.

I am also a bisexual male.

I am also a Slav (Pole, have a massive hatred for south Slavs) who doesnt know how to speak any Slavic languages but can speak German, quote ironic, huh?

I am also a gamer, although I almost exclusively play Europa universalises 4, Hearts of iron 4, Victoria 2, and eve online.

I am 100% serious, really I spent my whole childhood talking to old people, I have no idea what popular culture is anymore. 


My life is horrible.

PM if interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely solo fascist America. You get to chose who you attack, only country that could possibly attack you is the Soviet Union, you get to do whatever you want while being the strongest power eventually. Don't have to fight in the pacific at all, instead to Caribbean theater, invade Germany eventually. Operation sea lion though faroe islands.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Nor Latvia, Estonia, or Lithuania. Or Finland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the mittleafrika story? (Other an Goring being leader) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me Britain is so much easier to invade as than japan even as the U.S. what I do is go through north Atlantic islands except Iceland, which is normally garrisoned a ton. Get to faroe islands, build airbase and invade Scotland 
+10 points for landing in two spots, one south of the port in north Scotland, encircling any divisions defending the port (if there is any) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too would like to know. I have yet to figure out how to do a successful purging of the untermensch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deciplining </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> very </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was Napoleon "good" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I have read it was that he was a dictator, but not a tyrant.

And he was mostly better than any of the other absolute monarchies in Europe at the time, he freed some peoples form their oppressors, such as Poland in the duchy of Warsaw. 
   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was improvising, somewhere there probably where Pakistanis celebrating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slavs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
