<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2337</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 18:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to install the factory recovery .img in fastboot for the update to install correctly, also you'd need to have an unmodified system partition. I assume if you've got TWRP running you have an unlocked bootloader- so it shouldn't be too tough for ya  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 17:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently it is true. Hats off to those on the MFN for somehow not posting a link to either update zip thus far... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 19:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Common sense would think so as well. It's the network the 1060 belongs to that worries me more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 19:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see nothing about a certain 2013 X variant. Figures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upgrading a few old Onkyo's, looking for advice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 21:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry guys, gonna be a long post:

Current Hardware: http://imgur.com/a/b1l6s

I'm looking to upgrade my receivers- mostly because I'm tired of watching MLBTV inside the chrome browser (instead of a native app) but also because I think it's time for a needed change. My problem is that the A/V cabinet where the receivers are and the television sit a long (100' or so of cable run distance under an older house) way away. With newer tech like chromecasts/apple/fire/android TV out there all using HDMI this really limits my surround sound ability. I currently have digital audio to the surround receiver (TX-SR601) via 2x 50' of optical cable with an amp in-between (that I haven't had problems with, besides my current limitation) and the Google TV acts as a passthrough for the DirecTV or anything I watch natively (Plex/Youtube/Netflix etc). As for the other (read: ancient) amp, it's an Onkyo TX-903 stereo that delivers sound throughout the house with the help of the Niles SPS-6. We use it in conjunction with the SR601 to play music via a different input (as digital audio can't be pushed through the zone2 output) 

Couple of other facts:

I use those old Radioshack IRRF extenders (the ol' pyramids) and they are inconsistent at best.
I have 6.1 channel surround speakers that are not moving (unless demolition is in order)
I have networking (cat5) in both locations, but independently they go back to the router (in an even better spot far away)
I will be upgrading the TV in the near future, but not right meow.
The Google TV box throws a kink in my solution, but with the blu ray player and the DTS passthrough (amongst other things) I would like to keep it if I could-


I guess that brings me to a few questions-

Am I about to be running a ton of cables in order to upgrade these suckers? Could I replace the TX-903 with the SR-601 and just run it in stereo? Is there some super simple solution I haven't thought of? 

Any input would be super helpful- even laughing at my current setup so I can help justify this upgrade... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
