<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3191</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell is light treason? He gave away a few nuclear codes, but they were pobsolete? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean as a nice girl.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys get accused of mansplaining, what are examples of Ladysplaining? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ketchup and mustard on hotdogs. People who do this need to die </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Objects in your rearview mirror appear closer than they are by Meatloaf. I always thought that would be a good movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every mass shooting in the US. News fir a week and people move on. If its islamic terror, it gets more play because right wingers use it for political bullshit, then ignore the other mass murders. Little talk about gun control, then NRA blows it off and calls gun the same old tired argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those eyes creep me the fuck out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is the theme for Trump University. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she did this a few hundred years ago in Salem, they would burn her as a witch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He hasnt dissappeared. He will show up on a subway giving handjobs for doritos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They look ninja </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check my reddit history, I get then/than wrong all the time. I had a post once proposing we just pick one. Having both are infficient. You can always tell from the context. So its unecessary. I also want to get rid their, there, they're. They are unnecessary you can grok it from the context. Its the software engineer in me that makes want to refactor. The english lft us with a convoluted bullshit language. We need to refactor and make it American.

Going grammar nazi is stupid. Come on guys. Trump is a cunt. Go after the cunt part. We dont need this bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump was having a senior moment. He was thinking about the pudding he is getting later and forgot where he was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does a moon matter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every bird that flies anywhere in the remote vicinity of Donald Trump shits on him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shitty Genie gives you 10 year old tires with no tread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a job. Hippy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 06:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read an article linked from reddit last year that argued that its unlikely life develops as you get closer to the center of the galaxy. Stuff is closer together there so much higher chance of asteroids, solar flares, supernovas, whatever. This means we should rule out the vast majority of stars in the milky way and focus on stars at the edge. First off we cant see stars on the other side of the galaxy because the core is too bright.

There is more to it than earthlike.

1. Goldilocks zone.

2. Really small stars like trappist are unlikely. The earthlike worlds in the goldilocks zone close to the star so more at risk to solar flares.

3. Planet needs a big metallic core that can create a magnetic field to block deadly radiation.

4. Large jupiter like planet whose gravity pulls asteroids to it and reduces the chance of asteroids hitting the planet.

5. Seismically active might be a big help to life

6. Quiet part of the galaxy with little other activity that could kill off life. This eliminates the core and most solar systems in the galaxy

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its less the vastness of space and more ho hard it us to get into space due to gravity. If intelligent life evolved on a world woth less gravity they would have an advantage for getting into space. However, i dont know if less gravity means less fossil fuels would be created due to less pressure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is a radiolab? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its mostly democrats being aborted.so if these fetuses grew up they would overwhelmingly be democrats. You will be radically out number by secular progressives. We will cancel Christmas. Keep abortion or we will cancel the Cheistmas Holiday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are the Dragon Reborn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supreme Court ruled against Bill Clinton when he claimed he couldnt be sued for flashing his dick at a woman because he was president. The court was right in 1997 and precedence holds today. The argument that I am president so I can flash my little dick at anyone I want didnt work for Clinton and this argument wont work for Trump either. 

Note that being president hasnt kept trump from suing others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was a minor noble. Not exactly a farmboy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I first read wheel of time when book 1 was the last book published. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have read books my whole life. I ever noticed the difference. As long as it doesnt fall apart when I read it, I am good. I generally only read a book once. I think the vast majority of readers are like me. Only a small percentage are collectors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christians do write fantasy. It is called the bible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So amtrak will just be in blue states. The unprofitable part of amtrak serves poor mostly conservative rural areas. Fuck them they voted for trump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The heat death of the universe. The universe is expanding faster and faster. Eventually all galaxies outside of our local group will be moving away from us faster than the speed of light. This means in the future the visible universe will be much smaller. Eventually all the hydrogen will be used up and all stars will die. The last remaining power source in the far dark future will be black holes. They will eventually evaporate. All matter will break down into component parts. The universe will go dark for an inifinite period of time.

There is no hope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reverse feminism. The guy wants the woman to not be a housewife. Wants her to keep her well paying job. Ok if she makes more than you.

Woman: feminism is bullshit, you support me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how long will this take? damn apple is annoying. please add a way to export to other platforms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant fire the cleaner once i hire him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What headaches are apple giving you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do charms get better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im in ng+. On my 3rd meditation. Even elite charm bonuses are so small they dont matter. Even if i stockpile all my precursors. I use them and the bonuses are so small they dont matter.

The value to dungeons are he huge power drop rate. You dont drop down in levels sp power drop rate is much higher. I save most of my power drop and gold runes for dungeons. I frequently recall just before the boss repeatedly due to the big power drop bonuses. I stockpile keys for periods when my powerdrop gain slows down.

2 keys when you are at the last before ng+ is great. Used them and when i got back 45 minutes later my power was 100x higher and i cruised past him. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do charms get better? They kinda suck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So charm bonuses get better? They kinda suck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think runes stack additively. If you see a separate rune nd not one piled on top of another they stack additively. If you use the same rune several times you will see a stack. This means they run consecutively.

There are 3 spell runes that raise xp bonus. Id use all three then the bonus i occassionally get xp bonus charms that are up to 10%. Some for one color spell. I dont know if those are additive or multiplicative wirh runes. You can check by looking in the notebook and seeing how much it goes up.

For z runes. I would wait for new game+. This doubles spell xp and higher marks need alot more xp. Train the runes you have to have their spell xp passive at the existing mark. Wait for late in the eun when you have several levels of the skill that trains all runes. They do 5% per level and does not reset wirh meditation(but resets with ng+).

Id also spend stones on the bonus that cuts xp training in half before using. Get alot together to use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What TM lag do you use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am on new game+. Been using 4. Anyone test different ones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a wiki max levels are there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is dana? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the same team is unlikely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phil simms. Go back in time to 1984. Put a gun to george youngs head and say reggie whites name or your brains oare going on that piece of paper. Giants passed on him.

Lt/harry carson/reggie white same defense. No free agency.

Simms would have gotten 2 more rings for sure. All qbs with 3 rings are automatic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoe did reggie bush make all that money? He wasnt that good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tony romo is an egg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That 2002 oline crop must have been shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eagles fans having positive attitudes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants were 9-7 in 2011 and won the superbowl. It was over the patriots so it was a gimme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black head coach, black gm, black majority owner. White running back and 2 white corners </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Washington redskins not having drama every year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kurt warner didnt get drafted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stl lost 2 teams in the last 30 years. Unlikely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald trumps alt account </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chevy Nova. They tried to sell it in Mexico. No Va in Spanish means No Go.  It bombed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lost 2 offensive linemen. Lets see how he does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should have changed his tattoo on his arm to his wife in his brothers jersey instead of mark sanchez. Better dediction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to be posted here in 5 years when he is a bust </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they dont remember a time before 9/11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve bannon , roger ailes, ronald trump are fat slobs and they are eich </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mans a cuck. Real men mow the lawn with a push mower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 04:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you know it avoids 90% of damage? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if im killing faster i get more runes? So lets say i want to uae the runes that increase rune drops you can save. Would i get more runes if i recall as soon as my kill rate slows down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So crafting is basically only for gunslinger due to how hard it s to train crafting skill for other classes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are static leap and conduit useless? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Static leap you jump backwards. This just slows your run down. I asked what blink does and that leaps you backward. I was told it doesnt do anything.

Conduit is supposed to enhance other lightning spells, i tested it with 4 lightning spells and had conduit at 1.5, my kill rate does not seem to go up. 

What do you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tip i like in wilds or raids. Equip runes that make do summons. Add cooldown increases. Get a stack of runes that also do summons. After you get 2 summons casting, use your stack stack of summons. 

Then have a stack of runes that increase how long they stay. 30 second ones are best. Switch off summoning runes to other stuff for offense since you have butt load of perma summons. Use mage celeration, have heal and immunity, use xp bonuses here too. You will fly up zones. P
Dont use in dingeons. You lose all summons each room.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get power much faster in dungeons than in wilds. Keep repeating and let your mage power go up. I frequently cant get past the first room of a dungeon. Those are the best. Ill end up getting the most mage power. In wilds when you restart, you have to run through zones that get you very little power and gold. Dungeons are more efficient. Ill even make it to the end of a dungeon and recall before finishing several times to get more power.

I generally dont do this with centaurs in the final room. I have to use too many heals and immunity.

Never leave a dungeon early. Its absolutely worth it even if it take several hours to finish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 08:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In true millenial style she will move into her parents basement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where are you going with cafting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ios version just updated and i see a workbench and basic crafting mentioned. Where are you going with this? Do any other nethack variants have crafting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wouldnt like me. I am human. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hw do you know that? Its rare guys will walk away from $20m a year. I find it difficult to beleive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At his age with this line, he is one awkward hit away on the end. He has never been injured which is great, but ine blind side hit and he could be done.  Older players are at more risk of this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brandon jacobs was a stud pass blocking running back. Past prime he had more value as a blocker. Can blount block real well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong side of 30. Running backs dont decline gracefully, they fall apart. Nfl minimum contract.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id like to see them follow a team for a whole season like that socumentary on the cardinals a few years ago. There would have to be less interviews with players and coaches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cutler is a team killer. You could pry geno smith from the giants?

If i were the texans Id make an offer for Phillip Rivers. San diego sucks and they may want to save a ton of cap space as part of a rebuild. Might have to offer a #1 pick for him, but that would instantly make texas contenders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can have any blue voters ho dive on flaming tables </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody said these people dont bang their sisters either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id take leron. Id offer all gis descendents free circumcisions and free pastrami for eternity to get him to convert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He will never finish the series o why bother starting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have moved on to peruvian chicken </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50 Shades of Grey. I read the blurb on Amazon. Got tired and fell asleep. Its all I could handle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald trump rally? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It counts more red state votes matter more due to weighting in congress, senate, and electoral college </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eli way over Romo. 2 rings. Romo chokes and cant stay on the field. Eli never missed a game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a jew , we almost got lebron to convert a few years ago. We need him to swell our jock credits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the cowboys get smart and leave that inbred cow fucking shithole and move to a new state, I will support them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lawrence Taylor used to kill the redskins all time offensive line. Joe Gibbs would triple team him. There was a game in 1986 on a play the redskins had a 25 yard completion. John Madden made a call. Hold against LT. He was double teamed by Jacoby and Grimm, then held by Bostic. Madden also credited him with forcing 4 INTs in that game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erik Flowers of the giants. Fucking terrible for a top 10 pick so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marajuana is not legal in every state. It legalizing this gives an edge to some clubs. Given how addicting opiods are, id legalize it. Nfl players aleays have pan. Its about pain management.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoe namath. He threw 1/3 more ints than tds. He had 2 good seasons. He is in the hof for winning superbowl 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emmit was the most important player n that team. Aikman was a good, not great qb. He is in the hall due to all the talent around him. In spite of that talent he only threw 20 tds one time. There are alot of guys who threw alot more tds who are in the hall from that era. On top of that he had Irvin to throw to who was one of the 3-4 best receivers of his era. Great offensive line. Real good fullback. Good defense so not alot of pressure on him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 05:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think elon musk needs security. Putin is going to put uranium in his tea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 05:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And according trump we will finally learn that Ted Cruzs daddy was involved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 05:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When democrats take everything back and they will with the way trump is going, impeach them all and fire them. If necessary change the law so judges get a single fixed term.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so i have to keep pressing v and spacebar to get the bonuses up?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when i click on the link it says weed, etc... it was different 2 days ago?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please keep gilded runes in the ios release. Its the best part f the release. Even if that means a delay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dirty Harry was more clutch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horry has a case for HoF outside of his numbers. He hit big shots in those playoff runs. He was always a complimentary player, but you can take the case on alot of teams he was the piece that put them over the top.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Francis uts the black dont crack motif in the grave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL 2 women tried to murder the most insignificant president of the 20th century.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grammar nazis. I am american and I got grammar nazi response 2 hours ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baby trump was fucking ugly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you ask for relationship advice on the internet you deserve this. Better than telling him to sell her cat to, chinese restaurant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the paid russian trolls during the campaign last year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the plus side reddit gets a lawyers panties in a bunch. I am really tempted to friend this guy and reply to his posts with stuff that doesnt make sense. Just for the joy of fucking with a lawyer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you have shitty hobbies. What do you expect on subs dedicated to collecting used panties.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its worse when they go none and then recommend something unrelated cause they likes it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason I thought he was taller and bulkier. You sure that is 1964? He looks mid 20s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a cop is being a dick make sure you are recording to the cloud in case he takes the phone. The idiot cop turned a regular traffic stop into a bunch of bullshit. Pull the guy over, give him his ticket, go on with your life.

When my customers are dicks to me I cant even give them a ticket or a warning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe, he hopes a shark will come and then leave him a few chunks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many states have open primaries. Its also trivial to change your registration. If trump is pushing a primary challenge, I can see democrats in small numbers refistration as republicans. If turnout in off year primaries is 7.5%, first that is split between republicans and democrats. If 5-10% of democrats in some districts register as a republican including a push by trump, he could get a few of them. If he is smart he will run a conservative as well, but one who would compromise so people in the district dont really have any reason to turn out if you care about him. Trump supporters are also serously hardcore and it doesnt take many in a primary.

He could get a few of them. If he gets say 5 of them, that is 5 of the 21. Since these are safe red districts,I dont think there will be any fear of it going democratic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prosecute him for what? Knowing the russians were hacking Clintons email and coordinating he release? That kind of bullshit is legal. No one gets prosecuted for the Hatch act. Like ever. Trumps Justice department wont prosecute on that. Its stupid to prosecute. The penalty he suffered was political. He deserved to be fired. If Trump coordinated with the Russians he deserves to be impeached. What is the crime that can put someone in jail? This looks like one of things no one thought to make illegal until it happens. 

CNN covered this. Its common for people to ask for immunity even if you didnt do anything. You never know if an asshole prosecutor will maliciously prosecute you. Supposedly lawyers will tell you that. Its why the people who worked on Clintons servers wanted immunity. Its blurry when this stuff is illegal so you never know if someone will dick move you.

Trump media outlets are killing Flynn recently. He could be pissed. He could be angling for lobbying jobs. Look who I know in russia. Right wing speech circuit?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do those curved monitors make a difference? I saw some curved tvs at best buy and they seemed like a hoax. Screen didnt look better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe. Really rosy red districts tend to be really right wing everything. So most people there probably support the freedom caucus veto, but the voter turnout is so low in congressional primaries(its like 5% and that is split between republican and democrats), it doesnt take alot. Plus democrats might vote against the freedom caucus as a fuck you to republicans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wrote an entire paragraph that basically ignored what I said. Go you. Truly astonishing. You wrote a completely generic paragraph, I could copy and paste practically verbatim from all over reddit . You paragraph is not germaine to what I said. 

Voter turnout in congressional primaries is about 5% and that is split between republicans and democrats. So figure in a heavily republican district its 3.5% of total voters turnout for republican primary. If he can get 3% of people to turn out and this can include democrats wanting to fuck the freedom caucus they could lose. Even in very conservative districts you will have democrats and moderate republicans. Such low voter turnout makes it possible for him to get a few. The primaries are over a year away. Who the hell knows what people will be talking about?

Im a democrat. Never voted in a congressional primary like just about everyone else. I might turnout to vote against the freedom caucus just to ass fuck with republicans if trump organizes this. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only a very conservative democrat would have any chance in texas. I doubt any democrats gets 40% against cruz.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think freedom caucus members are from the reddest of red districts. Any republican can win there. Primaries have maybe a 5% turnout. So its possible that trump could get people excited to primary a few out due to only needing a small increase in turn out. If his approval rating is hovering around 30% he wont get any.

Basically if the democrats pick up seats but dont take over the house and freedom caucus holds pat they control the agenda since they can veto anything unless trump goes far enough left to get democrats on board like the infrastructure bill. If that passes it will take mostly democratic votes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like something from minecraft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This trailers tells us nothing. Most of the clips are not even from the show and just filmed for the promo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This helps explain the absurd upvotes on the_donald </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about rune drops </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. What is the percent f runes that are ones you can save? I know most you cant.

2. Do you only get a better chance at good runes with the research that improves rune drops or do also get better drops at higher stages and ng+?

3. Is the rune drop rate just a percent chance per kill? Im saving my runes that increase the odds of getting runes you can save until just before I go ng+ ( i have meditated 4 times) . I figure i have the best chance at getting good runes to save at that point. I am wondering if i should do a raid repeatedly then use the rune that speeds up my mage to max my kill rate. If you have a percent chance per kill to get a rune drop this strikes me as a good idea. 

4. Runic table changes once a day right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When will the IOS 1.8 come out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Said a few weeks. Just asking. I know there are delays when uploading code to ios. Is the code done? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most employers who have insurance also provide disability insurance. There is short term which pays more and long term insurance. You should look into and apply for that immediately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants/49ers rivalry from 1981-1993. Met in the playoffs six times. 5 times winner won the superbowl. Giants ended their 3 peat run. Played on MNF almost every year during that period. 

Bill Parcells/Bill Walsh/Bill Bellichek/John Gruden and others were coaches.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a little confused. Lantern recalls at 1 minute. Auto recall runs at 6 minutes. Wont the lantern run first? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need to turn off lantern to use auto recall rune? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lantern runs every minute. Autorecall runes i have are every 6 minutes. Do i need to turn the lantern off for this to be used? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When will version 1.8 be out for ios? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How rare is it to find an untiuched tomb?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google it. Tennessee traded up to get conklin ahead of the giants. You can also google the joe thomas trade discussions. Im not doing it for you. 

Google conklin giants.
Google joe thomas, giants trade. Giants offered a 3rd round pick just before the trade deadline. Browns wanted a two.

These have been posted on this sub a number of times before. Its easy to find in a google search.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend not reading the OPs poorly written piece of trash post. The subject is enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a common type of posts on book subs. These posts happen every day on fantasy sub. If you dont like these posts dont read them. This sub isnt super active. Any cool discussions are welcome. I asked once looking for certain types of stories. I liked the responses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should have negotiated this in private instead of presenting it publicly. He misread his caucus. Paul Ryan didnt want to be speaker and had to be talked into it. He just wanted to run the budget committee.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants were set to take Conklin last year and move Flowers to RT, but Tennessee traded up. They tried to trade for Joe Thomas midseason. If it was successful they would have moved him to RT. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I expect a restructure of jt thomas or they cut him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants do t sign guys like that. He is a minimum contract signing with no guaranteed money. Guys out of the league  this generally dont come back. You lose the edge and level of play. Muscles change. You need football muscle. You do t just get back in shape. Then the likelihood of him snorting coke again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could also mean I like bacon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teach them how to use the uber app. Then they can get to work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1986 giants were the best giants team ever. The 2007 and 2011 teams were far inferior.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1986 giants. 

Beat Joe Montana/Jerry Rice and the 49ers 49-3 in the playoffs.

Beat the 12-4 redskins 3 times.

Phil Simms 22 of 25 with 3 drops over John Elway and the Broncos in the superbowl. 

Lawrence taylor lead the league in sacks, DPOY, unanimous MVP.

Mark Bavarro was Gronk back in hevday. Joe Morris had 1500 yards rushing. 2 HoF and an all decade player on defense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if he looks in the mirror and he sees his white adopted mother and screams because he doesnt remember why he is black? CTE is a bitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just delays the inevitable when these two are driving ubers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We gotta bring back public hangings ahead of Trumps treason trial. Then bury him next to John Wilkes Booth

Hashtag: Hang him up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No bruce smith is several notches below reggie white. He didnt draw as much attention as reggie. Wasnt as strong against the run as reggie. Teams didnt game plan against him like they did reggie.

LT/ Reggie White are one and two. Everyone else including jj watt are several notches below. 

They were almost team mates. Giants passed on white in the 1984 supplemental draft. Parcells wanted him, but he only won 3 games his first year.

LT/Harry Carson/Reggie White and no salary cap or free agency.

Then add Carl Banks all decade team. Leonard Marshall two time all pro.

Gary Reasons/Pepper Johnson also made the pro bowl 

Bellichek used to move LT all over the place. He likely would have moved Reggie White around too. Picture both of them standing up over he center. Good way to get teams to waste timeouts.

Parcells said in an interview that White would have played NT some, but mainly DE on the strong side. Marshall was the DE next to LT. Giants ran alot of stunts using LT as a decoy. They would have stunted with White too. Giants occassionally used LT as a cornerback in zone. Probably would have done that more with White. Giants likely also would have played with 3 rushers (LT/White/Marshall) and used 8 guys in zone alot. Those 3 should be able to get pressure by themselves. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 07:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dak prescott. Lost 2 offensive lineman. Teams have tape on him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 07:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Browns will double their win total </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 07:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO is a filthy town. He drank the water and got montezumas revenge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
