<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3535</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm assuming that's Addison, right ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ME:A Spoilers] If you could roast a squadmate, who would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other day, a friend of mine sat in on one of my playthroughs, specifically where I was driving in the Nomad with Vetra and Liam. After an hour of hearing their dialogue, she got so upset at Liam's treatment of Vetra that she asked me: "Do you have the option to roast him?" This got me thinking, if you guys had the option of roasting a squadmate or a character in Andromeda, who would it be?

Just to clarify, by roasting I mean to humorously mock or humiliate someone with a well-timed joke, diss or comeback. I appreciate the cooking your squadmates comments, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] I just had to post this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, I'm getting horrible flashbacks right before class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, its just spiders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can officers from OTS go into either STO or CRO? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 10:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if that is the case, I trust Marvel to handle the teen drama stuff with more subtlety and nuance than something like the CW, and that's coming from someone who likes the CW superhero shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Option d is just walking away while this plays 
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5FjWe31S_0g </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And to top it all off, the ark is actually a dormant reaper with Cerberus agents hidden in it. The Quarian pathfinder was getting really homesick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never really thought of them as spiders. I knew they were insects, but they didn't come of as arachnid in nature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to get space spider repellent? SPACE SPIDER </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking something along the lines of the spiders in DA, but you know, in space. Or something like the literary depictions of the bugs from Starship Troopers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not the only one. I had to play from behind door and would peak my head only when i wasn't in combat.  I also tried to pay my older brother, who wasn't afraid of spiders, to play the cave levels for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then I hope Bioware gives us:
a.) The option to say something along the lines of "Were we that nostalgic for the milky way that we bring the Rachni?" or just plain "nope." 

b.) The option of punching either the Captain of the ark or the Quarian pathfinder for bringing them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully Bioware won't pull the same thing again:

Go into a Remnant vault? SPACE SPIDER.

Investigate a signal on a planet? SPACE SPIDER.

Board a Kett ship? SPACE SPIDER. 

Walk into a crew members cabin? SPACE SPIDER (wait, its in Liam's quarters? ok, leave it)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I'm picturing Cora in Daisy Dukes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] One thing I'm glad Bioware didn't put into Andromeda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spiders. Like Dragon Age sized space spiders. I was playing the other night and was half expecting them to show up in the caves on Kadara.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One thing I'm glad Bioware didn't put in Andromeda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to see them play with the idea of planetary gravity similar to John Carter where you're on a planet with low gravity so your jumps and melee are twice as high and as strong. 

Also, when you say space boarding, I think of something like this 
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VjXIswnrWTA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would personally like to see a planet that appears dead but is actually houses something scary that stalks you and your squad. One thing I hope Bioware tries to convey in future Andromeda games is that exploration can be extremely scary, especially when your in a new galaxy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ME:A Spoilers] What kinds of plants or environments would you like to see in the Andromeda sequel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since its pretty certain that we're going to be expanding to the rest of the Andromeda galaxy, one thing I hope Bioware does is get really creative in regards to the types of plants we travel to. I hope they begin to go away from the typical 'ice, desert, jungle' planets we saw in the first Andromeda.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And he's supposed to be the demolitions expert?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What did you notice about the officers in your class, specifically what they did right and common mistakes they made? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I haven't watched Man in the High Castle, but I've heard nothing but good things about it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 07:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of wished that happened just to see Cora record her berating  you on her omni tool and post it online.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would agree on the light bar. At the very least, I would've liked to have the option to change the color.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] why I prefer the Pathfinder armor to the N7 armor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the course of my several playthroughs, I've grown fond of the Pathfinder armor (with the default color scheme) to the point where I prefer it over the N7 armor from both the OT and in Andromeda. A few of the reasons why include: 

1. The helmet design: I like the more open, transparent visor. I think, its indicative of current astronaut EVA helmets. It also allows  for Ryder to be expressive while still wearing the helmet as opposed to the closed visor of the N7 helmet.`And yes, I know that the Pathfinder helmet is meant for exploration while the N7 helmet is meant for combat.  

2. The armor to cloth ratio: One question I always had with the N7 armor is how is it put on, and was there some kind underlaying cloth beneath the plates, especially with the N7 armor from ME1. With the Pathfinder armor, the existence of a cloth layer beneath the armor is more apparent. I also like the

3. The color: I like that the red has spread out over the entire suit as opposed to keeping it relegated to the right arm with the N7 armor. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do I[20M] do about a high school crush [20F] I still have feelings for that seems distant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever since my sophomore year in high school, I've had feelings for this girl, who at the time, was dating one of my closest friends. Since then, she's had a string of bad relationships, all of which I've been there to help her through (I remember her literally crying on my shoulder after she broke up with her boyfriend one year). 

Since then, we've grown closer and my feelings for her have grown, but we haven't dated . She more than likely knows how I feel about her and we both care about each other, but whenever I've tried to talk with her on a more personal level, she becomes distant. We both have similarities personality and career wise, and we both care about each other, but so far, nothing's happened. What do I do?

TL;DR: A girl I've known and had feelings for since high school haven't become romantic. What should I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't count the Crusader. Its damage is in the 700's. but it takes a full clip to bring down regular kept or outcasts, and 3 to take down shields and armor (even with something like incendiary ammo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My older brother's addicted to it, but I see where you're coming from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just looked up images of it. How the hell did something like that make it to series? ABC's been doing pretty well with Agents of SHIELD and what I like to call their soap opera trilogy (Quantico, How to Get Away With Murder, and Scandal), so why would they shoot themselves in the foot with a show like Imaginary Mary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your least favorite show on tv right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, it is unequivocally the new Hawaii Five-O. I tried watching the first five seasons on Netflix, and I went from mild interest to actively disliking it in a matter of hours. Everything from the writing to the characters to the growing disregard for plausibility and basic logic(there's an episode where they have to solve the theft of an iron man like exo-skeleton) to the plain corniness of it. And I get that CBS procedurals aren't the most sophisticated shows on television, with the exception of Person of Interest, but still.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I would agree to a certain extent. Yes, the amount of RPG/roleplay elements are not as well developed as they should be, but I would still want the exploration aspect to be a big part of the game. Ideally, I would like to see something along the lines of the Witcher 3 in terms of how much stuff there is to explore and do, but decrease the size of the maps only slightly, so there can somewhat of a balance of content and open space. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's nothing to say you can't have both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right in saying that that its not a historical documentary, but that doesn't mean Bioware couldn't pull from history to make their story more compelling, as most science fiction has done.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But rather than immediately jump to the big existential threat that is the Kett in the first game, the story should have been more focused on just trying to live in Andromeda while dealing with the people who live there. I think Efvra and the Rokaer should have been the main antagonists of the game, as they are much more relatable, sympathetic, and compelling. With them, their entire reason for being hostile is because they want to protect their home from the strange and potentially dangerous aliens that came out of nowhere. That's a compelling, relatable motivation, one we can sympathize with seeing as how that premise has been the basis for a majority of Science Fiction, and it provides the player with an enemy whose reason for doing the stuff they do is realistic and something we can understand, as opposed to the 'blah blah exaltation, blah blah you will be great' stuff the Archon was spouting. 

What I would have done is make the Rokaer the primary villains for the first game, with the Kett being the enigmatic threat over the horizon similar to how the Reapers were in ME1. You would hear about them, and maybe even meet one who came to Heleus to tell of the impending arrival of the Archon ala the Heralds of Galactus from Marvel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying that there shouldn't be a personal antagonist like the Illusive Man or Saren, but what I am saying is that the environment of a new and completely alien galaxy should be a problem for the Initiative. If there wasn't some kind of difficulty with settling worlds in Heleus, then it would frankly, be unrealistic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'd be difficult seeing as how the Mako is over 600 years old and 2 million light years away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not by the standards of a show like Chicago P.D., but I would say they're attractive in an everyman sort or way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little do people know, this is actually a leaked screenshot from an upcoming DLC where Kallo is fed up with Gil's shit, and uses Kett Performance Enhancing Drugs to put him in his place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article did mention that NSW put out some statistics that were contrary to the report, but like you said man, I'm going to keep following it. I also hope other SOF units aren't experiencing anything like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The theme song for Terriers still gets stuck in my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hope this isn't as bad as it seems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Choices like that are what we should have been able to do. Like you said, it would better define your Ryder as a Pathfinder, and the new dialogue system could have been used to give unique and in depth answers for why you made the choice you did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well we know who Kallo's going to call when Gil starts messing with the Tempest again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like the idea of having the Kett encroaching on the area of Heleus you're exploring. Maybe we encounter ships scouting the area. That way, the focus is on exploration, rather than gearing up for war with the Kett. 

Actually, I had an idea. One thing I noticed is that during dialogue with the Angarans, they never once mention any alien species aside from the Milky Way races and the Kett. What Bioware could do with this is have it to where the Angarans haven't ventured outside the cluster due to both technological limitations and their war against the Kett (similar to how the humans in the Milky way weren't able to venture outside the Sol System until they activated a relay). Now that the Kett presence in Heleus has been minimized and the Initiative figured out how to access, use, and even retrofit Remnant technology, its now possible for both groups to venture outside the cluster. 

Something along this line could provide us with an opportunity to have legitimate first contact with species we haven't seen before all while providing a story backed reason for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or uses reverse psychology or brings up something personal to get the suspect to crack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think surviving in Andromeda would have the exact opposite effect for several reasons

1. Having Andromeda itself as antagonist would allow the player to deal with a wide variety of threats. Rather than having to contend with just the Kett or pirates, Ryder could have to deal with toxic environments, unstable weather, hostile natives, strange cosmic phenomena, and everything in between. Bioware has an entire galaxy to fill, so I don't think players could run out of new things to encounter. For a tangible example, think about how the Witcher 3 had so many different creatures and monsters in its map. now picture that, but spread across different planets. 

2. It would be more, for lack of a better term, realistic. If the Initiative didn't have difficulties navigating and successfully settling an entirely new galaxy, and only had to deal with the Kett and the Angarans, then that would be extremely unlikely, regardless of how advanced the Initiative is Technologically. History has shown that explorers, and people who've lived in barely settled lands have dealt with things like inhospitable environments, hostile natives, ect. To say that wouldn't be true when trying to settle and explore an entire sector of space wouldn't make any sense.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably, the simplest option, but I guess I'm overthinking it/being overly anxious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And towards the end, the boss ends up either making the arrest or is the one interrogating the main suspect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there's a way to have an open world and have a more linear storyline. Games like Red Dead: Redemption, the Arkham trilogy, and The Witcher 3 have done this to carrying degrees of success. 

Also, I'm kind of confused. Do you disagree with the idea of making surviving in Andromeda one of the main challenges the player faces or using history as inspiration for the atmosphere and side quests? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to reconnect with a girl I haven't spoken to in months. How should I go about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR: I'm a 20 yr old college guy who wants to reconnect with a girl I was friends with, but had feelings for, from a class I had last semester, but lost contact with when I transferred to a different school. Its been 4 months since I last saw her, and I don't know if she has a boyfriend. How should I go about reconnecting with her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That should be the title of an animated show on FX. Think Archer meets Harvey Birdman: Attorney at Law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
