<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1499</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks I may check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I would love to live in a fantasy world dictated by my mind. I recognize that in reality I live in the grand but at times flawed nation known as the United States of America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But T_D bans other opinions  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't personally attack others, offer constructive criticism. Even if the other party is contrary to popular opinion. On the other hand I kinda agree with /u/biochemguy after dealing with trump supporters a few times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going off tangent here, is that much military spending necessary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Methods matter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would go sideways with that, but in all due fairness at the very least it should not be on the same tier as meth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reason for this subreddit. Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would assume whenever it's convenient.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just vote on a different representative or senator, many years voter participation edges close to 49% for congressional elections.

https://www.census.gov/newsroom/press-releases/2015/cb15-122.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most weirdest thing I have heard was FDR potentially having an affair. It made me rethink disabled people, in a good way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The older generation that remembers the chaos of the breakup and the USSR are his strongest base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Munching on popcorn as the other is clearly self-righteous  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try a zeal item before the IE. The damage plus bonus effects are great for its price. And the build order as well.

By zeal item I mean firecannon or shiv. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this country we live live by the rule "guilty until proven innocent" a very vital rule to prevent abuses.
If you would be so kind to try to prove your statements that would be wonderful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's around 5-6 feet tall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ CA ] who owns the fence on a property line? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>    There is no trouble. There is a fence that is bordering the property line of our small residential lot, my family built it with permission from all parties after the last fence had too much wear in tear, in particular our neighbors had a vicious dog that would throw itself as the fence until it broke through one day. As we built the fence do we own it? Asking out of sheer curiosity as we like to hang things on the fence on top of the beams, such as straddling 2 by 4s on top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to upvote this for the reference  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus it's dmg low lv is small and the CD is huge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also what lane and match up, Shen sup vs a jhin is pretty one sided :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His build doesn't seem to wrong by the end result, maybe the build order? I default build IE or ES first followed by berserkers boots and zeal, followed by IE or ES.

In lane phase with jhin you have to exploit windows of power with jhin, especially learn his power spikes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish he left memoirs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greek fire of the Byzantines </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In door plumbing by the midians of Cyprus  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you would be so kind to provide a link, I would not be so viable to dismiss your claims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to read further on this, could you post a few links? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I'm sorry if I wasn't able to read your mind, but I would argue trump reacts much more strongly to leaks critical of him. Such as how White House administration was trying to abuse its power to try to uncover the identity of a twitter account that was critical of the trump administration. (The account claimed to be an employee of the national immigration service)

Will be back with a link

Edit here it is:
http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-39535929 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But does the country, not private citizens, fund orgs with the intention to cause harm to the West? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry couldn't connect the dotes without the assumption that you were possessing misconceptions. Care to elaborate on your vague post? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first Rome total war phalanx was a joke. Put 3 at a gate and you can win a battle vs 12 units. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be difficult to pull off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a question of morals now. My morals say it's better to stop such atrocities but from what limited information I posses I think the manner in which this was executed is wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the irony of the cartoon passed over you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got your point. I personally think it's a grey area what is going on, though a justifiable dark grey. The Shia vs Sunni conflict can get brutal. Plus I would assume a Saudi funded extremist is safer than a ISIS extremist. As Saudi Arabia shares information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was reading up on this and I'm going to conclude they were not directly funded by Saudi Arabia to commit terrorist acts. Though if you have more information you are welcome to share. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 15/19 https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hijackers_in_the_September_11_attacks

Just a minor peeve if it's not hard to cite it please do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting could you link a wiki?

Edit: I assume it's a typo and you meant to say isis and not NATO. Or  fund extremists more than they fund NATO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From how often roman metro crews have this happen to them, I wonder if they are annoyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red herring 

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Red_herring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not just have Japan do a conditional surrender? No they did not bomb for peace, there were better ways to do that, they bombed Japan bc of the USSR around the corner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... why does this make me think that EPA will get the FEMA treatment (cutting or redistribution of funds until it's only a token program) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Tu quo'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shouldn't we hold more scrutiny for committing offense acts though? I am more fine with people adopting an peace policy unconditionally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That and doesn't try to commit terrorist acts against the west. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it may have been a good thing to bomb Syria but how it was done was terrible. 

1. It's an attack on sovereign country without their consent, without congressional approval, and don't give me any 'tu quo' arguments. Not citing it because it's pretty obvious.

2 it's expensive at least 1 million per missile, assuredly more, why not do it in a cheaper fashion? (And one of trumps 'things' to say were concerned with money)
https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tomahawk_(missile)

Edit: in case you are not familiar with 'tu quo' 
https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tu_quoque </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah thankfully they understood science and now make controlled burns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scroll up to /u/joeliar

And down to /u/cakeandale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly from what you said I don't even know where to start so I will go with the most basic generic one, cite it, give facts and figures.

Edit: I think you may posses misconceptions about my statement so in advance I'll remind you that end-result is not good enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 10:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On one point funny, in the other hand you reminded me of how screwed up the prison system is in the US </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 10:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as no one is hurt in the end it's a tale to tell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 10:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aye got into a caracident where the bumper bounced back, the freaken radiator was a goner but you couldn't tell that from the outside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 09:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dunno trivializing rape? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 09:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Medieval popes were dirty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 09:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> QQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 09:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rome was kinda tolerant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 09:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now population wise and pop density? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 09:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh the horror </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 05:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> En he was a dictator but from what I have gathered it's a bit unfair to say during the war he focused the communists but one can say that before the war he was focusing on communists more than a potential Japanese threat, but that's also reasonable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 05:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fertilizer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 10:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the Spanish Armada the English despite having less fire power and less ships won due to the English cannons having longer range than the Spanish cannons, allowing them to win the battle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 10:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Spanish armada lost despite having more total fire power but their tactics sucked while the English planned well. (For that one guy, the Spanish Armada was defeated by the English and THEN got nailed by a storm.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 10:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's always fun to read about battles were this was ignore and a ally ship would fire through its own partner to hit the enemy ship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 10:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roman construction never ceases to amaze me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm assuming that each family is around 5 members that survived to reproduce 5 more, it would be nearly 2 million so I assume there were exceptions or people flat out denied being related.

Edit: wow my assumption of 5 per family was nearly spot on (4.95 avg) but women after marriage were no longer considered part of their family so if we use only the figure of 2.5 per family, you would only have to kill ~3,800 people to punish up to the 9th degree. Definitely doable.
Also the figure is not taking into account relatives marrying and potentially many more factors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it was more to bad information. They thought their artillery did a good job of softening up the union, but the artillery failed (and the guy responsible for telling lee that didn't, for whatever reason) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Constantinople one of the best fortified cities of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aye if the solviets stayed the same after Finland Germany would have an easier time, but lessons were learned and USSR changed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 12:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> imagine a bunch of if statements where

 if bullets_fired = 1: 

   vertical shift = o

   Horizontal shift = o

If bullets_fired = 2:
  
   Vertical shift = 3

   Horizontal shift = -2
If...

More probably it's a list or something but if statements are easier to show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 12:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as darkmare flying off to the distance sometimes... until you realize that kills it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 12:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries I beat it and mastered it... though I forgot to bring any fire resistance  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 12:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much I concluded I will RW a wall, skip Sheepsong, caith sith as white mage with toy soldier, pirate lady USB (Farris I think?), and 2 ice mage BSB. Aeorith healer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 12:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 12:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mega-death! Game over </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 12:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinking Cait sith toy soldier, Farris USB, Aerith, and 2 ice mage BSB

RW wall, not using native magic shout </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 12:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They tried to recruit Slavs? Didn't they view Slavs as slightly better than Jews? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 12:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unquestioned loyalty to a cause is when you don't ask such questions  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 12:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the yellow haze in the back is light pollution from the coast? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 12:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have edea BSB and another ice mage BSB, it was just the damage that was wrecking me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most my attempts only used full break but should I bring out every break possible out? It's his mag dmg that kills me in the end </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help with Ifrit from Mote dungeon, or a link to a mega thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't find the mote mega thread so posting here. I can't freaken beat ifrit despite mastering all else. At this point I am going to take 4 white mages and serioth BSB. I have ice mage BSB, I have magic shout, I have wall, I have mages but I can't beat ifrit. Tell me how please.

Ps: what are good mage and summon abilities to hone, sitting at 50 major orbs each and around 10-15 crystals each.

Edit: alright got my answers, downvote this so it won't take up anymore space.

Mastered it, despite one of my mages getting killed off the bat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going from 126 stamina to 151... all in one sleepless night  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much US installed missiles in turkey, turkey is not that far from Russia, so the USSR in retaliation installed or mostly installed missiles in Cuba. Cuba missile crisis happens and backroom negotiations happen: US removes turkey missiles and USSR removes Cuba missiles.

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cuban_Missile_Crisis

Edit: more information. It really feels like a play the whole crisis, with the US and the USSR making bold statements but secretly contacting each other. Such as USSR making a televised statement painting the blockade as an act closer to war but secretly sending telegrams to the US saying we won't actually do much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 10:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will the fine be cheaper than the cost for renting equipment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 10:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first time I saw the city respond the same day as a report was when there was a huge rotting egg smell (most likely gas) in the road in front of my house (in the suburbs).

Edit: deleted redundant posts below </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are rightfully entitled and should rightfully use their vote, now about the large portion that decline to do so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only as ethical as the least ethical man in power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think your quip about e-cigs is a bit misleading, not entirely false, but misleading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I see is more food for my assassin corps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guessing you make deals with dwarves? Because for me greenskins are more than happy to break all treaties the moment they think they can get away with it. (I play on hard so that's my experience so far) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 aa batteries is 50 micro amps? Is this in series or parallel?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What no mention of the breakup of the USSR? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity did they talk about the missiles In turkey which prompted the Cuban missile crisis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see Ukrainian soldiers betraying  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SVN useful or not useful in most instances? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a grudge against the memory cards. In FFX just defeated sin after getting all the ultimate weapons, (screw caladbolg and thunder). Card goes to hell. 7/10 pissed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The more you know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's easier to fight off one of those hairless rats than a pit, in my experience they tend to be good but if one was raised poor... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would talk to my adc in select, if they were cool I would get thresh, Braun, etc. if they were jerks or a mute hey lux is a 'support' but can also carry somewhat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use it to wish luck, though there are moments where I step back and reach for the popcorn... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just scrolling to see how many times will it be triggered in this thread  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U has been used in pottery glaze as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't there a subreddit that is devoted to making fun of fedoras? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
