<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject398</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 15:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may be right. But... Then again... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 06:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still in the idea/development stage. I do have a site being built at this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 06:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had my interest, now you have my attention.
PM me please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 05:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both, customers can build their own and my site or others will be able to have kits built for them. Say, if you have your own recipe you can pay a small membership and post your recipe on the site. If someone buys a kit of your recipe you get a small cut.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 05:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Thanks for the input. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 05:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is going to be hard to under cut me. I buy from the largest wholesale supplier of these ingredients in the country and since they are right down the street from me I have no shipping costs or warehousing costs. I pick up 5 days a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 05:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 04:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No sweatshop route here. Believe in paying a livable wage. It' not illegal or potentially unprofitable, it just hasn't been done yet that I can find. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 04:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope not affiliate marketing. Something different. Thanks for the well wishes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 03:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A full stacker is what I'm looking for. Not so much the site being complicated but it will need to be able to pull ingredients from a spread sheet and put the recipes together. PM me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 03:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why pick this guy? Tell me what you think. And yes you can have some stickers if we ever feel the need to get any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 03:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, not cupcakes or anything baked or anything weed related. I understand the ROI of marketing, I've spent and seen spent 10s of thousands of dollar on it and understand how low it can be. This product lends itself to others marketing for a cut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 03:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, not yet. Maybe after November. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 03:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes there is a way to PM me. Impress me and figure it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 03:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe you understand the time and dedication it takes to build this sort of online business. I have been part of it before. You wouldn't have time for college with the many fires you have to put out daily. Thanks for the reply but stay with your studies and maybe get back to me when your finished. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 03:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been worse but I'm in a pretty good state of mind at this time. Thanks for asking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 03:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes the site is "buildable". You are correct concerning the up keep and and such. Also the advertising if possible. I will handle the physical end of getting the kits put together and shipped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 03:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the help. I hope the right one or ones show up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 02:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be great to get a youngin' in on this but how do I know a good one when they are in front of me? In the past it was my son and me, but he is making a good living and a free life from the store we built and doesn't want more work or need more money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 02:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do I find the right partner for my idea? I am shipping manager for the third largest online supplier of ingredients for ahhh... let's say... brownies. (It's not brownies but I don't want to give my niche away.) So, I can get all the ingredients for any "brownie" recipe at wholesale cost and have the ingredients put together into a kit for an extra 10% of the costs. This is a huge niche with hundreds of dedicated sites, some having thousands of recipes and thousands of followers. But! Not a single site offers a kit to put it all together. 
Here is my problem, I don't want to do any of the online stuff. I'm 63 and about to retire and want to travel, a lot. I can do most of the online stuff needed but am not interested in the time it takes to build this product. I am having a website built at this time but am not sure how it's going to turn out with the fellows I have building it. I don't need a lot of money, I lead a small life and travel on the cheap so, I am willing to give the lions share of profits to who ever I partner with. I also have what I consider a small budget, a couple thousand dollars, to get this thing rolling. So, how do I find the right partner in what I am pretty sure will be over a million dollar biz a year? Just some back ground, I helped build the supplier I work for into what it is today, from deep in dept to over 2 mil in sales this year.
EDIT 1: Thanks to Mornighead for the post and to all of you who have replied. The response was, as expected, overwhelming. I will try to reply to everyone and not leave you hanging. It looks as though we might be able to build a team and help out a bunch of people. I am humbled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 15:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biotin, 10,000mcg. Very cheap and works like crazy for hair and nails. I take 2 a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 20:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 15:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judging me for being, acting and reacting like a "man" without considering I may not like it any more than you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]Why did they used to call it a "fanny"? Come to think of it, I haven't heard a woman called Fanny in a looonnng time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 16:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
