<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2472</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "Let me tell you something," says Carmine Caridi, 83, an actor best known for small parts in the last two films in The Godfather trilogy, as he takes a seat at Vinoteca at The Four Seasons. "Everybody does it, OK?" By "it," Caridi means lending out screeners sent by distributors to Academy voters for Oscar consideration. The problem for the long-divorced resident of West Hollywood: He loaned videos to a man who turned out to be one of the most notorious movie pirates in history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Godfather' actor Carmine Caridi, the only AMPAS member to be expelled for sharing screeners, reflects on his Oscar infamy and a career that might have been. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He also expressed concerns about reports of border agents asking American travelers for smartphone PIN numbers to access their mobile devices. Reports surfaced in mid-February that a U.S.-born NASA scientist traveling back to the U.S. was pressured by border agents into handing over his smartphone PIN number. I intend to introduce legislation shortly that will guarantee that the Fourth Amendment is respected at the border by requiring law enforcement agencies to obtain a warrant before searching devices, and prohibiting the practice of forcing travelers to reveal their online account passwords, Wyden wrote in the letter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dem bill would force Border Patrol agents to get warrants before searching devices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They also own a ton that constitute defenses against possible negative branding, which are equally (or more!) illustrative of the way the Trumps think of their own business:

    * TrumpMultiLevelMarketing.com

    * TrumpNetworkFraud.com

    * TrumpNetworkPyramidScheme.com

    * TrumpNetworkPonziScheme.com

    * TrumpScam.com

    * ImBeingSuedByTheDonald.com

    * VoteAgainstTrump.com

    * TrumpMustGo.com

    * NoMoreTrump.com

    * DonaldTrumpSucks.com

    * TrumpVodkaSucks.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You cannot buy DonaldTrumpSucks.com because our president already owns it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Hellboy III' Officially Scrapped, Guillermo del Toro Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, Conway said that: ["He doesn't tweet about everything."](http://www.cnn.com/2017/02/07/politics/kellyanne-conway-jake-tapper-interview-cnntv/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The president said he has spoken out against anti-Semitism whenever I get a chance."

For real? [Douglas Brinkley](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/02/trump-obama-golf-235217) was absolutely right when he said:


 "Donald Trump has zero worry about contradicting himself because he does it all day long. He figures he can get away with it because he does it all the time. There is no worry about it. He says one thing and then says another, and his supporters don't hold it against him." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Predator' Reboot: First Cast Photo Revealed, R-Rating Confirmed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So? She's reached that conclusion based on a WSJ reporting as well as her own sources. 

 As the Wall Street Journal first reported (and as Ive independently confirmed through my own sources), the Trump transition team instead ordered CEA staffers to predict sustained economic growth of 3 to 3.5 percent. The staffers were then directed to backfill all the other numbers in their models to produce these growth rates. Set aside for a moment the sheer intellectual dishonesty of this approach. Let me first offer context for how nutty such a forecast would be. Inflation-adjusted economic growth over the past decade has been under 2 percent. And independent projections for the coming decade are equally lackluster, thanks in part to population aging. The Federal Reserve, the nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office and private forecasters predict about 1.8 to 1.9 percent annual growth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  After the election, the Trump transition team began the long, arduous process of putting together the presidential budget. As is always the case, it worked with the (non-political) career staffers at the Council of Economic Advisers. Normally this process starts by asking the CEA staff to estimate baseline economic growth under current policies. These professionals then build on this baseline to forecast how the presidents proposals will affect the overall economy, as well as budget deficits. The end results are often more optimistic than what independent forecasters predict  the White House is factoring in new policies it believes are pro-growth, after all  but not wildly so. The numbers still need to be credible. Like I said, thats how things normally work. Not this time around. As the Wall Street Journal first reported (and as Ive independently confirmed through my own sources), the Trump transition team instead ordered CEA staffers to predict sustained economic growth of 3 to 3.5 percent. The staffers were then directed to backfill all the other numbers in their models to produce these growth rates. Set aside for a moment the sheer intellectual dishonesty of this approach. Let me first offer context for how nutty such a forecast would be. Inflation-adjusted economic growth over the past decade has been under 2percent. And independent projections for the coming decade are equally lackluster, thanks in part to population aging. The Federal Reserve, the nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office and private forecasters predict about 1.8 to 1.9 percent annual growth. In other words, based on nothing but expediency, the Trump team prophesies growth thats more than a full percentage point higher than almost anyone else expects. Even conservative economists who believe that a tax-cutting, deregulatory agenda will unleash pent-up growth must find Trumps forecasts-by-fiat hard to swallow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French left seeks united front in election: A combined vote could squeeze a left-wing candidate through to the runoff round. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Speaking to reporters in Florida on Monday, President Donald Trump said hell name Lt. Ge. H.R McMaster as national security adviser.

H.R? So it's confirmed, we live in The Flash universe!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump names new national security adviser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *After* the tape was leaked and not before. Just like Trump who fired Flynn only after the press leaked the news about Flynn's call with the Russian ambassador.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  After suffering through some of the days drudgery, he returns to cable; as the New York Times reported, he recently upgraded the flat-screen TV in his private dining room so he can watch the news while eating lunch. When the day is done, he retreats to the empty residence  his wife and young son remain in New York  to end the day with more cable news. Which means that cable, and Fox News in particular, is setting the presidents mental agenda. The problem is that while its critical for any president to remain focused and avoid distractions, cable news is all about distraction. With 24 hours a day of talking to fill, it shoots off in all directions. The only time its focused is during a crisis when everything else is put aside in favor of one story. So when Trump tunes in, he sees something and says, Oh my god, look whats happening in Sweden! and is seized by that particular story, even if its absurd or irrelevant, all because of a decision Carlsons producers made that morning. So the erratic nature of cable news makes Trumps focus more erratic. He could be in the situation room deciding whether to launch a nuclear war, and hed have one eye on Bill OReilly to see if hes getting sufficiently praised. Yet theres an underlying logic to what appears on Fox News, one that is almost custom-built to play to Trumps worst instincts.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Trumps obsession with the media endangers his presidency  and all of us </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We initially extended the invitation knowing that the free speech issue on college campuses is a battlefield where we need brave, conservative standard-bearers, he said in a statement, which was released in the early afternoon. We continue to believe that CPAC is a constructive forum for controversies and disagreements among conservatives, however there is no disagreement among our attendees on the evils of sexual abuse of children. The videos of Yiannopoulos, tweeted and retweeted Sunday night by accounts such as the Reagan Battalion, had been available online for years. In one clipped part of a lengthy January 2016 interview show, Drunken Peasants, Yiannopoulos denounced the arbitrary and oppressive idea of consent as fellow guests asked if he was defending molestation. Im grateful for Father Michael, he said. I wouldnt give nearly such good head if it wasnt for him. When pressed, he argued that his interviewers were blurring the meaning of pedophilia, misapplying it to consensual sex between post-pubescent men, even if one partner was below the age of consent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I just sent a message to the mods about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe he was part of the election operation and the FSB/GRU are tying up loose ends. 

Edit: Added two words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a scene in 'Arrival' when Dr. Banks was dreaming and in the dream a heptapod was standing against the wall, it reminded me of the giant spider at the end of 'Enemy'.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry but Trump told us otherwise.

 [Don't believe the biased and phony media quoting people who work for my campaign. The only quote that matters is a quote from me!](https://twitter.com/realdonaldtrump/status/736671884247478272) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We look forward to informing the US administration about Swedish immigration and interrogation policies, the embassy tweeted in response to Trumps explanation.[...] The segment on Fox Newss Tucker Carlson Tonight featured documentary filmmaker Ami Horowitz, who links an influx of refugees into Sweden to rising crime rates. However, Reuters reported crime rates in Sweden have fallen since 2005 even with the addition of hundreds of thousands of refugees.

Fake President tweeting fake news from a fake network.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you watch Fox News? They're the one encouraging him to silence the mainstream media.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Trump in 2014](https://twitter.com/realdonaldtrump/status/521813597799067648):

 Can you believe that,with all of the problems and difficulties facing the U.S., President Obama spent the day playing golf.Worse than Carter

Edit: Would you like to know more?

 [Sean Spicer: The Word Vacation Will Not Exist in a Trump Administration](http://www.foxbusiness.com/politics/2016/12/23/sean-spicer-word-vacation-will-not-exist-in-trump-administration.html): He will never take a vacation he cant sit still. Hes so eager to get things done and change things up  there is never an idle moment and so there is not going to be the word vacation will not exist in a Trump administration, he said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * [Fox News Apologizes for False Claims of Muslim-Only Areas in England and France](https://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/19/world/europe/fox-news-apologizes-for-false-claims-of-muslim-only-areas-in-england-and-france.html)

* [Fox news apologizes for false Baltimore shooting report](http://www.baltimoresun.com/news/83462983-157.html)

* [Fox News Apologizes For False Numbers In Food-Stamp Fraud Report](http://talkingpointsmemo.com/livewire/fox-and-friends-false-numbers-food-stamp-report)

* [Fox News Bret Baier Apologizes For Falsely Reporting Hillary Clinton Faces Indictment](http://fortune.com/2016/11/06/fox-news-brett-baier-false-report/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the press conference with Netanyahu, Trump was asked about the rise in anti-Semitic violence in the United States after his election, in his response [Trump said this](https://youtu.be/f-g9uINtRgs?t=1328):

 Well, I just want to say that we are, you know, very honored by the victory that we had. 306 electoral college votes. We were not supposed to crack 220. You know that, right? There was no way to 221 but then they said theres no way to 270. And theres tremendous enthusiasm out there. I will say that we are going to have peace in this country. We are going to stop crime in this country. We are going to do everything within our power to stop long-simmering racism and every other thing thats going on, because a lot of bad things have been taking place over a long period of time. I think one of the reasons I won the election is because we have a very, very divided nation. Very divided, and hopefully, Ill be able to do something about that. And Iyou know, it's something that was very important to me. As far as people, Jewish peopleso many friends, a daughter who happens to be here right now. A son-in-law, and three beautiful grandchildren. I think that youre going to see a lot of different United States of America over the next three, four, or eight years. I think a lot of good things are happening and youre going to see a lot of love. Youre going to see a lot of love. OK? Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're talking about old shows, check out 'Rubicon' a brilliant show about an intelligence analyst, played by James Badge Dale, and his quest to uncover a mystery.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait to see what the 'Ex Machina' team will do with ['Annihilation'](http://www.indiewire.com/2016/07/alex-garland-annihilation-photos-tessa-thompson-rob-hardy-1201703636/). The movie is based on the first book in the Southern Reach series and it is written   directed by Alex Garland.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 20:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, I'd love to see movie adaptions of 'Revelation Space', 'Pandora's Star', 'Rendezvous with Rama' and many others but with a risk-averse Hollywood I wouldn't hold my breath on seeing something original anytime soon. Best we can hope for is for Netflix to continue producing series and movies like they are doing now with the upcoming Richard K. Morgan's 'Altered Carbon' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 20:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to read Tintin magazine that featured other series beside Tintin, my all time favorites were [Luc Orient and his science team](http://www.ghermandi.it/wp-content/uploads/2016/09/20160915b.jpg), [Blake   Mortimer adventures across space and time ](https://10deb7fbfece20ff53da-95da5b03499e7e5b086c55c243f676a1.ssl.cf1.rackcdn.com/9fa7257404cbfcc58774f56358a76002_xl.jpg), [Bob Morane](http://www.bdoubliees.com/journaltintin/couvertures/t3249.jpg), [the post apocalyptic world of Simon du Fleuve](http://bdoubliees.com/journaltintin/couvertures/t3112.jpg) and [Bruno Brazil and his special unit.](http://www.bedetheque.com/media/Couvertures/brunobrazilcouv04.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kaleida's Think - Perfectly matched the feel and urgency of the club scene in John Wick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From THR:

 Such committees have become the norm at Hollywood studios.

We're living in interesting times!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Paramount was last among the six major studios in market share in 2016 with only one movie, Star Trek Beyond, cracking $100 million in domestic box office. (The movie was also its top performer overall with a worldwide haul of $343 million.) Others, such as Ben-Hur, Zoolander 2 and Silence, were flat-out bombs. Under pressure from new Viacom CEO Bob Bakish, Paramount is trying to replenish its dearth of franchises by developing several Transformers spinoffs and movies based on Hasbro toys.

More Transformers spinoffs and movies? I'd rather they spend money on making Trek movies and spinoffs and release them every two years or something.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paramount CEO Brad Grey to Exit After 12 Years: Paramount was last among the six major studios in market share in 2016 with only one movie, 'Star Trek Beyond,' cracking $100 million in domestic box office. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paramount CEO Brad Grey to Exit After 12 Years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Priebus whining about unnamed sources and then goes on and make a claim about the IC community citing unnamed sources of his own! What a moron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 17:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baghdad Priebus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Priebus: 'We don't have problems in the West Wing' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 17:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 16:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a headline from RedState, another conservative website:

[Listen As Trump Talks About A Terrorist Attack That Never Happened](http://www.redstate.com/sweetie15/2017/02/19/listen-trump-talks-terrorist-attack-never-happened/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Swedish Prime Minister Carl Bildt took to Twitter early Sunday to mock President Donald Trump after Trump used a terror attack in Sweden that never happened: What has he been smoking? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 16:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 21:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The online survey 

All you need to know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Beyond the two FBI field offices, FBI counterintelligence agents based in Washington are pursuing leads from informants and foreign communications intercepts, two of the people said. This counterintelligence inquiry includes but is not limited to examination of financial transactions by Russian individuals and companies who are believed to have links to Trump associates. The transactions under scrutiny involve investments by Russians in overseas entities that appear to have been undertaken through middlemen and front companies, two people briefed on the probe said. 

Now we know why McConnell said this on Friday:


 During a Friday morning press conference, the Senate Majority Leader was asked, Trump said nobody he knew of from his camp was in contact with Russian officials. Do you believe him? The Republican Senate Majority Leader said, I have no idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Hillary Clinton won the popular vote by more than 2.86 million. FACT!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So say we all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The online survey .. 

LOL, Nope.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is what [Trump said about Watergate](https://twitter.com/realdonaldtrump/status/265570772767100929) in 2012

 Benghazi is bigger than Watergate. Dont let Obama get away with allowing Americans to die. Kick him out of office tomorrow.

And in a prophetic tweet [Trump said this in June 2014](https://twitter.com/realdonaldtrump/status/474134260149157888)

 Are you allowed to impeach a president for gross incompetence? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  During President Trumps transition to power, his team reached out to Elliott Abrams for help building a new administration. Mr. Abrams, a seasoned Republican foreign policy official, sent lists of possible candidates for national security jobs. One by one, the answer from the Trump team came back no. The reason was consistent: This one had said disparaging things about Mr. Trump during the campaign; that one had signed a letter opposing him. Finally, the White House asked Mr. Abrams himself to meet with the president about becoming deputy secretary of state, only to have the same thing happen  vetoed because of past criticism. [...] You have a new administration that also has fewer people familiar with the processes and systems of government, including the importance of the vetting process, said Max Stier, the chief executive of the Center for Presidential Transition at the Partnership for Public Service. You cant operate as they did in the campaign context, with a smaller than usual group  it doesnt work. Indeed, Mr. Trumps failure to vet candidates in advance has led to some stumbles. A White House scheduler was fired this past week because of an issue that surfaced in her background check, something that normally would have been completed weeks ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump, an Outsider Demanding Loyalty, Struggles to Fill Top Posts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mr. Trump complains about the slow pace of congressional confirmation of his appointees, but the obstacle is at his end. His staff doesnt bother to vet nominees in advance. His pick for labor secretary failed in part because no one in authority seemed to know that the nominee had employed an undocumented immigrant and had been accused of abusing his ex-wife. Everything he rolls out is done so badly, Douglas Brinkley, a presidential historian, marveled recently. Theyre just releasing comments, tweets and policies willy-nilly.

Such a fine-tuned machine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 17:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the link. There seem to be a lot more "twin films" than I originally thought!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 17:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And who is going to investigate Rep. Devin Nunes, chairman of House Intelligence Committee, who was on the Executive Committee of Trump transition team?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The compliments of the guests, however, dont come for free. Part of the appeal, for Trump, is that theyre all paying him. Last weekend, after delivering a joint statement on North Korea with Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe, Trump stopped by a wedding at the club. Theyve been members of this club for a long time, Trump said, referring to the bride's family. Theyve paid me a fortune. Since his election, Mar-a-Lago has reportedly doubled its initiation fee to $200,000.

We need a real billionaire to pay off this lunatic out of the White House  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 03:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help wanted: National security adviser who can handle the chaos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, I re-read OP's comment now and you're absolutely right.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Triangle did it first! 

I need to watch that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samuel L. Jackson Reveals His Reaction to Seeing Split; Teases Sequel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The reality is, insiders say, that there has been a chill in the information flow. Intelligence sources say the agency is intent on protecting information, and if there are concerns it could be compromised, it will be withheld. The ongoing investigation into whether Trump associates coordinated with the Russians remains a concern for some who handle sensitive data. It can be inferred that there is a lack of trust, and because the CIA has had a role in uncovering signs of Russian cyber intrusions, there are also concerns that sensitive information could be shared with adversaries.

We're living inside a Homeland episode, the IC people need to do something about the Cambridge Five redux at the White House.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are some of Joe Scarborough's tweets the past hour.

* [Conservatives, feel free to speak up for the Constitution anytime the mood strikes. It is time.](https://twitter.com/JoeNBC/status/832724853346033666)

* [This president attacks the judiciary's legitimacy, the intel community, and calls press outlets critical to him "the enemy of the people."](https://twitter.com/JoeNBC/status/832724567017689089)

* [NOT FAIR! NO PRESS! NO COURTS! NO BAD POLLS!!!! #38% #39% #1stAmendment #JudicialReview #ChecksAndBalances #Madison #Hamilton #USA](https://twitter.com/JoeNBC/status/832721073221218304)

* [Someone is cranky that Gallup has him at 38% and Pew has him at 39%. So now he's resorting to FAKE TWEETS. SAD!](https://twitter.com/JoeNBC/status/832719070508101632)

* [It's not even Saturday morning and someone is already losing his shit.](https://twitter.com/JoeNBC/status/832718137996959744)

* [Only a FAKE PRESIDENT would declare the First Amendment to be the enemy of the American people.](https://twitter.com/JoeNBC/status/832717936401883137) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joe Scarborough's twitter feed right now is such a gold.


* [NOT FAIR! NO PRESS! NO COURTS! NO BAD POLLS!!!! #38% #39% #1stAmendment #JudicialReview #ChecksAndBalances #Madison #Hamilton #USA](https://twitter.com/JoeNBC/status/832721073221218304)

* [Someone is cranky that Gallup has him at 38% and Pew has him at 39%. So now he's resorting to FAKE TWEETS. SAD!](https://twitter.com/JoeNBC/status/832719070508101632)

* [It's not even Saturday morning and someone is already losing his shit.](https://twitter.com/JoeNBC/status/832718137996959744)

* [Only a FAKE PRESIDENT would declare the First Amendment to be the enemy of the American people.](https://twitter.com/JoeNBC/status/832717936401883137) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US troops deploy to Bulgaria as part of NATO operation to support Eastern European allies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean Trump himself confirmed that inadvertently at his bizarre press conference when he said "The leaks are absolutely real. The news is fake."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [Trump](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/832708293516632065): The FAKE NEWS media (failing @nytimes, @NBCNews, @ABC, @CBS, @CNN) is not my enemy, it is the enemy of the American People!

Fucking insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump: You know what uranium is, right? Its this thing called nuclear weapons. And other things. Like lots of things are done with uranium. Including some bad things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessary, this seems a trend that comes and goes every decade. 

* Comets hitting Earth (Armageddon/Deep Impact)

* Volcanos (Dante's Peak/Volcano)
 
* Mars (Red Planet / Mission to Mars)

* Attack on the White House (Olympus Has Fallen /White House Down) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Told You So! Trump Never Filed Those Lawsuits Against Times, Accusers That He Promised During Election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sam Raimi to Direct 'Bermuda Triangle' Movie: The film is one of three Bermuda Triangle projects in the works in Hollywood. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Jason Chaffetz](http://www.politico.com/gallery/2017/02/the-nations-cartoonists-on-the-week-in-politics-002405?slide=6) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump needs to fire himself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The leaks are absolutely real. The news is fake." sounds like something out of 1984. #Newspeak  

Also Trump inadvertently confirmed that all the recent leaks about him and his team are real.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget "tremendous". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The end is near.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Germanys defense chief on Friday hit President Trumps dismissive attitude toward Washingtons European allies, giving a frosty reception to U.S. envoys at the largest conclave of U.S. and European officials since the inauguration. Speaking to a packed hall that included Defense Secretary Jim Mattis and Homeland Security Secretary John Kelly, German Defense Minister Ursula von der Leyen hammered Trumps attitudes toward Russia without ever mentioning the U.S. leader by name. There can be no policy of equidistance between allies on one side and those who on the other question our borders, our values and the principles of international law, von der Leyen said to applause at the Munich Security Conference, where Europes senior security leaders were gathering to figure out how to respond to Trump.[...] Without dismissing the spending guidelines, von der Leyen said that NATOs strength was far more than an economic balance-sheet. Burden sharing is a matter of funding, of money, but sharing the burden is also much more than what can be expressed in euros and in dollars, von der Leyen said. To share a burden is to first of all share the principle to stand up for one another. Without exception. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German defense chief hits Trump attitudes on torture, Russia and Muslims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, we're dealing with a fake administration, rather than giving answers they label everything they don't like as "fake news".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Asked if he could say for sure that there were no contacts between the Trump campaign and Russia, Priebus couldnt, instead offering, I dont represent the campaign,

So he couldn't deny it and at the same time it sounds like he's distancing himself from the campaign.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The tweets from Pushkov, chairman of the Information Policy Committee in Russia's upper house of parliament, came a day after US Secretary of Defense James Mattis and US Secretary of State Rex Tillerson commented on Russia while attending summits in Europe. Pushkov tweeted early Friday: "Trump hopes to make a deal with Russia. Mattis thinks (in vain) that he can put pressure 'from a position of strength'. Tillerson is playing a 2nd Kerry. Three lines from 1 administration." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian lawmaker: Trump and top advisers differ on Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's more reason to push for thorough investigations to get to the bottom of the the whole issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did the president know, and when did he know it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Several White House staffers were dismissed Thursday morning after failing FBI background checks, according to sources familiar with the matter. Some of the aides were "walked out of the building by security" on Wednesday after not passing the SF86, a Questionnaire for National Security Positions for security clearance. Among those who won't be working at the White House was President Donald Trumps director of scheduling, Caroline Wiles, the daughter of Susan Wiles, Trumps Florida campaign director and former chief of staff to Governor Rick Scott. Wiles, who resigned Friday before the background check was completed, was appointed deputy assistant secretary before the inauguration in January. Two sources close to Wiles said she will get another job in Treasury.

The best people!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A Democratic lawmaker on Thursday explicitly questioned on the House floor whether the Trump administration is compromised by Russia. Are we witnessing the first Manchurian presidency in the history of the United States? Rep. Donald Payne Jr. (D-N.J.) asked. The term "Manchurian," used to describe a compromised political actor, is derived from the 1959 novel, "The Manchurian Candidate," about an American being unwittingly brainwashed into an assassin for a Communist plot.

Trump sure acts like the  ~~Manchurian~~ Siberian candidate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Dem: 'Are we witnessing the first Manchurian presidency?' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While this is true, his message is being drowned out by the rest at Fox News. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mr Trump asked Robert Harward, a retired navy special forces officer to succeed Mr Flynn, who was fired as national security adviser on Monday. At a press conference on Thursday, he said his decision to replace Mr Flynn had been made easier because he had an outstanding candidate to serve as a replacement. But Mr Harward is said to have turned Mr Trump down. Harward is conflicted between the call of duty and the obvious dysfunctionality, said one person with first hand knowledge of the discussions between Mr Trump and Mr Harward. The second person said Mr Trump had asked Mr Harward to return to the White House for another meeting to try to change his mind. Appointing Mr Harward, a well-liked navy veteran who is close to James Mattis, US defence secretary, would help Mr Trump start to reduce some of the turmoil that has rocked his administration in recent weeks. The White House did not respond to a request for comment about the decision by Mr Harward. On Thursday, Mr Trump lashed out at suggestions that his administration was mired in chaos, saying it was running like a fine-tuned machine [...]. One of the people familiar with Mr Harwards decision said he was concerned about whether the top advisers around Mr Trump would allow him to install his own staff on the NSC  particularly after suggestions that KT McFarland, Mr Flynns deputy, had been asked to remain. When he was offered the position, Mr Harward had told Mr Trump that he wanted some time to think over the idea.  

Smart man. 

Edit: Also he's right to be concerned about KT McFarland, from what I read about her she sounds like an ignorant lunatic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  President Donald Trump fumed about intelligence community leaks during a meeting at the White House with his earliest supporters in Congress, according to two of the attendees. He was furious about that," said Rep. Mike Kelly (R-Penn.), one of 11 lawmakers who huddled with Trump and posed for pictures with him in the Oval Office Thursday.

Not so much fun when *your* own stuff are leaked.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump fumes over leaks at private meeting with Republicans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Shep Smith to Trump](https://twitter.com/SteveKopack/status/832337307466334211):

 Your opposition was hacked and the Russians were responsible for it and your people were on the phone with Russia on the same day it was happening and we're fools for asking the questions? No sir, We are not fools for asking this question, and we demand to know the answer to this question. You owe this to the American people. Your supporters will support you either way. If your people were on the phone, what were they saying? We have a right to know, we absolutely do and that you call us fake news and put us down like children for asking these questions on behalf of the American people is inconsequential. The people deserve an answer to this question at very least.

His talents are wasted at Fox. 

Edit: Fixed a typo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Shep Smith to Trump](https://twitter.com/SteveKopack/status/832337307466334211):

 Your opposition was hacked and the Russians were responsible for it and your people were on the phone with Russia on the same day it was happening and we're fools for asking the questions? No sir, We are not fools for asking this question, and we demand to know the answer to this question. You owe this to the American people. Your supporters will support you either way. If your people were on the phone, what were they saying? We have a right to know, we absolutely do and that you call us fake news and put us down like children for asking these questions on behalf of the American people is inconsequential. The people deserve an answer to this question at very least.

Edit: A typo.

Edit 2: Thanks for the gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope more reporters will follow Peter Alexander example in the future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a waste of time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not answering the question, seems that you're totally fine with Trump's response.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you still think he was "deserved to be cut off."?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You asked for the question, the clip gave you that and part of Trump's response. For the full press conference you can look up the link in this thread.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is the bizarre exchange.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4LkFtuSgEYA)

Edit: Updated with a longer clip.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Snaps at Jewish Reporter Who Asked How He Will Tackle anti-Semitism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is the clip.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-lBm3DMcm-w) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In the letter addressed to Trump and obtained by NBC News on Wednesday, the 10 members  approximately two-thirds of the commission  stated their objection to the president's "portrayal of immigrants, refugees, people of color and people of various faiths as untrustworthy, threatening, and a drain on our nation." [...]  Among the members who resigned are its chair and vice chair  Tung Thanh Nguyen, professor of medicine at the University of California, San Francisco; and Mary Okada, president and CEO of Guam Community College  and actor Maulik Pancholy, who told NBC News that the decision to leave was "an emotional and difficult" one. "The choice to stay on under the new administration was with the hopes that I would have a seat at the table to be able to bring up the issues that are important to our community based on the work that's happened over many years under this commission," Pancholy, who was appointed to the commission in 2014, said. "It became very clear to me in the last month and a half that that voice at the table wasn't going to be able to be effective inside the administration the way that I hoped it would be." 

Good on them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he was asked about the recent rise in anti-Semitic violence in the United States after his election, [Trump said this](https://youtu.be/f-g9uINtRgs?t=1328):

 Well, I just want to say that we are, you know, very honored by the victory that we had. 306 electoral college votes. We were not supposed to crack 220. You know that, right? There was no way to 221 but then they said theres no way to 270. And theres tremendous enthusiasm out there. I will say that we are going to have peace in this country. We are going to stop crime in this country. We are going to do everything within our power to stop long-simmering racism and every other thing thats going on, because a lot of bad things have been taking place over a long period of time. I think one of the reasons I won the election is because we have a very, very divided nation. Very divided, and hopefully, Ill be able to do something about that. And Iyou know, it's something that was very important to me.    As far as people, Jewish peopleso many friends, a daughter who happens to be here right now. A son-in-law, and three beautiful grandchildren. I think that youre going to see a lot of different United States of America over the next three, four, or eight years. I think a lot of good things are happening and youre going to see a lot of love. Youre going to see a lot of love. OK? Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 01:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What we know only makes what we dont know feel all the more ominous. But I believe that facts are forthcoming. Reporters are digging like a crew of coal miners hopped up on a case of Red Bull, and sources in Washington are leaking to anyone with a press credential. Drip, drip, drip it goes until the dam breaks and the truth spills.

Good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone tired of winning? Not me :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The sources said the intercepted communications are not just limited to telephone calls: The foreign agency is also gathering electronic and human source information on Trumps overseas business partners, at least some of whom the intelligence services now consider to be agents of their respective governments. These operations are being conducted out of concerns that Russia is seeking to manipulate its relationships with Trump administration officials as part of a long-term plan to destabilize the NATO alliance. Moreover, a Baltic nation is gathering intelligence on officials in the Trump White House and executives with the presidents company, the Trump Organization, out of concern that an American policy shift toward Russia could endanger its sovereignty, according to a third person with direct ties to that nations government.[...] The Western European intelligence operations began in August, after the British government obtained information that people acting on behalf of Russia were in contact with members of the Trump campaign. Those details from the British were widely shared among the NATO allies in Europe. The Baltic nation has been gathering intelligence for at least that long, and has conducted surveillance of executives from the Trump Organization who were traveling in Europe. [...] While nothing improper has been detected, the Baltic nation also launched an investigation by its intelligence service into the relationship between Secretary of State Rex Tillerson and his longtime personal friend, Igor Sechin, the head of the Kremlin-controlled oil company Rosneft. Sechin and Rosneft are on the blacklist of people and entities designated for sanctions following Russias incursion into Ukraine. He was Tillersons main business partner when he worked as the chief executive of Exxon Mobil and is a powerful figure in Russia who is both a former member of the FSB (the federal security service that is the primary successor to the Soviet Unions KGB) and the former head of presidential administration in charge of the security services.

drip drip drip! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Little Fhrer is seeking a safe space.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In response to a question about the recent rise in anti-Semitic violence in the United States after his election, [Trump said this](https://youtu.be/f-g9uINtRgs?t=1328):

 Well, I just want to say that we are, you know, very honored by the victory that we had. 306 electoral college votes. We were not supposed to crack 220. You know that, right? There was no way to 221 but then they said theres no way to 270. And theres tremendous enthusiasm out there. I will say that we are going to have peace in this country. We are going to stop crime in this country. We are going to do everything within our power to stop long-simmering racism and every other thing thats going on, because a lot of bad things have been taking place over a long period of time. I think one of the reasons I won the election is because we have a very, very divided nation. Very divided, and hopefully, Ill be able to do something about that. And Iyou know, it's something that was very important to me.    As far as people, Jewish peopleso many friends, a daughter who happens to be here right now. A son-in-law, and three beautiful grandchildren. I think that youre going to see a lot of different United States of America over the next three, four, or eight years. I think a lot of good things are happening and youre going to see a lot of love. Youre going to see a lot of love. OK? Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The video.](http://www.mediaite.com/online/the-fix-is-in-cnns-jim-acosta-on-trump-only-calling-conservative-outlets-at-presser/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The video.](http://www.mediaite.com/online/the-fix-is-in-cnns-jim-acosta-on-trump-only-calling-conservative-outlets-at-presser/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is ... Nixonian: Reporter was taped by White House in heated exchange </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 03:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, the look on Sen. Mark Warner, the Vice Chairman of Senate Select Committee on Intelligence, during the interview with Wolf Blitzer on CNN was very telling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He expressed confidence, Flynn said. Thats when he told me that we need to go out and talk more. So Im going to do that. He added, I havent been fighting back because Im not that kind of guy. Im behind the scenes. Ive always been behind the scenes. But this is ridiculous. Its so out of control. Ive become an international celebrity for all the wrong reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schumer calls on Sessions to step aside from Flynn investigation, allow independent probe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 23:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another one?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 23:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was sitting on the side with the staff looking at her phone during the press briefing. And I'm sure you know that she can tweet using her cell phone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 23:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Entertainment studio Regency Enterprises hired a fake news creator to generate viral buzz for its new film A Cure for Wellness. According to BuzzFeed, the studio launched five local fake news sites to host banner ads for the film, while also adding references to the movie into hoaxes about President Trump and vaccinations. The stunt, in effect, became a misinformation campaign that potentially deceived audiences that consumed the hoaxes online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rep. Cummings Blasts Republicans for Zero Oversight on Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a hint, her last name is Conway.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And hopefully not the last.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMC's 'Humans' lures Carrie-Anne Moss back to sci-fi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, the Republicans with their inaction are making it very clear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they deny it, then that is a confirmation that they indeed have dossiers on members of "The Opposition Party". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good on Jim Acosta to call him out on that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Trump administration staffers are reportedly communicating by using an encrypted messaging app that erases messages shortly after they have been received. The Washington Post reported on Tuesday that officials were using the app, called Confide, to avoid being caught talking to the media, as President Trump moves to crack down on leaks. The Post report followed a report from Axios last week that reported Confide had become a favorite app for Republican staffers.

Edit: [The New York Times](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/02/12/us/politics/national-security-council-turmoil.html) reported this on Sunday about the NSC staff

 Three weeks into the Trump administration, council staff members get up in the morning, read President Trumps Twitter posts and struggle to make policy to fit them. Most are kept in the dark about what Mr. Trump tells foreign leaders in his phone calls. **Some staff members have turned to encrypted communications to talk with their colleagues, after hearing that Mr. Trumps top advisers are considering an insider threat program that could result in monitoring cellphones and emails for leaks.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump staffers using app that deletes their messages: report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should all keep asking what did the president know, and when did he know it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Again opsec matters.

Only when it comes to Clinton, I guess. But Trump using unsecured Android, senior Trump team using private emails server and other security risks are all fine, they are not Clinton!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're ignoring all these security problems and restore to Whataboutism?

And your statement is WRONG, Trump "has not had his emails leaked" because he DOESN'T USE EMAIL. 

 [CNN](http://www.cnn.com/2016/12/29/politics/donald-trump-computers-internet-email/): "I don't do the email thing," Trump said in a sworn deposition in 2007, as reported by The New York Times. His secretary sometimes sent emails on his behalf, but he did not. Nor did he own a personal home or office computer. In a 2013 deposition, Trump said he used email only "very rarely."[...] "I'm not an email person," Trump said during a July press conference in which he invited Russia to uncover and release Clinton's deleted emails. "I don't believe in it because I think it can be hacked, for one thing. But when I send an email -- if I send one -- I send one almost never. I'm just not a believer in email." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time for reality check, comrade.

* [Trump White House Senior Staff Have Private RNC Email Accounts](http://www.newsweek.com/trump-emails-rnc-reince-priebus-white-house-server-548191): Senior Trump administration staffers, including Kellyanne Conway, Jared Kushner, Sean Spicer and Steve Bannon, had until Wednesday active accounts on a Republican National Committee (RNC) email system, Newsweek has learned. The system (rnchq.org) is the same one the George W. Bush administration was accused of using to evade transparency rules after claiming to have lost 22 million emails. [...] But after then-candidate Donald Trump and the Republicans repeatedly called for locking up Hillary Clinton for handling government work with a private server while secretary of state, the new White House staff risks repeating the same mistake that dogged the Democrats presidential campaign. They also face a security challenge: The RNC email system, according to U.S. intelligence, was hacked during the 2016 race. 

* [Trumps Still Using His Old Android Phone. Thats Very, Very Risky](https://www.wired.com/2017/01/trump-android-phone-security-threat/): The headlining concern around Trump using Android is that hes likely not protected against phishing attacks or malware. All it takes is clicking on one malicious link or opening one untoward attachmenteither of which can appear as though it were sent from a trusted sourceto compromise the device. From there, the phone could be infected with malware that spies on the network the device is connected to, logs keystrokes, takes over the camera and microphone for surreptitious recording, and more.

* [Trump under fire for lax security practices](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/02/donald-trump-security-cyberattacks-leaks-234973): Complaints over Trumps security practices have piled up since the start of his presidency, with the furor peaking Saturday when Trump took a phone call about a North Korean missile test while sitting in full view of the guests at his private Mar-a-Lago club in Florida.[...] Before this weekend, critics were already raising red flags over Trump tweeting via whats reportedly an unsecured Android cellphone, a habit that could potentially expose the president to personal tracking  which could even determine where he physically is in a building  or give hackers an entry point into other parts of his phone. And last week, Trump left a lockbag  a secure pouch for transferring intergovernment information that requires restricted access but dont meet the threshold for classified material  with the key in it sitting on his desk as the press snapped photos of him.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This asshole is more concerned with protecting Trump than doing his fucking job.

Devin Nunes, the Republican chairman of the House Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence, in an interview with a pro-Trumb journalist about [the Flynn scandal](https://www.bloomberg.com/view/articles/2017-02-14/the-political-assassination-of-michael-flynn):

 In the end, it was Trump's decision to cut Flynn loose. In doing this he caved in to his political and bureaucratic opposition. Nunes told me Monday night that this will not end well. "First it's Flynn, next it will be Kellyanne Conway, then it will be Steve Bannon, then it will be Reince Priebus," he said. Put another way, Flynn is only the appetizer. Trump is the entree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We just need to be a little bit patient, we got Flynn and the rest will follow. Even his supporters are worried, check what Devin Nunes, the Republican chairman of the House Permanent Select Committee on Intelligence, told a pro-Trumb journalist about the [Flynn scandal](https://www.bloomberg.com/view/articles/2017-02-14/the-political-assassination-of-michael-flynn)

 In the end, it was Trump's decision to cut Flynn loose. In doing this he caved in to his political and bureaucratic opposition. Nunes told me Monday night that this will not end well. "First it's Flynn, next it will be Kellyanne Conway, then it will be Steve Bannon, then it will be Reince Priebus," he said. Put another way, Flynn is only the appetizer. Trump is the entree. 

Edit: Update with the link.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But so far it hasn't been the case. Nothing has stuck 

Flynn resigned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 03:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No misleading, he was just following Trump's orders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 03:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe there is a dossier about him at Lubyanka Square.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report suggests Russia tried to conceal airstrikes on Syrian hospitals: A new report released Monday provides fresh evidence that Russian and Syrian government forces repeatedly targeted hospitals in rebel-held areas of the Syrian city of Aleppo and shows Russian efforts to conceal the attacks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 03:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 03:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  At a hearing Monday, U.S. District Court Judge James Robart rejected the Justice Department's call for a delay and invoked Trump's own Twitter comments seeming to seek quick action in the case. "**I thought the president said we'll see you in court?**" Robart said, according to a KOMO-TV reporter present at the hearing.

LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seattle judge lets Trump travel ban suit roll on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 03:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have Eleven so far!

* Sonequa Martin-Green: Lt. Cmdr. Rainsford - USS Discovery

* Doug Jones: Science officer Lt. Saru - - USS Discovery

* Anthony Rapp: Science officer Lt. Stamets - USS Discovery 

* Michelle Yeoh: Captain Georgiou - USS Shenzhou

* Maulik Pancholy: Chief Medical Officer Dr. Nambue - USS Shenzhou

* Sam Vartholomeos : Ensign Connor - USS Shenzhou

* Terry Serpico: Admiral Anderson

* James Frain: Ambassador Sarek

* Shazad Latif: Kol - Klingon 

* Mary Chieffo: L'Rell - Klingon 

* Chris Obi: T'Kuvma - Klingon 

New *crews* indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carrie-Anne Moss and Gemma Chan Talk Humans Season 2 and Memories from The Matrix </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Terry Serpico comes aboard as Starfleet Admiral Anderson, a high-ranking official in the fleet. 53-year-old Serpicos role will be the first Admiral to join the regular cast of a Trek series.

* Newcomer Sam Vartholomeos: The young actor will take on the role of an Ensign Connor, a Junior Officer in Starfleet Academy assigned to the Starship Shenzhou.

* Maulik Pancholy is playing Dr. Nambue, Chief Medical Officer of the Starship Shenzhou. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Star Trek: Discovery' Adds Three Starfleet Officers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, Flynn will get in touch with the Russian ambassador by [text message, by phone and in person](https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/national-security-adviser-flynn-discussed-sanctions-with-russian-ambassador-despite-denials-officials-say/2017/02/09/f85b29d6-ee11-11e6-b4ff-ac2cf509efe5_story.html?utm_term=.06847f488ce3)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A [Facebook post](https://www.facebook.com/richarddeagazio/posts/10154937288174840) with pictures from a member of Mar-a-Lago.

 HOLY MOLY !!! It was fascinating to watch the flurry of activity at dinner when the news came that North Korea had launched a missile in the direction of Japan. The Prime Minister Abe of Japan huddles with his staff and the President is on the phone with Washington DC. the two world leaders then conferred and then went into another room for hastily arranged press conference. Wow.....the center of the action!!!

And [one more](https://www.facebook.com/richarddeagazio/posts/10154937179614840)!

 This is Rick...He carries the "football" The nuclear football (also known as the atomic football, the President's emergency satchel, the Presidential Emergency Satchel, the button, the black box, or just the football) is a briefcase, the contents of which are to be used by the President of the United States to authorize a nuclear attack while away from fixed command centers, such as the White House Situation Room. It functions as a mobile hub in the strategic defense system of the United States. It is held by an aide-de-camp.
and Rick is the Man.

Update: Looks like he deleted the FB posts but the images are already online [1](http://imgur.com/gallery/nnRMW), [2](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C4jtUCmWEAATGhD.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A [Facebook post](https://www.facebook.com/richarddeagazio/posts/10154937288174840) with pictures from a member of Mar-a-Lago.

 HOLY MOLY !!! It was fascinating to watch the flurry of activity at dinner when the news came that North Korea had launched a missile in the direction of Japan. The Prime Minister Abe of Japan huddles with his staff and the President is on the phone with Washington DC. the two world leaders then conferred and then went into another room for hastily arranged press conference. Wow.....the center of the action!!!

And [one more](https://www.facebook.com/richarddeagazio/posts/10154937179614840)!

 This is Rick...He carries the "football" The nuclear football (also known as the atomic football, the President's emergency satchel, the Presidential Emergency Satchel, the button, the black box, or just the football) is a briefcase, the contents of which are to be used by the President of the United States to authorize a nuclear attack while away from fixed command centers, such as the White House Situation Room. It functions as a mobile hub in the strategic defense system of the United States. It is held by an aide-de-camp.
and Rick is the Man.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like they can't find the light switches at Mar-a-Lago as well!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Brian Klaas](https://twitter.com/brianklaas/status/830565403361304576):

 Trump has golfed two weekends in a row (out of 4 as president). Here are 11 times Trump criticized Obama for playing golf as President. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Still, Mr. Flynn presents additional complications beyond his conversations with the Russian ambassador. His aides say he is insecure about whether his unfettered access to Mr. Trump during the campaign is being scaled back and about a shadow council created by Stephen K. Bannon, Mr. Trumps top strategist, who was made a member of the council two weeks ago. For his part, Mr. Bannon sees the United States as headed toward an inevitable confrontation with two adversaries  China and Iran. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're giving Flynn too much credit, from this [NYT report](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/02/12/us/politics/national-security-council-turmoil.html?hp action=click pgtype=Homepage clickSource=story-heading module=first-column-region region=top-news WT.nav=top-news _r=0) the guy comes off as ignorant as his boss: 

 Two people with direct access to the White House leadership said Mr. Flynn was surprised to learn that the State Department and Congress play a pivotal role in foreign arms sales and technology transfers. So it was a rude discovery that Mr. Trump could not simply order the Pentagon to send more weapons to Saudi Arabia. [...] Several staff members said that Mr. Flynn, who was a career Army officer, was not familiar with how to call up the National Guard in an emergency  for, say, a natural disaster like Hurricane Katrina or the detonation of a dirty bomb in an American city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a fun great movie. I'd love to see a sequel, not those cheesy direct-to-DVD ones, with Paul Verhoeven at the helm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kirk Douglas: I never thought Id live to 100. Thats shocked me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nazi-Themed Thriller SS-GB Invades Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SNL Hits 6-Year Ratings High With Melissa McCarthy, Alec Baldwin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Box Office - Sing Swells To $500M Worldwide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 17:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 17:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be a joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 17:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, he sold his stake to a ["family trust".](http://money.cnn.com/2017/01/09/media/jared-kushner-new-york-observer/)

 Kushner's lawyers told CNNMoney on Monday that the Observer will be sold to a family trust. Many of Kushner's other divested assets will also be sold to that trust, while some will be purchased by his brother Joshua.  Kushner, his wife Ivanka Trump and their children are not the beneficiaries of the family trust, the lawyers said. By keeping the Observer and other business assets in the family, Kushner is taking a page from his father-in-law's playbook. President-elect Trump has said he will pass his own business interests over to his sons, Eric and Donald Trump Jr., though it is not clear whether he intends to fully divest himself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 17:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "To have such an unstable figure, incapable of accepting reality, at the center of the world, is an extremely dangerous thing," Sullivan said in an interview for Sunday's "Reliable Sources" on CNN. Sullivan's view is that the president is exhibiting "bonkers" behavior -- and that if they tip toe around it, journalists are doing the public a disservice.

Edit: Latest tweet from [Trump](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/830769247185952772)

 I know Mark Cuban well. He backed me big-time but I wasn't interested in taking all of his calls.He's not smart enough to run for president! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Andrew Sullivan says journalists should be talking about Trump's mental health </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 17:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exploring the Expanse: Three ways of looking at empathy - Examining humanity in the depths of space </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 17:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exploring the Expanse: Three ways of looking at empathy - Examining humanity in the depths of space </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 17:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "Yes, think that's an appropriate action," Cumming said Sunday during an interview with ABC's George Stephanopoulos. "But, George, there's something else that needs to be asked. That is: Did the president instruct General Flynn to talk to the ambassador? And did he know about it? If he knew about this conversation, when did he know it? That, to me, that is the key question. And we need to find out what that answer is." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cummings: Flynn should lose security clearance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF, this is coming from Kushner-owned newspaper? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In her attempt to do Trump's bidding, she may have crossed one of the people closer to Trump than herself  Ivanka Trump. A source close to Trump said that his daughter scolded Conway for dragging her brand into an ethics mess and told her not to mention it again on TV. This was a continuation of a conversation that Ivanka Trump had with her father weeks earlier about leaving her business out of the politics, that Conway wasn't aware of.

Ivanka Trump seems to be the only smart person in Trump's world.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "I am so proud of my daughter Ivanka. To be abused and treated so badly by the media, and to still hold her head so high, is truly wonderful!" Trump tweeted.

Projecting again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: Media has 'abused' Ivanka </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'The Expanse' - Interview with Wes Chatham and Steven Strait </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The talks between Flynn and Kislyak started before the election and continued during the Trumps transition into the White House, The Post reported, citing unnamed officials. Kislyak had confirmed that he talked with Flynn on text message, phone call and even in person. He decline to say whether sanctions ever came up.

Nothing to see, just two BFF talking about the weather.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 21:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baghdad Sean's press briefing is like a train wreck that you can't stop watching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hurley explains 'Lost' to his mom. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The movie is based on a [short film](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gryenlQKTbE) by the same writers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix swoops on world rights to Martin Freeman zombie movie 'Cargo' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 17:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How did Flynn get it?

He was the director of the Defense Intelligence Agency, that's how he has a security clearance. Last December Democratic senators asked the Obama administration to [review Mike Flynn's security clearance](http://www.politico.com/story/2016/12/michael-flynn-security-senate-232654), not sure what happened afterward.

As for how Bannon received his clearance, a [Newsweek national security reporter Jeffrey Stein is asking a similar question, he is suing the government](https://qz.com/904880/a-newsweek-reporter-is-suing-the-federal-government-to-learn-how-it-vetted-trumps-advisers-for-security-clearances/), 

 To find out how some of US president Donald Trumps closest advisorsincluding Steve Bannon, Rex Tillerson, and Trumps own family membersgot the necessary clearances to begin receiving security briefings, despite allegations and connections that he argues should have raised red flags in the reviewing process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A top deputy to National Security Adviser Michael Flynn was rejected for a critical security clearance, effectively ending his tenure on the National Security Council and escalating tensions between Flynn and the intelligence community. The move came as Flynns already tense relationships with others in the Trump administration and the intelligence community were growing more fraught after reports that Flynn had breached diplomatic protocols in his conversations with the Russian ambassador to the United States. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CIA freezes out top Flynn aide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Batman Has Found a New Director in Matt Reeves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing that CNN is going to strengthen their Investigative Unit.

 [CNN Beefs Up Investigative Reporting](http://www.npr.org/2017/01/30/512457231/cnn-beefs-up-investigative-reporting): CNN is embarking on what it characterizes as a major new initiative in investigative reporting as executives pull together accomplished reporters into a single unit and promise to hire at least a dozen more.[...] The legendary investigative reporters Carl Bernstein and James Steele, both Pulitzer Prize winners, will serve as contributing editors to advise the team on their work and executives on hiring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 02:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ramped-up immigration enforcement in several cities this week has resulted in the detention of hundreds or more people in the country unlawfully, according to attorneys and advocacy groups, who said that they expected the majority of them to be deported. Illegal immigrants were rounded up in the metropolitan areas of Atlanta, Austin, Texas; Charlotte, N.C.; and across southern California, among others, they said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump administration begins immigration raids across the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 01:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 01:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The 1924 law gives congressional committees that set tax policy the power to examine tax returns. It was used in 1974 when Congress looked at President Richard Nixon's returns, and in 2014 when the Ways and Means Committee released confidential tax information as part of its investigation into the Internal Revenue Service's handling of applications for nonprofit status.[...] Asked if he thought he would succeed, Pascrell said he believes many Republicans in the House and Senate "are absolutely intimidated by this president."

Crooked Republicans are scared of a tweet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 00:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't know yet, either he made a mistake or someone from our side tipped the FSB off about him. 

From [USA Today](http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2017/01/26/report-arrested-russian-intel-officer-allegedly-spied-us/97094696/)  report last month:

 Sergei Mikhailov, who worked for the FSB, the successor to the KGB, was arrested in December, along with Ruslan Stoyanov, a top manager for Russia's largest cybersecurity firm, according to the economic newspaper Kommersant. Stoyanov was also charged with suspicion of treason.[...] The Russian newspaper Novaya Gazeta says Mikhailov was arrested during an FSB meeting in early December when officers came into the room, put a bag over his head and took him away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 00:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From Russia with love.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From [CNN](http://www.cnn.com/2017/02/10/politics/russia-dossier-update/index.html):

 But the intercepts do confirm that some of the conversations described in the dossier took place between the same individuals on the same days and from the same locations as detailed in the dossier, according to the officials. CNN has not confirmed whether any content relates to then-candidate Trump. **The corroboration, based on intercepted communications, has given US intelligence and law enforcement "greater confidence" in the credibility of some aspects of the dossier as they continue to actively investigate its contents, these sources say.**  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A [counterintelligence task force](http://www.businessinsider.com/trump-russia-dossier-claims-cia-2017-1) is still investigating Trump   his team.

 The task force included the FBI, the Treasury and Justice Departments, the CIA, the Office of the Director of National Intelligence, and the National Security Agency (NSA). It was set up after the director of the CIA, John Brennan, received a recording of a conversation about money from the Kremlin going into Trump's campaign coffers, the BBC's Paul Wood reported. The recording was apparently passed to the CIA by the intelligence agency of one of the Baltic States. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Grotesque History of Donald Trumps Sexual Comments About His Daughter](http://www.politicususa.com/2016/10/08/grotesque-history-donald-trumps-sexual-comments-daughter.html)

* Ive said that if Ivanka werent my daughter perhaps Id be dating her.

* On a 2013 episode of Wendy, Ivanka was asked, Whats the biggest thing you have in common with your father? Ivanka: Either real estate or golf. Trump: Well, I was going to say sex.


* You know whos one of the great beauties of the world, according to everybody. And I helped create her. Ivanka. My daughter, Ivanka. Shes six feet tall, shes got the best body.

* A year after that, in September 2004, Howard Stern asked Trump if he could call Trumps daughter Ivanka a piece of ass. And yes, Trump said that was OK, that Stern could refer to his daughter as a piece of ass. 

* Shes actually always been very voluptuous. Shes tall, shes almost 6 feet tall and shes been, shes an amazing beauty.

* As recently as a September 2015 Rolling Stone article, Trump bragged, Yeah, shes really something, and what a beauty, that one. If I werent happily married and, ya know, her father </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not yet, that might be the next leak!

But they confirmed "several conversations in the dossier involving foreign nationals." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Russia dossier: US intelligence confirms truth of some details </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The useful idiot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on, this is an update.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A winner he is not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For the first time, US investigators say they have corroborated some of the communications detailed in a 35-page dossier compiled by a former British intelligence agent, multiple current and former US law enforcement and intelligence officials tell CNN. As CNN first reported, then-President-elect Donald Trump and President Barack Obama were briefed on the existence of the dossier prior to Trump's inauguration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US investigators corroborate some aspects of the Russia dossier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A senior Russian intelligence officer inside the FSB was working for us until they caught him last month. It is not far-fetched to imagine that the Russians have something like Cambridge Five spy cell inside the White House and the government.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on, he has no time for fishing expedition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sarah Shahi to Star in NBC Virtual Reality Thriller Reverie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oscar Isaac to Star in WWII Thriller 'The Garbo Network' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Universals Scarface Reboot To Hit Big Screen In August 2018: The Coen brothers are rewriting the script, the studio said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  President Trump likes to watch TV and tweet things about what he sees. So when he apparently saw "Morning Joe" on Friday discussing an article that took some issue with the 9th Circuit Court of Appeals's decision against the Trump administration Thursday night, he pounced.[...] This is something Trump does quite a bit. But in this case, he probably should have first read the article that the morning show folks were discussing. While the Lawfare article -- written by former Washington Post editorial writer Benjamin Wittes -- takes issue with some of what the federal appellate court judges said (and didn't say), Wittes ultimately decides that the court made the right call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oops: Trump calls courts decision disgraceful  by citing an article that says it was right </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sean Spicer tomorrow: Gen. Flynn has been counseled and that's all we are going to go with!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the author of that law blog Benjamin Wittes [tweeted](https://twitter.com/benjaminwittes/status/830046040644526081) this in response to Trump's idiotic tweet

 You decide whether the POTUS is quoting me in context. Here's the article. For the record, I support the decision </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
