<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2240</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 05:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very clever!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unlikely Pokemon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 22:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 22:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today's episode is brought to you by the letter A, for affair...
ABBY CADABBY: Elmo, I know about you and Zoey!
ELMO: Abby, it's not what you think-
ZOEY: I'm pregnant with his baby! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sweden World Cup Team Names Henrik Sedin Captain, Confuses Him For Daniel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 21:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> STOCKHOLM, SWEDEN  The Swedish World Cup team suffered a major gaffe, naming Henrik Sedin team captain when they meant to give the honor to his brother, Daniel.

We are super embarrassed, confessed a representative for the Swedish team. We meant to give it to Daniel, but theyre twins! How can we tell them apart?!

The Sedin twins did weigh in on the event. Im flattered but confused. I really dont know how something like this could happen. I am happy for my brother, though, replied Daniel. Henrik was  understandably  more upset. They only gave it to me because they thought I was him?! This whole captainship is justa sham! Ill wear the C to honor my country, but I wont really feel that great about it, he finished.

The Sedin parents also shed some light on the situation. This isnt the first time something like this has happened, their father told us. In elementary school Henrik got the part of lead tree in their class play. Turns out their teacher meant to give it to Danny! I cant believe this keeps happening!

At press time, Henrik was reached for comment, although we actually meant to speak with Daniel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Las Vegas Team Not To Be Named After Wayne Newton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 20:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LAS VEGAS, NEVADA  After fake names were leaked for the new Las Vegas team, front-office management confirmed that the squad will not be named after legendary Las Vegas performer Wayne Newton.

We dont know how this got leaked, said George McPhee, general manager for the Las Vegas squad. Names such as Sand Knights and Desert Knights got out, and we were kinda okay with that. But this was never really a name option. Dont get me wrong, we love Danke Schon, but we would never name a team after him. Elvis, maybe, but not him.

Las Vegas hockey fans were surprisingly disappointed at the news. I really wanted a team named after Wayne Newton, said local Bill Fulton, 32. Every team is named after an animal or something cool. We should have a team named after one of our greatest performers!

At press time, it was leaked that the team could be named after the legendary Siegfried and Roy. Management neither confirmed nor denied the claim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: Czech World Cup Players To Wear Not Jagr On Jerseys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 01:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PRAGUE, CZECH REPUBLIC  In an incredibly bold move, the Czech national team announced today that instead of players wearing their names on jerseys, all players have been designated as Not Jagr.

Lets be real, began a representative for the Czech national team. People watch our team in hopes of seeing Jagr play. This just makes it easier for the viewer at home. They see every player isnt him, and then they can decide if they want to stay and watch, or change the channel. Its that simple.

The idea was popular in sectors of the American market. This has revolutionized my plans for watching the World Cup! said casual hockey fan Dan Clarington, 25, of Baltimore, Maryland. I was gonna check out their games. But now that I know Jagrs not playing  so long, Czech team! Time to continue streaming Narcos on Netflix!

But not everyone agreed with the sentiment. Ales Hemsky, forward for the Dallas Stars and the Czech national team, expressed his unhappiness with the idea. Yeah, this sucks, he began. Im an individual, and people want to see me. This is a terrible idea! Carolina Hurricanes and Czech national team defenseman Michal Jordan also expressed concern. Theres more to the Czech Republic than Jaromir. I mean, hes awesome, but there are other players and other stuff. I dont know, it just seems weird to me.

At press time, the executives for the Czech national team agreed that all players can wear their own names, so long as they agree to wear a wig of Jagrs signature mullet under their helmets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liam Neeson Threat Brings Vesey to Rangers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 00:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NEW YORK, NY  After a long process, college phenom Jimmy Vesey is officially in the National Hockey League, joining the New York Rangers. Veseys journey to New York, though long, became a necessity at the end. Liam Neeson called me, threatening to kill me, Vesey explained. I couldnt say no. I love New York, but the threat was the big reason for me.

Oh, yes, that was me, explained Liam Neeson. Hes got a very particular set of skills that I think would be good for the team. I told Mr. Vesey that I may not see him during the off-season, and I may not see him during the pre-season, but I would look for him. And I would find him. And I would kill him.

Ive seen the Taken movies, said Vesey. I know theyre only movies, but I wouldnt doubt him. Hes so scary!

The threats reportedly did not stop there. Mr. Neeson threatened to monitor Veseys progress throughout the season, and reprimand him on his own if his performance was below standard. I have ways of making athletes improve. Too many penalty minutes? Not productive enough during practice? Being selfish during a game? Ill shape him up in no time.

At press time, the Rangers appointed Liam Neeson to be Co-Associate Coach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 06:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "So I hear you don't want me to break up with you? Well..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 06:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Binding Nemo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 06:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "An IOU for a lunch? Not again, mom!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terrible ice cream flavor ideas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 00:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 21:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Kale? Again?!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 20:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I've never heard of a secretary needing a secretary, but I can answer your phone calls and take down memos." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 18:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd see this. Several times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 03:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent point. I tried to go with the game of "disliking uncommon combinations" with a focus on combos of trivial things, really.

It's not a perfect story, which is why I'm glad I'm getting helpful advice like this. Thank you for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 03:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Perhaps we'll never know who stole the cookies from the cookie jar." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 03:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Through it all, I stood tall, and did it Elmo's way!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
