<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3788</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simple mistake, call them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really cool how you could connect with your own past. I live in MI and actually did the ancestry thing too. I found a cemetery in PA with my family in it as well. All of the relatives that had come to US from Ireland. It absolutely amazes me in one way shape or form my DNA is buried in the ground there; humbles you. 

Document all the graves you can.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honesty is the best medicine, pun intended.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You both need to look into the PSLF program. Your going going to qualify based on a number of factors, then after meeting all those conditions the reaming balance of your loans will be paid off at 10years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen set ups at HomeDepot that would work for this door; you may need to drill a hole or two, but nothing major. I think the call on getting a sturdier door is on you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are getting college at an EXTREMELY low rate, sometimes even on full rides. 

There is a lot that goes into that answer. It may be the international students drive. The school's intent for federal aid or diversity statistics. American students mostly don't have the drive to learn. 

Whatever it is, it's mostly the scholarships.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is the problem. I don't know though, the wave of students over the past 10 years are children of students who's parents were hit over the head with "go to college and get a good job." But now, you have a wave of students who are getting all the bs with the current system; their kids may be pushed in different directions because of jaded parents. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think findgrave pays you. I did this for a local graveyard I found in a old part of town, and I had people reach out to me to go back and do some more digging; apparently I had found a lost family grave and they had me search for others near it with the same name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see that, and I would accept that in my field (law).

I think we would benefit from that type of system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would ask them then, straight up. 

It's just a weird situation, and I may not be reading into it far enough to grasp the issue. 

Regardless, you don't have standing to sue, even if that's what you wanted to do. I would just suggest asking them individually how the heck they connected the dots. 

Maybe the realtor went behind your back to see if you were pre-approved or something. Then the bank/lender got the address and just jumped the gun and ordered the appraisal. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn I had the same knuckle tat planned!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The girl I sat next to at the bar exam had purple hair cropped at her right shoulder. She was also wearing a tank top that barely concealed her 300+lbs (no discrimination, just an observation) and the random collection of anime/Pokmon tattoos. 

I'm slowly designing a quarter sleeve myself. It's not the old days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was the lender and realtor in contact before hand? 

You don't have any privileges to confidence with either party. Your all working together for the common goal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a really good question and concern. I think college will always be around, but there is going to be a wave of skeptics that will drive prices down. Technical degrees will always be around. And even if things get automated, who's going to fix up those automated thing when they break down? Jobs will always be around. Just be glad you don't have to buy in now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here in Michigan. It does create some headaches on the chain of title, but I think it's a rather nice tie to the past. 

I was discussing this the other day with another Attorney, but with same-sex marriages, how does Dower apply? 

There isn't an answer yet, just an interesting concept.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Document all the head stones you can find. They have websites for this and people will actually pay you money to get a photos, GPS cords., and document the names/dates. 

Super cool though, it's a piece of history not a lot of people can see the bright side, these people are not forgotten. 

Andrew Harkins would have thought reddit and everything else we take for granted today was witchcraft.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you pull it out of the wall a bit? 

Mine is like this, but more of the vent is sticking out. Maybe in the move or whatever it got pushed back into the wall and  then fell down a bit.

I had to put a new vent on mine because it cracked and was letting all the lint shoot out. So I bought a new venting pipe to affix to the return on the dryer and then the vent. Also, I bought some of that nice heat proof duct tape stuff, specifically made for heating vent. 

Wasn't more than $15.00 at HomeDepot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deep breaths to focus your thoughts. You have gone through everything before so you have an advantage of how it works. You know the law. Go and execute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dignified Recipient of X award.

Haha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. You have to be able to know when to put it down. Seems like OP has to much on their plate. Come the end of the day, say 5pm, my brain just starts to flicker. I may continue a little while longer, say 30-40 minutes or so on what I was doing, but I always have a point where I stop. Op is just going, no boundaries on where to stop, and it keeps overlapping; the adderall is a crutch to get them through.

Work life balance is key.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Encouragement. 
Food. 
Space.
Look past hygiene. 
Nudes. 
Quiet space to study.
Ease them back into the world, similar to PTSD after they take it, it's going to take a moment for them to catch up. 
Just thank them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dower, eh....Michigan?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was lied to my entire childhood, thanks mom! Urgh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's so interesting. 

What a difference 8.5 duty is as opposed to 14.9 duty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. After the first day of the exams I had a KILLER migraine, luckily my wife had thrown some Motrin in with my stuff; I was having a hard time falling asleep and started to freak out. 

(Back story, I never get headaches and never take pain killers, it was super random)

All your study stuff. 
Computer supplies. 
Ear plugs. 
Paperwork. 
Money. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bombed my practice, passed the Bar the first time. 

Your unconsciously preparing yourself for war. You got this. A lot of this test is mental. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's tipping over I just noticed that! Haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Friendly Succulents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 17:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 17:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a cactus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 02:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really depends on what your trying to claim. I would suggest reaching out to an Attorney who will give you a free consultation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 14:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. I've got a $3,000 old mustang in my garage, pretty junky. Unless you keep them up they are usually driven to shit; it was my wife's first car she can't get rid of it. Plus I don't know your reason to get one, but girls now days don't care about what you drive. Get a car good on gas and just gets to A-B. Save the money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just, wow. Didn't they make a couple movies about this girl already? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called fraud, this is a crime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they are not convicted of anything, then they walk free. It's highly unlikely that are not convicted of anything based on everything they were charged with. If they plead down and try to consolidate charges they are going to have to play ball with the prosecutor. I seriously doubt they walk away without some jail time with what they were charged with; that's some pretty heavy charges. If that "person" doesn't already have an Attorney, they need to get one. Good luck to them, seriously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jail. The length with determine the outcome of the case and what charges they are convicted of. There are sentencing guidelines for each charge. Your jurisdiction will set the min/max for terms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you buy a used car so full coverage is not needed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This really isn't a high school math equation. 

This is a legal question you should consult an Attorney on. Find a local real estate Attorney who offers free 30min consultations and talk with them. 

Who is on the lease? 
Is the lease in writing? 
Are there separate leases? 
How have y'all paid in the past, individually? Separately?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a tricky little sentence ya got there.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't step on any cracks while you walk to the Post Office either, sir! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you building, a shed? No offense, but there are a lot of costs associated with building. You going to need a team of people, literally, unless you can do it all by yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. 

You should have a list of items you have done research on that you know they will sell. This post was *never* intended to direct you to buy everything. You need to do your own research. 

If you didn't do your own research and continued to purchase items that didn't sell, that's on you. Maybe you should re-consider your primary business model before continuing? 

As you can see in the original post, * I did a few hours of research*, before I started to negotiate with the seller.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Employed Individual here...lol 

This is a hobby for me. Always nice to sell something for a profit; we (assuming you do) live in a capitalistic society, bud. 

Just *shh*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I have 1/4 inch tape in red, green, blue, black, yellow, and white. 

If you go on Amazon you can search by width; they have an "under 0.8 inches" selection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not if you *split* the payment, BUT if you pay *two* payments bi-weekely, then your going to make *A LOT* more headway on the loans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Electrical tape, separate it by color.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask. Be curious, you already are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time management. 

Find what works for you individually. 

Don't be afraid to sit on something until you actually understand it, a lot of law school stacks onto the next topic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does that even mean? Lol. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can find free guides online. 

I also have some LSAT studying books by Kaplan laying around somewhere; I will look for them. 

If you want to do good on your LSAT I would suggest doing as many practice exams as you can. The LSAT is a *big deal* it can determine your scholarship potential, and could potentially save you thousands of dollars. 

PM me if you want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha!!! Dude I'm sorry, that's so cruel. 

I'm sure you just wanted to smash that clock sometimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Target looks to not be carrying them any longer. Walmart has them available for $156.99 apparently. 

Has anyone flipped a Sega Genesis Classic? They are on Walmart for $59.95; Target has them in-stores for $39.99.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michigan to Australia. (9,873 mi)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like the disc games, but now that I just looked those up, they are now on my list! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree,slightly. I've made $84 this month flipping video games.

I do agree with you that the market is over saturated with retail, and that the retro trend has sparked higher prices.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 13:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smash Bro and Mario Cart are easily $40 a piece; I've seen them recently together go for $120.00 on eBay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, nice grab! How much were they going for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I think someone else on here put Video Games as a good entry level flip. 

Biggest part about flipping is knowing what you can flip and for what.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a list of PS1 games you buy? 

$4 is a decent price for those two games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be jealous. We make money off stupid people like you who don't google what they have. Continue to buy stuff and give it away, ya troll.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do agree. I was just tying to say if you do see one, regardless of what it is, pick it up and buy it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of those $15 games may be $30-40 though so price out a list of what you can purchase at that level. 

I don't normally go to Flea Markets around me, they are always combed over and over priced garbage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've found a lot of video games at the sales I've gone to. Im just saying if you can grab it, but some people don't have that on their lists of buying. If not, put it on there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was suppose to say *never* grab. 

The only one I've seen worth it is that soccer game I listed above. They just make so many of those games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I sleep...good morning to you sir/ma'am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo, perfectly said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like two screws and three lights. On a scale of 1-10, I'd say a 6.75 on a Sunday in the summer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. That's why when I find pretty much any game I snag it up. 

Take for example Bomberman 64 The Second Attack. Came out right before N64 was discontinued, highly sought after. The true collectors KNOW what to look for and that game would most likely get passed up. Same thing with Harvest Moon 64, easily $40-50+ for the game loose. 

Only games I never grab are Wrestling and Sports. Unless it's that unlicensed soccer game that came or for N64; International Superstar Soccer 64, only a few were produced because they couldn't get enough funds to get FIFA licensing. 

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bulk buys, possibly comparable. 

I think the concepts of BIFL and Frugal are pretty similar actually. 

I just fixed my saggy-ass couch by stuffing it with more polyfill and cutting a OSB board to stick under the cushions instead of spending an ungodly amount on a new couch just to fart on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jealous... 

I just bought this one for life: ["The Beast"](https://i.imgur.com/BI6qbjg.jpg) 

Figure I will hand it down to later Paleontologists in the my family (I'm a lawyer). Haha!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video Games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friendly reminder to BOLO for VIDEO GAMES. 

I know a lot do, but video games is an easy way to get into this business. You can find games at garage sales/estate sales for next to nothing and sell them for $10-$20-$40+ on eBay. 

I just spent a few hours browsing eBay to calculate a lot of Nintendo 64 games for sale near me. The lot is for 30 games, various titles, and I concluded it's worth roughly $647.00 retail. The buyer has not responded to my negotiation attempts, but still goes to show  the deals are out there. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do actively search for rare and collectible books, including Bibles. 

Printers did not start mass producing the Bible like they do now until the 70's and 80's; you should search for bibles before 1960. Even then it will depend on the design and style of the Bible. I don't like to spend more then $0.50-$1.00 for my books, unless I know what they will fetch, or I want it for my own personal collection. 

Obviously more elaborate Bibles will be worth much more then generic Bibles. Condition is everything. Bibles in good condition can fetch a few hundred dollars. 

This also goes for other religious texts as well. My wallet does not discriminate based on the origin of the dollar it holds. 

Edit: The "good" ones are hard to come by. They will usually be the "family" Bible and be passed on. I'd try estate sales before going to the Goodwill. Also, if you can tie the Bible to a notable figure in history--goldmine. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! I didn't know that, but that's hilarious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right! I thought the same thing. That is a lot of money. You could just step out of your house and actually engage people for free, I hear that's how the old folks use to do things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "notes" are what you signed to take the loans out. They are legal contracts that bind you to repayment and give the lender the authority to seek collection and other remedial actions in the event you default on the loan. 

Ideally they want you to pay. They put you in collections and you agreed to pay $200/mo to satisfy the balance of the loan, including any interest that accrued during the time it took to repay the loan. 

I'm sorry but you agreed to it and signed the notes, sometimes called the Master Promissory Note, contractually  binding you to repayment of the loan to received.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't even say, honestly. I have been doing this for close to 15 years. 

I easily put in 1-2 hours per day, 5-6 days a week doing my quick scans of the places I buy from. 

If your looking to get into this I would suggest picking a category if items you enjoy first. Your research will be more fun and you will be able to focus more. Google is your best friend in this endeavor. 

Knowing what your looking for, how much you should spend, and when to walk away are the three most important aspects of flipping. The worst thing to do is buy an item to high; you must know when you buy or walk away. I have seen items I know I can sell, but the price wasn't right, so I had to walk. Just be able to have enough knowledge to negotiate to a point where you can make money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really varies on how many items I come across. When I'm really moving I can average $2-300 per month. I've hit some good buys in the past and it's been as high as $3500. 

It really depends on what you find and how much you have on your laundry list to look for. The more you have on your list the more options you have to buy. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interest is going to continue to accrue. He didn't agree to settle the account for the $6,000, he agreed to pay the entire balance at a monthly amount, they agreed to a monthly payment. 

Yes, 30 payments of $200 is $6,000, but each month interest is going to get tacked on. 

Your going to have to pay over the monthly amount to pay down the interest before it accrues. 

I'm sorry your in this position. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How large is he artist? If it's considerable you'd might be better going with the traditional auction route. 

If the artist isn't "on" eBay, that doesn't mean there isn't a following. Not being able to find items is sometimes good because there is nothing to compete with your item. 

What is the artists name? 

What is the pieces name(s)?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do both. It really just depends on the item. 

I've bought online and sold in person. 
I've bought in person and sold online. 

Usually I will buy in person and sell online. Like I said I get a lot of my items from garage sales/Estate sales. I have though bought off Letgo/Offer Up/Craigslist and have sold the item on EBay. 

I sell majority of my items on EBay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of the business aspects were a struggle for some of my friends who went solo after graduation. It's not that simple to graduate, pass the bar, get licensed, and then jump into your own thing; there are a lot of moving parts to become successful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything I can buy low and sell high. Pretty cliche, but that's  how you make your money. I don't buy anything I can't make at least $20, unless it's a really low buy I don't mind taking the risk for under. 

I do have a laundry list of items I look for at garage sales and estate sales. I've been doing this for some time so I know what is what and the price the item usually will sell for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/flipping 

This is basically how I make side money.

r/frugal

This is basically how I don't spend any money. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incredible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeez, that really blew its load. 

That is a really nice angle of the Mt., great shot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every pot head has a main stash...a side stash...a back-up cover blown stash...and the end all be all apocalypse stash. 

Don't cha know, eh?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doooo it! I love pizza haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's either you or him. I'd give him a damn plaque though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whole cherry tomatoes(?)...if so, bomb.

 Call it The Cherry Bomb Pie!

All the juices cook inside the tomatoes and just before the pizza is done...they burst open, releasing their savory flavor all over the crisp toasted pie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cruel Joke...I think not!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be a little bit of both. My mother's family is from Tennessee and they all lived in a large farm house when she was growing up. I her dad's workshop he had made something like that and kept a shoe box full of gadgets and whatnot my grandma told him to toss out; it was like his little junk drawer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michigan is a no-fault state. Prices go up because PI Law suits generate millions for accident victims. Insurance companies have to pay out, so they raise rates and premiums. No-fault has its benefits, but there are also a lot of pitfalls that come with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the wood just split, you might start to get some sagging. I would call a structural contractor out there to see if they could give you a free quote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would write it like a cover letter, but slightly modified. I would most definitely put in the email your friend's name and make that connection. I would send your resume as well just to cut an email out on his side requesting it--don't want to waste his time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did like this one, but I felt the "IT" was slightly lost with the "I"design. 

Possibly shorten or angle the tail to resemble an "I" more. To me it looks like a "J" because of the angle right now. 

It kind of looks like a jalapeo too (little random thought).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is another jurisdictional legal question. In some places the landlord must furnish a suitable living environment, and in other jurisdictions they don't--only occupation. Same thing when the tenant leaves. I know a lot of property management companies will tack on cleaning fees, most of which can be mitigated and tossed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welllllll...who has that laying around? 

The $250 is bullshit. It's probably the cost his Attorney charged him to draft the new lease. 

This may be a jurisdictional legal question actually. I would call a real estate attorney that offers free 30min consultation near you and ask them if there are any jurisdictional impediments that would restrict a landlord from charging a "contracting fee" to a new tenant; they should be able to tell you off the top of their head. If they want you to come in, call another, and do so until someone gives you a flat answer. 

I get the first of the month rent part, that is standard. It's not a down payment though, even though it's damn near close to a down payment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your lender will have a requirement sometimes. If you don't have a lender, then I would suggest replacement value. 

The market price is "iffy" to me because the market always fluctuates. If your home burns down or gets blown away by a tornado, the market is going to respond favorably when you list a brand new home for sale. But if you get sold on market value, the market could be down and you may not be able to even build a new home. 

You could increase the coverage also if you have property (wedding rings/etc) you'd like to include if lost or stolen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like a re-up on the deposit. If it was the same two tenants I'd say BS, but he doesn't know them, even if you thumb up them. I would have them negotiate with the landlord to term this as a deposit, to which they could receive a refund following termination of the lease, otherwise I'd tell him either he can have his units rented or vacant. He just wants to make more money that's all. I really wouldn't baulk at it to much, $250 is pretty cheap. Usually your going to pay $500 deposit plus one months rent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the 6th logo (blue w/ black ball). 

The name is clearly visible and legible. The logo design is engaging and made take a second look to see if that really was a ball or just a figment of imagination. I like the colors as well. I'd be curious to see it with red; I feel red against black really makes things stand out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your dads a lawyer...he gives us all bad names, screw him. You could report him to the ethics committee of your state for mishandling of funds. He might already have a bank account in your name, who knows maybe even some credit cards...If you suspect anything I'd pull your credit and go to the cops and find another attorney. You can find Attorneys who will give 30min free consultations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
