<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1772</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unit Tests. You're not actually a good programmer until you can do some nice mocking, to test every aspect of a component you write to make sure it's functioning normally for every test you can throw at it, and continues to function normally, especially when refactoring. The other challenge is actually understanding how the heck the code is supposed to work, so you know what kind of tests to write. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's something I enjoy doing. Creating something as perfect as I can write, and growing as a programmer to be able to write anything. To show off what I created, then being able to just think if there's anything I'd want to create for myself, that I have the skills to get to work on any such project, with an understanding for things like budget, etc. I've always had a fascination for how things work as a kid, and taking an active part in that, and contributing back to the world is the greatest feeling.

Some days I have to drag myself through, but I'd have it no other way. I get to work from home on flexible hours, and spend to my heart's content. Get to hang out with co-workers for tech meetings. I landed my dream job. It is that feeling of belonging, and not letting down the team. There are times I need to tell the team I need vacation. But once such days are out of the way, it's back to the sweetest job ever.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5k. Cut spending and bring in an income. As long as you find a pattern to pay off more than the minimum each month, you'll eventually have paid off your credit card. Just be careful not to spend what you paid off again. Make a note each month of where it was at, so you have an idea of the milestone to clear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First kiss, losing your virginity, getting a degree from college and/or certifications, landing your first "real" job, buying your first car, getting your resume and/or portfolio together, landing your dream job, getting married, etc... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have mad piano improvisation skills and can play for an hour straight without getting repetitive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything related to maintaining health and cleanliness. Showering often, so you don't smell. Oral hygiene so you don't have bad breath and/or bad teeth. Keeping your nails cut, so you don't stab people. Keeping pubic hair under control. Keeping on top of pimples. Staying in shape, visiting the gym. Keeping up with your laundry so you have clean clothes to wear. Having at least a decent diet, not one full of only junk food. Getting some sun. Frequent check-ups to make sure you're maintaining your health properly. Honestly, anything related to staying in mint condition. The sky is the limit. As long as people want to be around you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, wish you good luck as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, probably a time factor. Just wish there was a way to speed up the process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think my expectation is too high and I'm looking for someone that doesn't exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those of you that married your soulmate, what advice do you have for others to improve our chances, and when did you know they were your soulmate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pizza and a bottle of Jack Daniel's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're part of the company now, treat yourself as such. Speak up until you're heard, or you'll become a company liability later where everybody loses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Linkin Park - Numb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By having time for other people, and being consistent at what you do. By showing an interest in what they have to say, and actually understanding them. To be there when they need somebody to be there, and be presentable rather than an eye sore. To have great hygiene, being pretty/handsome helps, not offending or upsetting others, or making them feel threatened by your presence. To be fun to have around, and to be useful. To cry when it's a time to cry, to laugh when it's a time to laugh, to love when it's a time to love, and serious when it's a time to be serious. Honestly, just liking yourself and hanging around the right people which can like you for who you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The key to all the mysteries in the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :gives him reddit gold just to prove you wrong: j/k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Batman, Superman, Spiderman, ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends if we're talking about `0.00` Total Dissolved Solids (TDS) water, tap water which usually has various contaminates, minerals and added fluoride, or if we're talking "filtered" water which most filters don't remove fluoride and other contaminates, or if we're talking reverse osmosis water, or even alkaline water. Thus water will taste different from state to state and country to country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lindsey Stirling because she's an amazing violinist that can dance and does really cool videos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you don't have to prove it to yourself with such questions, as it's a given. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, whatever bugs you about the home the most. If it's the door handle, have a locksmith come over to fix it. If it's a leak in the sink, have a plumber come over. If it's a flickering light, replace the light bulb, or have an electrician come over if you think it's the socket. If it's a pest problem, have an exterminator come over. Or if you got some money to spend, just call them all over on the same day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 08:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take out a flamethrower and burn the whole bloody calendar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think Anna and Hans represent the ideal "soulmates", or are soulmates really something more destiny-bound like Anna and Kristoff? What's your experience show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People running stop signs near a school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Physical Education. People pass it just by showing up, even if they're doing homework instead or ditching campus. What knowledge have I gained from the class? \\\_()\_/ I was one of the latter folks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> guinea pig - andes cavy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he's saying it's a kerning fail. Where exactly, I think he means the digits being lined up namely the 1 with a star in front of it. Either way, he's using the wrong word as this is an align issue not a kerning issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never!  `flush();` </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's neither, it's broken code as shown by the IDE complaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you disagreeing on? This is PHP and the code will encounter a syntax error as shown by the wavy underline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs to be `Exception $exception`. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 07:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, just noticed the connection between the flag of Israel and the element triangles as the flag is the star of david with a line on top and a line on the bottom. Almost like it endorses the system. Even has its own [unicode block](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alchemical_Symbols_%28Unicode_block%29):    
Anyone recall a reference to any of this from Kabbalistic writings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of those are strictly from other mysticism circles. The triangles pointing upwards with lines in them though, symbolize air. While pointing downwards is earth, up without a line is fire, down without a line is water. These symbols are not used in traditional kabbalah to the best of my understanding, but I've seen them used before and they follow traditional kabbalistic concepts closely enough that you can say they have a basis in kabbalah. Namely that fire goes up, water comes down, air is light in weight, earth is heavy in weight. The star of David is essentially the six sefirot of zeir anpin plus the center which has nothing of its own: malachut (nukva of zeir anpin).The sefirot are separated into three columns: Aleph (air), Mem (water), Shin (fire). Malchut (earth) sits in the middle column. And because Malchut has nothing of its own, the sefirot can be thought of as a ladder of up (fire) and down (down): the star of David, a triangle pointing up, and a triangle pointing down. So it seems triangles have Kabbalistic significance, however I don't know of any sources to credit for the the adding of earth and water as using a triangle with a line through it. The concept seems to sit seamlessly with Kabbalah though, so if it originates in some other stream of mysticism, there could be a basis for it. Wicca for example credits King Solomon for much of its stuff. Not that they should be deemed a reliable source as they could come up with some idea of their own and promote it by crediting King Solomon. He was the so-called wisest man that ever lived and commanded the demons using divine names, etc, etc according to Jewish tradition. However this doesn't discredit the possibility that a decent portion of their stuff has Kabbalistic roots. If is very likely that some of the stuff surviving in such circles of mysticism, although in very small fragments, could be authentic Kabbalah despite us having no way to validate it. The triangles with lines through it could very well be authentic Kabbalah, even if we're unable to validate it: I see no reason that would immediately invalidate it and it plays nicely with Kabbalah, so maybe it is authentic and maybe there is even an authentic Kabbalistic source out there which I'm just not familiar with. If however these symbols are used in other mystic circles, and developed concepts of their own beyond the symbols themselves, it's very likely such concepts are biased by whatever circle they are used in, and tied to things that would contradict major Kabbalistic concepts. Usually such contradictions result from many years of misunderstandings, mistranslation, misinterpretations, etc. There are also entirely different schools of thought with little or no relation with one another. But in general, as nomemory says, these symbols have no relationship with Kabbalah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 08:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One red paperclip - two-story farmhouse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 08:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Estimate how long it would take, and plan a time to start doing it without stopping no matter what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 08:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Move to Tennessee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 08:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You like all Richards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 08:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 38 million dollars a gallon? Time to switch professions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pay your sibling a quarter to bitch slap you on an interval. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That feeling you get when you have money in your bank and can buy whatever the fuck you want, and just go running errands, buying anything you can down. Then you come back home with several bags full of "groceries" with your favorite foods and junk that will keep you going for the next two weeks, and you go back out but this time you go to the mall and buy anything that even slightly interests you. Finally, you get back home, slouch back in your chair, put on a movie, and eat all the junk you picked up before, and order out so you don't have to cook dinner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same way the first kings became king, fighting over a hill and being the last man standing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I prefer email, easier to type" and because they're harder to write being more formal, they'll eventually wear out like my ex did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deliver a speech full of promises I'd never get around to fulfilling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can start by learning anatomy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, call the nurse instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but when you open them again, the world retroactively resumes. So the secret is to never open them again. Proof of this is a blind man can get into a woman's bathroom, but a man closing his eyes can't because he will open them later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did, and ultimately all we did was reinvent hieroglyphics:
`, , , , , , , , , , , , , , `.
Much like is the case with sheet music:
http://socks-studio.com/img/blog/prelude-the-last-hope-in-c-and-c-minor.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he wouldn't stay dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the idiots that named it thought it was flat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 22:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, it was when their wives hit them over the head in protest of polygamy. They discovered fire later when a lightning bolt struck a club they were going to bash them with, and we keep the same fire alive today in the olympic games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 22:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some desperate passengers tried floating on iceberg pieces, due to the shortage of lifeboats, only to learn they were on thin ice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 22:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> `-ology` means the study of, and because science is so concerned about getting a firm grasp of the obvious, it never matured to Scientology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely a chickendog, all bark and no bite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pharmacy `!=` Bar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 09:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Learn something new every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Last Airbender. I think Peter Jackson would have done the film justice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Create a dysfunctional world filled with drama for entertainment purposes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 07:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under my bed, pressed against the wall, on top of another box. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 07:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Realize short-term it's ok to admire and grow with a person, but long-term you'll probably go separate ways due to synchronizing issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 07:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reevaluate your priorities, and when the laziness of resisting beats the laziness of giving in, you can resist anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [liquid hands](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WRGvAMu_lJ0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cut them regularly very short so it's hard to fit them into your mouth or between other nails. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 18 hour uber drive? Holy crap, besides costing a fortune, that must've been really hard to drive that many hours in a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most interesting conversation you had with an uber driver? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Don't piss me off" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're all crazy in somebody else's mind. What matters is you're not crazy in your own eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 05:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spending and consuming all your favorite foods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eating Contest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming from a master at improvising on the piano here, I'd say: harmony and learning how to play angry music, sad music, happy music, haunting music, romantic music, and other such emotions, then once you know how to play all these, bundle them together with a beat and express yourself whatever you want your music to sound like and change it as your emotions change. Feel something, anything, let the music you play affect your emotions, think of something you want to emulate, something that you want your music to emulate, then emulate it as best as you can and before you know it, you've written a Hans Zimmer "interstellar" or "inception" soundtrack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the plot armor superheros. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rags   Riches, Tales   Itches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mystique /thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sunday, because it's your last chance to spend all day spending, before you go back to work on Monday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The back quiver as per Lars Andersen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quietness helps you think. For example, who can focus on their homework when you got two wild siblings running around yelling at the top of their lungs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All my favorite dishes in one gourmet-style restaurant to satisfy even the pickiest palate. Homemade-style pizza with an emphasis on fluffy fresh dough. Fresh homemade-style veggie stir-fry. Fresh bagels and cream cheese. Salmon fillet. Grilled cheese sandwiches. Freshly made spaghetti, using a homemade sauce. Baked potatoes. Homemade-style french fries using only large peeled potatoes fried in canola oil. Strawberry-banana vanilla milkshakes, chocolate also offered. Vegetable soup *(mushrooms, carrots, celery, potatoes, onions, broccoli, bell pepper, tomatoes, lentils, garlic, squash, yam, and spices)* Eggs *(scrambled, poached, hard-boiled, or omelet: cheese optional)*. Ice-blended imitation coffee (vanilla and mocha) as well as espresso coffee in various flavors. Various salad choices, *including my personal favorite: Persian cucumbers and Roma tomatoes in the same ratio with a moderate amount of red onion, all diced very small, roman lecture in slightly larger pieces, graded carrots, graded broccoli, sliced avocado, and diced bell pepper topped off with a dressing using 4 parts extra virgin olive oil, 3 parts apple cider vinegar, 1 part lemon juice, and a teaspoon or so of white pepper.* Lasagna (my recipe uses spinach). Biscuits and gravy. Mac and cheese. Build your own taco: *cooked black beans (your choice of blended or not), graded mozzarella cheese and cheddar cheese, graded carrots, graded onion, sliced avocado, diced fresh tomato, sliced olives, chopped roman lecture, and a homemade-style salsa.* Stew: *cooked green beans, tomatoes, corn, broccoli, potato, carrot, yam, onion, and garlic in a pot.* Tuna casserole (with peas and corn). Heck, this post is too small to list all my recipes, but all my recipes are gourmet-level amazing. I've been told I should do catering, but I would rather contribute something major to society as a programmer, so I code. I purposely left out meat and poultry to keep it more of a dairy restaurant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 07:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy next to him resembles Hans Zimmer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 09:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The new zealand "deck" ad on youtube </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 08:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would have been my second choice. Be really cool to use the dragon balls for some wishes. Probably wish for the ability to effortlessly gather the dragon balls, thus obtaining pretty much anything your heart could desire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 08:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a fan of the Arthurian legends, I'd go with the sword in the stone as it is probably the most peaceful of the adaptions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 04:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like viral marketing to land itself on social media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 09:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I burst out laughing at this and it's the middle of the night with people sleeping in the house here. Yeah, I should probably go to bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 09:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edge, too bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While statics may have convinced me in the past, after throwing numbers around for a while, I've learned that no matter how many numbers you know, there will always be someone out there ready to counter any argument you use them for with their own numbers. No matter how convincing those numbers are, all it takes is for a new consensus to counter any logic you used them for or for the source to be discredited by a source you trust. Toss lying and corrupt politicians into the mix, and it's no longer voting for whose policies appeal most to you, but trusting your gut regarding what's right and wrong in respect to what you value within a given context over a period of time. There's no one argument which wins all of politics. Politics are controversial for a reason and it's ultimately up to the individual to decide their own verdict. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably politics related, but ultimately I still go with my gut feeling no matter how convincing their argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 09:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd suggest piggyback off family while you still can rather than sell yourself short. But if you're drowning in bills, I'd suggest doing work in a field related to your desired career. What I mean by this is if you're working on a computer programming degree for example, why would you want to do man labor when you could do something computer-related like bookkeeping? I'm not necessarily suggesting this is a good option, but I think it's a better option than blue collar work if your desired career is white collar work. The latter option you mentioned is probably the best option long-term if you can find gigs to keep you afloat on the side. If you get into this, I'd suggest things like dog walking, uber driving, craigslist gigs, or the latest craze you find on thepennyhoarder like breeding insects and selling them on ebay which people buy to feed their reptiles etc. But if you're unsure about your career, and/or flat broke, blue collar work is perfectly fine as a temporary job -- everybody has to start somewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 09:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't sure so I put a question mark. Pulled up wikipedia and still managed to read his birth place wrong. I was like wtf? Australia? I know what the Australian accent sounds like, but his accent isn't that. idk... but, if wikipedia says so, I'll take their word for it. But maybe his accent is something else so I'll just reply with a question mark.  
Yeah, Austrian sounds right. Thanks for correcting me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 09:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'll be back." Australian? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 08:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean they would consider normal from their outside perspective of my experience or do you mean normal if they also had first hand experience? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 08:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call 'em a racist and defend the position like a hardcore liberal would. When they think they have you figured out, tell 'em you don't share your political views, leaving them with nothing and walk away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 08:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An author instead of a web developer.  
Keeping up with technology isn't what it was like 20 years ago when everyone suddenly needed a webpage. Initially for me it was just freelancing here and there, and I could work it into my own time and choose whatever I wanted to work on. No frameworks, just vanilla code so we were one big community. Now there's dedicated sub-communities for each aspect of web development and unless you fit the shoe, and keep up with technology when older technology is no longer used, you'll find it hard to land work. The market got a lot more competitive, so if you're only offering part-time, the person hiring can easily find someone else. Writing on the other hand has never been easier. With the rise of ebooks, I could publish 20 pages of potty-humor with a cover that is pretty much click bait like some half-naked model, and all of a sudden you got the bucks coming in for complete trash selling online for something you wrote over a coffee at your local coffee shop. If crap sells, imagine actually putting in the effort for a decent book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 07:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Theseus's paradox](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ship_of_Theseus). Basically if you have a ship and you make repairs to it, is it the same ship? Now if you continue making repairs over the years until the ship uses completely different wood, is it the same ship? Now what if you made a ship with all the old wood? This paradox is also similar to human beings with cells dying and replacing each other so that ultimately every 7-10 years the body we become essentially new people. Are we still the same person. When a person dies, are we still the same person? What if a solder takes a bullet and becomes an amputee, is he the same person? He gets a robotic limb and some robotic organs. He goes into a coma and becomes a vegetable unable to respond and has some circuitry installed to help his short-term memory. His wife is glad to have him back and he seems normal and acting like how she remembered him. Same person?  He starts experiencing memory lapses with his long-term memory so he gets some more circuity installed. He starts remembering things with ease and his wife is very happy. He decides to get more and more of his brain converted over to electronics until ultimately he goes from cyborg to robot (with a human soul?). Is it the same person? Now what if we his human brain and connected it to a CPU, add some blood veins, and some organs? The solder's wife is now confused. Both appear to be her husband now. Do we acknowledge his physical human identity? His machine identity? Did we lose him somewhere during the cyborg process? Do we declare him dead at some point? What if we found a woman that felt she was a man and trapped inside the body of a woman and a man that felt he's a a woman but trapped inside the body of a man? So they come to Dr. Frankenstein, and he saves a copy of all their memories and injects all their memories into their counterparts. Voila! Who's who? Mind fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 06:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many messages deal with requests, Q/A, or transactions.  
  
   
**1**\. "Can you grab me a beer from the fridge? Thanks *(in advance for the beer)*"  
**2**\. "I'm available until noon. How's 9am? Thanks *(in advance for taking the time to respond and/or cooperating)*"  
**3**\.  "That'll be $73.50" "Here you go." "Thanks! *(for the groceries)*" "Thanks! *(for your business)*"  
   
   
In situations where "Thanks" doesn't work, I tend to use "Sincerely", "All the best!", "Best wishes", "Cheers!", or whatever feels appropriate for the given situation. Whether the conversation exchange was more formal or informal is also another factor to keep in mind. If you're exchanging messages such as like over an instant messager, you don't toss "Thanks" on the end of every message as it's one continuous conversation. But when the conversation is reaching a close, you can end off with something like "Thanks! (for chatting with me) Have a good night." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adam Sandler. He's had about as many bad movies as Nicolas Cage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comprehensive resume critique service from fiverr for 5 bucks (plus 1 dollar processing fee). The one I used quintupled since last I looked and still worth it in my opinion. I've considered looking into other such services on fiverr to get more feedback, but my resume passed every hiring manager I've gave it to since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 09:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I have seen the Face of God.  

Moses only saw God's "backside" whatever that means in the upper worlds. Anything else simply can't be described as "God's" face; Moses couldn't even reach such a level as per [Exodus 33:20](http://www.mechon-mamre.org/p/pt/pt0233.htm): "And [God] said: 'Thou canst not see My face, for man shall not see Me and live.'" If we get too loose with the term "God" and/or "face", just seeing anything that resembles a face whether in the physical or upper worlds would qualify as "God's face". Such terms are heavily rooted in Kabbalah and not to be taken lightly as they're all code for higher things in the upper worlds. If you saw a face in the physical world it isn't the same as a "face" in the upper worlds. God doesn't come and go as embodiments, rather He doesn't change ([Malachi 3:6](http://www.mechon-mamre.org/p/pt/pt2403.htm)). If God could turn Himself into any sort of embodiment, that would imply a change of God. Rather it is the world which changes. The prophets when they speak of seeing God, they are only shown a level of God's radiance clothed behind as many worlds as necessary depending on the level of the prophet how far above the veils he ascends. But anything clothed within the physical is too yucky to transmit Godliness for such an encounter to be understood in any sort of meaningful way. [Ezekiel's prophecy was experienced when he entered the world of Yetzirah through meditative techniques](http://www.chabad.org/library/article_cdo/aid/361902/jewish/The-Four-Worlds.htm). The world of Yetzirah is the world directly above us, also called the lower Gan Eden. The difference between what he saw and what imagery we may see in the physical world, is that he elevated himself to such a state that he passed through one of the veils.
The world of Beriah is where the throne sits, the higher Gan Eden and where the souls of the most-righteous can be found such as the soul of Moshiach, etc. It is in this world, Beriah, which such souls and the angels can be dimly aware of their own existence. In the world of Atzilut, the beings of this world are overwhelmed by Ohr Ain Sof and unaware of their own existence. It is in this world, Atzilut, that the Shechinah "sits" on the throne. It is to my understanding that the tetragrammaton, as it appears in the bible, only refers to the Shechinah. God in His essence is beyond the concept of names as the letters require a constriction. But His essence can be implied depending on usage. Why would it be able to only reference the Shechinah? Isn't it obvious? The letters of the tetragrammaton refer to the four worlds themselves, thus the power of this name allows one to elevate oneself to the level of the Shechinah, as we see by the Kohen Gadol. Any higher, Adam Kadmon, the tip of the Yud, and one not only loses their awareness of self, but are completely lost in God's unity. When the bible uses terms like God's anger, God's face, etc, it's obvious these all refer to the Shechinah as any higher and all such distinctions get lost in Ohr Ain Sof. Once you understand these sort of things, you can move forward in understanding: Any sort of embodiment isn't God. There's even to distinguish between the [Shechinah and Aif Sof](https://www.reddit.com/r/kabbalah/comments/31ygex/i_have_a_question_about_the_kabbalic_conception/). The best we can do is ascend to Ohr Aif Sof, and then descend again except once we descend again then we take nothing with us as we'd be a new constriction. The only distinction would be an impression left on the soul. You don't ascend and remain there with physical understanding of the experience. Ascending to the degree of having re-entered this unity, as God does not change, the only way to do this is by nullification. Ascending and descending isn't a topic to take light of. There's many dangers involved and I won't enumerate through them in this post and clarify what this even means in terms of consciousness. But if you've achieved it, or anyone else reading this has, then we're all on the same page. Maybe in a later post I'll cover it when it's the topic at hand. Thus whatever you understand when part of this unity, would be above the physical and human understanding. The only thing you can take with you back to the physical is an impression whereby you'd know your soul ascended. But the understanding of what the soul experienced isn't something which can dwell in the body without the worthiness to have elevated the body to such a level that it can understand such things. The physical world is too yucky for Godliness to dwell. We await the coming of Moshiach to elevate the physical world to a state whereby it has the capacity for us to understand such things. The closest thing to a physical embodiment of God is man himself as we were created in His image. Yet by the Holy Temple in Jerusalem, the Shechinah dwelt there, and by Yom Kippur the Kohen Gadol would enter the holy of holies and would have his encounter with God when he pronounced the tetragrammaton with its proper vowels. Yet this doesn't means God came down, rather the Kohen Gadol went up. Thus the closest thing to an embodiment in the physical would be the Kohen Gadol himself for having ascended and descended. But the Kohen Gadol isn't God. By Passover we speak of God Himself going around during the 10th plague killing the firstborns, God and not an angel. Yet this isn't a form of God which any could see, as such an embodiment wouldn't be God but would in fact be an angel. Thus as God runs the world, its within His power to affect the world as He pleases. But nothing revealed can be described as God Himself unless we're using loose terms in such a manner that we promote even a rock to the level of God as it has its unity with God and it would therefore be "God" as-is everything else existing thus making the term completely useless as there would be nothing to contrast it. Few coins make the most noise. When you advance some more, you'll start to understand the nullification aspect some more. The physical world remains the physical world. You can only take so much with you between worlds. If you're here to say you've elevated your soul to a certain level, congrats. But if the point is ascending one's soul and descending again without coming back empty-handed, there are many Kabbalists which have accomplished impressive feats in meditation. There's loads and loads which have from the many people I've met and were able to explain some lofty stuff about their new found understandings from such encounters. Do you have anything useful to contribute which we don't already know as Kabbalists? If not, at least congrats on acquiring the impression. But if you take nothing with you, what affect does such an experience have on the world? How does one know one has a correct understanding of the experience? It's not like you can use a pencil to write anything about an experience as it's happening; such things are above our understanding even during the experience. But when you elevate your body enough later, you may find yourself able to access higher levels of the soul whereby you can understand such experiences better. The only use of such encounters are the impression. The impression is like a seed which may sprout into more much later as you progress. Best of luck with your journey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 00:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BDSM sort of dares. Add in some cosplay and things will get kinky all by themselves. You'll be doing things you've never dreamt in your wildest. The truth part has a risk factor to it if you dig too deep and corner your SO. But if used moderately, it definitely improves the communication of the relationship and you'll find yourself able to love them more. It's a win-win for sure. Of course all games get boring over time. It's a good occasional game if you're both completely out of ideas and bored as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 23:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A younger version of Bernie Sanders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 23:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truth or Dare </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 16:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "When you like a flower, you just pluck it. But when you love a flower, you water it daily."  
This one-way sort of love is very easy to understand. Relationship love is a bit more complicated. In my opinion it's about bonding and becoming one: A woman stubs her toe and the husband brings her to the doctor. "What seems to be the problem?" "Our toe is hurting." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a cruel, cruel person. :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High Five </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
