<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3297</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While that's cool, I was kind of expecting them to at least try to distance themselves a little more from the original trilogy after The Force Awakens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But the Jedi aren't supposed to be the emotionless zealots we see in the Prequels. The idea with that was supposed to be that the Jedi were corrupted. They would bicker needlessly when in ages past, they would let the Force guide them to the answers they seeked.

The problem with the Prequel Jedi and Yoda and Obi-Wan in the OT was that they were the good guys, but were so deeply devoted to their ideology that they cut off parts of life that expands one's understanding of it - love, redemption, and forgiveness. Luke was able to find it in himself to realize that while there is a right choice, it's not a canyon between sides.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yeah but he's not in charge anymore.

With how The Force Awakens turned out, that's obvious. Read into that what you will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Killing off L from Death Note mid-way through the show's run......like....why? It didn't help that I felt the two replacement characters felt like rubbish replacements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't even the idea of Diamondback taking over as main villain with a Biblical perspective of things that threw things off. It was more that he felt significantly underwritten and if they introduced him earlier that may have been avoided </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were more like simulators to let the audience relive awesome fight scenes from the movies, that just sort of generally covers the film's plot. And that's fine. It did its job well.

The problem with Shadow of Mordor lies in the original story of having the game's main narrative be about revenge and violence which were always portrayed as negative things in the novels. It's still a fun as heck game, but the movie tie-ins managed to be faithful to the source material where Shadow of Mordor wasn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be careful with that joke. It's an antique.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say that science is far more complicated than just the mechanism to explain itself as you have to have faith in how science operates within the universe. I refer you to [John Lennox's discussion](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MXeccyg3SPo) about the rational intelligibility of the universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The much more common sentiment is that Atheism in no way encourages violence of any kind towards anyone, 

Well, from the Soviet Union and the forced State Secularism, they encouraged violence against religious. Atheism was apart of their doctrine, especially in how they were able to justify throwing Christians into gulags. Their programs and governmental punishments against the religious were motivated by their ideology, chief among them being their atheism, as reasoning for their distrust and hostility towards religion. 

 This is functionally impossible to disprove, as there is no "atheist bible", nor any prerequisite or core beliefs required for one to an atheist other than simply not believing in any religion.

No, there isn't a unifying atheist doctrine across all life (outside of the general idea that there is no God), but atheism has been used to justify horrendous actions. 

  No atheist has ever killed someone due to any sort of idea stemming from Atheism, 

I say that's not true, especially when a country's advocacy for atheism and the punishment of the religious had led to widespread atrocities. 

 Since Atheism has no "teachings" or any sort of "holy book", this should be a rather difficult, if not impossible, assertion to disprove.

Atheism is the belief that there are no Gods. You can just be a regular joe about having that belief, and that's not a problem, but groups and organizations can be militant about it and demand complete subservience to atheism at the threat of punishment, like it was with the Soviet Union, Mao's China, or Cambodia.

  (i.e. how can we know what someone TRULY believes, rather than what they say?) 

We don't, but the difference is that the Soviet Union's policies and programs that encouraged atheism and punished religion is an indicator of a group's general ideology.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Are you saying that because they persecuted Christians the leader/state can't be seen as analogous to a religion?

No, I'm saying that they're still killing in the name of an ideology - atheism and state secularism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Those weren't done in the name of atheism though.

Yes, they were. They were done in the name of State secularism/atheism and they had persecuted the religious for the sake of their atheism which had been apart of their Communist ideology.

 Soviet Russia and communist China actually rely on the same part of our humanity that religions do, the ability for people to accept things without evidence and to live according to rules that would seem oppressive if the critical thinking switch was turned on. They didn't sanction religion, but the state itself became an object of worship, with the leader as the figurehead (I don't know anything about Pol Pot, so that may or may not apply).

Well, agree to disagree, especially where human rights and respect for your fellow man come into play. Marxist-Leninism in the Soviet Union directly [persecuted Christians](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Persecution_of_Christians_in_the_Soviet_Union#Resumption_of_the_anti-religious_campaign) and resulted in a death toll that eclipsed any religious conflict in the history of mankind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, scientists need faith in the rational intelligibility of science in order to do science.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not...even...close...nobody has ever died in the name of atheism

(Looks at Soviet Union, Mao's China, and Pol Pot's genocides). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if these are repeats of others suggestions:

True Romance, Gattaca, Jurassic Park, Pulp Fiction, Saving Private Ryan, The Matrix, The Usual Suspects, The Iron Giant, The Big Lebowski, The Shawshank Redemption, Tremors, Go, Toy Story, Malcolm X, Independence Day, Dumb and Dumber, Grosse Point Blank, The Truman Show, Starship Troopers, Fargo, The Sixth Sense, Terminator 2: Judgment Day, Galaxy Quest, The Santa Clause, La Haine, Heavenly Creatures, The American President, Aladdin, Se7en, Heat, What About Bob?, The Crow, Blade, The Rocketeer, A Few Good Men, Absolute Power, Doc Hollywood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Funny coincidence. Not to mention the bad guy on the Venture Bros. is the Monarch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I didn't know they were going to include Gungans! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boy I haven't seen this post before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Force Awakens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe V for Vendetta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conan the Barbarian was made with the mindset of it being an art film </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the amazing Spiderman films, and I personally think they get way too much flack and hate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Kaz...I'm already a good boy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed the multiplayer of Halo 5, and while the campaigns story wasn't great (I'd love for Chris Schlerf to come back), I did like the set pieces, presentation, and a lot of character moments in Halo 5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  KOTOR has a different story, yes, but it is still all based around Jedi and Sith.

As that's one of the defining aspects of the series. It would be like having a Star Trek story not have the Federation. 

 Same with The Force Unleashed, which still had a lot of Vader in it, and even had the cheesy as hell Darth Maul cameo.

They actually did have a natural way to work in the cameo with Proxy taking the form of former Jedi/Sith for the sake of combat with Starkiller. 

 Republic Commando was a cool game, but nobody remembers the story to that game because it wasn't notable.

I agree that the overall story wasn't great, but it was the steady escalation of combat, pacing, character moments, different perspective of the Star Wars universe, and universe exploring that made it an engaging narrative. 

 Star Wars, as it currently stands, is a very limited property as far as storytelling goes. 

I disagree. I think it's just that the current type of storytelling that's influenced by mythological storytelling and informed by classic archetypes isn't as popular right now. 

 Rogue One was the first anthology film, and it was subpar.

Okay. I strongly disagree as I thought it was a great film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy who sang the thong song?

Was Dominion war Farscape? Or Babylon 5? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Rogue One was really good, but I respect your opinion on the matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally disagree. I think there's great storytelling in the Star Wars saga, and too much of the franchise is just chalked up to "oh, it's just special effects" when we have such mainstays in culture like Luke, Vader, Leia, Han, C-3P0, Chewbacca, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  When they run out of Skywalker/Darth Vader stories they are fucked.

Not if they're inspired by stories like Knights of the Old Republic, Star Wars Legacy, Republic Commando, The Force Unleashed, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For myself, I HAVE been emotionally invested since I watched them at the wee age of 6. It connected to something deeper, and for myself, I think it was my younger self attempting to connect to the spiritual side of the storytelling (which I know not all subscribe to, but I do as a Christian). The eternal storytelling of good and evil, the cycle of violence, parent to child, governments and rebellions, love, spirituality, and family. 

I disagree about the films not presenting an emotional investment in the characters (especially with the original trilogy). I think that the six Lucas era films (yes, even the prequels) will be constantly revisited for the type of epic eternal archetypes and issues that the narratives provided.

I do have a problem with The Force Awakens as it, in my opinion, is a far less interesting (and well told) version of A New Hope that taps into recognizable iconography rather than storytelling, assumptions on tropes rather than writing, and reliance on references rather than universal laws of storytelling. I think TFA is not only a bad Star Wars film, but a bad film in general in terms of it's structure, it's characters, how it's filmed, and over-reliance on audience familiarity of the universe to do anything inventive. However, I think that Rogue One is a great addition to the saga as it has terrific characters and feeds outstandingly into the saga while building upon it in interesting ways.

I think the merchandise and expanded universe came from the appreciation of what Lucas was able to create with a sci-fi saga in which the FAR more familiar motifs of sci-fi universes were ousted in favor of the idea of spirituality, and has rightfully taken it's mantle as the king of speculative fantasy. Seriously, ask anyone who Luke, Darth Vader, Princess Leia, or any character from the main Star Wars saga are. Chances are you'll get an accurate answer. Ask someone a character or plot point from Mass Effect, or Star Trek, or the Marvel Cinematic universe, and chances are that you'll be far less likely to find that universal recognition, out of universal appeal.

  Anyone else think that the nostalgia and the expectations and memories surrounding it maybe hamper our ability to objectively view the Star Wars saga as films in their own right and not just cultural behemoths?

I think that the original trilogy are a fine collection of films in terms of writing, characters, acting, set-pieces, artistic direction, etc. The prequels are where we get into the dicey mixed bag area. They deserve to be the cultural behemoths they are because, in my opinion, they were films that understood storytelling, and did it well within the medium of filmmaking and have EARNED their place as staplemarks of filmmaking that did change the way we look at movies in terms of artistry as well as spectacle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude I loved that one spot I'd be in the map that I assume no one on the planet knew about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shadows and dust... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What in tarnation?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "No shit." Says everyone who watched the red-band trailer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe in God and I try to do the same. I hope you have a good day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   if only because it's one less bias against the good of the people. Religion is not something that is favorable to the general population.

You just swapped one bias for another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the Crusades, 

That was a response to [Muslim expansion into Europe](https://religionannarbor.wordpress.com/2011/03/22/book-review-god%E2%80%99s-battalions-summary/).

Not to mention that the biggest governments and organizations that have committed the worst atrocities known to man (the Soviet Union, Mao's China and Great Leap Forward, Pol Pot's Cambodian party) were all secular groups founded on atheism. 

Christianity has also become an overwhelming benefit to humanity [throughout history](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Role_of_Christianity_in_civilization#North_America). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John Lennox agrees. It's a pro-Christian discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Left button. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 08:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By enjoying two great games? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, you guys DID invent the [Stargazy Pie](http://www.foodsofengland.co.uk/recipe-stargazy.jpg). That thing's a flakey crime scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the Halo series, with both Bungie and 343 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quantum Break, Witcher 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Please clap." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The vast majority of the German population were practicing Christians and they allowed it to happen.

So, are you saying that because the vast majority of Russians were atheists, they clearly allowed the genocides and horrific actions the government took because of their morality/beliefs (or lack thereof in the case of abandoning religion)? 

 Also, plenty of other world changing breakthroughs came from other belief systems. 

Of course. I'm not saying that they didn't. 

 The fact that those breakthroughs came under religious authority does not speak to the religions role in those developments, it is simply the inevitable result of human ingenuity.

Human ingenuity supplied, organized, and encouraged by the institutions. Humanity exists outside of the person as well as within, including within organizations. 

 Those same developments could have happened under no religion,

The Soviet Union's developments of technology and science were tempered by their ability to dehumanize human beings and commit atrocities worse than any religious conflict. Not only that, but even under a doctrine demanding state secularism/atheism for the masses, it still had ideological restrictions on scientific developments, such as the forced acceptance of Lamarckian inheritance. Here's a more detailed page outlining all of the [Suppressed research in the soviet union](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Suppressed_research_in_the_Soviet_Union). You cannot say "it would have happened" without any evidence to the contrary. No civilization pre-20th century had any development in any area worth speaking of without religious institutions. The entire western world is based heavily on Judeo-Christian Greco-Roman history and developments. Not ones holding secular/atheist doctrines.

 I was alluding to the detour that the crusading armies took into Eastern Europe to slaughter Jewish communities.

You mean a splinter group in which the Pope and the Bishops decried the attacks as horrific and un-Christian? A quote from the summary site concerning Stark's book: 

 Along the way, one of the German Crusades leaders, Emicho became set on killing a community of Jews. It is unclear if the motive was financial or religious (viewing them as enemies of Christ) but his aggression prompted other Christians to rise to the defense of the Jews. The Bishop of Speyer took the Jews under his protection in his palace. Undeterred Emicho broke down the gates and killed about five hundred Jews. This pattern was followed in Mainz where the bishop attempted to shield the Jews only to be forced to flee for his life. Lest anyone blame this horrible moment in history on the Christian religion, Stark notes it is important to heed the words of a distinguished historian of Antisemitism named Leon Poliakov. It is important to note that almost everywhere.bishops attempted, sometimes even at the peril of their own lives, to protect the Jews.  After these two encounters with bishops, Emichos forces were careful only to attack Jews in towns without a resident bishop. Sadly, several thousand Jews were killed. Emicho was the worst offender but not the only one. Members of both the Peoples Crusade and the German Crusades sporadically killed Jews in their journey. The pope condemned the attacks. The bishops condemned the attacks. The church was clear  attacks on Jews was inconsistent with the faith. When the troops that had attacked the Jews reach Hungary, the Hungarian knights denied them passage. When they attempted to force their way through they were routed. Their defeat was viewed by the rest of the Crusaders as a just punishment for the murder of the Jews. Stark notes that this attitude of protection and tolerance toward the Jews was consistent throughout the rest of the Crusade (with one possible exception).

 a spaghetti monster, 

As a glib insult to religion from Richard Dawkins who made the creature from his argument of incredulity, I think this is bupkis in terms of an actual argument, because no country (or institution for that matter) has the flying spaghetti monster as a serious religious figure to build off on, including in ways that affect morality or societal structures. 

  the Catholic Church or Scientology.

This is false equivalency, especially since Christianity has [proven itself throughout history](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Role_of_Christianity_in_civilization) to be overwhelming positive in its influences over the world for science, philosophy, art, human rights, and government. 

 I am unsure as to why you're arguing against a well established history that Christianity, and other religions, have had with suppressing scientific developments and social progress.
 
I'm not saying they didn't, especially when it went against different Christianity sect's that held particular scientific axioms as infallible truths. What I am saying is that science advanced so much because of Christianity's involvement, not in spite of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the explanations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's because people have different interpretations of a Holy text. That's not uncommon for any ideology, especially ones based on doctrines. No need to be a dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Holocaust and the Crusades were both caused by Christians. 

Wrong on both counts. First and foremost, how do you determine Hitler as a Christian or that the Nazi movement was Christian based? Do you seriously blame all of Christianity for that movement? Do you blame all atheists for Marxist-Communism that tortured and murdered FAR more people in the Soviet Union than any movement based on Christian doctrine? From all the sourced information, there's more evidence than not to suggest that [Hitler was against Christianity and religion](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Religious_views_of_Adolf_Hitler). The point is though, that it would be a fallacy to blame the actions of person based on their beliefs more than when considering personal responsibility for sins and crimes committed in a ideology's name. 

Second, the Crusades were started up because of Muslim expansion into Europe. I suggest reading Rodney Stark's impeccably researched "God's Battalions", but if you'd like a quick overview of each chapter and what the author advocates as the truthful exploration of the Crusades, here's a website for a brief overview: [link](https://religionannarbor.wordpress.com/2011/03/22/book-review-god%E2%80%99s-battalions-summary/)

 I guess we should all forget about Galileo and Copernicus and their struggles with the church

Not every scientist was met with hostility and fear-mongering from the Church, like Rene Descartes, Sir Francis Bacon, Michael Faraday, or Gregor Mendel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yes, there was a bloody and brutal history with Catholicism and the crusades.

Yes with the inquisition. Not so much with the Crusades as that was actually a response to Muslim expansionism into Europe. I recommend reading "God's Battalions" by Rodney Stark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be praying for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 07:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What is compelling about any of those characters?

Well, let's just take a look at Master Chief in Halo 4. In the story, Chief is portrayed at the start as a stalwart soldier who wants to save Cortana. However, as the story goes along, more and more layers of Chief's humanity are revealed showcasing a man who has to contend with an emotional loss rather than a obstacle. The narrative showcases that his determination to save Cortana is actually a denial of reality in the fact that Cortana is going to die. It's important to note that both he and Cortana's character arcs are directly tied with one another in this story as it explores the nature of humanity with two characters who embody ways in which they are not human. Cortana not only questions what she herself is, but places that question forward to Chief to consider as well. The fact that his character arc places him in that mode of existential questionings showcases just how much deeper Chris Schlerf's fantastic script is willing to delve into the real meat of these characters, and gives his character so much more hope as a person as he begins to reflect on his humanity through loss. That's one very brief description of one character. 

We could talk about Blazkowicz's abstract American ideology in how the dichotomy of good and evil are eventually vindicated through that lens, how Booker's obsession with solving problems through denial and violence lead him to self-destruction, Jackie's obsession with Jenny in the Darkness games acting as both a redeemer for the character as well as a center of damnation, Elizabeth's justifications for her actions actively leading her to be worse than her father and her redemption from that providing the spine of her narrative. 

Let's take a look at Artyom in the Metro games (for protagonists with "audience choice" attached to them). His personal struggle doesn't come from a desire for personal change, but rather his want to see his community and humanity thrive and the difficult decisions concerning what is the best course of action moving forward. For Adam Jensen, the character and player are both discovering what it means to be human in a world of transhumanism; with Adam's personality, he starts off being a reserved and withheld individual, but due to the nature of the story and his own reactions to his augmentations, he grows into a far more outspoken person, regardless of the player choices.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  None of those games have deep and well developed characters, 

Alright, I disagree. 

 the characters are almost always who you make them out to be based on a few supporting details given by the developers.

Not at all. Blazkowicz in Wolfenstein, Master Chief in Halo 4, Jackie in The Darkness 1 and 2, Booker in BioShock Infinite and Elizabeth in Burial at Sea all have direct (well written, in my opinion) and clearly defined personalities and arcs throughout their stories. 

 the characters are almost always who you make them out to be based on a few supporting details given by the developers. 

From the previously mentioned list, we also have Artyom in the Metro series, Adam Jensen in the Deus Ex games, Subject Delta in BioShock 2, and Subject Sigma in BioShock 2 where they're still well written characters and the audience choices are still consistently written, so that no matter which path you take, it still fits within the story and still contributes to their character. Choice only enhances their character traits. And this is only talking about the playable protagonists on a very surface level way. 

And we still haven't talked about the incredible cast of characters in these games, or even the narrative content the game explores.

 FPS games are not character driven dramas and the only difference between most CoD games and the games you listed is that redditors don't hate them as much.

No. I listed them because I genuinely believe they are good stories. For instance, as much as people love Half-Life 2, I am not one of them. I don't begrudge anyone's love of the game, and if they do, more power to them. I didn't like the game's narrative, so that was one of the game's I did not choose to mention. 

 Again lol. 

No need to be disparaging because I have a different opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  lol It's an FPS series. Of course they don't spend lengthy periods of time building characters backstories. What you know about the characters you learn through brief in game dialogue and occasional flashbacks. No one wants to learn about the motivations behind why your team of SF dudes decided to take that route in life.

Wolfenstein: The New Order and The Old Blood, Portal 1 and 2, Halo 4, the BioShock series (1, 2, Minerva's Den, Infinite, Burial at Sea), Metro: Last Light, Deus Ex: Human Revolution/Mankind Divided, Chronicles of Riddick: Escape from Butcher Bay, The Darkness 1 and 2 to just name a few first-person shooter games with a great amount of terrific writing. For the games I've mentioned, story and character are just as intrinsically woven into the enjoyment of the game as the gunplay. The first Modern Warfare game also focused on a particularly well executed story with a good cast of characters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, they have to be trying like hell to do anything worse than the first class posters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I call bologna on that and an intellectually dishonest excuse. This isn't 1996. Video games I've had a multitude of great stories with fantastic characters, who are layered and interesting, and the call of duty franchise has done nothing to push that forward outside of the first modern warfare title. In my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention John Carter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brotherhood of the Wolf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still better than the [X-men: First Class teaser posters](https://static.squarespace.com/static/51b3dc8ee4b051b96ceb10de/51ce6099e4b0d911b4489b79/51ce61fee4b0d911b44a8a81/1299641420052/1000w/x-men-poster-goo-2.jpeg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the Empire Strikes Back of audio books! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention that Marvel had to be incredibly smart about spending when they were starting up, who they got onboard their projects, and how their films connected. 

WB/DC shat the bed trying to do this, SONY desperately trying to get 25+ Spider-man property projects off the ground demonstrated that they had no idea how they were going to make a cinematic universe, and FOX's superhero franchise movies are sort of all over the place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That one corrupt cop that Del Toro takes hostage towards the end of the movie has more personality than 95% of the characters in the Call of Duty franchise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  a political thriller/war drama trilogy, with the right writer(s) and directors

Seeing as how it's Activision, they'll probably make it PG-13 to get more butts in seats, and cut down any questionable content in terms of who they frame as the bad guys since they won't have the conviction to make any actual political statements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was I the only one that used the 2-4 stars as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. Hope it's good, especially since I enjoy Rudd and Jones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Death always wins.

"Hold my beer." - Jesus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, over the course of 10 years, we've halved world poverty. THAT'S AWESOME! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't think that way! We're at a turning point in history where the internet has finally taken hold and the rules for international human connection have never been more free, a time to end the problems on the Earth to make way for a bright future, and a period in history in which we actually got to see the Cubs win the world series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take a nude selfie. Nothing you can text afterwards can be as uncalled for and unwarranted.

You've established a low bar to build up from! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found the guy who plays the Banker in Oregon Trail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is with me almost every day thinking about my grandmas on both sides of my family. It's grief-inducing thinking about whether or not you've spent enough time with them to not regret and feel guilty when they pass. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Platinum games: The quality of our narratives depend on how our ten sided die lands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's mastered canine style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if he updated his costume, he might as well do the same for his search engine preference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know "The Amazing Spider-man" was a speculative fiction film when Peter started using Bing rather than Google.

Full disclosure: I like using Bing on occasion, and I loved The Amazing Spider-man films. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, don't worry. It's alright for him to treat others like shit because he's sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm somewhere in the middle. I thought it was just okay. Not as bad as post episode 3 of Jessica Jones, but still something I wouldn't put at the top of my "must watch" list. It's competent enough not to be bad, but not interesting enough to be goos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better yet, who the Hell would believe Elon Musk randomly living as with a corporate break-in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one not steamrolled by communists, the one with Atlanta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! Great video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless of how you feel about the show itself, cartoon network has oversaturated it's scheduling with only having that as its main flagship show. It's gotten ridiculous how much they rely on teen Titans go for content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Kunis is fine in acting. Scarlett seems like a nice woman in real life, but I genuinely feel like she's not that good of an actress and that better directors usually find good ways to write AROUND her like Whedon or the Russo brothers. 

Portman's good. I like her as an actress. I didn't love Black Swan like everyone else on the planet, but she genuinely has a great filmography. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carla Gugino. LOVE THAT WOMAN! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought she was alright in the film. Not the best, but I really felt for her during the "Mars Breakdown" scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the fucking problem right here. I don't like Donald Trump, I enjoy making pot shots at him, and I think he's a total buffoon of a president, but when you have somebody who makes a point get shut out by strawman in his political argument, you're just being dunderheaded and you encourage more polarized politicking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sssshhh, this is America. You have to pick one of two sides and blindly defend them until you're dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After placating a woman who advocated [shutting out white people on skin color alone](https://www.google.com/amp/amp.dailycaller.com/2017/01/23/white-candidate-for-dnc-chair-says-her-job-will-be-to-shut-other-white-people-down-video/), fucking over Sanders, and generally being a piss poor organization, they have to damn WORK to get my sympathy again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I meant producing western animation in the west. Samurai Jack was made by William Street animation studio, located in Georgia. I believe he was originally from Russia, or that his parents immigrated from Russia, but he's an American citizen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is Joseph Stalin on this slot machine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn you! Now I have to go watch "who framed Roger rabbit" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope that Gendy Tartakovsky, after this last season of Samurai Jack, takes up a role of executive producer to help Adult Swim get more action/drama Western made animation out in the world. I mean, we already have so much adult animation in terms of comedy, that I'd really like to see western animation finally step over that last hurdle of animation and get some more serious work in there. I'm so glad that samurai Jack is getting so much praise and acclaim right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. I thought it was abysmal. You could literally replace James Edward Olmos' character with a series of concerned emails from the employees and nothing would be missed.

I also really like it how Seth Rogen thought that "getting skinny" meant slimming down to the size of young Kevin Smith.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the disaster that was Green Hornet, in worried about them teaming up for ANOTHER superhero movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hot topic sales jump %200 with this news </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We're killing ourselves right now with Teen Titans Go marathons." - Cartoon Network </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for having such a civil dialog with me. I appreciate it greatly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  given that theism and atheism are dichotomous, the latter is no ideology. 

I would say that it is. I present to you, The Scandanavian Skeptic - [link](http://www.rzim.eu/the-scandanavian-sceptic-or-why-atheism-is-a-belief-system). I consider atheism to be a belief, one in which some of its followers are terrified to call it a belief out of fear that somehow pointing out what it is will lessen its merits. 

 but you can't possibly attribute that to their atheism.

Yes, you can. If you don't believe in religious doctrine, and particular morality put forth by those religious beliefs and sources, you may be less inclined to act morally as that doctrine outlines. 

Militant atheism, and total obedience to the secular state, in the Soviet Union, was used to justify horrific acts of wide-spread murder and torture against the religious. They justified their abuse of the religious BECAUSE of their atheism. 

As historian Paul Johnson writes: 

 The collapse of the religious impulse among the educated classes in Europe at the beginning of the twentieth century, he argues, left a vacuum that was filled by politicians wielding power under the banner of totalitarian ideologies  whether 'blood and soil' Fascism or atheistic Communism. Thus the attempt to live without God made idols of politics and produced the century's 'gangster statesmen'  Stalin, Hitler, Mao, Pol Pot  whose 'unappeasable appetite for controlling mankind' unleashed unimaginable horrors. Or as T.S. Eliot puts it, 'If you will not have God (and he is a jealous God) you should pay your respects to Hitler or Stalin.'

Ridding a people of their religious and spiritual values can cause a moral vacuum. The abuse and murders of the religious at the hands of the atheistic Communist governments of the 20th century were done to keep the State's power. That doctrine adhering to atheism is what opened the floodgates for the destruction of the religious by forcing the people to accept the concept that the only God is the God of the state and all other heretics would be killed. 

 but you can't possibly attribute that to their atheism.

You're right. I don't blame atheism. I blame the people who twisted that ideology to suit their justifications for murder. When it becomes a rampant enough problem that leads large groups to frequent enough acts of destruction and violence, that's when the ideology must be addressed. Marxism-Leninism was a clear case of atheism taken too far to justify atrocities. 

 Everyone who doesn't specifically accept the narrow set of theistic claims as true, is an atheist. 

That itself is an acception of a narrow claim as true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So if someone died in war fighting for a country believed to have an atheist leader at the time, that person is responsible for the death? Or what?

....what the Hell are you talking about? I'm referring to a government, organization, or institution pushing an atheistic/secular doctrine when they committed horrific genocides as justification. I don't think that people are atheist naturally have any predospitions to violence, like any rational human being. I'm pointing out the fact that people have twisted ideologies into terrifying tools to justify oppression and killing others. I do tend to lay the majority of the blame of people who are responsible for mass killings and wars at the feet of people who declare them.

Not a Communist WEBSITE. Communist organizations CAUSING death. We have things like Mao's Great Leap Forward, Stalin's Holodomer, or the Cambodian genocide. 

Martin Malia in the Black Book of Communism came to the number of people killed by the ideology (which used a main tenant of atheism to support it's belief structure), as between 85-100 million people. Even the most conservative estimations of Communistic regimes following tennants of militant atheism still eclipse the larger estimates of people who've died in the Crusades itself. 

 You don't even have to add anything else up to see that the claim in your quote is bullshit.

Yeah, I don't think you actually the argument is based on the fact the numbers you're quoting are using deaths contributed by Communist forces.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Instead, atheism made the most sense to these regimes because the state was the god. 

If we're cutting into semantics, the state was the highest power not God. Anything and anyone claiming otherwise was a threat, and religious institutions citing power above the state were deemed dangerous. 

 But people were not actually murdered in the name of atheism,

They were. They were killed because they refused to abandon their religion for total obedience to the secular state, and the state ideology of atheism. They were killing people for their worship and religion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, dude, when citing your examples, don't use statistics from Communistic regimes. You're proving my point: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mass_killings_under_Communist_regimes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And your lack of comprehension is showing.

Did you miss the part where you quoted that "Good people to do evil things, that takes religion"? The quote is saying that religion itself is what solely drives a good person to be evil, which is dangerously ignorant of the fact that good people can be driven to do evil acts for a variety of reasons and ideologies. My point was that devotion to state secularism and atheism in Communist states led to the deaths of countless believers, and some of the worst genocides in human existence were led by those who believed in getting rid of religious influences. 

An ideology you hold doesn't make you evil. Mao, Stalin, and Pot were atheists and were influenced by their ideology, but that doesn't inherently make you evil if you yourself are also an atheist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm offensive, and I find this gay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, love every Halo game. One of my favorite series since you can have a plethora of these kinds of stories with you and your buddies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, to be fair, you can be an atheist, like Stalin, Mao, and Pott,  listen to no religious doctrine telling you how to live, and still commit heinous acts of murdering people who hold different beliefs than you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "Religion is an insult to human dignity. With or without it you would have good people doing good things and evil people doing evil things. But for good people to do evil things, that takes religion" ~ Steven Weinberg

Your hypocrisy is showing. 

 "Apparently it was just an amazing coincidence that every Communist of historical note publicly declared his atheism there have been twenty-eight countries in world history that can be confirmed to have been ruled by regimes with avowed atheists at the helmThese twenty-eight historical regimes have been ruled by eighty-nine atheists, of whom more than half have engaged in democidal acts of the sort committed by Stalin and Mao 
The total body count for the ninety years between 1917 and 2007 is approximately 148 million dead at the bloody hands of fifty-two atheists, three times more than all the human beings killed by war, civil war, and individual crime in the entire twentieth century combined." - Theodore Beale

Don't make sweeping grand-standing statements about ideology, because then it can be reversed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So you honestly don't think there's a difference between how white people perceive Asians vs. other minorities?

I wouldn't genuinely know, because I personally think judging an entire race of people is stupid. 

 I was speaking in other cases. Not this one.

Okay, do you have an example of a previous situation?

 I don't understand your argument. White people can't see Asians as a model minority because you (and other white people) love Asians?

No, my argument, then, as well as the additions was that the media or portraying asian characters isn't the "model minority" as complex characters so I do want to know what you mean by "culture". General perception of a race in their entertainment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not a conspiracy theory that Reddit is hostile to minorities. Lol wtf?

Yes, because questioning your stance on a topic is....hostile? 

 And you're actually trying to act as if Asians aren't considered the "model minority" in American culture.

In American culture? Which parts? Like The Walking Dead where the a whole slew of people refused to watch the show anymore because the heart and soul of the series died with Glenn, the everyman character? Or Elodie Yung brilliantly playing Elektra in season 2 of Daredevil, who I will fight to this day about concerning how great she was in a great season of TV. How about Benedict Wong as one of the best parts of both The Martian and Doctor Strange?Sleeping Dogs where the Chinese main character is a man performing his duty as a morally conflicted cop? Brian Tee playing the wonderfully slimy Nobu in The Wolverine? 

 I'm not saying the concept of the "model minority" is factual.

Okay. 

 I'm referencing the perception that Asians are a model minority in the eyes of white people. And that's just a fact.

So, the abstract notion of a model minority isn't factual, but the abstract notion of Asians being a model minority in the eyes of all/most white people in the U.S. is factual?

....wut.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Riiiight. It's just a coincidence that a majority white subreddit and website is notoriously insensitive to minority issues and that "model minority" behavior (a sociological fact) is constantly exhibited on this subreddit in regards to Asians vs. other minorities.

....are you actually making a racial conspiracy theory right now? That's just....really sad.

I want more diversity in video games, films, and shows. However, that's out of a personal desire to see more diverse people in films, and not one that should be propagated as a marching order for studios for the sake of social change. I like seeing good movies with minority actors in them, so I'll be especially on the lookout for a diverse cast, which is how you make change in a capitalist society, especially with productions closely tied to financial gain with entertainment.  

What's even more confusing is that while the argument of white-washing (which just gets tossed around these days, looking at the insta-controversies of Doctor Strange and Iron fist, that I feel were poorly argued from a lot of people decrying that the stories were racist) is still valid in some arguments (especially in context to the original character in comparison to Johansson in the role), no one seems to be talking about the idea of transhumanism as a core theme to the story, and only analyzing it within the bubble of controversy they see. My bigger gripe with the Ghost in the Shell film is that it's not a good movie. Full stop. 

 (a sociological fact)

No, it is not. Even bringing in the articles debunking that stance (link)[https://theithacan.org/columns/debunking-the-myth-of-the-model-minority/], it is not at all a scientifically proven anything. At best, it's a concept with outdated bulk data. One that rational human beings don't subscribe to because judging an entire race of people is foolish on either end of the spectrum, and it makes no sense to do that. 

Arguing that model minorities are a real thing would be the same as arguing for any other issue surmising an entire race (or a majority of a race) having a certain characteristic, which is damn foolish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Because you're still making the fallacy of assuming someone's character (or an entire group of people, even partial) based off of their melanin levels. You completely missed the point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming all white Redditors have a problem with a different opinion (i.e., blindly judging an entire race of people) is racist. Switch out "white" with any other race, and see how that sounds when saying it out loud.

By the way, I am white and I upvoted the article, so maybe not assuming someone's character by their skin color is the best way to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  White Redditors don't actually care about what Japanese people have to say about this subject unless they agree with them. 

Wow, that's racist as hell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fully armed and operational </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Zoinks! A gu-guh-ghost! Let's high-tail it out of here, Scoob!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
