<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1565</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This world of instant gratification and online shopping is not an improvement. The people who say things like were said to you speak from a position of ignorance. I'm so glad I grew up at the time I did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a huge disappointment when there was no foldout. The best bands always seemed to realize this and had great booklets too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fully agree. I think back to all the Saturday mornings that I spent with my best friend jumping on the TTC and riding down to Sam The Record Man or HMV in downtown Toronto to buy the newest CD or (cough) cassette from our favourite bands. The thrill of walking in the door, seeing the display, and then picking up your very own copy is not something that youth today get to experience, which is really sad. Once it was mine I would rip open the plastic wrap and immediately take out the little booklet inside to see what the artwork is and if the band had put the lyrics in. I would have some of the lyrics memorized even before I got to hear some of the songs. The experience of just getting an album was half the fun. iTunes can't replicate that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes they do. Any merger can be stopped and reviewed by the government. For example, why do you think the Manitoba Telecom / BCE deal took so long? Because the government stepped in. If they have a problem with a potential merger they can and do step in. Take the Allergan / Pfizer deal in the US last year. The US government had such a problem with the deal that they essentially created a new law that prevented Pfizer merging with Allergan and becoming an Irish (tax haven) company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big tobacco will never be allowed to buy weed companies. The government would reject the merger, as it would look exceptionally bad for the most taboo industry to seize the profits from legal weed. Not to mention, so many people would boycott any weed sold by a tobacco company that it would be a very bad investment for the tobacco to make. Tobacco companies may take a shot at themselves, but they won't buy any of the big names. My opinion only.

Big pharma should be scared shitless, as there will be a lot of people ditching pills for weed. Suffer from anxiety? Fuck Ativan, smoke a joint or put a few drops of oil under your tongue. Pharma seem the most likely to try and make an acquisition, but again, I have a hard time seeing the government allowing it, and they reserve the right to approve or deny all mergers. Again, my humble opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 11:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! It's nice to know I'm not the only person who find this annoying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget the Kiwis. New Zealander's, especially those with Maori backgrounds say "eh" more than the Canadians. Found this out being a Canadian that lived in NZ for years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
