<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3240</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading. I have ADHD and it's really difficult for me to stay focused on one task or complete projects. Books with good, interesting content allow me to focus on something for a long period of time, and being able to actually complete something really motivates me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheating on your partner, having "side hoes", etc etc. The normalization of abusive relationships too. The amount of memes I see about partners being posessive, jealous, and paranoid is just straight up disgusting and sad. This isn't healthy and it shouldn't be the norm, stop making it into a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom grew up in northern Wisconsin on the edge of Lake Superior (if anyone knows where Washburn is, it is beautiful and my grandfather was county sheriff for like 25 or so years) and they also had bagged milk. Seems the really northern parts of the US actually get some of that Canadian culture you guys seem to think doesn't exist. All my relatives there have the accent too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 18:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always had a really open line of communication with my parents, so it never bothered me because they pretty much knew everything I was already doing and were okay with it (they understand that 20 is a pretty normal age to be having sex, drinking, and maybe the occasional joint) so I never had to worry about asking them to leave or stay. I think the way the nurse posed the question, "I'm going to be asking personal questions" instead of like "I'm going to be asking you about drugs and sex" was a good idea. And parents should also understand that if their child needs them to leave, it is for their best health interest.

I saw some story once about a girl who was ill from an early pregnancy that was having complications, and the doctors couldn't figure out what was wrong because she INSISTED she wasn't sexually active because her parents were there the whole time. Her brother finally went off on his parents about how they need to accept their daughter is an adult (she was like 22) and that she could be having sex. She finally told them the truth and they managed to save both her and the baby.

TL;DR parents need to respect their child's medical confidentiality, regardless of personal belief </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 20:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might be more affective to tap the 'k' key three times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 20:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I was super supportive of my sister other than the occasional joke (because we're siblongs, it's what we do) until I realized she only does it because she has a superiority complex and is just doing what everyone else is. I'm just waiting for her to become an anti-vaxx, gluten-free super lib at this point.

And I love garden burgers, they're super flippin delicious, especially if you get a veggie patty. My best friend is a vegetarian due to medical issues and she's super chill about it, knows all the good recipes haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 03:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "See you later." (Midna, Legend of Zelda: Twilight Princess)

Maybe not the MOST depressing video game moment ever, but damn, Midna was so cool and seeing her shatter the Mirror of Twilight and after all of her character development...damn. Also Fi at the end of Skyward Swoed, but her annoyingness made it a little less emotional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
