<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1101</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 05:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> streamline

mainline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 05:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are you laszlo lowenstein? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 09:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heart Songs needs more votes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 20:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Pinkerton but you should hear Blue first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 23:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Dreamin'. But it's going to be Angel and the One. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 20:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably my second favorite on the album after Pathetic. Love the "be brave be strong" bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 04:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 03:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably because the Rock Band multitrack is easily available so editing it smoothly is easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 02:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why should you try to be intimidating? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 06:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Golden Eel is the best song on that album for me, that or the title track. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 06:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a fan. Their best album would be White Pepper for me, or Quebec. Let's hope this reunion ends up making another album, La Cuch is kinda lackluster especially as a finale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 20:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> marryin a beyotch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 18:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have probably seen like 50 "nice shot lol" jokes in this thread. Even if it wasn't S0 Edgy, how do people actually find that funny? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 05:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, so great to see another Stylised fan in the wild. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 05:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always like hearing it. It's cool to me that it's so widespread and long lasting. Just feels like a neat shoutout to hear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 17:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically it's only 1/3. Poor Scott. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 06:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh? No, you don't get EP credit just for directing the first episode of a show, that wouldn't make any sense. For instance, Fargo's first two episodes were directed by Adam Bernstein, but outside of them he has no other credits on the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 23:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming the OP is sarcastic, I'm pretty sure Prince himself was planning on doing this anyway. He told his manager that he wanted it to be like Graceland eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 21:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'll go with Pardon Me. It's just kind of a less good Hold Me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 19:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 6'4" and I've since realized that after unintentionally whacking my head while trying to exit the bus about 1000 times I kinda hate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 09:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the most recent SP seasons, that's actually not too implausible... ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 18:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont you need the two ws? It sure wouldn't sound the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 17:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok I'm pretty curious how this is what came to mind for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 17:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No dude, 2HF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 21:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to see Haunt You Every Day doing well. One of their best closers imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 06:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see why not. He still has an active second account at @BarackObama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 19:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freak Me Out is kinda stupid, but I love the harmonica. One of the few tracks on the album that actually sounds interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 20:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, this is really bad. Reminds me of the Raditude days when he was out to collaborate with every known artist alive regardless of their compatibility (remember that duet he did with Miranda Cosgrove?). The lyrics are nothing special and the rap seems insanely out of place over that loud diseased beat. Not gonna listen to this again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 20:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great song. Big fan of the harmonies on the "I want a girl" line in the chorus, and Brian's extended "and if you watch her gooooooo". It's definitely one of Blue's more simple tunes but I'm never not in the mood to listen to it. Kinda reminds me of Susanne in that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 20:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you take it at face value it's definitely misogynistic. Although it's meant to be over the top I'm not too surprised there would be people who would come to that conclusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 20:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Song is definitely modeled after Pork and Beans, I can't hear much of Beverly Hills in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 19:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 40-Year-Old Virgin, Knocked Up, Funny People, This Is 40, and Trainwreck were all directed by him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 19:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> something like "Trump and the GOP want to court black votes but then slam voting rights for felons". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 18:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true but IMO with Apatow there's a difference in the more wordy and lengthy movies that he directs himself and the ones he's produced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 17:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the record Apatow didn't direct any of those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 17:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I watched it after too many years of massive hype, was extraordinarily underwhelmed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 10:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For them I'd go Exactly Where I'm At, You Were the Fool, and The Golden Eel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 08:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is going to be the last one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 06:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Review got cancelled a while ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jack Riley (Eliot Carlin on 'The Bob Newhart Show,' Stu Pickles on 'Rugrats') Dies at 80 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 22:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It took i real beating when kobain died, however it was soundgarden rhat put it to rest when they broke up. Most of us had a feeling about lane stayley and creed showed up to make sure it was dead and nickelbach made sure ir wouldnt come back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 05:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 00:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh? I see it there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 21:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this hour?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 04:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the "first article" in this case? The one I saw here was from dorkly, and AFAIK it just reprinted the Cartoon Brew comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 04:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article clearly says they spoke to some of the animators, and Variety have been around long enough and have built up enough goodwill and credibility for that to be plausible coming from them, as opposed to sites that just reported on the comments coming from the Cartoon Brew article. How are they a blog? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arthur Hiller Dead: Love Story Director Was 92 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 22:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 19:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Variety isn't a blog, it's one of the oldest entertainment magazines out there. They wouldn't publish something without verifying it first. Most other sources simply went off of comments on the cartoon brew article, while Variety stated they spoke to some animators about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calm down friend, you posted this like 100 times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 00:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, I love Getchoo. I guess I'm just weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 19:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I like it more than most, but I can understand why the triple punch of Beverly Hills + We Are All on Drugs + My Best Friend does some folks in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 19:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, a lot of rich celebrities do it, the tax breaks are pretty great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 04:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> El Scorcho

I mean, it's okay. But it's probably my least fav on Pinkerton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 00:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red will probably be a lock for Angel and the One. I see Dreamin' in second. First to get knocked out will very likely be Heart Songs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 07:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you need the U? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 05:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hyped for MB though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 21:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just worried they won't have someone like Jake Sinclair or Ric Ocasek holding down the fort. Rivers has said in interviews that Sinclair pushed for a more classic sound on White, and Rivers wasn't a very big fan of that. But hey, I quite liked I Love the USA, so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 17:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a good bassist, but Green wasn't a good use of his talents. Practically all of his basslines are turned way down in the mix and simply follow the guitars, so it's hard to tell what he's doing. You can isolate some of them with the help of Rock Band stems, and it's clear that he's a solid player. It's a shame he never really got to spread his wings in the band musically, and the scenarios surrounding his departure bum me out. Scott is a talented guy, although for a while dull production and mix burials made it hard to assess his talent. Thankfully he was with the band long enough to get to do interesting things on bass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 07:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's Scott even up to these days? 

I have no idea how you would even go about getting an AMA with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 18:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now this is tricky, because most of these are all equally good, with a few being especially good.

I'm just sad because it looks like you poopyheads are gonna kick Slave out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saturday Night Live is losing Taran Killam and Jay Pharoah next season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 05:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 01:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...what's wrong with Slave? easily the 3rd best on the album. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 20:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scott is 51, Brian and Pat are 47, and Rivers is 46. Getting there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 23:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one's better: http://i.imgur.com/5U4J6te.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 22:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aaron Burckhard, Dale Crover, Dan Peters, Mark Pickerel and Dave Foster. 

They never played on any albums, that was just Chad Channing and Dave Grohl, but you can hear most of them on a few choice songs on *Incesticide*, *With the Lights Out*, and a few other compilations. Although I'm fairly sure Foster never recorded anything with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 15:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slave currently leading the pack? Sheesh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 18:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tax returns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 08:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Rentals are a good answer to OP's question, actually. Return of the Rentals is a breezy pop record with earworms galore, but it's followed up by the crushingly bloated Seven More Minutes, which reeked of the band trying too hard to prove they could do more beyond little Moog jams. Lost in Alphaville is essentially their first album but more soulless (although Irrational Things is pretty solid) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 04:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So wait, what's bad on Pinkerton? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 01:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably won't be, Reddit loves Pinkerton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 17:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 07:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i mean, *wow* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> wow look at this guy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 07:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 22:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Maladroit top five would look like:  
1. Burndt Jamb   
2. Slob   
3. Slave  
4. American Gigolo  
5. Keep Fishin'   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 18:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> get outta here Love Explosion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 18:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK so this strawpoll is fucked but I'm just going to state my intentions to vote Possibilities until it dies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 21:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he's a fine drummer and his simple beats usually work but he goes for the bare minimum at times when a song could really use a drum beat that kicks the song up a bit, and not many of his beats are discernible/memorable/interesting.  Example: TGFG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 19:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The comment says revere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 03:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is probably a popular opinion? Most people I see rank White third.

For me, Mala goes behind Pink/Blue/Green/White/EWBAITE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 03:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Say It Ain't So" isn't that good. The Yahoo Hootenanny version is much better.

Green  White and it's not even close.

Pat has never been a great drummer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 00:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that underestimates how much pull John Landis actually has in the industry. Connections are everything, and John has them. Max's first credit was an episode of some horror show that his dad co-wrote and directed. Obviously I doubt nepotism was the reason American Ultra got made or whatever, but it's played a major role in his career, so the disdain is somewhat understandable?

(Also, huh, I didn't know John and Max were born on the same day.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 19:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great tune. I'd probably rank Devotion and Tragic Girl above it though. The "mine is the loneliest of numbers" harmony bit is probably one of my favorite Weezer vocal moments? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 06:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the fuck is this funny? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 23:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is Hash Pipe still in? I actually love the Green album. But, man do I hate that song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 23:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maladroit is probably my 6th favorite album (pinkblugrenwhitewb ahead of it). It has a few really great tracks (Slob/Slave/Burndt Jamb) but shits the bed near the end with a bunch of forgettable tunes - Possibilities is one of their worst tunes ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 07:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "a sweet in floral prints" = "see her searching for a prince" in pink Triangle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 02:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe he meant Monterey Park !!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 21:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Jonas #1 for sure.
* Tired of Sex
* American Gigolo - Maladroit is a clumsy album with more misfires than hits but it still has a few really impressive highs and this is one of them
* Ain't Got Nobody, killer opener. shame it's followed by the album's worst though
* California Kids. I like this one. Bit dry though.
* Don't Let Go. I like Green... don't really care much for this though. Coulda be swapped for a b-side or demo like Burning Sun or something.
* (If You're Wondering If I Want You To) I Want You To
* Troublemaker
* Memories - this is bad
* Beverly Hills - this is really bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 21:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mykel   Carli?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gthcClVkYAk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 07:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it a lot, but I don't know about that. Gonna list all the post-PP songs I think are better because I'm bored:

* Smile  
* O Girlfriend
* Slob
* Burndt Jamb
* Slave
* The Organ Player
* Dreamin' 
* Unspoken
* Blowin' My Stack
* Ain't Got Nobody
* Go Away
* Cleopatra
* (Girl We Got A) Good Thing
* Do You Wanna Get High?
* L.A. Girlz

Woo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 14:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still like the song, but it's the weakest on Blue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 13:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Undone - The Sweater Song, El Scorcho, Hash Pipe, Possibilities, My Best Friend, Heart Songs, Love Is the Answer, Smart Girls, Back to the Shack, Thank God for Girls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 08:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whaaaaat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 04:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roses! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 05:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I'd been thinking about him ever since Garry Shandling died and I saw a few people thought it was Marshall.

He was pretty up there in years, but was still appearing in movies/TV and directing too (his most recent film came out in April) so it still feels too soon. RIP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 21:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who? Parent comment got deleted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 20:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not exactly actors, but Megan and David Ellison deserve to be mentioned here. Their entire career is simply based around them funneling their billionaire dad Larry's money into funding movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 20:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...delete it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 09:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't he like 19 when that movie came out? Weird that they would've considered him and eventually cast Mykelti Williamson who's 16 years older. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 06:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a few Green solos I dig. Crab/Smile/Simple Pages/Hash Pipe are pretty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 06:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smart Girls. 

It's essentially the only solo on the album and it's just a boring short smothering overproduced one that's pretty much just the verse melody. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 23:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the one about guys getting vasectomies so they can watch March Madness during their recovery downtime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 08:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> twitter dot com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 08:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Simpsons, Treehouse of Horror XIV

Homer: "I'll curb him, but without enthusiasm!"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 21:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worst Weezer album by far, imo. The production is both boring and awful (the clipping on *Ruling Me* - how was that not caught and fixed?) which is probably the biggest issue - for me, almost every song is impossible to listen to with all the weird shit going on. I guess it's to mask how Rivers' vocals sound so dogged and that the rest of the band aren't bringing much in the way of passionate playing either. Even if the album actually sounded fine, practically none of the songs have interesting or salvageable loglines. Where's My Sex and Smart Girls are two of the most embarrassing tunes to ever be put on a record anywhere, not just Weezer. You know an album rots when there's a bonus track written by the composer of Yo Gabba Gabba for a kids' show and it's still better than almost each tune on the regular release.

(Unspoken is pretty awesome, though.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 18:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you really do it without Charles Napier? He was one of the best parts of the original series.  Also Christine Cavanaugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
