<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject322</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 08:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man. I admit, I would have done the exact same. thats a very strong team composition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 07:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. That's why you mute them and tell the others too as well. Arguing will never win you the game.

I'm willing to speak up once, if he argues back I just stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 06:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. It's just so frustrating. We ALL wanna dump on this guy. We really do. 

But it just doesn't help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The boss on Towers of Doom is a finisher, the towers give you the momentum to win the game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 06:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bascially, if you wipe the team and it's a question of taking lanes or taking boss? You always take the lanes. Because the lanes will give you more damage on your towers. (Boss does four, but 3 extra lanes + 3 towers = 9.)


Even having two extra towers and taking two towers you get more value.


BUT it also sets your enemy back. They cannot safely run up that lane now to escape you, they need to take those towers back to be able to do base damage again, and while they're taking one back you can take another.


LEt your split pusher split push while you defend a tower. Build that momentum. Then when the enemy has four points left, take the boss for the win.


But there is almost no instance where taking boss is better than taking a fort.


Azmodan, Gazlowe, Slyvanas, Zagara, Hammer, Xul, Murky, Abathur and The Lost Vikings thank you for your time.
Pushing really does win games on Towers of Doom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: The boss on Towers of Doom is a finisher, the Towers give you momentum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 06:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please don't antagonize the asshole on your team </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 06:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen this several times. One player gets super self righteous when an asshole pops up. And I can see why! He's an Asshole! You're in the right. YOU are a super hero. YOU are batman. He's the Joker. EVERYONE knows that you're in the right here and he's a stupid poop head so calling him out feels so damn good.

Then he throws the game. Ruining it for everyone else.

Because he's an asshole.

The only way to beat an asshole, is to be super smug and superior AFTER the core is dead. You're right, you shouldn't be held responsible for standing up to a flaming shithead troll. But you are. It's your fault for pushing him.

There's so many reasons. Maybe he's had a bad day and is just looking for someone to "beat" (In this case making you lose) or maybe he really is just a bad person and is petty AF. But whatever the case, you chose to confront him.

Stay positive. Don't fight Ass with Ass. Be the ray of sunshine shooting up his ass until he feels BAD about being such a dickhole. Make him your friend. Make him love you during that game. 

Back him up. Cheer him on.

Then at the end dump all your petty shit back on him. But don't do it during the game. Please. I have begged people to swallow their pride and just say sorry to an asshole. Yes. He is wrong you are right. BUT he is okay with being super wrong and ruining the promotion game of that one guy who has been quiet and just wants to play and have fun. 

But you gotta take this asshole personaly, and this asshole takes the game and everything else personaly. "It's just a game" he laments as he begins to throw. "No" the others beg "It's ranked. It's more than just for fun. Don't set us back." 

"Blame him" The asshole cries, as he points to you and your justice boner. But you will not relent. The asshole knows he's an asshole and he's using you as an excuse to be an asshole. But you won't let it go. You wont let it slide. 

Thus you become what you hate.

Sorry for the rant here folks.... Just... I just got promoted. But every one of my promo games the last few days (About 5) have had one troll, and three of them, have had this exact interaction.

INCLUDING THE ONE I JUST WON! I begged them to stop fighting and they actually listened and we won in the end.

EDIT: ITT Lots of people justifying why it is okay for them to to provoke the asshole during the game is stead of at the end, ruining it for the other people "Because we can't let the bullies get away with it" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 01:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Light armour needs to be leather or wood, sad too saym </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure. But surely not 4 hours at a time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, LARP is a long term thing. I'd reuse the costume, or at least the character, for many months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well! I certainly wont use it for eight hours of the course of two days haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help me make my own costume! Please and thanks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 14:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone! I'm about to start Larping again, and I'll be playing a type of bard. Oration will be my game, as I'm pretty great at Improv acting and vocalizing. 

I was just wondering if anyone had any good tutorials on how to make Leather Armour?

I want at least a little for my character, and I can't afford to buy it online.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 12:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I probably wont. But thank you for the insight. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 12:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do I need to use a new cotton wick each time? Or is one good for multiple uses? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 12:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the last and only question left is, how long would a charge last on this, do you know? Since I'd be taking it camping and what not.

Thanks so much for your help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 12:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect! Thanks so much.

What are coils?

I'd like to be telling a fantastical story and puffing smoke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 12:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, do you know how I'd use it? 

Like I said. I don't vape so I'm not certain if this build needs specility cannisters or something. 

Or if I can just pick up any old Vape Juice(That's what it's called, yeah?) and call it  a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 12:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude. The brown skin on it is perfect! Thank you so much!

It's a bit pricey, but will look great with my costume. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to get a long pipe vape for a costume I'm working on. Think Gandalf from Lord of the Rings. Is there such a thing for less than 150 dollars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 10:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.amazon.com/Gstar-Long-Churchwarden-Tobacco-Cleaning/dp/B00IGJ6V5K/ref=pd_lpo_60_lp_t_3?_encoding=UTF8 psc=1 refRID=5YGRNEVBZ8C5BA8QA8FS

See? That looks great. But I'd rather a vape because I can get non nicotine smoke for it. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 06:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Accordion to a recent survey, replacing words with the names of musical instruments in a sentence often goes undetected. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 06:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inspired by the Avatar Aang skin tint on Kahrazim, and the Samus/RC tints on Morales. What non Blizzard characters would you like to have as SKINS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 00:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, Mario, Luigi and Wario for the TLV would be hilarious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 23:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A different night? Why not tell me a bit about yourself and your characters this time around? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 13:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Groovy. I like that. If we play together I'll ask for more details. I'll let you know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 12:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay cool. Read up on Roleit and decide who you think would fit best into this world.

As for messaging, I'll message you my Discord when I decide we need to chat.

But to message, just click my username. You'll be able to navigate from there. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 11:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well like I say, post them here. 

BUT also check out RoleIt. Since we're using their world, figure out which ones fit in it best. It's obviously not done yet, and the ship is sailing out from one of the Furbiri islands. You also get to pick where your character wants to go once he or she hits the mainland.

I wont accept you until I've spoken to several people, but I might invite you in at a later date to help round out the roster. I'll probably also want to chat with you over discord or some such just so we can see if you and I have an affable chemistry. 

But totally post which ever of your characters you're really wanting to play. I promise ANY of them fit, as long as you fit them into the RoleIt world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A game that's also an Ad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 10:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everyone!

https://www.reddit.com/r/lfg/comments/5mjnkd/online5eest_looking_for_an_experienced_player_who/

I have posted this in the main LFG subreddit, and obviously I will be using the RoleIt rules.

The idea for this, at least for me, is to draw in an audience to help RoleIt grow into something bigger! Does anyone have any suggestions for set pieces I should include to really show off what RoleIt has to offer?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Online][5e][EST] Looking for an experienced player, who prefers roleplay over min maxing for a solo adventure that may grow to include more players as your story grows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 10:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All you need to know for your character, you're traveling from one part of the world to another upon a ship.

Using the RoleIt world 
https://www.reddit.com/r/RoleIt/comments/4yg82w/frequently_asked_questions/

Meaning, if you make your character an Elf nobel who had gone to visit a colony, I'll fill in the blank details including neighbors and what not too your kingdom.

I want an interesting backstory, but it doesn't need to be rich and full. Less than one page please, just the major details I can use. your character's back story will be revealed too me in minute ways through natural roleplay. (That's part of the fun for me, is hearing your story, not reading it like homework.)


You start at level 1.

PS: If you have a buddy that you really enjoy playing with and have great chemistry, we can start it as a two person campaign, but no more than two people. The game and story will grow organically over time to include new people.

EDIT: Bonus if you want to keep notes on our adventures that we can share with the community but not necessary. We will live stream the game for the community to enjoy. If you do not want to "preform" for an audience then it might not be for you. Webcam and Microphone is a must.

EDIT2: I have just changed my mind, the game will start on a ship but we will be using the Roleit world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 04:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PLus they don't trust people to sort their recylables and organics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 06:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then why is this exciting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 04:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? Such a bummer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Playing Dragon Ball Fusions and combining all the randoms be like </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 10:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 08:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then my four man bottom takes a fort, and I've never had a problem with Xuls Skeletons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 00:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or on blackhearts also double soaking

With bribe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 00:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is worth playing. He's just weak and hard. Tomb of the spider queen is his best map as a counter to the Xul double soak cheese. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 20:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pffft I thrive on those comps.

Roamers coming after me? I just play safe, and my team has way easier rotations.

The people I hate are faltadd, if he cat he's you unawares you cannot escape his combo.

And tracer. She is the devil for the vikings.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 09:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who rocks the master TLV skin everytime I'm on Garden of Terror, this is nice to hear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 11:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I came into the comment thread wondering if there was something I missed about the video, but everyone is just really digging it. As long as they're happy I suppose haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 07:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah well that could be a third demonic themed set for Warcraft, it is Blizzard's biggest series. But I feel the horde and alliance are the most recognizable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 05:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OVERWATCH - Roadhog Olaf, Hanzo Baelog, D.Va (Out of her Mec Eric.) Now. I don't mean like, it is D.Va. I mean Eric in a pink jumpsuit.

STARCRAFT: Archon Olaf, Infested Baelog, Vulture Pilot Eric

Diablo: Angel Olaf, Nephalim Baelog, Demon Eric

Warcraft Horde: Tauren Olaf, Troll Baelog, Goblin Eric
Warcraft Alliance: Worgen Olaf, Gnome Mage Baelog, Draenai Eric </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 04:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soulstone in his belly button I think you mean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 15:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pressing Alt+R will "Self cast" your ult. In this case, it'll cast it right under your feet, for even quicker plays </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 04:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 03:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What. That's awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 02:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   guac boi

I keep seeing this referenced. What was it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 01:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah! There'd be SO MANY legendaries from an Overwatch set </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 21:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Telepathy of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 19:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I used creature instead of Minion on Abathur I think.

I was doing my best to make them reasonably not OP while still fitting the fantasy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hearthstone Legends of Starcraft! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 18:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/a/UuOKn

Those are just three zerg themed cards I came up with. But I was thinking, what's stopping Blizzard from making an expansion based on Starcraft, or Diablo.

Nothing, really. I mean, obviously they've got some great ideas to still build on Warcraft, but I think it'd be a fun little event to mix some Starcraft style cards and characters into the mix. Even add heroes, like Tassadar in place of a Shaman, or Dehaka in place of the Warrior.

Do you guys have any ideas for Starcraft themed cards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were her buddies first. So it sucks. Not all of them believe her cause she's pulled this shit several times though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dated a girl, it was wonderful. Found out she lived with her ex. Okay. They're friends. That's cool.

They introduced me to LARPing. AWESOME! 

Found out she was manipulative and SUPER abusive to her ex. (Only mildly abusive too me.)

I left her.

She began telling all my new awesome LARP buddies that I was emotionally and manipulatively abusive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I "Drank milk sideways" the other day. I'm not sure how, but I drank like, a piece of milk that was too big to drink, and it hurt going down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something very basic that you, your mind, or body has forgotten to do in non life threatening way? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 10:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on the Patron. I think the Great Old One literally doesn't even know it's a Patron. Like, you are so insignificant too it, that it doesn't even realize you're tapping into it's powers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 09:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AS A LEVEL TWENTY AZMODAN, THAT'S HOW WE GET OUR SHIT AZMO-DONE. THAT'S HOW GAMES GET AZMO-WON. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 09:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MEDIVH, ZARYA, TASSADAR, ABATHUR, ZUL'JIN SUPER TEAMS COMING AT YA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 09:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'D RATHER FIREBAT, BECAUSE THEY JUST FEEL MORE POWERFUL THAN THE FLIMSY LOOKING HELIONS, THOUGH THE MOUNT FORM WITH LINE ATTACK IS A COOL FEATURE, IT JUST LOOKS WEAKER IN ROBO FORM. PLUS, WE ALREADY HAVE HELIONS AS MERCS ON THE TERRAN MAPS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 09:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'D RATHER 3 HOURS THAN THE MONTHS AND MONTHS IT TOOK FOR SOMBRA. TBH THIS WAS MUCH BETTER THAN THE CHROMIE, DEHAKA, MEDIVH, XUL AND LI MING REVEALS. IT GIVES US ENOUGH TIME TO GET HYPED, BUT NOT SO MUCH WE GET FRUSTRATED! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 09:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Err I meant SC Broodwar lol My bad. But yeah, what I mean is. He's never really had any support-esque traits. Especially now that his more iconic form is the SC2 version.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't he a Ghost/BattleCruiser in SC2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought they'd make a great third ult. At level ten you take "Fang!" and you get the werewolf, with a life steal on auto attack, as a fourth TLV to control, and then at level 20 you take "And Scorch!" and you get the Dragon, with a DoT burn effect, as a fifth. Each time every Vikings Respawn counter increases by ten seconds.

Mad Micro for days! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I missed it. Where is this Zul'jin teaser? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 16:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this concept. It fits him way better than the support build I read for him awhile back. 

Instead of the Spine Crawler, though, I'd give him the infested tank he gets as a custom unit in his Co-Op version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 09:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's pretty cool. 

Like they didn't just throw it in your face. It happened as naturally as if you were introduced to her male partner.

http://comic.playoverwatch.com/en-us/tracer-reflections </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Cheers love, the Calvary's Queer!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 08:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Cheer's love, the Calvary's Queer!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 08:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only is Tracer Overwatches first LGBT character, she's also Heroes of the storm's first!

In honour of that, I thought I'd share with you guys, her amazing Heroes of the Storm Skins that she should totally get here in Overwatch.

http://imgur.com/z6WiCza

http://imgur.com/3GlYeQR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 04:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit. Ten minutes as of posting this. Here we go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 21:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is what prompted my question in the first place. So I thought other people would find it funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 21:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/handicat told a story about his sister getting a giftcard for Christmas. This was a lingerie giftcard and it was from his grandmother. He had to go in the store to buy it, and when the cashier asked who it was for he replied with "My sister... Well, my grandma." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is one time where a lie would have be perfectly acceptable, but for whatever reason, the person didn't? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 21:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 18:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Mosh would play the opening riff for this.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JQyV9qMK7FM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 22:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's what I meant. Reach out the community and see if there are any artists who want to contribute. 

You could even do a thing where anyone who helps in such a way gets one magic item custom made by the admins to include in their next character. (Nothing game breaking, something unique though. Like the "Scarf of Goblin Form" or something.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25[M4R] Spadina and Bloor, Toronto, Ontario - The Holiday's and New Years - You're not alone in the city. Friends are here! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 22:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, I'm Tom. How's this fantastic fall treating you so far? Me? It's going great. I was once new in the city, alone and all that Jazz. I want to be the person who helps you fix that.

I'd be happy to have a few people over for Christmas Dinner, and if we hit it off I can even invite you to my new years party I'm throwing.

Now just because you post here doesn't mean you get an instant invite, and I hope you don't take that personally. But I can only have so many folks come around, and depending on the attention it gets, and whether or not I think we'd click as buddies, or more, I may or may not invite you. That might sound harsh, but there's nothing lonelier than being in a group you don't fit in with. And I wouldn't want to force that onto any of us.

BUT I'll help you make your own post if you want.

Anyway, enough negativity. This is about those folks whom might click with one another! I'm a huge nerd. DnD, video games, anime, comics. All a great time. I LOVE too cook, christmas dinner would be a pleasure, rather than a chore. (You can help me with the dishes though. ;) ) We'll listen to music, we'll have drinks, sing christmas songs. It'll be great.

Feel free to bring some food, we'll do it potluck style. Folks from all over the world are welcome. Let's keep it 18-30 age wise. I'm 25 myself so I'm still living in both worlds, and I know that I can actually get on with folks much older. But I want all my guests to feel welcome, so we'll keep the age group tight-ish for now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25[M4R] Spadina and Bloor, Toronto, Ontario - The Holiday's and New Years - You're not alone in the city. Friends are here! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 22:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, I'm Tom. How's this fantastic fall treating you so far? Me? It's going great. I was once new in the city, alone and all that Jazz. I want to be the person who helps you fix that.

I'd be happy to have a few people over for Christmas Dinner, and if we hit it off I can even invite you to my new years party I'm throwing.

Now just because you post here doesn't mean you get an instant invite, and I hope you don't take that personally. But I can only have so many folks come around, and depending on the attention it gets, and whether or not I think we'd click as buddies, or more, I may or may not invite you. That might sound harsh, but there's nothing lonelier than being in a group you don't fit in with. And I wouldn't want to force that onto any of us.

BUT I'll help you make your own post if you want.

Anyway, enough negativity. This is about those folks whom might click with one another! I'm a huge nerd. DnD, video games, anime, comics. All a great time. I LOVE too cook, christmas dinner would be a pleasure, rather than a chore. (You can help me with the dishes though. ;) ) We'll listen to music, we'll have drinks, sing christmas songs. It'll be great.

Feel free to bring some food, we'll do it potluck style. Folks from all over the world are welcome. Let's keep it 18-30 age wise. I'm 25 myself so I'm still living in both worlds, and I know that I can actually get on with folks much older. But I want all my guests to feel welcome, so we'll keep the age group tight-ish for now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 22:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! You should reach out to the community. I'm sure there are talented folks who'd love to help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 08:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds good my man. :) If you want to add me as mod of the forums or something, I'd love to chip in. (I opened the December LFG thread, and I'd be happy to do one each month.)

But as for web design, my idea was pretty simple. Display the image of the map as a background, and just add buttons in reach "Region" that players can click on, to get information about the region. It's way better than looking at a list and trying to line it up with the map. 

Makes it more "Real" ya know?

Like someone can click on this country, read about it and rather than look for their neighbors in some alphabetical ordered list where they're seperated and it seems kind of disjointed, they're just right next to each other. So it's easier to visualise.

Also, and wood and brass colour scheme would make the site look great and fantasy esque. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 06:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem! Send me a PM and I'll give you my facebook link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 06:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome to show up. For sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 06:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A later supper and drinks could be fun. Part of the reason we have a young crowd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25[M4R] Spadina and Bloor, Toronto, Ontario - The Holiday's and New Years - You're not alone in the city. Friends are here! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 05:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, I'm Tom. How's this fantastic fall treating you so far? Me? It's going great. I was once new in the city, alone and all that Jazz. I want to be the person who helps you fix that.

I'd be happy to have a few people over for Christmas Dinner, and if we hit it off I can even invite you to my new years party I'm throwing.

Now just because you post here doesn't mean you get an instant invite, and I hope you don't take that personally. But I can only have so many folks come around, and depending on the attention it gets, and whether or not I think we'd click as buddies, or more, I may or may not invite you. That might sound harsh, but there's nothing lonelier than being in a group you don't fit in with. And I wouldn't want to force that onto any of us.

BUT I'll help you make your own post if you want.

Anyway, enough negativity. This is about those folks whom might click with one another! I'm a huge nerd. DnD, video games, anime, comics. All a great time. I LOVE too cook, christmas dinner would be a pleasure, rather than a chore. (You can help me with the dishes though. ;) ) We'll listen to music, we'll have drinks, sing christmas songs. It'll be great.

Feel free to bring some food, we'll do it potluck style. Folks from all over the world are welcome. Let's keep it 18-30 age wise. I'm 25 myself so I'm still living in both worlds, and I know that I can actually get on with folks much older. But I want all my guests to feel welcome, so we'll keep the age group tight-ish for now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 25[M4A] Spadina and Bloor, Toronto, Ontario - The Holiday's and New Years - You're not alone in the city. Friends are here! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 05:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spadina and Bloor] The Holiday's and New Years - You're not alone in the city. Friends are here![25M4A] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 05:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, I'm Tom. How's this fantastic fall treating you so far? Me? It's going great. I was once new in the city, alone and all that Jazz. I want to be the person who helps you fix that. 

I'd be happy to have a few people over for Christmas Dinner, and if we hit it off I can even invite you to my new years party I'm throwing. 

Now just because you post here doesn't mean you get an instant invite, and I hope you don't take that personally. But I can only have so many folks come around, and depending on the attention it gets, and whether or not I think we'd click as buddies, or more, I may or may not invite you. That might sound harsh, but there's nothing lonelier than being in a group you don't fit in with. And I wouldn't want to force that onto any of us.

BUT I'll help you make your own post if you want.

Anyway, enough negativity. This is about those folks whom might click with one another! I'm a huge nerd. DnD, video games, anime, comics. All a great time. I LOVE too cook, christmas dinner would be a pleasure, rather than a chore. (You can help me with the dishes though. ;) ) We'll listen to music, we'll have drinks, sing christmas songs. It'll be great.

Feel free to bring some food, we'll do it potluck style. Folks from all over the world are welcome. Let's keep it 18-30 age wise. I'm 25 myself so I'm still living in both worlds, and I know that I can actually get on with folks much older. But I want all my guests to feel welcome, so we'll keep the age group tight-ish for now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 05:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey dude. Tell me more about yourself, age etc. 

I'm a guy as well. But if you're looking for friends, I might be able to help you out with a party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys I'm a (bad) web developer, but I'm good enough for this I think! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 05:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's say we got our own webpage, yeah? 

One of the pages, would be a map, with Icons of all the major countries, you click on a country it takes you to a more detailed map with all the cities and what not that are on it. (If it's a big country, then it will be divided by regions.) Then you can click on the cities and get detailed information about them and the surrounding dungeons. 

This would be a great way for people to get a better grasp on where in the world they're playing. 

I'm willing to lend my skills to this, if other people are willing to lend their talents to create the art assets, and the written entries (Most of which we can just pull from the Wiki) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 17:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Samuro, Varian and Rag. Gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 17:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is because that is his true form, the tiny model is not his proper status </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 06:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Mercs. The Melee camp is a group of three random Murlocs. 

Possible Murlocs.

"Blue gil charger - Rushes the nearest hero, pursues until death."
"Murloc Tide Hunter - Summons 1 Murloc raider in a similar fashion to the fallen shaman. (Only weaker)"
"Murloc War Cheif - Similar effect to "Mercenary Lord" only effects other Murlocs"
"Murloc Tinyfin - Weakass murloc"
"Vilefin Inqusitor - All minions that spawn in this lane, while this murloc is a live, are now murlocs"

"Leper gnomes replace the siege minion. When they die, they deal damage to the nearest enemy hero within X range equal to 10%-20% of their life" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many could you handle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I heard something about universal education in Toronto next year, I want to finish school. Is that a thing that'll happen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a level 20 Azmo, I think its the best ult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 02:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I'm saying is, Luke Cage would have be easier to find than Spiderman, which by your logic shouldn't have happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 20:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5,556 at the time of posting, but more may have been bought since. But it may not have been. So it is about 5,556, for accuracies sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your argument is kinda flawed, when that is exactly how they find Spider-man. Only it's not even big news like Luke cage, it's shakey phone footage. I guarantee you they've got search things out for any meta human behaviour.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who else would find an easter egg funny, where there's a quick shot of former "Director's of Shield" and it's all the Marvel movie Directors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 18:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 00:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not hurting anyone. If they're really as bad as you say, they'll be replaced by better players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 00:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's amazing. Can you explain it too me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 00:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or we let those folks get their prizes and enjoy the achievement, even if it's a short term thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 07:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like your smurf is your main </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 05:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. They each have a random murky egg somewhere on the map and the only way to kill them is to kill their egg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 03:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone complaining that these kids ate acting out of character is wrong. I've always liked young heroes and said is nailing it so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 01:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But thank you for sharing this. I also did not know what that meant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 01:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no. I've heard that one. The duck torture one has like three sylabls and I think it's when she's hearthing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [don't upvote] What is Zarya actually saying when she says "Duck Torture"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 01:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [don't upvote] What is Zarya actually saying when she says "Duck Torture"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 01:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This might not mean much too you guys, but I'm happy to see it for myself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 01:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 00:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still bust out my Level 20 Azmo when I want to win (Or on towers of Doom, which = a free win usually) but that's the only time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 00:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The murky. The poly chain would be unending
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> March if the murloc now spawns that many begginer AI Murkys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 07:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Permanent member. She's a new teen hero, and if they don't do something with her, she'll fade off like Every other Symbiote other than Carnage. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 06:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god. Right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 03:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes grandpaw, I am on "The Discord" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 02:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I'm down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 02:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. This was said like, the year WoW came out. That if they decided to do Warcraft IV the two would each be their own thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 23:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They said years ago it would be an alternate time line. So both are canon,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no way. Could they really have snuck Venom into this movie? I'll be hyped as hell if they do him right. And bummed beyond belief if they don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes me think of early comic books dialog.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but that was done really well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Touching on the halfling lands, they have a capitol of sorts. The Great Oasis.

It is a small paradise in the middle of some very hostile lands, but it is too small to sustain too large of a population. So they leave their leaders, their elderly and their infirm there. A small group of elite warriors and scholars also remain. 

This oasis is surrounded by highly defensible terrain, taking the form of a natural fortress. Many believe it to be a gift from the gods, others believe it to be a trap, to distract from the homeland. 

Was the site of a civil war between fleeing families when the tried to decide what to do with it. Permanent population never exceeds 200, occasionally grows when nomadic tribes return to visit.

Potentially also the site of a huge Bazaar for commerce and trading?

The Din Thoram clash of champions could be a yearly festival where the dwarven tribes find champions from all over the land to do battle for their entertainment. The tribe that finds the greatest champion is revered for the rest of the year, and is called upon as a mediator for disputes between any two other clans.

During the Festival no Din Thoram dwarves may unsheeth their steel, and must leave any grievences throughout the year until after the festival. Many take this opportunity to embrace bitter enemies as brothers, and make their rivalry more friendly via betting or drinking or wrestling. Others that break this truce are treated harshly. 

The winner of last year's tournament hosts the next one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 03:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys. I'd love to join as a player at level 1 if there are any new campaigns starting up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> December LFG thread! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 03:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LFG during the month of December, 2016? Post here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 22:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, Mania would be an awesome way to add a darker inner conflict to the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 22:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's what made me think symbiote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Possible Symbiote sighting at the end of the latest Champion book? No white highlights, but no one else comes too mind. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 07:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was that second bit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohh I didn't know it was non cannon. I still see them using him like that, because its a cool concept. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 09:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neat list. Keep contributing to the sub OP. Though I will add that Egon would probably have something to do with the insane version they just introduced in the coop campaign, using a pet science vessel as a support rexxar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 05:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen that a bunch. What does pogchamo.mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a level 20 Ragnaros main who has soloed him to GM since release, he is not a specialist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 00:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The many minutes of my gameplay experience should speak volumes about my authority on this matter, but after one whole games as him I've come to realize his role as an assassin, which was hotly debated, is completely accurate.

Jokes aside, Ragnaros is exactly what I wanted Alarak to be, a Melee mage. You will find yourself harassing the flanks of a Team Fight, controlling the battle field and rarely auto attacking. Dipping in only to peel for an ally, secure a kill, or reposition for a talented blast wave.

His wave ult is perfect for defending and goes amazingly with his trait, give you ample ways to buy time for your team.

Where as with skill, your hammer ult is an amazing tool that you can wrangle enemy heroes into by using your mentor and blast wave to coral them.

Attacking with the mentor in the direction your opponents are moving is essential, and though decent at wave clear, he's no more impressive than either Kael, Jaina or Gul'dan.

More than most heroes Ragnaros will rely on skill and guile, to control the battlefield and keep yourself alive. As his glowing frame makes him an easy, and appealing target.

It should be noted however, that his melee range is comfortably long. Perhaps only outranged by Leoric. Allowing you to position yourself behind burlier allies like Varian or diablio, who need to get up close.

BOUNS TIP: Though I was not recording, I was able to kill three heroes on the bottom boss of cursed hollow using my ult. The range is such you can support the boss and deal catastrophic damage to enemies. Enough so that my very capeabke Diablo Ally (the only reason I escaped with one death during that game. Bless his damned soul.)  was able to secure an additional kill and the Boss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sgt hammer skin Idea "Omic Artillery" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 00:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The idea. Replace the Sgt hammer model with a "Bastion" head. Make the barrel into a tessla tower shape, that fires energy. (Not because of lore reasons, but because it would look rad, and when bastion gets in the game we don't want to confuse his ult with this skin.

A talon colour scheme an omnic chrisis scheme and an overwatch one.

Any thoughts?

Bonus idea. Bastion jet mode as an alternate ult. Can't auto attack, flies over all terrain, and drops bombs wherever he goes, like two a second.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Agony of being a 50/50 mum: Women once held the upper hand in custody battles. Now fathers are winning EQUAL access... and mothers are struggling to cope </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 23:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fun synergy build concept with the new hero changes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rehgar - Bloodlust  
Artanis  
Morales - Stim/reduce damage build  
Diablo - AA build  
Zarya - shield ally build  
  
Switch Artanis out for Illidan at any time, but I feel like this team provide a lot of a damage, and a TON of survivablity.

I'd love to get a 5 man together to try it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 15:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can coordinate that many autos, in that short of a time, on one person, perhaps you deserve that much bonus damage. lol

You could also make that the level 20 upgrade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 11:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like Mama used to make
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 11:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except the interface is a lot better. 

Trying to figure out those comment threads is a chore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 11:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol it's only 5AM and this is the kinda shit you think about in the shower? Must messed up thing I'll read all day if I'm lucky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 11:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Divergent timelines bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 11:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always tilt my chin up, and I look stupid. Because when I as young I tilted my chin down, and I look evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 11:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What games do you like? 

There's a subreddit for that.

What T.V series do you enjoy? 

There's a subreddit for that.

What movies do you love?

There's a subreddit for that.

Read r/relationships and sort by updated. Enjoy the juicy juicy drama.

r/prorevenge is a fun sub.

And I'm sure you'll spiral out of control before long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 11:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because while in the shower you failed to spare a thought </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 11:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate that people down vote these threads because they're tired if seeing them. The only way we'll get blizzard to acknowledge us and this issue is to address it over and over, to uovote and draw attention too it, and to report it to customer service time and time again.

Its been happening too me since the Zarya patch, and I think thats the earliest I've heard if it happening. Something happened during that patch that has been getting worse with every major patch since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 11:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's even better that he's infested hah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 11:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes he is hated, by unskilled players or by players used to folks forcing him into a team comp.

But if you draft well, as one of the last two picks, draft into your team( so with heroes he works with, two solo lane heroes in the party etc) and play him to the best of your ability. It should be fine.

If you can, fet an ally in the draft by being very excited when you see their pick. "Ooh an Illidian eh? Badass you will make my aba shine" basically say that to any melee assassin and other will be less likely to jump on you for your pick, because now there's two people in the "yay aba" camp. And people who play melee assassins are very vain and love the thought of having an Aba hat.

Source: level 9 Illidan and Butcher lol

Also, a tip. During objectives, get into the lane farthest from the objective and soak the xp with your body, and use your hat to either push and soak a second lane, or help your team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 11:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the demand for supports I see Zul'jin coming out as the first debuff support. Harming the enemies rather than buffing the allies. That will add more diversity too the support pool, plus give us a unique role not yet filled.

Though I do think he'll have "Big bad Voodoo"(all allies in a radius are invincable, you are not) from Warcraft 3, and probably his serpant wards.(places an attacking ward somewhere in a large radius around him. Good for scouting and gives a different flare than gazlowes turrets.) Chain heal(Rehgar inherited that) and hex(AoE poly morph. They might add it as a skill shot) I doubt will see the light of day. Unless Hex comes in as an ult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 11:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another way to do it, is if you're at full health when shadow stalk triggers, you gain bonus damage to the amount that would be healed on your next auto attack.

That plays to her theme of being a damage support, and gives you a reason to use it as a ganking tool before the fight starts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 10:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think, since all his abilities have models. Nazebo would be the best hero to get the first Carbot Skin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 02:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I prefer South America, because that way I have two ways to get my army out. The guy who bunkers down in Australia only has one way in, this is true. But he's also only got one way out, and it's easy to hem him in long enough to get a bigger lead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
