<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2577</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trust Me, I'm A Professional </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 23:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 00:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that you guys are looking at his shirt wrinkles to see the video edit. HIS TONGUE DISAPPEARS, GUYS!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you lost your left handed your right hand would still be your right hand, surely? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An ex of mine had [hammertoes] (http://images.medicinenet.com/images/slideshow/diabetes_foot_problems_s13_hammertoes.jpg), I'd never thought about it before but there must have been a few people that quietly freaked out when they saw her feet for the first time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 04:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UK, Notes increase in size with value too.

Green - 5

Brown - 10

Purple - 20

Red - 50

Red...again - 100 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What annoys me is that I literally caught a ditto a few seconds after the update and nothing since, despite catching thousands of pokmon :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 10:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention spending 1/4 of the year on holiday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 04:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer the Sahara. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 20:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  to nick the spirit of ecstasy
  what  

He tried to chief the old bird's ornament.


Honestly, it's like American's aren't native speakers of English. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 14:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because 90+% of people don't become addicts and can handle recreational drugs but our government have run smear campaigns that make it seem like you do one hit and you become a crack whore who would sell their own mother for a hit.

Just look at alcohol, it's one of the most addictives freely available drugs that we have but only 7.2% of people are alcohol dependent (AUD). And even then, the criteria to make that percent is pretty easy/gov are boosting the stat numbers to scare us [(selecting just 2 out of 11 criteria gets you on the list)](https://www.niaaa.nih.gov/alcohol-health/overview-alcohol-consumption/alcohol-use-disorders) People with severe alcohol dependance (i.e. what most people consider alcoholics) are 1% of the population.

It's as others have mentioned in here. People don't get addicted to something because it's a drug; most people get addicted because they have a shitty life and the drug is an escape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 13:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno about that, I'm a Londoner and I can't stand the cold, honestly I'm terrible with it.

But I have indigenous family in the UAE and when I visit them I'm much better in the heat than they are. I walk around and have even done 3 hour runs in peak summer heat and I'm completely fine.

You couldn't pay me enough to go for a run on a cold london winters day (I train inside for winter). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 13:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always hated a 9-5 because when I've had jobs that don't require me to be in a certain times that my natural body clock works in fact on 30 hour cycles. So I'll sleep for 8 hours then be happily awake for 22 hours.

Honestly it's a constant struggle to fit into 24 hour days. I've resorted to not sleeping on Saturday nigts so that on Sundays I can go to bed, sleep for 8 hours and start my 9-5 like 'normal' people. Honestly come friday morning I'm exhausted from the horrible weekday body clock adjustment.

At school and univeristy I used to do all nighters on Tuesdays and Thursdays and that wasn't too bad because my classes were set in stone but with work you often have to go in early/work late so I had to change it to just Saturday and it's been tougher to adjust to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 00:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And why am I yawning too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that during the four weeks following Princess Diana's funeral, the suicide rate in England rose by over 45% for women aged between 25-45; research suggests this was caused by the 'identification effect'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twist: you're a lesbian terrorist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 15:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost every work day my train will stop and say 'we're just waiting for a few minutes for the light to change', I can't help but think that they're just loading the next part of town. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 04:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Too all the Brits in this thread who may not be aware, Gary Oldman's sister is Big Mo from Eastenders.

Actually that's just Gary dressed up.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 04:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American actors can't really do normal English accents, 99/100 it's some weird royal accent that nobody has; they act like we all talk like we did in the Victorian times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 00:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> European here. Hospital bill? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last night I went to a comedy and philosophy convention. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 14:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laughed more than I thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 22:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jimmy Carr wants his stolen joke back     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 20:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bomb was discovered 4 days ago but they've waited until Christmas day as that's the most efficient day to evacuate people. Even their emergency evacuations are stereotypical German! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 12:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came in for this, not much we can do really but I'd be happy to take that flight discount if you're still offering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 17:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aliens invade and they kidnap all the Trump and Brexit voters.
Racism ends overnight, world peace shortly follows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 16:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe people didn't know this. I went to Catholics schools (2-18) and we were always taught about evolution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 00:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately all the women in my family suffer from severe periods and my sister has aspergers so I was taught to always carry fem products on me just in case (she would often lose hers).  This eventually led to me having some at work (she visits from time to time).

My sister isn't discreet though (she doesn't know how to be) so she has very publicly asked me for tampons/pads/medicine etc. Because of it I have had a few coworkers, over the years, discreetly ask me for products.

I've essentially become 'that' emergency guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 22:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but now you know kung fu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diamonds and men that buy them for engagement rings, you pay far too much for what they're really worth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 20:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that in England the retirement age for men was 65 and for women it's 60. Women live longer so surely it should be the other way around? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McDonalds found to contain human feet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 20:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 15:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asians killing dog shocker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 01:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I studied both in England (Kent) and in Madrid (Universidad Autnoma de Madrid).

Both Autnoma   Kent are top ranked universities.

Kent was fantastic in every way; Madrid however was godawful.

The way I always describe it is, if you imagine a typical movie where a teacher goes to a school that's atrocious and fixes everything by the end. Well Autnoma is that school but without ever getting fixed.

The courses weren't challenging and the 'essays' were a joke, I remember having to write an 'essay' on Fascism in half a page!

Want help from a teacher? Tough! Most have maybe a 1 hour window, once a week for you to see them but given that you have other classes you essentially can't go to see them, and most just ignore their e-mails if you tried to ask for help that way. 

Classes weren't open discussions like at Kent, it was you sit and listen for an hour, with most professors just talking without any clear plan about what will be discussed in the class, often we'd be asked 'what was I talking about last time'.

The social life was rubbish, campus life wasn't really a thing. Whereas in the UK campus life is a big deal.

I had two final exam clashes and despite having worked and studied all year I was told to just pick one exam and not worry about the other. Their logic was that you didn't need to pass every module to graduate as they only count your top few subjects when grading you. They really couldn't see why I was angry about this.

We had wild cats walking and crapping in the classrooms and corridors. 

The trouble with most Spaniards is that they haven't studied abroad, so they think that is normal but if you ask any that have studied both in the UK and Spain they will tell you how eye opening it was to study in the UK.

All the Spanish erasmus students that I knew at Kent didn't want to go back to their Spanish uni after as they realised how bad they were.

I'm happy to answer any questions you have because honestly if I could go back in time I wouldn't have gone to a Spanish uni and neither would my friends that did. We still joke about how bad it was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 00:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed loads of peple are missing Tangela but I've caught a few in London. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nearly Headless Nick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 21:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 15:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least he can say he walked off getting hit on the head by a Lorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 01:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never been more jealous of a redditor than I am now!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 03:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Daniel Day Lewis is on a 5 year hiatus

Always amazing that this is his second 5 year hiatus. How can someone not work for 10 years and still get 3 Oscars! Insane! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 01:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they don't want you looking at blank silhouettes, getting annoyed that those gen 2 pokmon aren't available yet. Just adding the ones that you can get doesn't look so bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 14:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank-you, why would you clickbait a title, just say $15k in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 13:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't sound like Spanish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 05:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone should just learn Spanish, eventually it will become the massively dominant language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 05:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the OP is an automatic driver; much, much easier to feel your speed in a manual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 04:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makeup in general. I'm really not a fan and if I'm honest I find it very  vain that you cake yourself up just to go to school/work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 00:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was not expecting to see a note written by a friend on the front page today :O!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 23:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In tears! Love this!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 22:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phillip De Franco show is notorious for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 22:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> World record held, world's oldest man.

Fin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 21:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything it said about me/my computer was wrong! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 00:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 00:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a disgusting waste of money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aleppo battle ends as Syria rebel deal reached </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And guantanamo bay was a beach resort? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He then said to her 'have you tried icing your nipples'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or the fact that it would get women walking the streets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a spoon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normal Mario hardly dresses like a capitalist :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've slept more at other people's houses than I did when I was a pre/teen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As it stands the first real recorded use of the word 'cheers' to mean thanks was by Grandad in Only Fools And Horses (1981) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 01:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 18:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad made the same joke but there were no car keys inside.

Though my parents promised to buy me a car after the joke. Well that was 10 years ago and I'm self sufficient now so I doubt their promise will be kept. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 18:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to break it to you, but they didn't really think it was a cigar case!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 12:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Flowerzzxu's gallery](http://flowerzzxu.deviantart.com/gallery/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 12:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heil hydrant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 11:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realise they are kids in the books right? Or at least I hope you do :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 01:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on guys it's 2016, you should know how to block ads by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 00:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dr Crane brought me here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was in primary school the maths was ridiculously easy so the teacher would send me and two others into an empty room and told us to work on two secondary school books that the school had. We finished them within a term (wasnt pretty easy tbh), we told our teacher when we finished and she just shrugged and said find something to do, so then wed use the time to mostly browse wikipedia and try to find the best trivia.

The headteacher walked in on us one day and had a massive go at us and suspended us for 3 days. When we went back we had to stay in the class during maths and do the ridiculously easy maths, honestly it was torture and a complete waste of my time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Equality is over; racism wins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next year I'm going to release a 1 billion disc set for $1 and become the top selling artist of 2017 (and all time with 1 sale) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 03:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How tall for her age is she? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 02:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genuinely astounded that this isn't on the front page, first time I've ever had to search the news sub for what should be a major story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 02:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're Spanish and last month my sister was travelling from the Dubai to London (she lives there) and the air hostess insisted she fill in an immigration form. The immigration form is only for non Europeans (EEA). The air hostess wouldn't believe that Spain is in Europe, my sister had to call for another air hostess so that the current one would believe her.

Also, last time when my sister went to visit new york she was 'randomly selected' by airport immigration and they asked her if she was sure that she wasn't sneaking in to become a maid. I mean wtf! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 01:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the north-west. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we please not make churros artisan, they're suppose to be peasant food, not pretentious. Is nothing sacred anymore.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you know that you can't be racist to white people :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 17:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I often feel like the rest of the world is letting me down when I get up and the front page hasn't really changed. We did our bit when I was awake, the rest of the world need to step up when we're asleep! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 13:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah we're still not buying it Chris. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 13:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad this is the top comment, came in for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 13:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or don't get caught. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 12:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It builds up the video perfectly tbf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 12:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't remember we did it Reddit! being part of the song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My past is as bad as my present, my potential future is the only thing keeping me going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 boxes of turkey stuffing. Perfect time to sell them :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 15:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Picasso museum (his house) in Malaga. It's pretty much a collection of sketches/paintings that he threw away but his family stored because they knew they'd be valuable.

Honestly most of the work is soo bad (hence why he chucked it) that people are literally laughing out loud around the museum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 15:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is there a sign in English in Mexico and why are they using dollars! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 15:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's nowhere near the same level of trauma!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 23:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has a penis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 23:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone with a phonetic Galician name I've yet to come across a native English speaker that can pronounce it correctly.

I lost track of the amount of times English speakers tell me why not just spell it xxx instead.

My name is already phonetic, what you are attempting is to make it phonetic in English and even then it's still quite off as you don't have the same sounds in English but it's better than nothing for English speakers who are never going to say it properly anyhow so may as well make it at least a bit closer.

Which is essentially happens when we translate city/country names. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 23:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it happened before I was born! 2005 is just mental. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 22:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It helps that the big articles are protected from new users/trolls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 22:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto, at least when you tranform make he strong, don't a wad weaker than who you are fighting.

Honarable mention for jynx for essentially being a gollywog and the west accepting that in the original games/cartoons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 22:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's odd is that I've never met anyone from Java but I've met loads of Yanks.

It's like my Burmese friend, nearly everyone he meets is there first encounter with a Burmese, despite their population being over 100 million :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 22:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> False, America lost the first superbowl. I will only accept a video of the whole game as proof to the contrary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about adding more pokstop to the rural areas of London.

None of our parks have any stops or gyms, could start there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should have deformed his face (with makeup) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When chickenpox came to my school the mums had a chickenpox sleepover (not that I knew that at the time), obviously we all caught chickenpox from the sleepover.

Fine, I can understand the parenting logic but then my mum refused to give me any medicine because according to her recovering with medicine means I won't have built up the same immunity as without medicine. Complete bs (but she believed it) but as a kid I accepted it and was in agony for a good week :(


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 16:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shigeru Miyamoto looks the same as when I was a kid! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 16:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were violent before the alcohol. Either you're the kind of man who beats children or you're not; alcohol does not change that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 00:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't see how this is a story, it's not much for what he earns, it be like a normal person spending $70. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 22:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cookies and cream taste nothing like normal oreos :S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the 100k club ruined, used to be exclusive :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I started uni I bought a box of 1,000 pens (to last me the 4 years) and said to my housemates, help yourselves as and when you need a pen. The box lasted less than a semester. I only used 3 myself :D :D :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many people own an ass :s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 43 thousand votes! How is that even possible :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 14:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic news, I genuinely find it disgusting that soo many cultures think male genital mutilation is ok. It's barbaric and should be illegal worldwide! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 14:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surviving doesn't factor in being traumatised though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play mixed badminton 3 times a week and nearly all the women there are muslim. They wear normal t-shirts and shorts but when they step outside they are culturally forced to cover up. They complain about this all the time but realistically there is nothing they can do about this.

The UK is a democratic country but you can't ignore the oppression a lot of these women face within their own community. Having a legal ban would help them massively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
