<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2840</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're absolutely right. I would understand if they're fighting to stop FGM(and there are groups that do this), but they're not contributing anything to society. The wage gap doesn't really exist(an actual feminist told me this).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Computer are essentially just a tool for humans to use. They can't be considered as an actual sentient being. The same way that you can't give a wrench or a screw rights, the computers can't get any either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most women wear the hijab out of choice, they believe that it's the right thing to do. There are women who're forced into it, but I know for a fact that my sisters could take off the hijab at anytime they want to and my parents won't do shit. We don't honor the killing of wives, we think of women as a key to society. People may have arranged marriage, but mostly it's out of love. We care about our women. Don't think Muslim = Saudi. Saudis are just crazy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yea ok I get it haha. The only thing that leaves the nuclear plants is the water vapor, not anything harmful to the environment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yea it's much better to be inhaling a bit of organic material mixed with water vapor than smoke. It's not 100% safe but it's a hell of a lot better than smoking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you elaborate on that? Where does the radioactive materials come from in the coal powered plant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Step one: Black people
Step two: agriculture 
Step three: profit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A list of things commonly found in cells:-

 Mitrocondrira
 DNA
 Black men
 RNA
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are black men an endangered species? No, absolutely not. Endangered species are protected by the law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A man with Down syndrome gets rejected by a women with Down syndrome chromozoned  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brother has an entire cabinet full of vape stuff lol. He talked to me about it when I asked to try out his vapes. He wasn't overly obsessive with it, rather he had a casual and genuine liking to it, which made my experience with the vape really nice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good on ya!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's night in the woods about? Sounds like a horror kind of thing, which is right up my alley. Have you played the last of us? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god imagine working in a Coca Cola factory. All that sugar gonna blow up like a balloon soon IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elephant run by Roland smith
City trilogy by Darren Shan 
The daughter of smoke and bone series by laini Taylor 

Elephant run is about this English boy who moved to Burma a few days before the japs invaded his elephant plantation and his Escape, which was epic btw. 

City trilogy is about a wannabe gangster who gets put into some very weird situations with his uncle, and there's a cardinal at the top of the food chain who controls the city. 

The daughter of smoke and bone is about this art student in Prague who's the adopted daughter of a monster who collects teeth from all species. She moves between countries through doorways which can only be accessed from the other side. Very strange love story and understanding one's self.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I see someone walking closely behind me, I always open the door and let them pass first if possible. Small little thing I do but the person feels honored and appreciated that I would do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nuclear power produces a lot of power for an extermely small amount of fuel. There's no impact on the environment(no CO2 emissions) and there's research to make fuel out of the waste products. The downside is that the waste is dangerous as fuck and sometimes shit like Fukushima and Chernobyl happen and everyone gets screwed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Germany is such an intresting country. Formed in 1870. Not even 200 years old and they're done so much in their time. To be fair, their history has been bloody with the Kaiser in WWI and hitler in WWII. Then the split into east and west less than a hundred years after formation. The entire thing is very intresting especially the fact that Angela Merkel basically controls the EU through peace rather than war, fulfilling the "German dream".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit man horse riding is so much fun. I love the horse itself and would forgive it even if she throws me off. Then I see these stuck up people who would spend a shit ton on an hour lesson, gets thrown off at 10 minutes and won't get back on. No refund. Blames the trainer for everything. I found this horse riding place that's full of people who enjoy riding horses and animals genuinely. It's much cheaper and the people there are so friendly. The trainer is a pretty cool guy and we would always chill while my horse is getting prepped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I used to watch anime religiously. Finished all of one piece and the first naruto series. Along with 20+ shorter series. After that I kinda stopped. I'm waiting for a few months then binge watch one piece then stop for another few months. I don't understand how people can watch a single episode every week. Seems kinda pointless to let the passion build, get 20 mins of release, then it returns as vengeful as ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I was listening to woodkid and I went into the comment section and I was so fucking surprised that there was not a single cancerous comment. I'm sure there was but I didn't see any. It was such a great experience for me since I really enjoy this artist and his work is absolutely insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feminists are the dumbest community I can think of tbh. The first three waves(right to vote, same economic benifits to both genders, freedom to express sexuality) were great and absolutely necessary. Now they're hating on straight white males, not advocating for their rights. I understand that there are many places that still have severe female discrimination that haven't yet to achieve this. Places like North America and Europe really shouldn't be shitting on the work of real feminists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The concept is extermely fascinating and the storyline is also pretty nice. I don't get why loads of people hate on it so much. The story is especially relevant now in the age of VR gaming, and it's only gonna become more advanced from this point on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
