<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1137</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 23:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well ofc its up to date, but I can just go ahead and delete this post, didnt get much out of it anyways </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chrome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 08:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, do you know of a couple of cameras that could fit for this task? Sorry for asking so blunt, but I really dont know too much about cameras :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 07:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry im new here,

But when i clicked "Ask a gear buying or simple question"
the page just crashed and i could not post anything... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need some suggestions for a camera that can take close up photos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 08:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hva faen er dette syke jvler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IM PISSED! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not bothering me, its just weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 08:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see why you feel down bro.
I also feel that if I dont do anything with someone for a while that friendship just vanishes. Its not easy but you should stop focusing on how depresse you are and just try to not think of it too much. If all you think about is sad stuff, you need to do more stuff that makes you happy! 

Try out a new hobby? Go to a convetion for something new, and meet new and interesting people? :) You never know where you'll meet new friends, but my advise to you is to try something really new, something you've NEVER tried before.

A few year back I got into Gas mask collecting (Weird i know hah) but even though this was just a Group on Facebook I was in, i got to know alot of awsome people, and i even met one of them in Oslo (Im from Norway) in 2015, wich was epic! 

You need something to do that can put your mind at ease! :) 
And if you feel like your just a random option to her, then really dont hang with her. Hang with someone that makes you happy!

I'd hang out with you haha.

Hope you'll get better bro! 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Free] Would appriciate if someone could colorize this for me. Thanks! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 07:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 06:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> https://imgur.com/gallery/lyGLo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 19:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its weird, I've never done anything on his FB page at all, i just liked and watched the shit he posted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Min-Liang Tan Blocked me from commenting on his facebook page?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So a while back I suddenly could not comment/like or send messages to Min-Liang Tans facebook page.

I dont understand why? Has this ever happend to anyone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahah np, bro :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i thought its a cool sub, I love making new outfits in GTA, its just really fun for some reason :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Current GTA Style! Whats your thoughts? :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out Gas mask Collectors Community on facebook! :)

My oldest is a Norwegian mask from 1934! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see your pain dude :(
Hopefully you still got back into collecting! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All your masks?
- Did you leave them in direct sun light?
- Did you store them in moist warm condition?
?? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 13:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats really cool! keep it up! Do you know other people who collect these aswell? Im into Gas mask collecting, and i didnt know there were people collecting them, but then i found whole groups for it on facebook!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 09:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful collection! How old are some of these? How long have you been collecting? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really interesting collection! How long have you been collecting? How did you get into collecting these? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
