<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3944</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twisted Metal - Michael Knight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 23:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RIP HOTS Forums? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 19:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> error 500 everywhere, cannot do anything. i don't think it's just me because last posts were like 30 minutes ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 20:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for a typical "all's well" cookie cutter build

reanimation,
willing vessel (hardened bones if i find myself taking a crapload of damage),
ghastly reach 90% of the time,
entomb,
burning rage normally, spell shield if they have a lot of burst heroes, and drain momentum if i feel confident,
consumed vitality normally, renewed swing on infernal shrines,
hardened shield and spectral leech are like, split 50-50 depending on what our team needs more of, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 08:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually a pretty quick learner. I always had the best performance on my team while playing Leoric, even hero damage (lacking assassins much?) 

I bought Sonya and won every game with her until level 7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 08:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll post a replay later, these games were all quick match because I didn't want to risk losing because of my poor performance.. I wish that was the reason I lost these games though. If Leoric was so good, why do so many people say he needs to fit into a specific team comp? Someone like Sonya or Muradin seem right at home anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leoric literally useless now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 06:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made the ghastly mistake of purchasing Leoric just now. $10, completely wasted. I got him to Level 5, and won a grand total of 1 game(s). He does negative damage, he might as well not even heal himself, and he has useless crowd control. In fact, his only good crowd control is hilariously situational that like 85% of heroes can just jump out of anyway. He can't clear waves worth crap, he can't fight anyone in a 1v1, he has almost no role in teamfights because of how squishy he is, soooo... Can anyone tell me I DIDN'T waste $10 on this guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 01:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My build is what everyone says it should be. I think Burning Light is bugged, because I don't see it procing anymore... ever.

edit: gear is filler for now, skills are correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 01:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently the only way to play ESO is with a staff, (that's what everyone is saying, not my words, ESO= Equip Staff Only), and Imperials have nothing that boost magicka. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm ruined.. I have no options left for my only character </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 22:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/oU8FEPt.jpg

5 hunding's, 5 viper, stamina DPS templar. He was a tank, then a DPS, then a tank, now DPS again... It appears no choice is valid now. With blocking becoming a thing of the past for tanks, I thought I should start over and go back to DPS, lo and behold, as a V14 with 2504 damage and 58% crit chance, I couldn't kill V9 tigers in Veteran City of Ash in less than I'd guess 10 seconds each. Is this it? Is it time to scrap my only character? My character I spent 16 days, 22 hours, 17 minutes and 10 seconds on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PC][WTS] Ancient Elf Motif 25,000g </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 07:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EP, @Treasure_Goblin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PC][WTS] a crapload of Daedra Hearts, 400 each. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 15:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @Treasure_Goblin

I have at least like 10-15 at the time of writing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WTB] Daedric Motif for 18,000 on PC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 11:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title, looking to direct trade if possible.

Ebonheart Pact.
US, etc, don't know if that matters.

@Treasure_Goblin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 02:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ritual sacrifice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 02:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u-turn and gunk shot are necessary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 02:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> minun  pachirisu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MINUN 1V5 SWEEP NO BATON PASS WTF </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 02:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 01:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breeding for shinies? If that's the case, then that's a good thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 09:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never use legendary pokemon. I was just speaking from a thematic standpoint. Victini is actually really strong though. V-Create, JESUS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 09:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually hate all legendary pokemon.. To use or otherwise.

There are two exceptions to this: Rayquaza and Victini.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 08:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you put that much effort into a non HA starter Torchic.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 08:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beat me off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 06:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You played terribly and beat a girl. Grats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 06:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't even bother if you're not in Japan, there's basically no point in hoping for much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
