<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1497</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was lined and I was home to a lucky land. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you mean Khe Sanh:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dTjvG4WJD_A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soviet national anthem, sung by the Red Army Choir wins hands down:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BYw_zamFGf0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, mate. I really don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bouquet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done a fair bit of searching and unless I'm missing something, I'm starting to doubt if it's possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I nearly got run over by the delivery van I was driving. It overheated and me and my boss were fixing it. He thought it wasn't in gear and I always leave vehicles in gear. 

So, I'm working in the engine bay and he goes and starts it. It's in gear, so it just goes. How I managed to roll out of the way, I'll never know. He had to chase it for 20 meters and managed to switch it off, just before it hit the wall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I just can't work it out. I've done it before but now I can't remember. You haven't had any problems after removing them? I can't see it being a huge deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good old Dragon. They had some really top songs. Guess they had to, to fund their smack habits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't see it. Where is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ['88 turbo S] I took the front bumper off and now when I'm putting back on, I can't remember where the two rubber 'cushions' go </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took off the front bumper and the plate that covers the intercooler. Now, I'm putting it back together and I can't remember where those two pieces of rubber go. They're black, with a hollow tube part and a 'tongue'. 

Anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why doesn't instagram have volume control? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate instagram, anyway but on the odd occasion I've used it, there doesn't seem to be a volume control (unless I'm missing something). Why?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am using dual monitors - does anyone know how to force VLC to open on the monitor I last closed it on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every other program opens up on the last monitor I was using it on. VLC is the only thing that does not. Is it possible to force it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I got a good response here:

https://www.reddit.com/r/AskEngineers/comments/682lnu/does_anyone_know_what_what_the_two_pipes_on_the/dgviq9s/?context=3

Seems like it's on the money. That second of the larger diagrams is what we were after. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks very much. Exactly the reply I was looking for. Cheers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No ill will or malice - and I'm the fucking Pied Piper. What a fucking joke these cunts are. Yeah, we just wanna be friends, I'm sure... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why don't you STFU? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weak. Hope someone else steps in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes - I'm an expert on wasting time. These kids are good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is ridiculous that they would have to use such nonsense. Just let them make/have as many as they need. Stop limiting teams with components. Stop fucking around with stupid penalties. It's a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone ever seen the "superdollars"? 

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Superdollar

US $100 notes that are exceedingly hard to detect. No one knows where they come from or who makes them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it not be easier to just keep using them, even if you know they are fake? Lot of effort to turn them in - much easier to just pretend you didn't notice and hand them back to the next poor sucker, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you even talking about? Makes a fucking big difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thousands of kids wasting their time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know what what the two pipes on the back of this turbine do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was posted in /r/machineporn and no one seems to know:

https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/f/fc/Whittle_Jet_Engine_W2-700.JPG

Anyone got any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I thought you'd say that. Exactly what I was thinking. Very interesting, though. Perhaps an /r/askengineers might help. I'll let you know if I have any luck with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah - it's a cunt of a thing when it goes wrong. You need specialist help with that stuff. Way above my level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 11:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautification of the bunghole is big business, bro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 11:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would the minimum revs he was doing be? Anyone got any idea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 11:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does H2O2 taste of anything? I know all about it's properties but I've never tasted it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here in Australia we use grouse to mean great, excellent. As in, "that's fucken grouse, cunt!". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the two pipes - looks like they act as a type of wastegate or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to force VLC to open on the same screen as I closed it on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want VLC to open on the monitor I closed it on - I'm using dual screens. Is this possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What it doesn't show is one of the more interesting parts - the analogue/mechanical computer. This:

https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/f2/84/53/f284537fb94f85b3bd4de31efca5b2ef.jpg

Is what lives down in the very bottom pan of many automatic gearboxes. It uses oil pressure and solenoids to shift the gears at the correct time. Another, showing the pistons which actuate things:

https://i.stack.imgur.com/BH6Q0.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My face is leaving in a quarter of an hour - I'd like you to be on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another useless muslim cunt. Should get an extra ten years for being so fucking dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People say this world is unfair. And I have to agree with that. I mean look at that Gary Glitter cunt - he gets three years for riding a couple of six year old girls. Fair enough.

Now, look at poor old Christoper Reeve - he only rode a horse, and they give him the fucking chair! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you weren't. That term didn't even exist at that time - anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boo fucking hoo. Oh no!, he said mean things. "Crime", my arse. Fuck I hope she wins... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent. God speed the Israelis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bullets are expensive. Surely, they could use gas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disproportionate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting mine next month. Maybe it will be slightly better than ADSL. I'm just *so* excited... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a pretty good deflagration to me. The tool made a spark and some of the dust went up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's what you get for taking in he tired old cliche sights, anywhere. Think of something different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Moshe and his almost complete destruction of the Egyptian, Syrian and Jordanian air forces in just one day?

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Operation_Focus

Unbelievable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Israel and the destruction of the Egyptian air force - while it was still on the ground. That Moshe cunt was a genius. Operation Focus:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Operation_Focus

One of the most successful air campaigns ever undertaken. The Arabs got exactly what they deserved, and some more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Witcher 3][PC] Are there any mods to lighten up the interior of buildings? Sick of it being do dark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second play through and I'm realising how annoyingly dark it is. It's bad enough that at 10 AM it's very dark outside but inside is worse. Pisses me off. Does it really have to be so dark? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering if anyone would believe it, to be honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free heater. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Witcher 3] Never expected this - I was fighting some deserters and one of then shot the other with an arrow, just as I about to deliver the final blow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never seen that before. It was pretty cool. Just about to deliver the final blow and the cunt's killed instantly, from behind. 

Anyone else see that before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Utter filth. And I don't mean our friend Tommy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he means that there is a lift force that has to be countered. Maybe it has 100 lb of lift with no wing and to get 500 lb of downforce you would need the wing to generate 600 lb. Having said that, I doubt a modern 911 would have much lift at any speed it was capable of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any racing success? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could break into a bank vault with that brow. Jesus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A million gallons in 64 years. Absolutely nothing in the scheme of things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Human locusts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah - not the parents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It fucking shits me when Steam asks if you are over the age before the page loads. What am I gonna do? Say no? Fucking retarded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's easy to tell. You just go to http://nullprogram.com/am-i-shadowbanned/

They cannot stop you making hundreds of accounts, no matter how hard they try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see lots of Chinese females with alabaster white skin at uni. I have often wondered how. It looks fucking weird. But hey, it's OK for them to be racist and not me. Go figure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whilst I abhor facebook in every possible way, why should they give up that data? It does not belong to the parents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incorrect. The law *is* who's right and wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just ask reddit for this exact same fucking question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen people say when you are using Tails (for drug dealing) that you don't want to use a VPN as well - that makes you more unique. I'm no expert but I have seen that a few times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I can get behind but it takes so many tries and then when I make a strike, it often does nothing or very little. Time for some grenades, maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old mate in the red bandanna don't know where the fuck he is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like he was the one freaking out. Say, "you just bought...." one more fucking time. Who the fuck is he, anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Preparing for a second attempt... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marketing gimmicks. Butts are already cellulose acetate and that carbon/charcoal is gonna do fuck all in the scheme of things. Little pellets of charcoal might catch a little tiny bit of any number of compounds on their surface but unless you force all or at least a good portion of the smoke *through* them (like a block as wide as the filter), all they will do is adsorb a poofteenth of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, never thought of grenades. Never bothered with axii. Cheers, I'll give it a go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use your fingers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've mandated cigars be packaged in containers without stickers (printed on warnings) for a long time, now. They just have to be fucking killjoys at every opportunity. Same thing with the metal tins you sometimes could get with limited edition runs of RYO. It's a fucking joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Witcher 3][PC] There's always one person in a camp of bandits or deserters who is much harder to beat than the others. How do you fight them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time playing on second easiest difficulty. This is pissing me off. The one tough guy will simply stand there block anything and everything I do. Signs to precisely nothing. You can't get a good hit because they just stand there with shield raised. And when you do get a decent hit, it does fuck all.

So what do you do? And what's with the second energy(?) bar underneath the first for them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put the cunt up for adoption. You need a special carer for a sproglet like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're no good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why didn't you give credit when you posted it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can't just pick one for the sake of a fucking online account? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know the first name or actual name of a good deal of my mates. I really don't. I've known them for years. And I'm happy for it to stay that way. I know several Gaz-es, a couple of Woz and I've heard plenty of birds referred to as Shaz or Kaz. If it is at all possible to shorten a name or use a nickname, we will do it without hesitation. Usually, it's the surname with -ey or -o tacked on the end. My fave was a bloke we used to call paedo (we spell pedophile with an a) - because he was a sick cunt, both in terms of poor health and his style of humour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is NOT original.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no problem with CODEX </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many dicks you you suck today? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What *are* you on about? How are FGM and abortion linked? They aren't doesn't matter where or which country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pay $60 for Winfield Blue or $67 (50 g) for Port Royal. Fucking highway robbery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My old man says one trick they used to play on people was to get a horse hair and thread it through a smoke, longitudinally. He says it just about makes you heave by the time you realise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you should read about Turing machines and Universal Turing machines. They have made some (limited) real life versions. They 'can work in a way that will never fail' depending how you program them but if you mean a physical device that will never suffer from wear or lose its tolerances, I very much doubt it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *living bombs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You make me sick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's with those pipe like structures at the bottom of the poles? Heaters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, you're not a super player? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of the bugged quests in Bethesda games. They're appalling with respect to the number of bugs they have. Every single one of the ones I have played has had major bugs in several quests. Inexcusable, in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why can't we skip or pause ALL cut scenes? Apart from where the game is actually loading, it's just bullshit that you can't do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's it about, in general? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Muslims. Such a charming bunch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is retarded. Smoking is not going to help you, with your existing cardiovascular problems from being obese. I know you can't "just stop eating" - you'd have done so earlier if that were the case. But smoking is NOT gonna do you any favours. Jesus christ, don't do this. Spend your smoking money on some kind of new diet or counseling or something. Anything. Get a gym membership. Go swimming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You appear to be saying women shouldn't have abortions. You're saying abortion and/or the rate of it is 'bad'. Is that correct? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't why anyone would use anything else than the SI units. Maybe DIN horsepower, if you must but fuck those other weirdo units. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love me a fistula, early in the morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stick to the fucking subject! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had something similar once. The startup screen was all fucked up and clicking on the options didn't work. Just try another .iso. Or maybe try reinstalling or mounting with a different program. Lucky it happened early on, really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're taking about muslims. Can you not stick to the subject? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF has abortion got to do with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL music is haram. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't even get a half mongrel with that shit. Had to watch something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope they have a big warehouse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't know what happened before this, so why are people here talking so much shit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That wailing is absolutely atrocious. Jesus christ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they don't die because of that. Wake up to yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
