<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2997</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I wish we just had one.

So, basically a cable TV bundle but with streaming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other way around; Scrubs was produced by ABC but aired on NBC (except for the last two seasons). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately for him the only points jerseys up for grabs here are for intermediate sprints and KoMs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I remember she was originally supposed to be a main cast member for this season

That was never more than a completely unfounded rumor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My thoughts on this are that it's a moot point because the likelihood of it happening is pretty much nil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a broadcast ratings milestone that prior to now had not been reached. Therefore it is relevant to the state of broadcast ratings. Was it unexpected that this milestone would be reached? No. But that is not a requirement for relevance. *Titanic* becoming the first movie to gross over $1 billion was relevant to the movie industry, Roger Bannister being the first man to break the four minute mile was relevant to athletics, in spite of both events being expected based on previous trends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'relevant'  'breaking from a previously established trend' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's rather iconic among readers of DC comics, not really among the general public. Things like, say, 'The Matrix' (which most of the rest of OP's 'Flashpoints' resemble more than they resemble Flashpoint itself) are *far* more iconic than Flashpoint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Many shows averaged above what you claimed.

No one claimed that *no individual show* did a 1.0 or higher last week, just the *no network's weekly average* was 1.0 or higher last week. It's relevant as to the overall state of broadcast TV ratings, not any individual show's performance specifically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The weekly average rating is irrelevant.

The weekly average rating *is what this tweet is talking about*. This was not meant in the context of individual shows or their renewal chances.

Edit: however this must be including CBS's airings of Ransom and Training Day on Saturday (which were originals to be fair), without them CBS's average for the week was a 1.0. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is for the weekly average rating...

Edit: Also this is for *last* week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is on average for the week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Pattern Day Trading' specifically only applies to margin accounts. Day trading is not specifically forbidden in cash accounts, you just have to do it without incurring Reg T violations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What people signed up for" was inherently unsustainable. Netflix benefited greatly from being among the first to realize the value of streaming, but the companies that owned the content were inevitably going to catch on and have, leading to vastly increased costs for Netflix to continue licensing their content. So Netflix's options are massive price increases or a shift towards less licensed content and more original content, and they chose the latter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That rule is just for margin accounts. But T+3 settlement will make doing much day trading in a small cash account difficult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The absolutely still do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   when will they be able to keep tv shows and movies permanently?

When they actually own the shows, hence Netflix's move towards primarily original content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  cw hardly promos the show

You're kidding, right? The CW promotes The Flash all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can buy the episodes on iTunes, Amazon, probably a few other places. There is no legal option that's free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I downloaded the CW app and they have free streaming, but the earliest episode they have is season 3 episode 13 or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. If someone without super speed just up and stabbed a speedster on the show everyone would be complaining about how dumb it was, but because it's Batman it's apparently the shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently just moving out of the way was beyond Thawne's imagination... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that was a major tactical mistake but not so much an instance of physical weakness. The only time Froome really collapsed in a Vuelta was 2012. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   ABC will pad and ride that syndication package until the wheels fall off.

The Middle's syndication package only helps ABC in that it might allow WB to sell the show to ABC for cheaper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Boonen and Cancellara are both the same age as him

And Contador is only a few years younger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is supposedly set 200 years ago, so I don't see why Kara would be mentioned at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black-ish Sells To BET Networks   FX Networks In Cable Syndication </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 10:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Sara and that corset </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The audience is more intelligent than what the showrunners give credit for.

Given the number of questions I see on this sub about things that were clear if you paid close enough attention to the show ("hey why aren't they using gideon?"), no, the audience would not have been clear on the distinction between "Zoom" and "Professor Zoom". Moreover that confusion would entirely unnecessary since they can just not call Eobard "Professor Zoom" and everything still works fine, whereas the time travel plots are an essential part of the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she ded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  On the show Trajectory's suit was destroyed with her. 

No it wasn't, it survived and was later given to Jesse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   confusing

I was going to say "stupid", but that also works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It amounts to the pretty much the same thing. ESPN may be listed as ~$7 a month, but it's only that low because its price is effectively subsidized by the prices of the "filler" channels. You'd never get stand-alone ESPN for that little. And again, what you consider "filler" will not be the opinion held by everyone. There will inevitably be some people who watch the "Indoor Flyfishing Channel" and not ESPN but pay for both; they're subsidizing the cost of ESPN for everyone else.

The bottom line is that for people who consume lots of content, a la carte will inevitably be more expensive than bundling (which is entirely consistent with a la carte menus in other situations). But again, a la carte itself isn't what a lot people really wanted; mostly they just wanted to pay far less for what they currently watch, and thought a la carte would guarantee that because they didn't actually think things through. Now that we're actually getting closer to a la carte with streaming services, they'll have to face the reality of the situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  it's a cooler nickname than Reverse-Flash 

Disagree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   it's that the channels which are desirable are being used to subsidize all the ones that aren't

But which channels are "desirable" varies by viewer and that goes both ways: I'm paying for channels I don't watch, but the channels I watch are subsidized by people who who pay for them but don't watch them. Switch everything to a la carte and you'd get to drop the channels you don't want, but you'd have to pay more for the channels you do want because they'd no longer be subsidized by others.

If you only want a few channels (with streaming services effective being a 'channel' for comparison) then a la carte makes good sense and would save you money. But if you want large amounts of content then a la carte was always going to be more expensive than bundling. Which people are now seeing (though it should have been obvious). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hence why I never watch this show sober. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's because what people WANTED was the option to pick and choose channels for a dollar or two a month

What people really wanted was the same content they were already getting but for a fraction of the price. Which was obviously never going to be viable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not. Supernatural's longevity is very rare, enabled in large part by an extremely loyal viewership base and only having two essential cast members who are seemingly content with their salaries. (And Arrow could not survive Amell leaving, that would kill the show). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If CBS put this on their main channel people would just end up complaining after it inevitably got cancelled for low ratings. Streaming makes more sense for a show like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Shitting it out on their streaming service only will end in an early cancelation

Well they've already renewed the first scripted show exclusive to said streaming service, so it's possible that they're treating it differently than shows on their linear channel (which would be a good thing here, since *Star Trek: Discovery* would likely flop on a major broadcast channel).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 07:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  fantastic show with subpar ratings

Legion's ratings are not subpar, they're in the top half of FX shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 07:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was 100% PR BS; if CBS had actually wanted it they would have renewed it themselves, once that fell through that was it. But talk is cheap, especially after the fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost certainly not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agent Carter was produced by ACB Studios just like AoS. It was presumably just cancelled because its ratings were too low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Flash has a lot more viewers than Arrow, so duh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duplicate news; this is just yet another article parroting the EW article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  it's ratings are worse

But it's on a different network. Arrow is one of the highest rated shows on the CW, while AoS is one of the lowest rated shows on ABC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Comic book . com is an aggregator type website.

That's /u/Mullet_Ben's point; why link to an aggregator website instead of the original article?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yeah, seriously. It doesn't take into account the multitude of ways that a show can be viewed at all, it only counts when people watch it on tv when it aired.

Well its main purpose is to measure how many people watched the commercials, and most of the other ways people would watch a show have either no commercials or different ones from the original broadcast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nielsen's main purpose is to measure how many people watch the commercials in a show and serve as a metric for pricing the sale of said commercials. That it marginalizes DVR viewers and ignores stuff like Netflix is a feature, not a flaw, since advertisers aren't going to pay for viewers that skipped the commercials on DVR or watched without commercials on Netflix. As for Hulu and Netflix, what matters to network/studio isn't necessarily the number of people watching a show on Netflix/Hulu but the amount of $$ that Netflix/Hulu are paying for the show, neither of which are typically disclosed to the public. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Every damn year.

This is the first year that AoS has been in serious danger of cancellation. Over the past four seasons AoS's ratings have slipped from 5th to 10th to 13th to 19th among ABC shows. Renewal has been a near certainty in previous years but that is no longer the case; there's still a decent chance of renewal this year, but do not pretend this is the same situation as before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's not the first time we've faced cancellation.

This is the first time AoS has been in serious danger of cancellation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given only those two choices I would have to go with the latter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, did I claim that Gilbert's Generation was clean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did I claim that Gilbert was clean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who of his era didn't get caught? 

He's a proven doper and deserves to be treated as such. Sure he's no worse than much of his generation as far as that goes, but he's no better either; the main difference is that most of his generation has retired by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valverde is the one with the stronger palmares, but then he's also the one with the doping conviction, so take that as you will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $$$ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just speculation based on the EW article, not anything new or definitive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought they were lying and officially saying that her grandma still lived there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This list has some seemingly questionable placements. 

However what does play to AoS's favor is that aside from TGIT (excluding The Catch) and Designated Survivor, ABC's dramas are all doing at least as poorly as it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In HIMYM many of their apartments weren't actually as big as was shown due to the unreliable narrator, IIRC there's at least one episode where they go back and visit someone's old apartment and it's actually tiny.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm kinda surprised they left HIMYM out.

But in HIMYM there's a strong unreliable narrator effect happening that we know applies to apartment sizes, so their apartments weren't actually as big as was shown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You completely missed /u/opelan's point.

Regandless of whether Kara is being written well, regardless of how good the current ratings are, the producers would still not want to eliminate something that could be used on occasion to boost ratings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I remember watching Lost and it running normally.

Lost's first few seasons had plenty of breaks. The last two seasons ran pretty much straight through (and the 4th would have if not for the writers' strike) but they premiered in winter and were only 16-18 episodes long which was somewhat unusual for the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Eight days after </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps, but again I'm talking relative to the network: people switching from watching on TV to watching online affects all CW shows, likely at a similar rate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's possible, but unlikely; shows with sinking ratings (relative to their network) don't tend to get budget increases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I do sell supernatural short.

Think what you want about Supernatural, but statements like "Supernatural pulls in much lower ratings [than Arrow]" are objectively false.

  Netflix didn't clamor to buy next day season broadcast privileges for it. 

This is in relation to what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've gone up and down; three years ago Supernatural had the second-highest ratings on the CW behind TVD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Supernatural pulls in much lower ratings

Supernatural's ratings this season are only barely lower than Arrow's (and if you don't include the crossover then Arrow's are lower than Supernatural's).

Arrow was still an obvious renewal, but don't sell Supernatural short. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit seems to love think that TV execs (aside from the CW) are ignorant dinosaurs with no concept of things like streaming. Nevermind that every major broadcast network has and advertises its own streaming site/app, SVOD is a major part of current syndication deals, stacking rights are a big part of the negotiations for picking up new shows, etc. The big networks/studios may have undervalued the importance of streaming when it first hit the scene, but they've long since caught on.

Now I would believe that the CW puts more weight on streaming than the Big 4 when it comes to renewal decisions, not because the CW knows anything the others don't but because the CW's revenue from its linear channel is much lower than for the Big 4 and the difference may not be as great for other revenue sources. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If you go look at the airdates for long running shows there are really only breaks for holidays and sports or political special presentations.

I've actually gone back and looked at airdates for shows from back in the day to investigate this very question, and they typically had lots of breaks that weren't for holidays or special events (which fits with what you expect from stretching 22-25 episodes over the course of the entire TV season). I think people just don't remember that because in-season reruns used to be a lot more common and people weren't bothered by the breaks like they are now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC the reason recent live-action versions don't put the symbol on the back of the cape is that it makes the CGI easier, so I wouldn't expect that to change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I remember it used to be fairly clear cut...TV seasons would start in September or October, run until mid-December and go on hiatus for a winter break...then come back around the end of January just in time for February sweeps and run until early/mid-May when the season finales would air.

You're leaving out the numerous weeks of reruns that would be sprinkled in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   networks do this with shows they want cancelled

If a network wants a show to be cancelled they just cancel it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not; series regulars typically get paid more than guest stars and Arrow's not in a position to be increasing its budget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So now the question is, which of the current series regulars will get dropped to make room for the additions? Segarra obviously, and I'm thinking probably one of Willa, Paul, or David as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is it more offense that they aren't redheads

Nowhere in this thread did I take offence to anything. I was simply noting an oddly specific (and probably statistically insignificant) trend in the Berlanti DC shows, not comic book adaptations in general so all your examples from thing like Gotham and the MCU are completely irrelevant to my comment. I did forget about Roy on Arrow though, he admittedly doesn't follow that trend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't the trailer for this come out weeks ago? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So is the fact that they aren't redheads or that they are black

Is *what* the fact that they aren't redheads or that they are black? I'm just noting an oddly specific trend on the Berlanti DC shows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason the Berlanti DC shows replace redheads with black people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  CW is one of the few networks that I know of which take online numbers into account when looking to renew shows

Lol every network takes streaming and whatnot into account when making renewal decisions, the CW apparently just has the best PR about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but Live+7 numbers are mostly irrelevant and C7 numbers aren't publicly available.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This week was 0.71 in prelims (though we'll have to wait until next week to see what the unrounded finals were). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if people stop watching them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Total viewers aren't important. In 18-49 it tied the NCIS:NO rerun and beat the Chicago Fire rerun, and was up 0.04 compared to last week (and higher than every other episode since January 10th). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  why shouldn't Netflix consider it?

I'm sure they've considered it, and decided it's not worth the truckload of $$$ that Fox would ask for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In L+SD Gotham has only dipped slightly from where it was last spring (~1.2), which is a significantly better hold than Flash or Arrow. L+7 ratings are largely irrelevant (C7 ratings would be relevant, but we don't have access to those).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotham is actually holding up pretty well this season as far as ratings go.

I think the CW's superhero fatigue problems are/will be significantly exacerbated not only by the number of superhero shows they have, but by the fact that they're all made by the same producers and are thus very similar. Viewers who might not by burned out by the superhero genre overall could easily still get tired of the Berlanti formula. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only Flash did a Flashpoint. Just having an alternate-reality situation does not make something "Flashpoint", there lots of stories that have done that many of which are older an/or more well-known than Flashpoint.

That all said, AoS is doing it the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They haven't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Designated Survivor is commissioned by ABC, Netflix just has the international distribution rights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fist few episodes were good, after that it became very disappointing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unrounded is 0.71, up from last week's 0.67

If ratings can hold at these levels I'll feel a lot better about its renewal chances than when it was getting 0.6s in the winter (and the recent performance of ABC's other bubble shows is making AoS look better as well). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  decent ratings

Not so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Literally everyone else who watches the show thinks it's 100% true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AoS, easily.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And Jessica Queller is from the CW....

Queller was a writer on the show last season, she's credited for *Falling* and *Better Angels*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But your example is wrong: writing on Heroes stopped during the strike, hence why the second season was only 11 episodes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is specifically for the US </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless the scripts for season 8 are already completely finished (which is unlikely), this could potentially affect GoT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub seems to like downvoting facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neflix having its own deal with the WGA means that shows produced by Netflix won't be affected by this. 

But Netflix itself doesn't produce very much content. Most Netflix Originals are produced by other studios and sold to Netflix, so if those studios are affected by the strike that will delay those shows and thus affect Netflix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Live views are the most significant part for season renewals.

C3 and C7 views are what matter for renewals, because those are what advertisers are paying for. Live ratings have not been the main currency used in selling TV commercials for years now.

So yes, if you watch it on DVR it's true that that won't count towards Live ratings, but that's not important. If you watch on DVR within three days and don't skip the commercials that will count towards C3 ratings (likewise for C7 ratings), which are what actually matter when it comes to renewal because those are what the network's customers are paying for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   the shit network where successful shows come to die

If a broadcast show is getting shit ratings then it isn't successful.

Now in some occasions it can make sense to blame the network for a show's lack of success (such as airing episodes of a serialized show out of order), but usually the show just isn't effective enough at attracting viewers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
