<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3901</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waking the Forest tutorial by Andy Goralczyk is now available on the Blender Cloud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waking the Forest tutorial by Andy Goralczyk is now available on the Blender Cloud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[In der Tat.](https://medium.com/startup-grind/fuck-you-startup-world-ab6cc72fad0e#.3d6m68brd)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hrt, hrt!!

**[Relevant!](https://medium.com/humane-tech/tech-and-the-fake-market-tactic-8bd386e3d382#.6glmxtms6)**

These pseudo-market patterns also mask patterns of subsidy, like the fact that Ubers current operations are subsidized by investors to the tune of $2 billion per year. Thats a cost that will be immediately passed along to consumers as soon as Uber succeeds in displacing conventional taxis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ich wohne in der Grostadt und ich bekomme immer meine 50 MBit/s. Wenn die mal nicht kommen, liegt es nicht an V-DSL.

Ich bekomme **nie** meine vollen 200 MBit/s (Telecolumbus in Berlin). Nicht mal annhernd! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich habe in Berlin einen 200 MBit/s-Anschluss bei Telecolumbus aber die tatschliche Geschwindigkeit ist zu praktisch jedem Zeitpunkt weit darunter!

Ist natrlich nicht mit den Problemen auf dem Land zu vergleichen, wo beispielsweise meine Mutter froh sein kann, wenn sie 3 MBit/s erreicht. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A developed country is not a place where the poor have cars. It's where the rich use public transport."

 - Enrique Penalosa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meritocracy: the great delusion that ingrains inequality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 10:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meritocracy: the great delusion that ingrains inequality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 10:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm definitely gonna pass on this one.

Looks like a fan film by a bunch of VFX students.

Just compare how amazing the overhead shot in the original is of him twisting through the air as she roundhouse kicks him... then compare that to the lame version in the live action scene, where he's flying through the air as if on a rope.

Nothing I've seen of this live action film makes me want to see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend **[this book by German economics professor Niko Paech: Liberation from Excess](https://www.oekom.de/nc/buecher/gesamtprogramm/buch/liberation-from-excess.html)**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  what actual application do you know of that will work your CPU at 100% capacity CONSISTENTLY for however long you want?
 There are none.

3D rendering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sie regen sich darber auf, dass Trump einen *awkward*en Witz darber macht statt einzugestehen, dass es keinerlei Hinweise darauf gibt, dass *er selbst im Trump Tower* von Obama abgehrt wurde. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> War **[ziemlich weird](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uLfukuEutIU)**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last Week Tonight: Trump-Merkel Meeting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 12:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 12:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[The Art of the Deal made America see Trump as a charmer with an unfailing knack for business. Tony Schwartz helped create that mythand regrets it.](http://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2016/07/25/donald-trumps-ghostwriter-tells-all)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the essay that popularised the term: David Graeber's **[On The Phenomenon of Bullshit Jobs](http://strikemag.org/bullshit-jobs/)**

It doesn't at all mean *all* jobs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Degrowth in the US: Thinking smaller where everything is big  r/Degrowth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Degrowth in the US: Thinking smaller where everything is big  r/Degrowth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Degrowth in the US: Thinking smaller where everything is big </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deep Green: Why De-Growth? An interview </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buy our product so you can be at work longer to make your boss richer!  r/Anticonsumption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't about a simple black-and-white "people are inherently good and civilised" vs. "people are inherently violent and cruel" argument. Both of those statements are utterly reductive and unhelpful.

My premise is that rape and murder are behaviours that occurred naturally in humans since the beginning of the species. And probably at no time in history has there been *less* rape and murder than today (even though there is still way too much), thanks to our collective cultural efforts to *counter* people's natural impulsive behaviours when they are too harmful.

Just because something is 'natural' doesn't automatically mean it's constructive, sustainable or helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bei der Sparkasse Kln-Bonn gehe es aktuell jeweils um Einlagen in einer Hhe von mehreren Millionen Euro, um die aus der EZB resultierenden Zinsbelastung in Teilen aufzufangen und nicht lnger in vollem Umfang subventionieren zu mssen.

(...)

Bei den einzelnen Sparkassen, die dazu bergingen, fr bestimmte Kundengruppen Verwahrentgelte zu berechnen, gehe es um Einlagen von mehreren Millionen Euro: Damit stellen die Institute sicher, dass fr die Breite der Sparer solche Entgelte auch in der Zukunft nicht berechnet werden mssen.


Milionrssteuer anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Als Veganer und Tierschtzer mchte ich hier differenzieren:

Die Sabotageaktion mit dem Lastwagen auf der Autobahn halte ich fr absolut irrsinnig und zutiefst zu verurteilen! Keine tierschtzerische Aktion tut sich oder irgendjemandem einen Gefallen, indem sie Menschen verletzt - oder in solche Verletzungsgefahr bringt!

Auf der anderen Seite finde ich es berzogen, Einbrche von Aktivisten, die schreckliche Haltungszustnde der Tiere filmen und dokumentieren, hiermit in die gleiche Schublade zu stecken und unter dem gleichen Label von "Radikalisierung" zu fhren!

Dass letzteres rein juristisch strafbar ist, steht auer Frage, aber hier sehe ich das hnlich wie den Fall von Edward Snowden: manchmal mssen Gesetze gebrochen werden, um die Wahrheit ber Ungerechtigkeit und Misshandlung ans Licht zu bringen.

Und ein zerbrochenes Vorhngeschloss ist wohl kaum damit gleichzusetzen, wenn jemand einen LKW-Fahrer auf der Autobahn in Lebensgefahr bringt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sparkasse: Negative Zinsen fr Privatkunden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Humans are omnivores. This is the way nature made us.

Humans are also murderers and rapists by nature.

Yet we have come to a level of civilisation where we socially accept that causing pain and suffering to other creatures for our own advantage or pleasure is not acceptable.

I think it's only reasonable that, as our collective social/cultural morality evolves further, we extend this to animals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, thanks for your reply! Yeah, I can understand your reluctance regarding discussing it with friends or family.

I have some basic Python programming experience but it's all more about scripting with the APIs of 3D graphics applications like MODO, Maya or Blender, rather than full-on software development. Thanks for your advice, I'll take that into account! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of development work do you do specifically? What kinds of clients/projects do you work at?

I'm a 29 year old German Visual Effects artist and *[Technical Director](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Technical_director#Film_.26_Games)* looking at transitioning over to software development myself.

What did you do before you became a freelance programmer and what was your personal path?

Thanks for sharing your experience and financial planning - it's great to hear from fellow Germans about this. As I'm sure you know, finances are a bit of a problematically 'taboo' topic here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I'm German and I didn't know that used to be a thing.

When did they change the capital gains tax to 25% flat rather than tying it to your personal tax rate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump appears to ignore requests for a handshake with Angela Merkel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 13:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the upcoming years and decades we'll have to make *much more radical* changes to our economic and welfare systems than to keep the birth rate at replacement levels and hoping things can continue as they have in the 20th century. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure what you want to hear to be honest.

It works, it's well-known and frequently covered in the media, it's a gemeinntziger (=nonprofit) [eingetragener Verein](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eingetragener_Verein), so nothing shady if that's what you're worried about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * https://arstechnica.com/business/2016/12/federal-report-ai-could-threaten-up-to-47-percent-of-jobs-in-two-decades/

* http://www.huffingtonpost.ca/2017/02/07/automation-dominic-barton_n_14634612.html

* https://www.theguardian.com/society/2016/oct/25/850000-public-sector-jobs-automated-2030-oxford-university-deloitte-study </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. We need to become way more efficient. But it's unrealistic to expect a 6.07x raise in efficiency (which would be necessary for the US to reach 2.7 tons CO2 per capita per year) without any reductions in material, energy and other resource consumption (like mobility for example - transport and flying is a *massive* environmental hazard).

We need to help curb population growth faster and reduce consumption and increase efficiency for the areas where consumption cannot realistically be reduced.

And don't get me wrong, nobody is saying we should *forbid* people to have children! I'm not advocating a global tyrannical one-child policy - that would lead to conflicts and suffering. What I'm saying is that we need to put more effort into accelerating the *natural and voluntary* reduction in birth rates that have proven to occur in all countries where women's rights are strenghtened (i.e. they're allowed to work, vote, and find other purpose in life than just being a mother), education is raised and contraceptives are made more accessible.

Nobody *forced* Germany, Japan or other first world countries to lower their birth rates - yet in all developed countries it is much lower than in most developing ones.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The growth rate is slowing but the world population is still growing.

Just like how sitting in a car, you can decrease your *acceleration* but your *speed* will still increase as long as your acceleration is larger than 0.

Why? The earth can sustain a huge number of people. What needs to be addressed is consumption/waste, not population numbers.

If we want to meet the 2 degree maximum climate warming goal, the world's population can only produce 2.7 [tons of CO2 per year per person](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_countries_by_carbon_dioxide_emissions_per_capita). Germany is at around 9.2 right now. The USA is at 16.4. So unless we all agree to live at no higher than the standard of living of Ecuador, we need to reduce the world population.

Of course you're free to convince everyone in the first world to reduce their consumption and waste down to the level of Ecuador or Brazil, but I think it would be easier to have fewer children than to fight against people's [loss aversion](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Loss_aversion).

The practical reality is that we need to do *both* because no single solution alone will suffice and succeed to a sufficient degree. I.e. we need to reduce world population *and* our consumption levels in reasonable measures.

Check out **[Dr. Niko Paech's talks](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eeb3h9sBm0Y)** on the subject of /r/degrowth.

(Also a related [blog post](http://lykkelykke.de/2015/04/dr-niko-paech-europa-ist-eine-maschine-der-zerstoerung/)). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the same, but it's a bit like a heroin dealer who himself stays clean - because he knows heroin isn't good for his health.

Actually, it's not even an apt comparison because a big part of the addiction in social media isn't just from *reading* other content but from the gratification one receives from other people's responses to one's own content. So you're still addicted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about controlled immigration of skilled workers. You can argue about how the German government handled the refugee crisis but even leaving refugees aside entirely, Germany is doing a better job at attracting skilled immigrants who contribute to the economy.

Japan is in a more problematic position here - and its deep-rooted culture of xenophobia isn't helping here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German Basic Income project "Mein Grundeinkommen" now has English info. Here's how you can contribute, and win a "basic income". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Englische Infos auf https://www.mein-grundeinkommen.de/infos/in-english falls Ihr, wie ich, Freunde habt, die sich fr Grundeinkommen interessieren aber kein sehr sicheres Deutsch sprechen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Mein Grundeinkommen" hat eine neue Website und erlaubt jetzt auch internationale Teilnehmer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German Basic Income project "Mein Grundeinkommen" now has English info. Here's how you can contribute, and win a "basic income". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm assuming it was in there for an American audience, in order to take the wind out of the inevitable Nazi criticisms he'd be confronted with for giving a "Germany does X better than the USA" talk by some Americans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need to start thinking globally. There's no 'sustainable birth rate' in isolation - it depends on world population as well as average resource consumption per capita *globally*.

If we have a world population with an average consumption per capita that is *sustainable* (which we currently don't - even though a majority of the world is *way behind* the US or Germany in terms of consumption), then a **[replacement rate](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Total_fertility_rate#Replacement_rates)** of little above 2.0 would be sustainable.

The replacement fertility rate is roughly 2.0 births per woman for most industrialized countries (2.075 in the UK, for example), but ranges from 2.5 to 3.3 in developing countries because of higher mortality rates. Taken globally, the total fertility rate at replacement is 2.33 children per woman. At this rate, global population growth would tend towards zero.

It's a lot easier to adjust our economic systems than it is to break the physical limits of the planet. That doesn't mean adjusting our economic systems isn't politically and culturally challenging - it only means that the alternative is impossible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 11:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ Reddit ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 11:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course we do - and we are. For example in Democratic Republic of Congo the birth rate is at 6.04 (down from 7.25 in 1994), and we need to further encourage education (sexual and otherwise) and women's rights, access to contraceptives, etc.

In Germany we certainly don't need to further *decrease* it, but it also doesn't make sense to subsidise a *higher* birth rate here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TEDx Jeff Rosen - Germany: Low Crime, Clean Prisons, Lessons for America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 11:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 10:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is already an issue because the world population is still increasing (and will continue to do so for decades) and people's consumption is increasing way faster than can be offset by the lowering birth rates.

Even if we froze all *increases* in consumption rates of today and continued to consume at current rates, the planet's resources would not be enough for us to do so sustainably. But in reality we are far from that - we're still *increasing* our consumption globally.

Time **is** an issue here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How One Man's Open Source Vision Changed the 3D and Animation World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 10:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How One Man's Open Source Vision Changed the 3D and Animation World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 10:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How One Man's Open Source Vision Changed the 3D and Animation World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 10:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 10:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you look at the **[world population](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/World_population)**, there's absolutely no need to 'tackle population decline' - at least definitely not by subsidising having more children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 10:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! **This** is the discussion we need to have!

Not the short-sighted *"Ermagerd, the world's gonna run out of pure-blood Germans!"*

The world population is exploding. Having a low birth rate like Japan or Germany is a *good* thing. Where necessary, population decline needs to be offset by controlled immigration - something Germany is doing a far better job at than Japan.

All countries need to move towards lowering their birth rate to, or ideally below, replacement levels. Thankfully, birth rates are dropping globally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NOAM CHOMSKY - The 5 Filters of the Mass Media Machine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me about it. I thought I was taking crazy pills here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Maya never crashes.](https://i.makeagif.com/media/8-09-2015/7HDVcz.gif)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My internal mic on my XPS 15 9560 seems to be broken. Every few seconds the recording sounds super muted and low-volume for a little while until it returns to full volume. Does anybody else have this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the XPS 15 9560 since early February and only just now noticed that the integrated mic seems to be screwed.

**[Here's a test recording](https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B0xqL7Ik7NRSR3c1SnVvUjBYTDQ/view?usp=sharing)**.

Has anyone else experienced this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not if you're running a studio though.

And places like **[Tangent Animation](http://www.tangent-animation.ca/)** and **[Barnstorm VFX](https://barnstormvfx.wistia.com/medias/u6ncrwhp6s)** demonstrate that nowadays it's actually viable to create feature animation and VES award-nominated VFX using Blender and Houdini. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 08:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to learn Blender. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schau mal in https://www.reddit.com/r/Finanzen/comments/5seall/ist_fire_oder_leanfire_realistisch_erreichbar_in/ rein - da sind auch wertvolle Tipps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know that. Just watched **[The Young Karl Marx](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dz-1BLjQlHo)** in the cinema last night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. The Book of Life was so, so good - unfortunately the marketing didn't really support it well enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The trailer is awful, the film is actually really good!

They completely fucked up the marketing though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greg Leuenberger rants about Autodesk's bullshit forced subscription move </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greg Leuenberger rants about Autodesk's bullshit forced subscription move </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greg Leuenberger rants about Autodesk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't mean the visuals were set to be that close to Brain Divided that early on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
