<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject366</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 05:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be there right around the time you will be.  I arrive tomorrow night and leave Sunday.  I'm speaking at this session if you want to stop by Friday at 12:30.   http://schedule.sxsw.com/2016/events/event_PP57822  I can meet you afterward.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 23:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm staying in a weird Air BnB trailer!  I originally booked a cool condo months ago.  The condo was $130 a night and it was located 1.5 miles from the convention center.  I was golden.  Then 4 weeks ago, they canceled the reservation on me and I was left stranded. I'm pretty sure they realized they could get $400 a night for it.   

I took this as a sign that I should do something weird and make the best of it.  I'm not poor, just adventurous.  This is my first time at SXSW, I'm actually speaking at SXSW Interactive.  So I wanted the full SXSW experience.  

I booked this janky old trailer on Air BnB.  I arrive there tomorrow night and will check out on Sunday if you want to come by.   Here is a link to it. https://www.airbnb.com/rooms/11372348

Here is a link to the session I am speaking in:
http://schedule.sxsw.com/2016/events/event_PP57822

My name is Tom Nardone.  You can email me:  Tom (at) subject366.com  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 04:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my first time and I'm 46.  I'm planning to lie and tell people I'm 44. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 04:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great answer!  Actually, I'm giving the exact same speech I gave in Grand Rapids, Michigan.  I doubt anyone in Austin has heard it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 04:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to bring awful news, but Talib had to back out.  We all agreed to speak a while ago and they only told us the day a few weeks back.  I guess he can't get to Austin by Friday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 04:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 04:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  That makes me a feel a lot better.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm speaking at SXSW Interactive - Could You Attend So I'm Not The Only One In The Room? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 06:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm a speaker at SXSW Interactive on Friday, March 11th.  It's a great session, but I'm afraid we have been stuffed into a weird location and no one will attend.  I hope you see this and give it some thought.  

Here in Michigan we have something new called Failure:Lab.  I like to describe it as the opposite of TEDx.  A noteworthy person gets up and talks about something they completely screwed up.  They don't preach or teach, they just tell you what they messed up.  It's really refreshing to see adults admit that they aren't perfect.  

Failure:Lab is growing.  They have had them in PA, India and a few other places.  SXSW is a big deal for the organization.  I'm one of the speakers.  My name is Tom Nardone and I spoke in Grand Rapids to a big crowd about a year ago.  My speech was well received and because of that, I've been invited to give it at SXSW.  There are three other speakers.  Talib Kweli is one of them, he's sold a few million records.  Also a magician guy and a film director.  

Here is a link:  http://schedule.sxsw.com/2016/events/event_PP57822  

The event is located in the Westin Austin Downtown, in the Paramount #1 Room, at 12:30PM on Friday, March 11th.

Also, if you have any advice for me about SXSW.  I'm trying to do it right.  I've booked a ratty trailer on AirBnB and I'm going to be getting around town by bike.  I have no friends in Austin and know nothing about SXSW, so any comments are welcome.
   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 06:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm speaking at a session on Friday.  If you went to that, you could make a new friend (me!).  http://schedule.sxsw.com/2016/events/event_PP57822 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 06:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is my plan.  I'm flying in to Dallas and driving down (the flight and rental car was hundreds less this way).  I'll be stopping at a thrift shop or pawn shop on the way down.  I'm going to buy a $40 bike and then leave it in Austin when I am done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 06:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm speaking on Friday the 11th.  I hope you will attend.  The session is called FailureLab and it is like TEDx's weird, backward brother.  Here is a link: http://schedule.sxsw.com/2016/events/event_PP57822
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 05:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm taking my kids there on Sunday.  We are from the Detroit area and are heading South on a road trip.  On the first day we are going to Hocking Hills.  Thanks for posting this.  We are quite excited about it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 05:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think his comment is valid.  Tesla has a track record of promising a low price and delivering a high one. The car models may be the same, but after Tesla introduced the roadster, S, and X all at significantly higher prices than promised, I think PM_ME_ANYTHING_FUN has a valid point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 05:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The $7,500 credits were meant to help companies pay the development cost of electric vehicles.  As such, the credits won't last forever.  Each manufacturer gets 200,000 of them and Tesla will be the first company to run dry.  The prediction is by 2018 for Tesla.  No one else is making enough EVs to even come close to the limit right now, so don't expect a big lobby to get the incentives extended.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 05:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tesla is amazingly awful at predicting their development cycle.  The Model X was two years late and then in the first three months of production, they only made 208 of them.  

The Chevy Bolt is going to beat them to market handily.  It will be available at the end of 2016 and will be $30,000 with a 200 mile range.  So the Model 3 will be at least a year late and $5,000 too expensive.  TSLA stock is dropping fast and their earnings report comes out tomorrow.  I think they are blowing smoke in a major way today to keep people's eyes off of their earnings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 05:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were really good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 03:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sticking up for me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 03:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey!  That's me.  I'm sorta on Reddit.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 05:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Far Out Space Nuts -  Two guys from the catering company are loading food into a rocketship.  The one guy thinking he is pushing the "lunch" button pushes the "launch" button and they are sent to space.  Every day I eat lunch or see the word "lunch" I can only think that I might launch into space too.  The show started Bob Denver (he was also Gilligan on Gilligan's Island) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 05:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LMFMO  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 07:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sent a message to the moderators.  This is indeed my creation.  I just completed the project and editing the video.  Thanks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 06:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can use an allen wrench to try turning the disposal backward if it is jammed. On the bottom of the disposal motor there is usually a spot where you insert an allen wrench to turn the motor shaft manually.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made a Giant Jenga game in a little over an hour for $24. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 06:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
