<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3065</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 00:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Electricity...most people didn't have it in 1800. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP Fidel Castro... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She would have already done it by now.  You don't need to have a concealed carry permit to own a gun, only a 10 minute background check. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 00:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Swim the red river </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They would put you in home defense like the Nazis did when you were a youngun lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever u/veloreyn replies a baby laughs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exercise.  Running, hiking, biking all make me feel better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also have a two man crosscut saw if that counts lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you are saying a 17 year old is incapable of making choices that will decide their future but magically one year later they are now adults?  I stand by giving them a choice because not everyone has the wherewithal or perhaps the motivation to go to college, why waste their time.  For the kids that have the opportunity and motivation to continue their education by all means provide them the college prep courses because they will obviously need it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 05:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She sells sea shells by the sea shore...rubber baby buggy bumpers...I'm a smart feller I feller smart...(said 10 times real fast) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 05:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pecan...I grew up in Michigan and pronounce it pee-can, now I'm in Texas and it's supposed to be pe-con. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 05:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would not make it mandatory but give them a choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 02:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give the kids a vocational school to go to if they want.  They don't have one here in Texas for my kids but I had one in Michigan I went to.  Half the school day I took diesel mechanics and that gave me the knowledge to be accepted into the Air Force as a mechanic, of which l am now retired from and now work for the railroad fixing trains.  I didn't want to go to college so why make me take college prep classes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 02:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1,3,6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 02:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the longest time I only lived on 5 hours of sleep per night, I didn't know you were supposed to get 8 hrs so I tried it and it helps but coffee is the magic answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 02:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends if they are your friend or not.  Friend:  Wipe grease on the back of their car door handle, put a funny bumper sticker on it, banana in the tailpipe...  Not friends:  Smash a brick through their window with a sticky note on it in the middle of the night </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 06:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I didn't give enough of a shit to cheat.  My government teacher let me sleep in class so that was cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 02:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice video!  I lived out there for a year and a half and never made it out to the cowboy trails and wondered what they were like.  I always went out to cottonwood and rode those...definately not as technical as your video but a lot more faster and flowing on the way back into town. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The U.S. fish and wildlife service can't make the polar ice cap come back...what do they expect? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever research you want to believe must come from a peer reviewed source.  This gives other established experts in that field the opportunity to fact check said research and if it passes it can be published as legitimate research.  In other words, don't take some "scientists" word for something because they are getting paid to say it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always look at who is funding the research before you go jumping head long onto their bandwagon.  Things are not always what they seem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A wise man once told me, sometimes in life it's not WHAT you want to do but what you CAN do.  Good luck to you in your future endeavors! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 08:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are smart and handsome you are such a good boy and me and mommy are so proud of you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 08:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A black man being a good role model to his own children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 08:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell him to get into bike racing, it worked out well for Lance Armstrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 08:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been married since before the Internet was really a thing so I didn't think of that lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 08:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Join the Air Force as an officer and do something useful with your life.  You will be surrounded by the most awesome people to work with that you will ever find.  It sounds like you are in a perfect position to dictate what happens in your future, you have nothing or nobody holding you back except yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 08:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never have and never gonna do it because that's how people end up missing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 04:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Texas: Big Bend National Park is nice and scenic...for Texas anyway.  Not much else going on here, you're better off going up through Colorado and Utah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 04:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 18:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew there was more to the exploding fingers...doesn't sound like a good time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 08:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That exercise can be fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 08:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mac n cheese, cut up hot dogs and ketchup...maybe throw in some tater tots at this point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 08:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michigan so yea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 08:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All ya'll southerners know how to make things taste good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 08:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wore mine in 1980 and knew I looked stupid then haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 08:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking red dot Indian at first lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 05:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure it wasn't Bryan?  Sounds like something a Y'an would do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 05:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see you started using drugs at a you  age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 05:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the same damn problem and didn't figure out that I needed the right hand scissors until 4th grade.  I think someone pointed it out to me.  But yea, fuck your bitch ass teacher.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You punched Ronald McDonald in the face? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had literal icicles hanging from my fingers one time while walking home from the bus stop, I fell down and didn't have any gloves on and my big brother didn't help me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 04:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry, we got those fuckers good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yea, that's what you're supposed to do with cardboard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oldest memory seen so far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was putting my uniform on getting ready to go to work when I was in the Air Force when I saw 9/11 happen.  We got those fuckers good after that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep the shirt and make your kid wear it one day  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I remember seeing the cheer leaders with their class of 2000 uniforms on when I was in like 6th grade and thinking how far away that was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 01:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *point and laugh kids* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 01:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had chocolate milk in bags.  You had to stab it with a straw just right or it would go through the other side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 01:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, my mom made me wear a brown corduroy vest with matching corduroy pants for picture day.  I knew it looked stupid and I was so mad I had to wear it that I looked extra pissed off in the pictures lol!  My mom never made me dress nice for picture day again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 01:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My teacher got mad and threw the eraser against the chalk board and yelled at me or the entire class "you better shape up or ship out!".  I had no idea what she meant but I understood she was pissed off about something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 01:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna make my kids eat it too lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 00:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna invest the money in lottery tickets, 7-11 here I come wooooooo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 00:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never actually tried it but I have a box of Mac and cheese and a pack of hot dogs in the fridge, might have to give it a shot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you guys cut up hot dogs and throw them in the mix?  I've always heard that about Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 01:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lolz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 08:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen one of these before, it definately is pretty old.  The leads are definately not original.  The resistance scale is measured in ohms and is included on the bottom of the volt meter.  The mystery screw thing looks like some kind of adjustment for calibrating the meter.  Usually to measure resistance a small electrical charge is sent through whatever you are testing so this thing might need some type of battery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 00:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The line from the wall in the background intersects with the side of her head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yea, why do all the hard work and time to grow the stuff when you can skip all that and just rob a grower? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 08:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When are you returning to Earth in the flesh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 08:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've owned both right hand and left hand drive cars.  I also thought shifting was gonna be a problem...the turn signal gave me the most problems, they put it on the opposite side so I would always put on my wipers when turning lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 08:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm left handed and when I was in school it took me a few years to figure out why the left handed scissors didn't work good for me...I was using my right hand lol!  I'm ambidextrous but didn't know it at the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 07:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was I that left, not him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 07:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about fluorescent orange?  It's my fave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 06:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One time when I was in the military my buddy and I were driving through Arkansas and stopped at a diner to get some lunch.  We get seated and the kid taking our order asks in a thick southern accent "ya'll here for the ralley?".  We were both from up north and we had no idea what he was talking about.  Anyway about 10 minutes later these 5 mother fuckers wearing white sheets (minus the hood) come strolling in for lunch and sit down across the room from us.  Both me and my friend just look at each other like you gotta be shitting me, the fucking KKK just walked in which means a KKK ralley is gonna happen.  I thought that shit died out in the 60's but there they were.  So the kid comes back and we ask him where and when it's going to be...downtown at noon.  It was almost noon so we hang out then go check it out.  Holly shit...there were maybe 20 klan guys all decked out with their pointy hats that were surrounded by maybe 100 very pissed off black people so we just kept on going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 02:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in the military and stationed in Fairbanks Alaska from 99 to 03.  I was constantly surrounded by such natural beauty that I wanted to capture it.  I bought a used Minolta x-370 to start with and started reading online how to take good photos.  I soon moved up to a Minolta x-700 because it had depth of field preview which is really handy when taking landscape shots.  I eventually learned the down side to using print film (you don't get consistent results from the development people) so I switched to slide film because back around 2000 digital wasn't around yet.  When I made the switch my shots started coming out the way I actually saw them which was what I had been looking for.  Eventually I got into digital and have recently gotten back into film with an old Minolta SRT-101 because it's fun to get your pics back from the lab and you don't have to jack around with a computer to look at them on a screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 02:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing too ambitious, gonna try to build up to 5 miles and see if my plantar faciatis flares up.  Hopefully it won't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 02:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to tell that is actually a book laying there...my first thought was wtf is that on the ground so I had to zoom in...maybe open the book up so it is readily identifiable, but it's still a wierd shot because the book doesn't "belong" there unless it shows signs of weathering like it's been there for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 02:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live near Dallas, this time of year has really nice cirrus clouds that add to an otherwise "dead" scenic shot.  I like finding old abandoned houses out in the country for something different.  There has been some really nice sunrises and sunsets lately.  It was very humid out lately as well which gave all the dead grass a richer brown color along with old stone buildings.  There is stuff out there just gotta get out and look around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 02:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe take a look at strava heat maps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 19:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived there for a year and a half, when you get off the strip it's just like any other same sized city.  There are a lot of good hiking and mountain biking trails in the area.  Also endless miles of off road trails to ride four wheelers on.  Just 10 min out of town is open desert where you can go shooting guns if you want, completely legal.  You should see that place on Saturday morning, sounds like WWIII starting off its great.  lots of cool events happen there...supercross finals, monster truck finals, NASCAR race, off road baja race.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It only happened once so probably 50% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was in 2nd grade there was another kid with the same birthday as me and the classroom size was about 23 people!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was stationed in Germany and they had whore houses all over the place.  I never went in one but the guys I worked with said you could get off for 20 euro...probably just a bj for that much but still that's pretty cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 01:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  more likely meth heads </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 01:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But this would not have happened if dude could just roll down to the whore house and get laid for $20. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 04:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did this with my iPhone 5s   https://imgur.com/a/RIb01 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 02:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was 14 and he knew it...gets what he deserves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 02:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She can try to sue, doesn't mean she will win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 01:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What part?  The cops performing a drug raid or the shooting of some pit bulls?  If I was a cop kicking in a door because some fucking crack dealer was stalling the cops with a fucking dog in order to destroy evidence and the dog was impeding my entry, I'd shoot it too and good for the courts siding with the cops.  Ever think about that?  Or were you letting a poorly written article which presented only some of the circumstances the dogs were shot to sway your opinion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandparents had one of these by their fireplace, you put the ashes in them and then go dump it outside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was born and raised in Michigan and lived 3 miles from Lake Michigan.  I have also lived in Fairbanks Alaska for 4 years, it is awesome there and I want to go back.  I lived in Shreveport Louisiana for 5 years and that area is shitty.  Also lived in Las Vegas for 1.5 years, it was ok...lots of hiking and mountain biking but the schools are not good for the kids.  I've also lived in Texas for 6 years now, it's a good place to raise a family because there are a lot of opportunities here and the schools are pretty good.  Been through Canada twice on the way to Alaska and really liked it.  Lived in Germany for 4 years and traveled all over Europe, it was nice but it was great to be back in the US.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 07:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my personal favorite country.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 06:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. USA  2. Canada  3. Germany  4. Italy  5. France </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 06:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What were the circumstances, were you snatched off the street by some dudes in a molester van or by someone you knew? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 04:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clip on for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 04:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 60 year old you is gonna have a heart attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 02:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandparents had a party line in the 80's, you could listen in on your neighbors conversations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 05:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good physical challenge is hiking up Superstition mountain by Apache Junction.  Also the Peralta trails on the back side of Superstition is really nice and not as strenuous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 05:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks good to me!  Good old fashioned work is what them boys are up to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 04:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I joined the military during basic training.  Prior to this I had never ran more than 1/4 mile in gym class.  By the end of the 6 weeks I was running 5 miles!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 02:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is another case for judge 1911/45... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 02:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad it wasn't the Sea Galley, that place is so good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 02:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't give a flying fuck about a persons mental state, if they do something like this take them out back and blow their brains out...after they dig their own grave of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 03:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This belongs in r/wtf or r/wincest...you are definately not ready  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 03:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chief will probably kill himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 20:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like they are doing a good enough job on their own, no need to spend taxpayers dollars to get rid of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 20:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe she had a sore throat and was trying to help her out with some throat lotion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only with hot lesbian sugar mommas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 02:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snakes, salamanders, tadpoles, baby birds, worms, caterpillars, a side of fire ants, crayfish, turtles, bat wings, mouse balls... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
