<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1239</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 18:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am infuriated by people who hold radical, irrational, superstitious and ideological views despite having absolutely nothing to back it up and insist on spreading their bullshit anyways.

"Your child died of leukemia because God needed an angel" 

"I got a new job because God is looking out for me (and ignoring all those leukemia babies)"

Or any non religious demagoguery:

"I don't believe in a state!"

"I'm so OCD"

"I identify as..."

"Global warming is a hoax!"

"My sign is a cancer so that means I'm X"

"Cleanse your body of toxins!"

"I'm oppressed by X Y Z and every other letter"

"I disagree with you so you're a racist (insert demographic)-phobe"

"It's just my opinion!"

Also virtue signaling. Congratulations you retweeted that article written by a rich suburban kid about sexism in the workplace. You're truly a visionary" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear this game is programmed to kill you by any BS necessary sometimes just to ensure you are dying enough to keep the atmosphere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 03:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The EU was absolute garbage. It's all crappy fanfiction that people got to make canon, I'm glad they erased it. Unfortunately, given EP 7 was just **A New Hope:Pirates of the Caribbean Version** and these stupid animated shows brought in all this "nightsister magik" and "sith imperial inquisitors" and all this other nonsense they really ought to just keep nothing but the original trilogy canon and start the whole thing over, prequels and all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 03:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Negan is one of the best things to happen to the show. He's fantastic. However, I get the feeling that it won't last because as others have said, he needs to kill people to maintain his atmosphere and there are scarce few members of the cast left that anyone would care about losing. I'm honestly not sure what tropes they can explore that the show has not covered. Once Shane died the show lost a lot of its "energy". Honestly I liked when the Governor made his return as a changed man, and quit watching up until the season 7 premiere after they just rushed him into getting himself, a tank, and his entire group killed by Daryl just when they were adding new and interesting characters to the show. If anything, he should have gone off to do his own thing  like Morgan for a couple seasons and showed up to clash with Negan as an anti-villain later on, to give us a three way conflict and tie up the show entirely. Have Rick die and pass the torch to Carl a la The Road, have the Governor have a Darth Vader style redemption and take Negan down with him, and end it. It's about time, it can't survive off of these "sort of following but sort of not following the comics" boring plotlines that lack any real substance.

EDIT: Also cut season 4 in half, condense seasons 5-6 into one season and cut out the bullshit. You'd think they would have learned from season 2 that it's boring as fuck watching them sit around and do jack all while having some random boogeyman kill off cast members just as they start to get interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 02:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are EU fanboys? Now I understand Hitler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 18:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What OP asked: What's the TL;DR for 2016?

What everyone read: Do your worst Billy Joel parody </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The weird thing is it isn't laggy when I play other multiplayer games or co op in this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think so, no. Would it cause that much of a difference? And how much harder would it be to find summons? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I give up. How *do* I git gud at PvP so my hits do damage instead of making them fart blood while they roll in circles and kill me by stabbing the air behind them ten feet away from where I actually am? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 06:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on PS4. Soul level 150 quality/faith build. NG+++. Trying to get tokens for Darkmoon and Farron covenants. PvP is nothing but me attacking people and dealing no damage even when I connect, and getting R1 spammed to death even when I'm not even getting hit. As in, I roll backwards twice or roll behind them and they keep swinging at a spot that I'm currently ten to twenty feet away from and I'm taking hit after hit.  I even went scrub and tried the estoc and dark sword. No damage. Even if I surprise them and run up and hit them, it just makes blood and impact noise but no damage as they roll away and then swing at the air across the room and kill me. Can't get a single kill unless i get summoned in with other people to do damage for me. Why am I experiencing such massive latency? I've tried defragging my PS4 drive to clean up any issues with the system. Still having extreme latency but only with this game, other multiplayer games are totally fine, no lag issues. Same with co op, no latency. Since I see people making videos all the time with no problems I'm guessing I have something set up wrong. Unless some hacker takeover is going on but that's just ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 08:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to Uni in Salem. Commuting through Salem made me drop out it was so bad. Guys, that witch stuff happened miles away from Salem as it is today. It just pretends to be the actual location because it kept the original name.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must have missed them traveling that far. I took a break after they killed him off. Didn't intend for him to be a hero though, still hostile to Rick. More like an anti-villain  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 16:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted his character to continue, not Woodbury. Imagine the governor suddenly appearing out of an absence to fuck up Negan just when Rick and company are desperate for something to give them an opening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 11:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only death that made me stop watching was The Governor, because that arc they had going when he came back was awesome, and really made him an incredibly interesting character, an anti-villain of sorts. I always thought it was Michonne's fault for starting that whole war and she should have died for it. Instead, they abruptly ended that arc and killed him off too quickly so they could rush into another season 2. So I got bored and stopped watching for a long time. Picked it up a month or so before this new season because Negan sounded cool, and the finale got me hooked. So far, Negan is awesome, really recaptures that old Governor thrill I missed. 

So, I think I'd be fine with anyone getting killed off, unless it's the villain being bumped too soon. I've known all the cast for plenty long enough, I can losing a few to make room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 11:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no way in hell the finale will not include another main cast death at the least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 11:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring back the Governor. That arc they had going where he was becoming a fleshed out and reformed character was great, I was hoping they would keep him on as a sort of anti-villain. It would have been amazing for them to have him wander off to do his own thing/kept him on as a side arc and then brought him back to clash with Negan to give Rick's group what they need to exploit the clusterfuck that would be the Governor rampaging through the Saviors (what a sight that would be). If anything, even if they had to kill him back then, they should have kept him around longer, that arc was just too good to just suddenly have him and his entire group (tank included) single-handedly killed by Daryl. And then follow it up with another season 2. 

Kinda think they killed Tyreese too early too. Thought Beth's death was pretty lame plotwise, the whole Hospital arc was just dumb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 05:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DS4?! DEAD SPACE 4 CONFIRMED </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 03:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joke's on you, I love being a medic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 02:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny how the progressive left is declaring everyone that doesn't agree with them Nazis when they're the one's censoring speech and banning books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 16:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of what ou said has anything to to do with what he said or what I said. You're making up a pointless straw-man so you can justify your crusading. The trial is about a woman accusing a man (who is not a rapist until PROVEN to be) of a crime, and she has to recount not only the details of that crime to the jury, but illustrate how she was in fact victimized. She can't say "Yeah he just raped me" and nothing else, lock him up, case closed. The law doesn't work that way. She has to illustrate to the jury "no he did X action against my will". If you had actually read my comment, I already addressed the purpose of this. To use your logic, if you were telling me 

"Yeah a guy came in and demanded I give him money"

I, if I were a judge would ask "And did you?"

"Yes"

"And why did you?"

"Because he had a gun to my head"

Bam. Now I have gotten you to announce for the jury to hear that you were in fact forced to hand over that money and not only is the defendant guilty of robbery, but ARMED robbery. Now in light of supporting evidence, the jury has a complete picture of the circumstances and can properly mete out justice if it is found to be warranted, because the judge was thorough and asked enough questions to give the jury a full picture of the crime.

We have these in my home state during self defense cases to. They go a lot like this:

"You shot this man in self defense is that correct?"

"Yes"

"And why did you use deadly force instead of trying to flee the encounter?"

"Because I was up against a wall and had no route to escape nor time to find another solution to preserve my own safety."

This is just basic due process. It is for the benefit of both parties to ensure justice is meted out and the facts are made clear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 13:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People seem to prioritize feel-good "justice" over actual trial. This question was in no way posed as "You really should have kept your legs together", which is what is being erroneously claimed. In reality, what he asks is for details about the event, including why she could not resist. This is to get a detailed account of what happened, and to make it crystal clear that she was in some way restrained or physically forced to engage in these acts. This is TO HELP HER MAKE HER CASE. 

You don't get to just pat the lady on the back, say "there there, no trial needed, you're a douche-bag if you want any details about what happened, just lock the guy up" and act like justice has been served. It's ridiculous.

Honestly, the real douchebags in this are the people putting their own ideology and feel goods above both justice and the reality of rape in order to either make money off the sensationalism, indulge their own virtue signaling, or suck a rape victim into their ideology to use as a publicity pawn.

Edit: Go ahead and downvote, you're just declaring the last paragraph applies to you

Also "acquitted rapist"

You mean the person ACCUSED of rape and found not guilty in court. Innocent until proven guilty. Fuck's sake, this shit ruins peoples lives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please stop joining Hardcore if you can't stop panic-shooting every single teammate you run into. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always been the type to prefer hardcore in battlefield games, simply because I enjoy it more. The problem with this game however is this new mechanic where teammates don't have icons above their heads until a second or so after you aim directly after them, which means half the time I run into a teammate, they'll just spray fire and kill me. (Personally, I think it's pretty easy to see the difference in uniform) Is anyone else having this problem-like, not just having it be an annoying thing you have to put up with here and there, but an every-two-seconds kind of thing? I understand the addition of the feature to make people hesitate to shoot and add to the realism, but it really seems that like many attempts to enhance realism in games, it just ends up getting in the way of the fun. I really needed to vent about this one because I swear that most of my deaths are from teammates this installment. Maybe it's just me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 02:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completed the fight. The lady with the scythe does in fact have an invisibility/teleport move that is almost exclusively fatal. You need to stay moving when she vanishes or she can hit you with the grapple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 22:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically you want to combine Sister Friede with Nameless King? a 3 part boss that can insta kill you with an invisibility/teleport and fill the map with OHK area attacks?

Sounds fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 05:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 0/10 you didn't actually weld your anus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
