<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3318</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TDY to hometown, her family can help.  Recruiting station?  
I'm saying this from my lounge chair.......talk is cheap shipmate.   Bravo Zulu for caring! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 23:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once you click, it it is gone, but you have a "clicked page" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 12:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the poising from Chemo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you wish you could give back? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 02:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 01:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go with a sexy surface mount?

Google search Lutron Model # DVWCL-153PH-WH
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 00:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone is correct.  Finally. the disk is to mark where your ball is on the putting green. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have the video of the inside of a Coinstar machine at work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 03:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 14:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It still works! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you keep an idiot in suspense? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 02:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you keep an idiot in suspense? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 23:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice - Don't want to discourage - I would hit up the rule of thirds.  With that said........asking for critique shows you have some balls.  Keep going!  #3 reflection is the best - rule of thirds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do these photographers know to put an orange filter over their flash? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 02:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 23:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where does the line for the kool-aid and the purple robes start? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 03:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there is a hole in the bottom it is the end for a curtain pole. Put the curtain on a wooden decorative pole and cap the end with a pair of these.  
http://www.mckinney.co.uk/products/curtain-pole-finials

Edit: added link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 00:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a voltage selector.   I have seen something similar on old x-ray machines.   The operator selects the power with a control knob, the signal is sent to a motor which turns a gear.  The gear turns the gear you have on your voltage selector to "dial in" the voltage needed by swinging the arm to a particular place along the brass contacts. Each set of brass contacts is a certain voltage.   X ray machines use kilovolts, so this voltage selector was inside a protective box. Maintenance included cleaning off those brass contacts about once a year or when the operator complained that the x-ray was not shooting at particular settings and cleaning off the connections on the arm that swings around the contacts.  I would put this in the late 50s to late 60s.  Now we use computers to select which relays will connect to a voltage divider when the x-ray button is pushed.
As a caveat:  I have seen them in x-ray machines, perhaps they may have been used for industrial applications where selecting high voltages is required.  Welding or motor speed controller?  Just a good safe way to choose the high voltages needed.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I may speak for others like myself, the next President (arguably) will name up to four supreme court justices. These justice picks are important for the future of our country depending on which way you swing - conservative or liberal.  Presidents choose Supreme Court nominees on the basis of several criteria including nominees perceived ideological position, rewarding political allies, appealing to voters, and avoiding confirmation battles in the Senate. Trump would most likely nominate a Justices whom are more in line with conservative values.   Clinton would most likely nominate a Justices whom are more in line with liberal values.  
Some critical issues which may arise for decisions in Supreme Court cases are abortion rights, immigration, affirmative action, death penalty, stem cell research, energy, euthanasia   physician-assisted suicide, global warming/climate change, guns, healthcare, same sex marriage, welfare.  
It is important to remember  What the Supreme Court says  goes.   
VERY IMPORTANT - The supreme court justices are appointed for life.  
If Clinton or Trump can stack four out of the nine Justices to rule cases toward their partys views, then the Supreme court decisions are more likely going to lean toward those views.  
So, as your question asks why are some of us "obsessed"   Well, I want the law of the land which the Supreme Court decides to go toward my views regarding things like immigration, guns, healthcare, etc.  This is a once in my lifetime chance to get up to four votes on the Supreme Court which will lean the country toward my beliefs and determine the direction of the country for many years. (liberal or conservative).  Once Clinton or Trump are out of office and probably until the day I die, the Supreme Court justices will be deciding cases toward or away from my views and beliefs. 
  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women and Dogs and Cats. Oh my! What is the neighborhood coming to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 21:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 05:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many to choose from,a buffet!  Delicious!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 04:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it! Thanks for bringing it down to my level. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
