<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2797</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> why does it feel like so much effort to do things? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 07:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It feels like tremendous effort to get in my car to drive somewhere to meet a friend. or to go to work or to write an email, make a phone call etc... it always seems so much better to just NOT do these things  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bloody boxing match. one of those thats actually a little hard to watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> could someone explain, in a strictly mathematical sense, what the problem is with quantizing gravity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is known to be difficult or technically impossible as I have heard Leonard Susskind once say. I have heard some parameters shoot off to infinity. I know first semester linear algebra, calc 1, 2, and a little bit of multivariable. also some discrete mathematics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 02:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Ill stop smoking when I draw my last breath
2. After a full week of work I just feel like Ive had enough of people so its hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just feel so much more alive alone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 05:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Im around other people I just feel like Im never quite myself, it drains my energy. It requires so much effort. When Im alone I can do anything, even though its usually just smoking weed and reading or playing online chess or some shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 06:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe Gauss because of how he really got going that notion of rigidity in proofs. he also just had so many really important contributions in analysis and higher arithmetic. another one might be John Nash simply because he was known for his originality and creativity  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 01:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks Im already comfortable with the basics and multiplication. I just dont understand what the material is going to look like this semester (first undergrad linear course) or what it will be used for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 03:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks. Im pretty comfortable with basic proofs. not sure on the curriculum yet Ill look.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> taking linear algebra and calc 2 next semester. what are some things I should practice over winter to help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 02:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what things are good to be sharp on going into these 2? for calc 2 im assuming trigonometry and a few other things. for linear algebra I have no idea. any advice is appreciated. thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 01:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you know of any sources to get started on that? that sounds fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 09:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> couldnt have put that any better myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 03:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 03:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks this paper looks awesome  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 03:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you see what I mean though right? that rows 2 and 3 have 1 unique number, 4 and 5 have 2 uniques and etc for each succeeding pair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> are there infinitely many numbers that appear exactly 4 times in Pascal's triangle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 21:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it seems that all of the triangular numbers after 6 appear 4 times. just wondering if there are any proofs conjectures etc. for this. thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 21:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is what I meant thanks I figured there had to be a proof already for it somewhere  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 21:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes. sorry I worded it poorly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if there are 7 questions and 2 will be picked at random, since the order doesnt matter we have c(7,2) which means combination 7,2 or 7 pick 2. this gives us 21. there are 21 different arrangements of 2 unique elements from 7 unique elements. If you study 2 questions, your odds are 1/21. and you can kinda go from there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is this a known property of Pascals triangle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if the rows are represented as row 0, row 1, row 2, ....

then if row 1 = n, for each (n+1) and (n+2) after row 1, the rows (n+1) and (n+2) have the same number of unique numbers in that row. Examples... rows 2 and 3 have 1 unique number, rows 4 and 5 have 2 unique numbers, rows 6 and 7 have 3 unique numbers, rows 8 and 9 have 4 unique numbers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 01:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to know how some people attack researching the problem. And I guess if possible learn some proofs within the topic. Just the next level above practice problems in a book that just introduces you to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 06:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> one semester of discrete math and a very basic understanding of group theory.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> huh huh... hWHOA! that was pretty cool  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> exploring the isomorphic graphs problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> been studying graph theory for a few months now and really like this problem. I was wondering if there are any decent books or other sources on it which will help bring me to the next step? thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 00:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks thats interesting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 00:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> which theorem explains the technique to answer this combinatorics question? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In order to list the numbers 0 to 7 in binary notation, we need 12 1s (000, 001, 010, 011,
100, 101, 110, 111). How many 1s are needed to list in binary the numbers from 0 to 1023?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 14:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sweet thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to everyone mentioning the double major, Im a little late in getting my first bachelors degree so I want to finish it soon and not delay it. thanks for the suggestions tho  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes I love it. Im actually switching over from chemistry  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do so thanks for the advice! yes I do like proofs thats been one of the issues lol theyre not in physics too too much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> major in math or physics ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I enjoy proofs but am also fascinated with physics. I also would like to do research for a living.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what could help someone decide between choosing to study math or physics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> anyone know of any good books on writing algorithms for non computer science majors? do you think this is a necessary skill for a math or physics major? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 00:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is the algorithm design manual a good one? any others? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> if you are having trouble deciding whether to major in/focus on physics or math, what are some things you can consider to help with the decision? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 20:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 20:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes my question was why say at least 6 red or 4 blue. but I think I understand it now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 20:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok this was pretty much the answer I was looking for. because the choices of 6 and 4 are what really threw me off. seems very arbitrary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> does anyone feel confident explaining ramsey numbers to someone seriously struggling with them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 15:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> im white. 2 black co workers hired months after me for the same exact job, they have no college ed, I do.... they get started with a higher pay because white privilege </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 21:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> white privilege ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
