<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3232</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop trying to bait an argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey buddy, knock it off with the hostility and insults, please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not personally offended by cunt. I think you're thinking of the other person you were arguing with. 

I'm the person that was informing you that "flip" is a slur. Which it is. That's all I had to say.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know what you're babbling about anymore--but chances are people might not even be able to see your comments anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like the mods are removing most of your comments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pedantic nonsense over whether or not a cake is truly "edible" if it contains fondant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I think that if you're arguing after the fact about if it's "we" or "I" it might betray some unresolved resentment/conflict that occurred during the pregnancy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know you can respond with multiple thoughts in one comment, right? You don't have to use a separate comment for each thought that comes to mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For most people, hunting is expensive AF.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boy, I sure am glad I live near Central Market! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zing!  Heyoooo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's pointless to even compare--the two experiences are apples and oranges. I can understand that a man might feel helpless and clueless watching his partner go through such a physically trying experience--and he'll never be able to know what it's like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the only thing I took was prenatal vitamins and a Vitamin D supplement. I didn't need any medication during the birth, either. I consider myself very fortunate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got lucky with my pregnancy, and only had heartburn and back pain in the last month or so. Really, there isn't much you can do to avoid it--it's a sign that the right hormones are being released at the right time, so there's even a silver lining to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is a cake like a pregnancy? There's a drama bun in the oven in /r/ShowerThoughts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...How did you know what my AP calculus teacher's hair looked like, *exactly*? This is amazing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt embarrassed for her. I actually couldn't make it through the whole thing. And it's such a shame, because I like most of her stuff so much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overcooked, I think. Glaze looks nice, though. I would think 30 minutes at 350 would suffice--40 minutes at 400 is overkill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Cool post. I work in finance." It's CPAs vs. MBAs in /r/AskReddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem way more offended by being told it's a slur than anyone else here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem day drunk. Are you day drunk? Or possibly huffing duster?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, you didn't come up with flip, you doofus. American military officers stationed in the Philippines used it as a slur way before you figured it out. It's like saying "gook" or "slant." You're better off not using it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the part of this story that's made up is the part where you have neighbors that actually talk to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah...they get to say that. You don't get to say that. That's how it works when you take back a slur. Go work on taking cracker back or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Flip" is a slur used specifically against Filipinos. But you know that. Carry on, racist troll.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep--you have eye liner, that's goes along the edge of the lid. Then there's mascara, that goes on the eyelashes. Then there's shadow, that goes on the lid. The eye shadow in the cosplay is lighter than in the game, as you point out. 

A lot of effort goes into cosplay makeup--that was probably an hour's worth of work right there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just they make everything have a gay spin

What's this "everything" you're referring to? And who is "they?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it speaks to one of the biggest problems with modern politics in the U.S. -- party affiliation is too often based on morals, not based on actual political positions as to how to govern the nation. So it's not about left and right, it's about "evil" vs. "good" and that's a huge problem IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fusion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh look, casual racism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I still don't understand what your issue was, but at this point I'm just going to chalk it up to a miscommunication. I find it ridiculous that you're saying I'm "targeting" you. It's absurd. I'm glad you enjoy our community. I hope you can learn to live with all the "ethical gray areas." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, are you talking about eye shadow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tagged him as a concern troll, because I don't think this could possibly be authentic, either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yes, they absolutely do. It's important that you learn to recognize makeup early, or you're going to have really unrealistic expectations for what women actually look like later on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey jaimie-lee! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* You linked directly to the full comments of a submission.  This  submission actually does merit an exception that rule, but as per the sidebar it must be submitted in a self post.

If you're unsure how this is done, check out our [wiki](/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules#wiki_submitting_self_posts_and_write-ups)



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all part of my secret plan to have my own opinions about things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's wearing heavy amounts of mascara, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The American Express Platinum card comes delivered in a block of wood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got news for you--they're wearing makeup.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should probably check out some women without makeup. She is very clearly wearing very heavy amounts of makeup in this picture--it's not even "natural look" makeup. She's wearing foundation, eyeliner, mascara, eye shadow, powder, possibly bronzer, lipstick, and lip liner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can help with this--the label given depends on the test given, actually. For example, the WAIS classifies anything about 130 as "very superior" while the Stanford Binet classifies 145160 as "very gifted." The Woodcock-Johnson classifies 130+ as "Very superior." The Standford Binet is better suited for gifted people because it gives more meaningful higher range scores. Although the term "genius" was first used in the first version of the Standford Binet, it is no longer used in official IQ classifications. If you took an IQ test that said you were a genius, it is not a legitimate IQ test. Scores over 160 are very, very rare--around 1 in 12,000 people. You need to be tested by a psychologist who is trained to administer IQ tests--so something like an online Mensa test or even an in-person Mensa test is not the same as an IQ test. Some people find this confusing. There are lots of intelligence measures out there, but not all of them are IQ tests, if that makes sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to make it myself because I can control how sweet it is. Sometimes I mix in some of the store bought stuff at the end because I find it helps with the consistency.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG, I was just about to link this. This recipe is great! I will also recommend [this one from Saveur](http://www.saveur.com/article/Recipes/Classic-West-African-Peanut-Stew). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there was a deleted comment, they deleted it themselves. You can always use ceddit if you want to know for sure. Accusing me of impropriety is pretty rude. 

I wasn't complaining

It doesn't blatantly come off as faultless.

You know, there's nothing worse than a rules lawyer who doesn't understand the rules. And if you didn't feel it was a big deal you wouldn't have been commenting on it to this extent. 

I'm unconvinced of your argument that just because rules are worded in a certain way that everything is ethically acceptable.

I still don't see what "ethical" issue you have, and you haven't explained yourself at all, you just keep complaining. In any event, if you disagree with the way the sub works, you can contact modmail to discuss you complaints further or you can avoid our community.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why married couples should have individual bank accounts in addition to a joint account. This is the advice I give to every couple I know that's going to get married--do NOT just have a joint account. Have some way to separate finances to some extent--it's very important.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, well, I don't think you understand the rules of our sub then. I'm having a hard time understanding why this is an "ethical grey area" to you. 

People are not allowed to follow links and vote in them. I never do that. But if I happen to be in a thread and see some outright foolishness and I vote on it and then later it gets posted here after the fact, there's nothing wrong with that. And if you vote someone up or down and then decide to link them here, there's nothing wrong with that. It is not a "grey area" because that's the way we write the rules of this sub. If you have a problem with the sub rules you're more than welcome to voice them and our team will discuss them--but frankly I don't see how it would ever be reasonable to ask people not to vote in threads *before* they're posted here. 

I make every effort to do things by the book in here--I usually even hold myself to a higher standard *because* I'm a mod. I think people should be good examples if they're going to be moderators. 

EDIT: 

The only thing that is surprising is that the one comment disagreeing with you was removed. There might have been more story behind that though.

What are you talking about? No comments in this thread have been removed. I can offer screenshots if you want as proof. The only one complaining about this is **you**--your comments are still here for all to see. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't link that here, please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made with imitation crab!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Sushi Pizza" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Archive](http://archive.is/K9IwQ) 

Spoiler alert: I'm pretty sure that guy's *not* a chef, self-respecting or otherwise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bitter butter rebuff in /r/GifRecipes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He worked for ten years in the Allium PD, interrogating vidalias for hours until they'd finally crack under the pressure. 

"The lights get pretty hot in here don't they, Stretch? Where were you on the night of the 21st? Well? Where were you, Stretch?"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You want something great? Wrap a pupusa around a hot dog as a bun and put curtido on it. Fucking amazing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, for that reason it feels like a work of art. It reminds me of one of my favorite albums ever *My Life in the Bush of Ghosts*. [Example track](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=52-zmNmplRQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF is that music? And it's shot diagonally, in the dark. Someone should edit and remix this to be like the credits of Kimmy Schmidt. "They alive, dammit! It's a MIRACLE!"

However, he's right about Goya Adobo seasoning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sigh...my 9am didn't show up so I have a few minutes. Link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Children are not the best judges of what is potentially harmful for them, which is why we do things like force them to go to school and eat balanced meals. Your argument is going the way I've seen countless arguments made by pedophiles go, and it is simply not happening in here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, we're not doing this here. Take your pedophilia-justifying arguments to another sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it could be argued that if his friends attempted to hurt him because of his femdom fetish because they think it's "gay," *that* would be a hate crime, and you could argue that her sharing the pictures precipitated a hate crime. But I'm not sure you can argue that sending the pictures itself is a hate crime. I'm not a lawyer though, what do I know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how he feels about the fact that almost all of his comments were still posted and shared? His bullshit story will forever live on in the museum of SRD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He does, indeed, seem to be full of it. I don't get why you'd make up a story like that, but I don't know why a lot of people tell the lies they tell. 

I do not know anything about Guy Fieri as a person, so who knows if he's a jerk or not. What I do know is that when I'm not feeling well and I'm sacked out in bed or on the couch, his Diners show is the perfect fit. It's going to be either that or *Con Air* for the zillionth time. Perfect sick TV.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am pleased to say I did not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a big deal, I only stickied the comment to make it easy for people to follow a working link.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I read through it and voted before I posted it here. That's not the same thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES. I'd give him 60% gross revenue in perpetuity for $1000 up-front

This man got his MBA from Shark Tank University.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, please remember NP links are no longer required--and in the case of /r/drama they mess things up. Here's a regular link:

https://www.reddit.com/r/Drama/comments/67w1ib/can_legaladvice_take_on_their_13_year_old_self/dgtpqxn/?sh=4ac477e7 st=J21QQUR9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not playing that game; I will legitimately be a multi-billion-dollar CEO and still play dumb pretending not to know the meanings of common finance terms, continuing to force plain-English negotiations. And you probably read all this and just shut down and have zero doubt that I'm incompetent. Which is why in the long run I will dominate your kind, probably create a trillion-dollar corporation and maybe destroy capitalism. 

This is what we're here for, folks. 

Honestly, I think this might be one of the best mental defense mechanisms I've seen in a long time. "I pretend I'm ignorant so that I can gain an advantage over you, but I'm a genius--even though I sound dumb as a box of hair!"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to see someone give me a single issue where Trump aligns with Hydra.

Is this real life?  

Guess what, pop culture is going to echo politics. I watched Jeopardy yesterday and Alex Trebek made a Trump joke about Hadrian's Wall (finally, I've been waiting for more people to make that comparison). People should prepare for years of this, because it's not going to stop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear, if I never hear the term "Donkey Sauce" again it will be too soon. Yuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because reading all that made me angry and contributed nothing to the world. I don't get how making up a story about Guy Fieri being an asshole helps anyone, ever. 

Except, of course, this post. Maybe I'll go back and take back those downvotes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, he was probably just not listening to Guy Fieri, which is the exact thing that he said Guy Fieri accused him of doing. 

Guy Fieri was like the teacher from Peanuts. 

*Waahh waahh wah waaah wah off the hook wahh waaah donkey sauce waaah wahh Flavortown USA.*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or how about when he got in a [fight with his hairdresser?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kZdr6E5tmik) Honestly, if I had his hair I would have kicked my hairdresser's ass *years* ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, I got the info I have from an episode of The Splendid Table in which they discuss the history of bananas, so if you are interested you can [check it out](https://www.splendidtable.org/episode/583). The way I understand it, banana cultivation (even come organic plantations) is often done on land that used to be rainforest, and for this reason there is an argument that we should stop buying bananas altogether. However, *if* you're going to buy bananas, there are some sources that are much better than others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's actually *one* good reason to buy certain organic bananas--there are programs like GROW that give proceeds back to the farming communities that produce them. Banana monoculture is terrible for the environment, but if you're going to buy them, go for a slightly better source, like EKO OK.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another weird thing is, Guy Fieri went to University of Nevada, Las Vegas--and I'm pretty sure he graduated high school. He was an exchange student and spent a year in France in high school. I mean, I guess it's possible he then dropped out and got a GED and then went to college, but it doesn't really make sense IMO. He got his Bachelor's degree in 1990, when he was 22.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that part is conceivable, for sure. What I, personally, do not believe, is that Guy Fieri told a kid to make "direct eye contact with him at all times." C'mon, now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They both love pudding and hoagies, though.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably an accurate call. He seems like a very smart but *very* awkward guy--and even though he's an educated adult, there's this strong immaturity that comes through in his comments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, sorry he deleted everything, but I have [screenshots of most of his comments](http://imgur.com/a/WZFlk).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hang on, I'm making an imgur link with the highlights.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Ask and you shall receive](http://imgur.com/a/WZFlk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama in Flavortown when someone tells an unflattering story about Guy Fieri </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, I just looked through some of the insane walls of text you've been writing in here, and you have officially surpassed the guy who thought it was called the Mylar reaction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I wanted to recieve a history lesson

No you didn't, you just wanted to bitch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? It's a stone's throw from becoming it's own SRD thread. He can't stop thinking about his stupid post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is an ethical reason to buy certain bananas, though--there are programs like GROW that give proceeds back to the communities that grow the bananas--and banana cultivation, as you know, is pretty damaging to the environment. I think there needs to be a complete overhaul in the system, personally, but if you're going to buy bananas it makes sense to buy ethically.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's unacceptable--it's revenge porn. If he had sent out pictures of her naked sucking his dick it would have been the same thing. What he did was terrible, but what she did was unjustifiable IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, how was your meal overall? I've heard so many wonderful things about that restaurant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, fuck you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is this like a savarin?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice job with the shaping! It looks great. I might have brushed a little butter on the edge of the crust to help precipitate the browning a little more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nashville inspired? Hardly! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, dude, I don't know what to tell you. I've made a lot of empanadas in my life, the recipe in the gif is pretty standard in terms of how the dough is made. If you don't like it, good news, you don't have to make it--you can try to make dumpling wrapper "empanadas." But they won't be the same, just like I can make pizza on matzoh but it won't be the same. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No insults, please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure there are, but you said "properly." That's not the way empanadas are made, just like they aren't made with dumpling wrappers. There are lots of variations on empanada dough, of course, but most are similar in structure to a pte brise, not a puff pastry. 

If you don't feel like making a dough yourself, some hispanic foods sections has empanada dough pre-made (Goya makes some, for example). That would be my best recommendation to you. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because empanadas are not made with puff pastry. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're making a large number, you can roll out a lot more dough, cut a bunch of mass circles at once, and fold them over--no question, that's easier. 

But I was addressing your statement that you can buy dumpling wrappers. That's just incorrect, and you shouldn't recommend it to people--it's a different type of dough. 

EDIT: just to clarify, there are numerous types of pastry dough--not all pastry is puff pastry. Pastry just means it's got flour, water, and some kind of shortening. Puff pastry is pate feuilletee. The pastry we commonly see in savory pies like this is pate brisee. Cream puff dough is pate a choux. Each has a specific way it's made.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that's just silly. It's a pastry dough. The way they made it is completely standard and there are no corners to be cut--unless you use a food processor. 

If you think you can use store-bought dumpling wrappers to make empanadas at home, you've clearly never had an empanada. If you don't want to make your own dough, don't--plenty of us are able and willing to do it, but not every recipe is going to suit every person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cane syrup and sausage. It's damn fine. 

Salt in the chocolate milk. 

And this one is strange but trust me: salami and grapes. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not weird at all. Maybe it's just more common in certain cultures. I had a roommate who was Russian and she put cream cheese and preserves on everything--waffles, bagels, toast, pancakes, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the butter?

Look, there are different kinds of dough out there. Pastry dough is a butter and flour based dough--sometimes with egg and sometimes without. This is a pastry dough. The texture is nothing like a dumpling wrapper. Have you ever had an empanada? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never used egg in dumpling wrapper dough. Or butter. This is a pastry dough, it's COMPLETELY different. I think you're mistaken.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well now you know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Can you blame me for not realizing how poorly that would come across

Yes. You come across as an epic supercilious snoot. But thank you for the material.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that's even more confounding and ridiculous then. 

Your post is now even more perfect for this sub, thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dumpling wrappers are NOT the same as empanada dough!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, I don't know what's going on here, but I see grossknuckles is following megasuspegasus around arguing. Don't bring that stuff in here, please. If it continues, you'll be asked to step outside and fight each other with garden implements until one of you loses consciousness. 

So stop it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost my best friend in a terrible bull-riding accident, want to come over for some half-eaten pad thai? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they're prepped in terms of what to say sometimes, and I think they're probably allowed to use recipes they bring or have time to prepare in some way, but they definitely have a lot of technical skills. I love the Kid's Baking Championship on the Food Network--those kids are the real thing. I can tell by the mistakes they make and the semi-crappy job they do decorating. But they're still amazing. I mean, 11 and 12-year-old kids who can make better macaroons than I can. And lemon curd. And ice cream. And it all looks just a *little* wonky because they're children so of course it's not professional. I get a big kick out of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes sense, as the two are quite similar but APD is more severe and is generally not diagnosed until (minimum) early adulthood. 

Do you do any kind of social skills training or group therapy to help with your symptoms? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because she lost her breasts. There's a lot of power to showing what you lost. And she's not going to get them back, and she's learning to be okay with that--that's an important message for survivors of illnesses and injuries who lose parts of themselves they can't get back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to discourage you from going--as far as I know this was a temporary "special" from a few years ago and is not how they serve all their meals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they're confusing helping in the kitchen with cooking. I "cooked" at five in that I helped out with very simple things. My mother picked stuff that I could do, out of her way, safely. For example, I was five when I learned how to crack and separate eggs. And measure out a cup of sugar into a bowl. Stuff like that can't hurt a child so it's ideal to teach.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea! I'm assuming he deleted it, otherwise it would say "removed" right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't think I did what? I didn't say I took this picture, I found the picture while reading an article in the Village Voice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I am the Empress of the Raccoon people, so you're not wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's not insane at all. I think people are worrying about nothing, honestly--it takes a lot longer than an hour for food to spoil, and refrigeration is a very modern invention when it comes to the history of food.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds weird, but it works amazingly well. You put a thin layer on the outside of the sandwich and cook as you normally would--perfect, even browning every time, and the flavor is great. If you feel like you'll miss the butter flavor, you can use half and half.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst part--it was in Hugh Acheson's restaurant. Dude's famous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typically professionals do not give both a diagnosis of social anxiety disorder *and* a diagnosis of avoidant personality disorder. Were those diagnoses given to you at two different times or by two different professionals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a pretty good summary, yes. 

I do admire the guy who commented that it wasn't appropriate and to "work on his approach." At least he seemed to have some sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meal served on a hubcap, from Empire State South in Atlanta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breast cancer survivor makes a post in /r/pics, and a commenter shares about his dead mom and asks her over for dinner--and receives some negative feedback about both things </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But a five-year-old can do it! Which, BTW, you should *not* let your five-year-old make a grilled cheese sandwich. That's asking to go the burn unit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet there was a montage, set to "Alright" by Supergrass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure, I get my oven up to 500 when I make pizza at home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That person has a weird vendetta against people who use the word "cooking" too casually. See [this post](https://www.reddit.com/r/SubredditDrama/comments/5mo5wo/guy_in_rcooking_says_cooking_is_not_a_hobby/?st=j1zb4rrg sh=20685e13) I made in SRD a while back. Sadly, she has since deleted ALL the comments about how "cooking is not a hobby."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit that's a lot of olive oil!

I make a very similar side dish at home, except I use only black beans and garbanzos, I use lemon juice and zest, and diced red onion. And a lot less oil. It's delicious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I crazy, or would that still be really weird?

If my husband came home and said "My boss just bought me a beard trimmer" I would tell him to start a paper trail immediately documenting the weirdness in case things started to escalate to backrubs and weekend "conferences." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you use for the browning? Butter, mayo, or both? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Archive](http://archive.is/961TI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> English on the menu? You're a fucking weeb. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tip, I didn't even know that was  sub but I'll give it a shot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love blood orange with salmon. I made a very simple sauce for broiled salmon once that was basically just reduced blood orange juice with cold butter whisked in at the end, and it's fabulous. 

Grapefruit is great with lot of things but because it's bitter you want to pair it carefully. My aunt used to make a killer salad that had baby spinach, supremed grapefruit, and avocado slices. The fatty avocado worked really well with the sour and bitter notes of the grapefruit. 

Yuzu is a great addition to salad dressings and sauces. It's a good addition to ponzu and homemade mayo, for example. It works well with seafood, and with Japanese flavor profiles, in particular. 

For kumquats, you could try to make a chutney, or as an addition to a salad. You can make a spicy grill paste out of kumquats and hot peppers that works well with chicken or pork. Also, you can steep them in vodka if you have a month or two to kill--makes great cocktails! 

Kaffir lime works well with Southeast Asian flavors, and is a good addition to soups and dipping sauces. 

Tangerines can be used pretty much anywhere you use orange--they're sweet and tangy. But my favorite use for tangerines is what my mother used to make on special occasions--a tangerine cheesecake with a gingersnap crust. It kicks ass. 

As a side note, I have the *Jerusalem* cookbook and I've made the recipe in it for [chicken with clementines and fennel](https://www.alexandracooks.com/2013/12/31/roasted-chicken-with-clementines/) and it's fabulous. So that's another tested citrus dish you can try.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My son bears as much resemblance to my husband as you do to your mother's liquor delivery man. So yes, he's the father.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree it's not limited to one gender or familial role, I hope it didn't come across as a sexist generalization.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 13-year-old making a grilled cheese sandwich isn't cooking. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on how much salt and vinegar you put on it first.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Baby's gotta get them rays](https://gotsomescienceonyou.files.wordpress.com/2013/04/bili-hut-3-3-23-2.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I left both my son and his bottles outside for at least an hour before each feeding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ideas for other citrus: grapefruit, yuzu, blood orange, tangerine, kumquat, and Kaffir lime. 

Honestly, I think it just comes down to your persona taste--what you like to pair together. Lime works well with Latin American food, but honestly I think lemon works equally well in some cases. Lemon is more common in Mediterranean cuisine and I think it works really well there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Archive](http://archive.is/LozM8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crispy drama in /r/GifRecipes over whether or not it's dangerous to let pork belly sit in the sun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A "true story" about makeup in the workplace causes HR problems in /r/AdviceAnimals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey ShilohShay! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* You used a biased title. Remain as neutral as possible when creating a title. A good title catches attention without making untrue statements or implying a certain side is in the wrong



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Burritos aren't Mexican food. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will change the flavor, for sure--you could just use brandy, or sweet white wine and brandy mixed. I use a combo of brandy and Kahla and it's killer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've used it for gummy bears. Here's a link to what I did: https://www.reddit.com/r/food/comments/42lglp/i_got_my_gummy_bear_mold_homemade_raspberry_and/?st=j1yxg0rc sh=fce4ced7

Also, you can use it for mirror glaze! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> English on the menu? You're a fucking weeb. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like it could be a combination of not enough salt and not a hot enough oven. Are you using a stone or a steel? How hot does your oven get?

I've had good results with this very simple recipe from [King Arthur Flour](http://www.kingarthurflour.com/recipes/the-easiest-pizza-youll-ever-make-recipe). Often when the crust isn't flavorful, it's a salt issue. You could also do an 18-hour cold ferment in the fridge to let it develop more of that sourdough flavor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is pretty good--tastes a bit like frog's legs. This looks particularly intriguing, because I've never eating it any other way than from frozen and cut up already.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That bun looks perfect to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Archive](http://archive.is/6dhYy) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the ones I find are non-Japanese people lecturing other non-Japanese people about how "authentic" Japanese food should be.

This is a European guy lecturing Japanese people about how to make Hamburg steak. It's a thing of beauty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's a palate cleanser, you retards. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try Koryo on Royal in Dallas next time you're in the area. It's the best I've had in this area so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, I don't get serving fries in little mini deep fry baskets like that. It's not like they're actually fried in those baskets, they're just supposed to be cute--and the lack of utility in that choice *bothers* me. That shake looks good, though. I'm looking forward to the mason jar trend getting over with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a weird compulsion when I was pregnant to tell people I was pregnant so they wouldn't think I was just getting fat. I know, that's weird and insecure, but pregnancy can make you feel weird about your body. I actually told my husband "we have to tell your parents, I'm starting to show and they're going to think I'm letting myself go." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, was that you? I removed the names so I can't remember...

That one was pretty amusing, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Sher101! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* You used a biased title. Remain as neutral as possible when creating a title. A good title catches attention without making untrue statements or implying a certain side is in the wrong



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We usually archive posts around here, it helps me keep an eye on vote totals and make sure there's no brigading (we're here to read, not participate!). We're a small sub so the risk of that is minimal, but I still like to be careful. 

And thank you, that was a bit of a laugh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> food mod here--I have three tips:

1) Posting at certain times of day will yield better results. Posting between 8-10am during the week will increase your chances of getting noticed. 

2) Make sure you post a picture that is in focus. I'm not sure if you used autofocus or what, but part of your steak is blurry and it is somewhat distracting. 

3) Post your procedure in the comments! We love hearing about how people make things. 

Thank you for your contribution to the sub--and nice job on your steak! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I've described above is, forgive me, the poor man's version of Hamburg steak, known as Salisbury steak. 

Hamburg steak is a German dish of 100% ground beefsteak, and frankly, it was often served raw (it's derived from steak tartar) in it's earliest iterations.


OMG, this is gold. Nice find!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Archive](http://archive.is/hNCYz)

[Post Edit Archive](http://archive.is/QEFdr) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Collision in /r/technology over traffic cameras. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I find cookbook authors I trust, I have more confidence in their recipes--there are tons of recipes online, but a lot of them are bad. A lot of them are good, too, but sometimes I don't want to take chances. There are certain cookbook authors I *know* will give me reliably awesome results (Julia Child, Marcella Hazan, Yotam Ottolenghi, Alice Waters, Jacques Ppin and Diana Kennedy, for example). Sometimes, though, you get both--Kenji's recipes, for example, are generally excellent both online and in print.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you don't *just* do that, that's more of a first step. And I guess I used a bad example--I wouldn't use the word "upset" so much as reflect the specific emotion--sadness, anger, embarrassment, whatever. You'd be surprised--sometimes just having someone notice what you seem to be feeling goes a long way. 

A few times I've had people react sarcastically. Here's how I handle it--they get prickly and say something like "well duh." So you counter it with "okay, so tell me about it." Don't react to the anger, because that's just a smokescreen. Then they can either A) tell you about it or B) refuse to talk about it. If they pick A, you listen. If you can relate, you can say so as a way of demonstrating that you have some understanding of their experience. If you know the person well, you can even offer interpretations--they'll tell you if you're wrong, and it will get the conversation going. If they pick B, you say "okay, I'm here if you do want to talk," and leave it up to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I highly recommend [Eating in the Light of the Moon: How Women Can Transform Their Relationship with Food Through Myths, Metaphors, and Storytelling](https://www.amazon.com/Eating-Light-Moon-Relationship-Storytelling/dp/0936077360). 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, for days--but I mentioned a lot of areas, what specific topic are you interested in?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would look at it like this--you *are* "fixing things" by providing a shoulder to cry on. Listening is an intervention. Try to be mindful when listening--if you notice you're thinking about the next thing you want to say, stop it and return to what the other person is saying. Reflect their affect--if they look upset, say "that makes you feel upset." Honestly, just this amount of effort will make a huge difference. 

And most important, I would say if you're not able to provide that kind of empathetic listening and support, tell them that up front. I've said this to couples before who continually got frustrated with each other--find other sources of social support besides each other, because no partner can be 100% of the support 100% of the time. That's not realistic or fair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm interested in pretty much every aspect of food--cooking it, trying new foods, photographing it, food history, the role it plays in culture, and the psychological aspects of our relationship with it. I find it fascinating that we all need to eat, yet it is becoming increasingly common to see people having an adversarial relationship with food--and for advertisers to play on this dynamic in order to sell products. Then there are some of the broader social issues related to things like urban renewal and food deserts and big agra.

Anyway, TL;DR I find the topic interesting, probably way more than most people, but we all need something about which we can feel passionate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely, it is related to gender roles in our culture--and that's what I tell them. I 100% validated their attempts to help. But I point out that there is limited utility to their approach, and then provide them with a different set of tools to offer support. I also warn them that it will take time--behavior isn't learned overnight and it's not changed overnight either. Setting realistic expectations is key.  I try to help them understand that listening *is* an intervention, and that it is extremely helpful. Also, I put the responsibility on the client to identify specific things their loved ones can do to show support, because they're responsible for communicating their needs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have no right to judge people based on blurbs in internet conversations. You have no right to judge things doing zero research and making knee jerk reactions. If you can't see the lunacy of this thread something is wrong...

Just answer me this.. did you watch the spud fit channel where the guy documents his entire diet? That was the first thing i told people to look at in the original thread.If you haven't done that then your criticisms are complete horseshit... and you haven't.. that is completely obvious...I'm going to keep posting about narcissism.. I hope this becomes the biggest thread on this boards history to wake you morons up...

I'm going to call this copy gnocci. God bless that man for dishing out such a generous serving of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IME, they did not understand the aspects of the disorder related to body image and to emotional eating. They were concerned strictly with the behaviors, but not the emotions and cognitions underlying the behaviors. Now, taking a behavioral approach is part of treatment, but it's not the only part you focus on. For example, dads who think they can solve their kid's bulimia issue by just padlocking the fridge and then taking the bathroom door off the hinges. That might decrease the incidence of the behavior in the short run, but it doesn't solve the problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it has to be 7.5 pounds of potatoes. If you're not eating a cat's worth of potatoes a day, you're not going to lose weight. It's science.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, he's too busy getting finger-blasted by the invisible hand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they'll give you a reach around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, that guy's comments had the tone of so many of the dads and husbands of clients I've worked with for eating disorders. Dads especially. They sit down and say "all she needs to do is eat XYZ, it's simple, and you just have to do it THIS WAY" while the client is sitting there balled up in rage rolling her eyes. They meant well, just like the guy in the linked thread means well. The issue is they're coming at it as fixers, and people aren't cars. The lectures are patronizing--these women probably know a shit ton about nutrition, it's not about them needing a lecture.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you guys done sucking each other's dicks yet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well put. It's the same as the Martha Stewart phenomenon. "Oh I just got these 5 pound beeswax candles out of my tobacco barn, they're great for any festive holiday occasion!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I posted it here. To me, pesto and pumpkin soup are two absolutely ridiculous suggestions for poor, busy people to make. If he had said "buy a bag of lentils" that's one thing. Pesto? Really? Oh yeah, let me pop down to my local corner store and just use my food stamps to buy pine nuts and fresh basil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's really taken it up to the next level. I mean, I'm not going to read all of it, but I'm genuinely impressed by the amount of effort expended.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's now spamming me with pop psych articles about narcissism. It's pretty hilarious. Apparently, my many years of graduate school and training don't have anything on his ability to Google blog posts about NPD. 

EDIT: Wow. I just woke up to 25 messages in my inbox, most of which were walls of text about narcissism. I see that apparently OP told someone to kill themselves, got into a fight with Jebus, ignored all warnings, and is now banned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is fairly disordered. He confirmed to me that he's on the spectrum, though, and it's not all that uncommon for people on the spectrum to eat a narrow range of foods. Sometimes it gets so severe that they will only eat one or two things. I don't know if that's the case with him, but he may very well find comfort in only eating one thing. Kids and teens with this can end up malnourished and underweight--and sometimes even *obese* but still malnourished. It definitely explains the "I don't like greens" thing. The only way to treat it therapeutically is with gradual exposure and behavior training. It's really hard to change because it's self-reinforcing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there,

I would definitely bring it up with your therapist. It sounds like you have body image issues relating at least in part to the emotional abuse by your boyfriend, and your therapist can help you challenge that negative body talk. Unfortunately, negative body image is common, but that doesn't mean it's inevitable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that's actually the cutest pupa I've ever seen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all you had to do is ~~look through my post history~~ read the comments in this thread to see I have aspergers

I don't need to stalk your history, dude, it's pretty obvious. 

Incidentally, some of the eating disorder patients I treated when I worked in that setting were on the spectrum--it's actually quite common to have highly restricted ranges of food when you're on the spectrum. Disliking certain textures is a very common issue. I once worked with a young lady would would only eat custard style yogurt. It's part of the sensory component of the disorder--so please know you're not alone in that department. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since we're handing out cracker jack, armchair psychology diagnoses here, I'm going to go our on a limb and guess that you've been diagnosed with Asperger's or high-functioning autism spectrum disorder. It just...comes across fairly strongly. 

I'm not using that as an insult the way you are using "narcissist" to everyone here, but rather I'm saying you should take a step back, look at the way you're interacting with people here, and recognize that this is a time when you're reading the situation wrong and responding inappropriately. 

With that, I wish you the best of luck with your diet. Have a good night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It's the product of a society where narcissism is completely rampant.. that's why you all feel normal...](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HMqZ2PPOLik) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  When you attack other people and belittle them does it take the pain away for a second? 

You can answer that question better than I, you're the one going nuts and calling people names because they dared to criticize your insane potato regimen. Honestly, take a look at your behavior today--not normal. 

Maybe throw some protein into the mix, you'll feel better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking of looking up "Dr. McDougall", check out one of the things you find [when you "look him up on the Internet."](http://www.marksdailyapple.com/vegan-island/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How were you damaged?

I went on an all-potato diet and lost a significant portion of gray matter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, you're clearly a narcissist, therefore he wins the argument. Stop strawmanning him, you narcissist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe your cognitive functioning will return to normal after you get off your all-potato diet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find your persistent misunderstanding of the term "narcissist" (not to mention the term "strawman") to be exceptionally entertaining.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the book you read on narcissism written by the same person who told you to eat 7.5 pounds of potatoes a day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean...okay, dude. I get that you don't want people telling you your diet is wrong, and if you feel good and it's working and your doctor is okay with it, who am I to say anything against it?

That said, I worked treating eating disorders for three years, and what your describing could be considered disordered. If you eat such a narrow range of foods that you, say, avoid eating with other people or situations where you'll have to eat, then that's a disorder--and I can't see how you could ever go to a restaurant or to a friend's house for dinner if you eat cheese and only cheese. Only eating one food long term due to desire to lose weight would be considered by many professionals to be a mental health issue. I have no idea if you're struggling with any of that, but you have to understand how it comes across to an outsider.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  About 1.5lbs skim mozzarella a day.

Hot damn, make sure you don't skip your routine colonoscopy. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, enjoy your rickets!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
