<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3288</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black flag best ac game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. GTA 5 will more than suffice until rdr2 releases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RDR 2 version is way betther than his original. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So hyped!! The witcher 3 is one of the best games ever. 
Edit: Seems like the interview in question was from 2015, and that he was referring to the dlc.
https://culturedvultures.com/no-the-witcher-4-has-not-been-confirmed-by-cd-projekt-red/
No more witcher comming :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I understand the beta is over in a few days, and by releasing a video they can decide what to show or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, if your troops surrender the minute they are surrounded that would suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think the frontline should be based on known enemy positions and your own troop enplacements. If you don`t know where an enemy is there is no front line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, gives me immersion. Having it as an option like in GTA 5 would be cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I was a bit sceptic at first, but after playing gta 5 on ps4 I must say I love first person. Gives me a totally new perspective of the game. Shooting and driving doesn`t really work all that well, but still. Gives me immersion when I can switch at will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anywhere to watch thre trailer uncompressed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really hope the focus a lot more on nativ americans this time around. Loved what little we got in RDR, but seeing as RDR2 is a prequel Natives have to get a much bigger role. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of players online all the time. Been playing every day for the last week, never have any problems finding games, even 10v10 games. The server list is more or less always full. But it, you won`t regret. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, not convinced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So hyped, more dlc/ updates for warhammer 2, next historical game well underway, black ops team for mor content for the older historical games... gg ca. gg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give me a hug? (or maybe a beta code, hehe) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was confirmed as fake by ca. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He`s gangsta.

"I loooove this shiet. We`s in the midle of it now boys!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn`t get a code.....

Everbodys having a good time and I`m just like https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/0e/89/8c/0e898c9c3ffb67a271503b47d42736c7.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just find a lobby with players and join. You will never find a match where 50 % of your team doesn`t leave mid game, it`s just how mature many wargame players are. Take it or leave it, eguen doesn`t care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never get to fort de vaux, always looses as attackers on verdun heights and always win as defender. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a side note, would it be possible to get that artwork used in the background as a wallpaper?? I really like it and think it would look great as a wallpaper.

Also, can somone confirm or deny if destructible enviorment is a thing or not? Sure looks like it when that bombers drops it load. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I almost never fail as attacker on oil of empires. iron walls are tougher but nowhere near the insanity of Verdun heights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think making the map a bit larger and have more space between the flags would work, and alos opening up som of the flansk so attackers can get around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Respawning grenades?? That`s why bf1 feels like a michael bay movie with the new dlc. Explosions everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Verdun heights impossible to win as attackers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Attackers really need more help in form of planes, arty or something, this maps is a mess ass attackers, life excpectancy is like 5 sec. 
The map wouldn`t be a problem if only the team would attack, but without voice chat there is no coordinations and therefore no way for attackers to win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) Love it. The geat leader always looks glorious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe we should make a grammar nazi division? :)
Just kidding, I agree it`s a bit hard to read but no big deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, sry dude. Just delete this post and repost it as your own if you want to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [DIVISION OF THE WEEK] 101ST AIRBORNE (US) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It`s horrible. There should be a LOT more weapons to choose from, most of the weapons in the game now were never used in ww1 or were only used late in the war, what about all the rifles and such that were used? It`s like they wante to do a ww1 game bud didn`t have the balls to go all in so we have a ww2 game in ww1 clothers. Love the game though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No? Just saw the video in by youtube subs and thought I would share. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don`t get your hopes up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imo the shows is overrated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drop the Normandy 44 and It`s ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. Rockstar knows their shit. I trust they know what they are doing and to keep GTA and RDR2 seperate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Voice acting info and no reason to believe rdr2 will be delayed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was just a big sale on the game last week, too bad you missed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
