<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2621</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why isn't there a side by side comparison  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it when celebrities have normal sized cocks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The west wing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up in a trailer park...family every time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start messaging one of them on Grindr and that's your in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let him be himself at his own pace dude. Just be there for him no matter what. You trying to force him into something is not what he wants or needs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take your time and discover yourself. Go slow and start thinking about going on dates with a guy, think about holding his hand, eating a bowl of popcorn at the movies together, think about running your hands through his hair. Build it in your mind and you'll get to know yourself more, don't be afraid if some of your thoughts feel wrong. Just go wherever they lead, remember that only you know what's going on in your head. 
Good luck discovering yourself:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say "I just really love dick, so why do you think I'd get rid of my own?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be worried about kissing. Just copy what the other person does, it will also come naturally very quickly. Most people are average do you don't have much to worry about and you can start off by licking the guys dick but luck it with some force. Use those tongue mussels my friend  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he's anything like me he forgot, not because he doesn't like you but because he has a ton of stuff on his mind and then when he did remember he went "oh shit well it's too late now" go get him bro ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Invite him to hang out with you sometime, have plans to do something fun then have that thing not work out. Watch a movie with him instead. Say you're tired but wanna keep watching. Lay your head on his lap and watch the movie. Don't do anything after that, that day. 
After he leaves decided how you feel. You did something decently intimate without making it weird. He will be thinking about it too but it's also innocent enough that he could brush it off easy enough. If you decide you want to go further then post again or message me bro. Good luck discovering more about yourself :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone involved in sex is enjoying it, don't worry so much about the other person having fun. They wouldn't be doing it if hey didn't like it. Even bad sex is better than no sex and unless you puke on their dick, kill $200 of fish and are named Matt, they have had worse.
Also...fuck you Matt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always lube before disk golf  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then the best advice I have for you is that you write him a letter that explains what your issues are, tell him he needs to read the entire letter before responding. Include how you feel about him in the letter and explain that you want a healthy dialogue, include what your idea of that is. After you write the letter you should sleep on it and read it again the next day. If you still agree with it then give it to him. Hopefully he'll see the effort that went into this. Good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can't have a healthy dialogue then why are you in the relationship? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The school year is almost over so finish out your year then move. You'll regret not doing it a lot more than doing it if things go poorly. Good luck out there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :)))) 
A cute boy like you hitting me up would make my day hands down every time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I a box that says "stop snooping this is my dildo box" then put a note in the box with your dildo that says "I warned you" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 24 and have no idea how old I look lol http://i.imgur.com/SLBPbms.jpg http://i.imgur.com/4ANXLU0.jpg http://i.imgur.com/DHDvlXS.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretend he has already rejected you and you're just showing off what he's missing. Confidence isn't about always winning, it's about being just as good loosing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened to me. Apologize to them for the inconvenience and say "I vote we talk about this never" it worked for me...only my brother makes jokes sometimes. 
 
Good luck with this awkwardness  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to have a really thorough conversation with him about this. You also need to look at your relationship and see if there have been any signs of cheating...I'm sorry but this doesn't look good. We are all here for you rain or shine though :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in Indiana and everyone here is celebrating :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever around Chicago hit me up then cute stuff. 
Ps hope I do it for you xD  http://i.imgur.com/mP7q64z.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FOMO = Fear Of Missing Out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A guy would bite me on my beard so marks wouldn't show up. Keep your beard clean and soft though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do people say daddy!?!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever need someone to talk with I'll be here, can't speak to the quality of my advice but I'll try my best lol
Good luck in your relationship  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to just say. Will you be my boyfriend  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure there's a money maker joke to be made here lol
Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm mid 20s and his actions are not really out of the norm. If it happens every single week then you might want to address the drinking but other than that it's not too different  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I wear to dates  http://i.imgur.com/cbe5AU2.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My little brother gets that a lot lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've been with him a month...you are moving way to fast. You are going to flame out. You need to take a step back and look at things. 
Take your time and move slow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you haven't already then give him the talk. Make condoms available in the house. He needs to be safe if he's with guys or gals. When giving him the talk you could say something like "I don't care who you sleep with just use protection, it's not just about birth control. Even if your partner can't get pregnant you still need to wear one."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you send me a dick pic and ask fir a dick pic then I send a dick pic lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 07:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do it in person or over a phone call. Not text lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are starting to care less around here lately and that's nice lol
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up in a conservative town with a ton of conservative people around. When I was younger I always heard people saying that being gay was a choice and that made sense to me, I'm bi. I thought everyone was attracted to both and you just chose one and went with it. After a few years i never really thought about it, that's just who I was, I was a straight guy. 

I dated plenty of women and never had any problems but at sixteen I joined weights class and we all showered together everyday after class. I couldn't stop thinking about the guys but I convinced myself that it was what every normal straight guy did. I had a girlfriend after all and she was about to be prom queen. I pushed it from my mind but sometimes when I went to relieve myself I'd think about the guys in the showers. I'd feel disgusted afterwards and this went on till I was 18. I started watching gay porn in college and first started flirting with the idea of being bi around 19. I got into a relationship at 20 with a girl and I once again pushed those thoughts aside. I didn't really embrace being bi until I was 21/22 then I came out at 23. 
I fucked my first guy at 23, a guy I met off tinder who is an actual millionaire...that was a weird time. I dated a girl for a bit after that and then I met my now ex. He is gorgeous and was some great sex big what really struck me was how easy the relationship was. It didn't last long but it felt very right. 

Today I still sleep with both men and women but I'm only looking for a relationship with a man. I've gone on a lot of dates recently and find that it's a decent bit harder dating men than women but there is a guy I'm talking to now that seems promising, have our first date Saturday, wish us luck....also thanks for sticking in this long lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 13:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he brings it up just say something like "it's not my fault you're hot and I'm horny" just laugh it off  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What helped get you into shape? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to get in better shape but every time I start to get in the groove of dieting and exercise I fall out of it. Any help or advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been told many times that I look better in life than my pictures...so here is a picture lol

I think it's because I have a very expressive face when I'm talking http://i.imgur.com/38CpYgc.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eating 20 chicken nuggets and a large fry with catch-up and soda while watching the west wing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub helped me too. You are among friends here bro  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's over the line. Sorry bro  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have that effect on people  http://i.imgur.com/cCT6Ams.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a guy who liked to be dirty talked too...I prefer my subs to have a bit of fight to then so I wasn't really feeling it but he just kept on begging so I got right up to his ear and whispered "you want me to talk dirty" 
he moaned "yes" 
I said "you don't deserve it"
Everybody wins :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've encountered this with people before. It's all good, I like seeing the person I'm with have a good time and that's all that matters during sex. Never let fear of being judged restrict you from good sex.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was feeling a bit down today but reading this made me feel like a hundred bucks :) 

Ps: I'm a dom top lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That hobby you had a decade or two ago, start doing it again (for me it was painting). 

Distract yourself on improving yourself. Make that level of joy you had with him your new regular. It's gonna hurt for a while, you'll be better for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have some great heights and deep lows ahead of you. You'll look back to this time for the rest of your life, nostalgia will build up your mountains and smooth over your valleys. 

Squeeze as much joy from this moment as you can, be yourself and be ready to discover things you didn't know about yourself. Have fun and be safe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clue, it's always a mystery who was in my bed last night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I woke up yesterday over my ex. It feels great and I can finally be all in on dates again. 

I have a first date tomorrow at my favorite restaurant with a guy I've been texting all week. Wish me luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, you and everyone else tends to let their first get any with anything. It's the first time we really felt this way, this person is the best by default and who doesn't want the story book life of settling down with their first love. We hear that everyone will be cheated on at some point in their lives, that some of our partners will be rude or cruel to us. Going into these relationships we know all the warning signs and we know, we KNOW, that we would never fall into the trap of a bad relationship. We think our relationship just has a few problems but it's my first so I probably did something wrong. 

No. You did nothing wrong. He is not the man you are meant to be with. If you forgive him he will betray you again. You need to get out. It will hurt. You will be better for it. 

After you leave, take some time and focus on you, you'll miss the relationship, but force your way through it and when you're ready try again. Don't go back to the first guy. 

You'll date people who buy you flowers for no reason. you'll find guys who build up a date for days, telling you it'll be the best date ever, you love every moment, a night to always remember, then when date night comes it's just a table set up in the middle of his apartment with a lit candle in the center and McDonald's on the counter, when you ask him what this is he'll say "I just wanted to stare at you in candle light for a while". 

There are great things out there for you. Go out there and find them. 

Good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes the next year, sometimes the next day. I do it when I'm ready.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does it matter to you if he's gay or not?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is the person with the bigger dick the top?

My answer: no we play Rock Paper Scissors and the winner gets to top </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kohls clearance section. 80% off and a large selection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
