<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1474</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 09:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 12:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks nothing like bill Murray dude, I thought it was either John c Reilly or bobcat goldthwaite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 05:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in an older suburb in Perth and I'm not scheduled to get the nbn! It's not even in their projected list of suburbs in 2017! Newer suburbs are getting it before me! What a cunt this fucktard is!

Suburbs next to me have it but oh no not mine! I have to put up with shitty vivid wireless speeds! This fucking iPhone is faster  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Portia D'Ellenswood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 01:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blessed on this day all shitters am </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I smoked it inside the house, had two cones worth. First of all my head became really heavy and the lead molten feeling melted down my neck and shoulders and into my torso. I felt like I was made of lead and concrete and my whole body was shaking. 

I realised I was laughing in hysterics, hence the shaking, but my body was so heavy I tried walking and looked at my feet, I was barefoot, they were on the polished concrete floor and I felt like I was absorbing the weight of my surroundings. I was becoming the concert box I was in.

I needed to get outside, slowly whilst in u controllable hysterics I made my way out side onto the brick patio, the roof was slightly higher out here and the air cooler and instantly I felt normal weight again, only this time I felt about eight foot tall. The small conifers in the patio garden all bowed down and shook there branches at me. I felt like thy were laughing too but later realised it must have been the echo from my own madman hysterics. 

Kept walking and ended up on the grass, I could feel the breeze on my face lifting me up higher and higher, looking up at the stars and I remember thinking how gravity's main drive is to keep you down and to root you to the earth, and how taller people have a greater power over gravity and me already being 6ft 5 had a greater power than most. I stretched really hard and became weightless, my hands stretched upwards to the sky, I could become the stars and concur gravity! 

I yelled out 'power' as loud as I could. That's where the trip ended. Arms up looking at the universe. I remember hearing my neighbours who were sitting in their yard next door asking each other what the fuck is he on? They would have heard pure hysterical magical laughter then me shout out as loud as I could, 'POWER!!!!'

Only time I have ever come across it in Australia, it's illegal here, would def do it again if I could. Thanks to Liam for that sweet journey man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 01:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would it be called?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am your fart(h)er </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
