<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2069</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 07:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im all or nothing. And nothings all I ever get :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 07:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like muscles on a gal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 07:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats what I mean, its basically thinly veiled drm

And I dont really get it, because youre punishing the people who put their money into supporting you , too. I dont agree with piracy in the slightest, but punishing people who spend money to support the developers and getting treated as a pirate anyway is not ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 07:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a shame he doesnt clense society of himself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 07:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didnt sea that coming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 06:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I dont get why our governments dont fucking fight this. We go on about human rights and bitch at other countries like russia while we let this go on?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 06:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldnt be opposed to the decision makers and lawyers over at nestle being hung in the streets. Complete cunts who use the law to get away with their evil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 06:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do ipads count? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate this new buzzword term "live service" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 06:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive heard it a few times recently for games. Is this really what people want for most games? I understand for games like fifa or madden where online and keeping up to date is a huge service but most games dont need that crap.

Whats worse is, some of the more mediocre games of recent times (division, wild lands, destiny) have not only had this "online service" thing baked in, but also sold brilliantly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 06:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol oops. But it might as well goddamn be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 05:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol yup pretty lame isnt it? Was announced 2004 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 04:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats why i dont play souls games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL

When i think dogs cant get any more amazing, this. Thank you op </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 01:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sea salty :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 00:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow what pieces of shit. the law really is an ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 23:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link? Wow if true how have these guys not been brought up on charges? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 23:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably a good choice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 23:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol how many on hold series make a come back anytime soon after being put "on hold"?

Dead space, on hold. But do you think there will be a fourth soon?

You people must have been gamers ten minutes if you cant read behind the corporate double speak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 23:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like you should learn to read between the lines. Surprises me how much corporate speak still bamboozles some people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RTs ancestors announced, looks damn good </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 22:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 22:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shame. It took me many hours to get into but around halfway in the story it really started to feel like classic mass effect and got me fully invested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looks like mass effect may be done </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 22:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 22:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 22:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After four years youd think so right lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 22:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hes not feline fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 22:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL edgy . Bitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 22:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah so terrorist sympathiser </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 22:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When your convictions arent in line with reality though, no matter how admirable.


And having racist diane abbott the albatross in prominant position is a huge no no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 22:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol its just a punch, stop being soft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 22:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what? It got trashed in reviews but i really liked the terminal reality game. It was very unpolished but i honestly felt the zombies were a threat which they arent in the show. One gun shot and they all came for you.

Thats all i was looking for, just with more polish and modern graphics. They fucked it up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 21:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read this too fast as "beating off all of them" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 21:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These developers really seem like conmen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, four years just to figure out the concept art. Skybound sure handed this game to the right studio </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LOL Overkills lame walking dead "reveal" was concept art. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Four years nearly for this...LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LOL So Overkills big walking dead reveal was concept art </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah i see my bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought you were saying youre strong. You dont want to do things to help combat them and just run riot, then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its because hes way, way too far to the left. Most people like some moderation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corbyn wants to disarm nuclear weapons. In todays world, thats insanely naive, stupid and even dangerous. He even said about a potential russia invasion with no nukes, he would just try talking putin out of it. Im sorry thats not a leader. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not really find if a gas dude can stuff you and keep holding you down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im talking rapists, murderers, child molesters. Why should ian huntly get luxuries or ever see daylight again? Id have no problem keeping vioent offenders locked up forever in shitty conditions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats fair enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sad part is labour is such a shit show she can do this and still win because labour cant get their act together and put people who are actually electable in charge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fairness channel 4 news are shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since youre one of the strong, why not go and fight isis then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vlad the Impiler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some really weak reasons to crow bar in other species </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Justice to me isnt our soft as shit prisons we have all these luxuries for scum like ian huntley

And im aware not all prisoners are scumbags but they have access to games consoles, gym, etc. They should get nothing but basic food and water  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats your point? English please?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly not for most people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It says aliens bug hunt. Id assume the aliens would have more than a cameo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cant help it, a shit opinion is a shit opinion. Hes still entitled to it though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well no, but they are far far better than clueless corbyn and dopey diane. Labour needs a rehaul to even stand a chance with people like me who would gladly vote for them if they didnt find the  weakest candidates to lead. 

Corbyn wants to get rid of nuclear weapons. That would be insanely stupid and naive in this world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> . Statistically and with todays technology theres far less errors. And capital punishment would only, ideally be meated out where theres an overwhelming amount of evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone getting dead by daylight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im always down for a horror game. Gonna be getting this and friday 13th!

Anyone else gonna play it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I respect his opinion. But its a crap one :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or dont buy it at all from these shady fucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My interest in this has taken a massive hit for several reasons.

Payday on consoles was a broken mess the developers had no interest in fixing

The incredibly shady actions of the developers over the whole dlc fiasco

Im worried it will be like the show, where the zombies are pathetically non threatening

And after so many years with nothing, im getting a colonial marines vibe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone read aliens bug hunt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bout halfway thru. Gotta say Im disappointed. Some decent stories, some bad ones (the burke one was wtf). Too many non xeno stories, and too much reliance on the movie characters. I was hoping for different aliens vs marines encounters across the movies time spans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im gonna sound like an ass so sorry...but stopped reading after saying "prometheus is my second favourite alien movie" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like that.some people here have major issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corbyn seems far less competent to me, and far too weak if that tells you anything. And diane abbott in any kind of power position is almost trump like. This is not to say the tories are good, far from it. But labor needs better leaders. Corbyn is too far on the naive spectrum for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its fucking insane how many women hating pussies here think this was an appropriate action to getting splashed with a drink </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He deserves jail time for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol go live in russia and india for a while then come back to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id argue  fear of your people getting gunned down because of a cartoon is quite rational </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldnt be against capital punishment for very violent and sexual crimes tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This, i want to vote for labor but with corbyn and abbott in prime positions, i cant do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like fight for new york, not the last terrible one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They need to fix the stamina system. Its total bs a guy can still hold you down and stuff take downs even though they have zero stamina. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really really want a sequel. Such a tease for vampires. But never fight them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Childish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im from the UK so forgive me but can trump legally fire a guy investigating his team??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it as difficult as lords of the fallen? Does it have difficulty levels? Found lords and dark souls difficulty off putting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why were you made to vote again after the resounding Rejection of the original documents? Then you said yes. Cucked.

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Irish_European_Constitution_referendum

They wanted your nations laws to be superceeded by the reich...i mean, the super states laws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldnt vote for any of the three . I cant vote in someone shit because they are slightly less shit. I think corbyns too far left and his party would do a different kind of damage. And lib dems are hopeless idealists with no regard for reality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didnt, I spoiled my ballot. Lib dems are tossers, and labor with corbyn and abbott are equally a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didnt accept the first  result, so yes, forced </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You a bitch bruh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Youre a woman hating pussy who gets koed by soft drinks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They voted no twice years ago and both times were forced to revote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Self defense from a soft drink? LOL what kind of pussy are you if that hurts you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really enjoy it, but not a fan of mission timers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you stop it though? I agree in theory but the tories dont seem to give a fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are arguing to beat up women over a spilled drink. Come on bruh, you hate women  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems to me you have issues with women, chum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who said other issues werent important?

But surveillance to help prevent future attacks is worth it if it saves even one mother or brother, isnt it? I think so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this game. It was unfairly derided and I highly reccomend anyone picks it up at this price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok tell me.... if it hurt him, how comes he showed no signs of it as he pummelled a smaller , helpless woman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats trivialising terrorism. Because one is an accident, the other is purposful acts of murder. 

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A childish outburst that didnt harm anyone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes the UK has lower death rates than the rest, thankfully </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wind down? No, it will get worse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Youre right, theres only been hundreds of casulties in europe last few years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would I care about what happens to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL "attack". She didnt "attack" him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id punch your mama while you watched in silence with head bowed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well fuck off and move there soon, hopefully in time for next one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok well we seem to be better at stopping them in their tracks. You guys just seem to drop like flies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/04/12/mapped-2015-was-europes-most-dangerous-year-in-a-decade-for-terr/

http://www.politico.eu/article/terror-deaths-in-western-europe-in-2016-highest-in-over-decade-report-terrorism/

2016 was worst year in a decade </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brown people i fear? Would you be so blase if it was your mother, sister, brother, etc who got run over in a truck for some lunatics religious beliefs?

Btw not all muslims are brown nor terrorists. Thats racist in itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its terrible because it throws everything in a blender. No restraint or thought other than "oh that would be cool". Its just silly for the sake of it.

Plus the delivery of the story thru nonsensical easter eggs is the worst possible way to tell it. I guarentee majority of players will never find it. Thats not great story telling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terrorism has increased drastically in recent years. Wonder why?

And Id rather live in UK than any european country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If youre a bitch made coward who has to punch a woman a third your size, maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hate to break it to you but germanys had more deaths in 2016 than we have since 2005 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> France :  230 dead  since 2015
Germany : 73 dead in 2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another terrorist threat just appeared in france too. LOL tell me again its uk whos fucked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And its probably going to get worse.

But hey opposing unchecked immigration is racist right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmmm nope. UK has nowhere near the terrorist attacks and deaths that france and Germany do because of unchecked immigration. So we will be ok :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Iraq </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless its vietnam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
