<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1563</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah absolutely to that second part. That's the whole point of getting the armor sets because the elixirs are a bitch. It's all opinion but I feel that the armor sets add to the immersion. You can't just climb to the peak of a mountain naked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not forced to do any of those things. Zora armor is needed to swim up waterfalls, but that isn't necessary because you could always get to locations by climbing.  Meals and elixirs can be used for stealth and for stamina. Elixirs can be used to make you flameproof or heat resistant. Elixirs and meals can be used for cold resistance. There are very few cases where you truly need a set of armor to do something.

Edit: also, I think it's a great thing that certain armors are intended for certain purposes. Why would I wear climber gear other than to climb? Why would I use flamebreaker armor? I feel this mechanic is awesome because it rewards players for upgrading all of their armors and not just investing in a couple. Barbarian is my go to and my only fully upgrades set. I find it fun and challenging when I need to go do something on Death Mountain and all of the sudden I'm vulnerable because I haven't upgraded the flamebreaker set. The only complaint i have is that the second upgrade isn't always great. Climber gear should let you climb in the rain. Zora gear should pretty much let you swim freely without worrying about stamina. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sure hope so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 13:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This show is trash now honestly. I missed the last episode and half of this one and don't feel like I missed anything. That's not good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 04:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing will change and nobody will care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you go to lakeside stable and start walking across the bridge right in front of it, he will start flying towards you from up above the waterfall. It's happened to me every time without fail. I farm him and then respawn at the shrine behind lakeside stable and do the same thing and he's always there. If only Dinraal could be so easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm saying you should watch your sodium intake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't feel pressure either, but I'm wearing fully upgraded barbarian armor. Plenty of defense (60 rating) and the attack bonus is incredible. Also one of my favorite looking sets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Farosh's horn is ridiculously easy if you know the spot to go (lakeside stable) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't know. The screen is just too small for it. Which i'm fine with, I love the size of the console. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a for profit company. They need to do what they can to bring in profits. The supply can't be greater than the demand. The console launched early March, not in the fall before christmas. They couldn't know what the demand would be so they needed to play it safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had no problems with scratching at all. The stand is fine but honestly there's no need for it. Handheld mode is way better than tabletop mode. I love the portability of this system it's truly incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you should preorder if you wanted the console. Sucks but this is how Nintendo operates. They can't afford to make a bunch of consoles that don't sell so they make a short supply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome. I can't believe I never knew this. I have almost 100 hrs in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, are they actually looking at the camera? Or do they just happen to be looking that way? If this is actually built in to where characters look at the camera i'm impressed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Four teeth? Is that another way to say jaw? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> which weapon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dye that shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Try to hit me" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the fact that it's a bandana and cutoff white tee though. This was the style I was going for: https://c1.staticflickr.com/4/3165/2969538469_c9209cd5a3_b.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I was clever enough to do that intentionally! Didn't even realize! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Murica! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Purple Zora armor with zora shield and greatsword

All white stealth armor, but with white hylian hood. (Assasin's Creed). Knights broadsword.

Barbarian helm dyed white (skull is black, paint is white, hair on back has white streaks), rest of armor dyed black (body paint), with lynel weapons

Soldiers armor all dyed black with royal guard claymore and royal shield

Desert Voe dyed all black with gerudo weapons.

Rito armor all white with great eagle bow.

Climbers gear all black

and finally Gerudo outfit dyed purple with a radiant shield and scimitar ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just realized Gerudo's looks like a pair of breasts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can be a girl, according to feminists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying STEM is the best, but when you have debt to pay off, certain fields will make it way harder to pay off that debt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Learned the hard way, yeah. I didn't know I'd never make a dime in the field until I was sunk in deep. Looking at my loans vs potential salary motivated me to get into a real field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish my parents would have beat my ass for going for communication. Now I'm going an extra year and a half for a computer science degree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL low test changes your bone structure  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. The whole splitting of athletics into male and female is because of biological differences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't deny biology. You can be whoever you want, dress how you want and express how you want but this is what happens when you just cast basic truths about the world aside. Men's bodies and women's bodies are different no matter how much you pump them full of hormones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need to read the whole thing just the highlighted part </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the third one and second to last one are my favorite. The colors make the most sense and I love the contrast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A really good weapon with awful durability  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can show gratitude while still upholding their sacred laws (at least publicly). Riju and her bodyguard both know you are a voe but allow you in their city. I imagine it's much easier to just let Link sneak in as a girl than have it be this big thing that a voe is allowed in the city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's hurtful about Bolson? I found him lovable and hysterical. He was flamboyant, yes but he wasn't a total effeminate pansy. He and Karston are beasts of construction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's dumb. It's Gerudo law, doesn't matter that Link is a hero. They can't openly let a male in the city. Especially since Riju is young and needs to rule over the Gerudos, breaking a sacred Gerudo law and tradition would be a quick way to lose all respect and influence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't every shield in the game a traveler's shield if you think about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could give you two upvotes. One for Cotera and one for using "couldn't care less" and not "could care less". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you dye any of these? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Why don't you take a seat over here, Link?](http://img2.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20150225052918/gtawiki/images/2/28/Hanson-exploitable-fixed.png)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tons of two handed weapons. If you are getting low on powerful 2 handers its the best place to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But then you don't get that precious loot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the problem is that we expected Calamity Ganon to be really difficult so we prepared heavily and made sure we did all the divine beasts. Imagine if you sank the same amount of preparation into fighting a lynel and the lynel loses health from the divine beasts. Also, traversing Hyrule castle was a feat itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That will never happen. Personally I would like some new enemies in a DLC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I use barbarian armor. Badass and it boosts damage output. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they have a homogeneous society  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there's no invincibility frames which makes dodging harder. You really have to watch enemy attack patterns because you can't just roll through anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/fashionzelda ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> explaining the joke always makes it funnier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know i thought he was cool, but apparently this sub is full of women and gay men (not that there's anything wrong with that) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree with climbing, food system and blessing shrines. 

Climbing is one of my favorite things about the game and it gives you a reason to invest in stamina and create stamina potions or food. Also, it gives a reason to eat foods or use potions to increase speed, plus a reason to get a certain armor set. If you have invested in these things, you can much more easily traverse the world. If you haven't, you'll have to take he main paths which are longer are filled with enemies.

As far as the food system, I don't care that there aren't that many recipes. I like that cooking is straightforward and easy. You know exactly what you're going to get so you don't waste ingredients. Yeah it would be cool if certain foods mixed together created special effects but i don't care that much. My issue is that you can't compound effects. I should be able to increase attack power, defense and speed all at once. I hate that I can't. One effect will overwrite another.

Blessing shrines are fine because most of them are in hard to reach places or require some kind of puzzle just to get to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also lizalfos, skeletons, and yiga clan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> found the sjw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ganon respawn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It used to be a problem, but I can't say that I've seen anybody bullied for having glasses since I was child. Nobody cares anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah because we're all so oppressed. I've been bullied every single day of my life for wearing glasses /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn nintendo really sucks at choosing launch titles. I'm happy enough with BOTW but looking at past titles, makes me wonder why anyone would buy a console at launch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, a minor mistake that most people never noticed until it was pointed out should lead to someone losing their job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a serious question? What could go wrong jumping on a horse with a sword attached to you... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can cheese those so badly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nearly wiped out an massive camp of bokoblins, using up all my meals, and then a blood moon rises. I got rekt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hurry , gather up a band of soldiers! Remember , it's required that their names end in son. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The entire Tarrytown quest was comedic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're honestly not that hard. The puzzles in OoT and Majoras mask had me tearing my hair out. These ones gave me trouble , but I never resorted to guides. They weren't impossible by any means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elephant, camel, salamander , Bird </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first I didn't, but after reading your post I changed my mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is well thought out and articulates. I definitely see how she was selfish and acted out of her own insecurity. However, she had never once seen any indication that she would access the powers to seal away Ganon. Can you really blame her for being skeptical of her fate? She spent her whole life trying to access this power and she can't do it. She starts trying to find out other ways to stop Ganon besides the prophecy. It's not out of "poor me, I don't get to just do whatever I want" it's more like she can't fulfill her destiny and all of hyrule depends on her doing that. The pressure is unbearable to her and she's trapped devoting her life to something that is, in her eyes, futile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darude - Sandstorm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you watch all of the memories? She dedicated her entire life to learning the power to seal away Ganon. I actually have no idea what on Earth you are talking about when you say her decisions are stubborn and selfish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmao that was my first thought too.

"What did you feed him?"

"Mescaline" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "epic" as in dying immediately  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> true i didnt think of that, but i found it easy to just have it fall in the slot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the difference of one letter, lol. Well two. remove the m and put the r there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Urbosa, u casul </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's all armor sets, masks, and dye </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's always raining and thunderstorms. That's all thats needed for hard mode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's one that is a labyrinth style maze that you need to use motion controls to get a ball to the other side. After failing a handful of times, I flipped the maze 90 degrees so it was facing upwards, and the ball dropped right where I needed it to. Then i just rolled the ball to the other side. That was probably the worst i've ever cheesed a shrine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know where you can put those balls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's okay to admit you're wrong, you know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's where you're wrong. Gay men don't think about vaginas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I commute to classes every day and i bring my switch to play during breaks in the library. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, but it helps for the lyrics to not be pure trash. 50 cent get rich or die trying was nothing impressive when it comes to lyrics but he actually said something more than random mumbling and half thoughts.

"My flow, my show brought me the dough
That bought me all my fancy things
My crib, my cars, my pools, my jewels
Look, nigga, I came up and I ain't changed
And you should love it, way more then you hate it
Nigga you mad? I thought that you'd be happy I made it
I'm that cat by the bar toasting to the good life
You that faggot ass nigga trying to pull me back right?
When my junk get to pumping in the club it's on
I wink my eye at ya bitch, if she smiles she gone
If the roof on fire, let the motherfucker burn
If you talking bout money homie, I ain't concerned
I'm a tell you what Banks told me cause go 'head switch the style up
If the niggas hate then let 'em hate
Watch the money pile up
Or we go upside there wit a bottle of bub
You know where we fucking be"


its sad when a song makes 50 cents lyrics look impressive. 21 savage is pure trash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but i hate that because i don't wanna post to facebook or twitter. There needs to be a cloud or something to upload to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.google.com/amp/s/genius.com/amp/21-savage-red-opps-lyrics

these lyrics are absolute shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's actually correct too. the colors are flipped like they're supposed to and the secondary rainbow is higher. damn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i thought it was established that traps aren't gay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> apparently so. They hate trump so much that they have to pretend they didn't loathe every republican president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> those too. I'm hoping it's something that will be patched but wither way it's a minor annoyance in an amazing game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> unless its a rod, then you can't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard xenoblade is great, i don't doubt its not but with limited money to spend on games i'm just saying id probably go for yooka laylee before this because i loved banjo kazooie. Eventually i'll probably get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ive never played xenoblade, so i'd probably teplace that with yooka laylee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems you have a selective memory  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 13:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This subreddit has always been a massive circlejerk over new consoles and new games. If you're going to complain about switch posts after it literally just came out, you're in the wrong subreddit. Btw bought a switch and it's FUCKiNG awesome!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 13:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hand-holdy

when you skipped English class too many times and you're adjective game is weak af </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he should have been more loki </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mine's completely fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could have picked a better title... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i realized that after i posted it. whoops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't get hit, it doesn't matter what armor you wear. Might as well look sexy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 08:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i think it could be possible with updates to switch the screen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You still have that right. It's called parental control.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
