<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3415</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't have good ol' Anvil on a Shelf when you grew up? Man you missed out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember the video of the old man nailing the Skateboard jump? Fail Army uploaded the clip WITHOUT showing his success on the third attempt, turning what was actually a WIN video into a FAIL video. Shame on you Fail Army! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Generalized Anxiety Disorder (or so the free public health doctor told me) and I find when I consume cannabis it helps me think calmy, rationally, and prevents the panic attacks/shakes I get from being so anxious all the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worked at McD's for about three weeks. The manager tried to tell me if the drawer came up short then it would come out of my check. I laughed and told them to their face how super illegal that was and I'd like to see them try. 

I was never short thankfully but I left soon afterwards. I suck at handling fuckery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In how many books do you honestly have male protagonist who actively rapes women? Out of all those books how many depict it as a good thing?

It's like no one looking at this chart cares about the context of these words only their association.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our culture 

Our culture doesn't paint anything, individuals do. 

Sure there are plenty of depictions of violence towards women but there are tons of violence towards men as well. Grand landscapes that show men brutally dying on the battlefields waging pointless wars against equally dumb founded enemies. 

But you and I both know that we don't ALWAYS paints women that way. 

I went to an art gallery several months ago and out of all the pieces there only one depicted a woman in any sort of peril. A lot of them were pictures of beautiful and regal women just sitting there. Hardly in any sort of peril. 

I think you're looking for sexism where it doesn't exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there is trope that isn't lazy that features the man as the perp and the woman as the victim? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Attempted suicide. She didn't actually kill herself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dragonland - Astronomy 

This is beautiful metal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this really tell us anything though?

Words associated with gender from the synopsis of just over 100k books from unspecified times ago. 

Who cares if "He murders" or "she kisses" why are they doing these things and to whom? What is the context behind these stories?

This is just data bait setting people up to think something sexist is going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does a female being the victim and the male being a hero automatically make something a lazy trope? 

It would seem to me you're dismissing the concept before it's even introduced. 

I may be going out on a limb here and I'm not saying you think this but it seems this chart is almost starting some kind of discussion revolving around gender and the roles these play in the literary world but is it so bad to suggest we hold our opinions until we read what the author writes?

If an author writes a classic hero saving the damsel in distress story do we dismiss it because it's follow a classic trope or would it simply be more prudent to read the story and judge it based on it's technical prowess, story, and message?

I think it's odd that people assume that because a girl needs saving it makes her weak...not saying you said that and it may be a strawman but it would seem to be the general idea. 

I find data like this to be unhelpful because it only shows us words in relation to the gender they were found by in the synopsis of the book's story. No context or reason for these words. 

I have nothing to gain from seeing the world "man" and "murder" next to each other just like "woman" and "kiss" mean nothing to me either. Who is he murdering? Who is she kissing? Why is she kissing them? Why is he murdering them?

The books aren't about our psyches they are about the story contained within and if you, yes I'm talking to you now /u/Reasonably_Lucid, can't see that you need to re-evaluate why you're reading a book in the first place. I certainly don't read books to power my psyche...do you?

In my personal opinion, your comment sounds very akin to a comment someone who was all about social justice would make. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diablo III is being held back by lack of gameplay. The game is in it's Twilight Years already in my opinion. I'm pretty much waiting for Diablo 4 at this point before I return to the franchise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes it clear the was abusive. I doubt "talk" is a good word for it. I was implying OP had a good relationship with his mother not simply stating only talking to your mother makes one not a serial killer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a Seris refuse to heal. When I asked for healing they said no and proceeded to not heal. 0 Healing on the Scoreboard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Norman Bates

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ed_Gein </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twenty years sadly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the kids playing the game have a penis between their legs...so...wtf? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finally got to play Blood Dragon and I am 50/50 on it. 

The game is really self aware and I like it for that reason but the whole experience is so disjointed and pointless sometimes. The unlocks cost so much money and once you get the gatling gun Blood Dragons are no longer the crazy threat they used to be.

I think most people play it and like the retro references so assume it's good but really it's super short and really limited in it's game play. 

It can be beat in less than a few hours and 100% in less than ten. Not that good of a game imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a huge fan of the Saints Row series I have to disagree with both you and /u/Taz666.

Saints Row 3 onward were just an outright mockery of what the Saints universe had become. 

They went from having a very serious albeit funny and unusual theme to just out right bonkers shit. 

It was the video game equivalent of a kid learning something makes you laugh then driving that shit into the ground until it's not funny anymore. 

Shit, the main reason Gat out of Hell even exists is because one of the endings resets the Saints Universe to make room for the next game they are making which will have the Saints in some capacity but it's a different world where the Saints never happened.

Even the creators knew they took it too far and wrote in an ending that would allow them to back out from their own bullshit. 

Saints Row and Saints Row 2 are golden examples of open world video games from the 2000's. 

Saints Row 3, IV, and Gat out of Hell were a mockery of the former games. Hell they were even easier to beat and less technically sound. 

Saints Row IV is literally a repainted Saints Row 3. They used the same fucking city for Christ sake. 

At least in the transition from Saints Row to Saints Row 2 they used the same city but made it different enough to qualify as a new map. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So because the law says so it must be OK? That is what you're telling me here. 

We both know smoking is bad for you and look at the little princess there tilting that bottle back...she's is def consuming more than she should. 

Oh well, fuck princesses and princes and kings and queens. Archaic old fucks who need to step down and get off their high horse. It's like the worst form of being born into wealth, "Princess and Prince."

Ugh... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in real life thankfully no, though I wouldn't mind. I'd tear them a new one, I'm not a pussy when it comes to conversation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SJW is cringey? 

It's an acronym for Social Justice Warrior is a term, whether given or taken, that is used as a stand in for those who fight excessively for social justice when none is to be had. 

What's cringey is the out right childish behavior displayed by groups emblazoned with the SJW moniker. The lies tons of college kids are believing pushed onto them by social justice teachers is sickening, it's like a hateful religion but without a god. 

There are people who seriously get on the news and say: "We just need less white people." And yet this people claim they are the paragons of social justice and righteousness. Bull. Shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Free Press doesn't matter they made us look like the idiots we actually are!" ~The Newstation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No the Bible is pretty clear that the only thing that matters is turning people to Jesus. Twist it however you want that man was doing what his holy book told him too. Religion is repulsive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 08:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a fan of the Batman series. I know what Joker looks like and modern iterations of him are interesting but this just looks like a dude dressed up as Joker smiling realllll wide.

Do you think this is a good representation of the character or are you going to continue being a pretentious turd and add nothing to the conversation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 08:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the simple fact you actively talk to your mother would make you more than likely not to be one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 08:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone's going to kick one of these thinking they are a ball or something and break their foot. They deserve it but still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 08:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, this Joker looks like rubbish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 08:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old School Cool aka Casual Child Abuse.

No biggy, just some kids doin shit they shouldn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 08:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems more to me when you have an opinion and also lack communication skills. 

People who disagree with you aren't attacking you or the concept you present...they just don't agree with you. And may or may not present a reason why either calmly or something more angry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I've never thought of us melding with the machines but that is also a possibility. Why give a machine a better brain than us when we could give it to ourselves?

That or my hypothesis a self taught machine, were it more advanced than a human, would understand concepts like mercy and empathy. These are human traits that are shown to develop with education so surely a machine would develop them too assuming it has a brain more complex than our own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What no one seems to understand is why would the AI go hostile in the first place? 

If a machine is capable of thinking as we do, self taught and learning, which is everyone fear, what makes it incapable of understanding concepts like empathy? 

Everyone seems to think a self taught machine would lack human qualities and we be absurdly evil in the pursuit of it's mission.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my! Good times indeed! 

Champions of Norrath was what got me into the hack n slash Diablo-Esque style of games. Me and my best friend used to play it a lot when he had it on his PS2. 

I miss my Drow... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GTA may not of invented cars going through hoops but they sure did capitalize off of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But how would we demonize our enemies then if we showed their human sides? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
