<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2894</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That I love Gods and follow Jesus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen if you lend yourself to see the lesson you are being taught and humble your heart to the new beginning you will see that you weren't in the right place or right path and this is a season of change. I'm not telling you to go to a church or to do anything but I promise you you won't go through anything you can't handle. You will gain strength and some point in the future someone will come along that you now possess the skills to assist. If you leave us we all loose. Look for the lesson.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And there you have it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's tacky to say and it varies but I'll say it's a lot more than I need but not as much as I'd like it to be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have answers for you but no time to deliver for you right now. I'll give the quick..1. I don't network well. I'm anti social but my work performance networks for me in a way. Ppl hear who can do stuff and they call. 2. I don't fail because I don't quit. The competition out here is weak. Lots of quitters. 3. No i do the opposite. I ensure the bad ppl get confronted. 4. Ppl play dirty on me. I believe in doing double positive. Meaning if someone e screws me I try my best to accept it and still do something positive for the person or group. Then never work with them again or charge 500% more 5. You have to take the shit work and prove yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the latest on the missing children, pizzagate, Wiener saga? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pizzagate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She looks cute to me. I love USA for our ability to wear dumb hats. Trumps hat is stupid too. Who cares about her opinion? Nazi's would  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 600-675 right now 628. Business management/consulting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regarding leadership, No I actually prefer the 2 slot. I've been put in the leadership positions since I'm 23 though. I think the #1 thing is motivation to solve the problem and #2 is humility to know my weakness and where I need help  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's made for a certain type of person. I do well in experiential learning and public school teaches kids to be workers not leaders  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump ones. Who knows what will happen next?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Small coal town in PA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Social studies focused on the Ming Dynasty  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
