<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3835</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking into M.2 SSD's: the Intel 600p 256GB seems suspiciously cheap. What's the catch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 15:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the link

https://www.scan.co.uk/products/256gb-intel-600p-series-m2-(22x80)-pcie-30-(x4)-nvme-ssd-3d-tlc-nand-read-1570mb-s-write-540mb-s-112

They're claiming 1570MB/s Read and it costs 85. What's the catch?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get one from Anker. They're well known as the best cable makers. Costs slightly more but will last longer than your phone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 13:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree to be honest. I don't know if the rest are as bad in from the perspective of their respective regions, but it stinks of "what Americans think the British sound like". It's pretty cringey but suicide seems like an extreme response.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 13:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least you tried </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> annual? What rocks are you hiding under? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scheduled messages were incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 14:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Safety aside, why the hell would you use a hair dryer in a bathtub full of water? The water makes your hair wet which completely undoes the work of the hair drier. Dafuq </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 14:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I agree with this. The warnings should be clear but shouldn't be misleading </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 18:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need double newlines in there when you copypaste your memes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 16:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SLICK COMEBACK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 15:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have a look, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 14:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think the sensation itself is weird. Just the videos used to trigger it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 14:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because I'd rather be caught watching porn than asmr vids

Oh sure, yeah this is definitely the reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 14:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an old 4S lying around. It'd be great to get it back onto iOS 6 - how would I do that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 14:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> girlfriend

Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 02:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you mean /r/absolutelynotmeirl
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 02:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get with the times. I have an imagination Blu-ray player, the quality is incredible. Shame about the lack of content though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 02:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Archive link because CNN

http://web.archive.org/web/20161225102408/http://www.cnn.com/2016/12/22/opinions/female-doctors-could-lengthen-life-expectancy-caudle/index.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TITLE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 02:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TEXT (optional) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 01:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You spelled 2013 wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 22:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smashing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 19:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/SUBREDDITNAME </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 18:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rough Christmas buddy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 15:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair across all timezones Christmas Day actually lasts a total of 48 hours so he has longer than you think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 03:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well removed posts aren't visible on the subreddit except to mods. So the fact that you could see it and write that comment means it was unremoved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 03:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He seemed so genuine. He obviously loves his job so much. I hope he never gives it up. Actually I'd be kind of let down if he deserted it, because he just seems the perfect guy for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 03:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 02:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aww fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 02:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loop? No this was the famous "How many chairs can one person throw into a wrestling ring in 30 minutes" world record attempt from a few years back. At the end of the gif he's presented with his Guinness World Record. It takes a while though so you have to be patient. What you can't see is the GWR official removing the chairs as he's throwing them in just off the left frame edge. [Link to the full video if you want the sound, and includes the interview with the GWR official.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 02:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.imgur.com/cOXixXx.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 02:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is a perfectly legitimate question and is within the rules. I'm really not sure why it was removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: When I exchange currency, why is the exchange rate often given to 8-10 or more decimal places? Surely nobody, even when dealing will millions of dollars, cares after the fourth decimal place. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 02:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems so insignificant and unnecessarily precise to say "We're offering $1 = 0.8462485301" (as I've just been told by Amazon). As a consumer I only care about the first two decimal places. I can understand if you're trading currencies or working as a business maybe you'd care about the third and *maybe* fourth decimal place. But is anyone really looking at that thousandth of a penny in the fifth decimal place? I'm absolutely certain nobody is looking at the millionth of a penny. And yet most currency exchange places - both brick   mortar and online - offer this insane level of accuracy, providing 8, 10, or even more decimal places. Why? And how do they come up with such precise numbers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 19:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it a lich king joke? I don't even understand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 19:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 19:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100 subreddits with gold, 50 without

https://www.reddit.com/subreddits/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> outputting 0.3 milliwatts, this would take ~5100 hours = ~31 weeks to charge my ~1700 mah iPhone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 15:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gone completely shit now. Used to be a great sub but now the single moderator has automod remove every post and only approves submissions he personally likes, sometimes only days after they're submitted. So it appears that there's only one submission per week or so when actually there are a lot more but they're almost all removed. You can easily tell because of the ratio between subscribers and comments to submission frequency. Such a shame that a great subreddit went to waste. I had to unsubscribe because I've used all my subreddit subscription slots and the rarity of posts made it a lower priority on my front page, so it got replaced with some other actually active subreddit. Maybe someone should create /r/outsidetwopointzero or something with a better name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rumours suggest that patch 20.1.7 is being finalised and could come out of beta any day now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 14:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No word on which bugs will be fixed though - what extra features are you hoping for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 15:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/British_Isles:

The British Isles are a group of islands off the north-western coast of continental Europe that consist of the islands of Great Britain, Ireland and over six thousand smaller isles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 13:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually it's not. Great Britain is just the single main island (If you can walk there from London it's Great Britain). This map also excludes all of the surrounding small islands, which collectively are the British Isles. But since the British Isles also include Ireland, which is shown on the map, the map actually shows "Europe except the British Isles except Ireland". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 12:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/anticlimax </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 12:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love reddit. 

Thanks for the link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 11:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny how this post fits perfectly with their advertising style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 10:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not to me. TIL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 10:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CGP Grey talked about this on either Cortex or Hello Internet (I forget which right now). He said that if your video is longer than 10 minutes you get an additional ad, or a higher ad rate or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 10:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I've got it on a 5S too but I've never had any problems with it. It's nowhere near as quick as my 7, obviously, but it's also nowhere near as slow as my iPad 4. It's fine. 

---

Also the epitome of this subreddit is you offering your experiences and getting downvoted for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 00:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sure? They're still selling Air 2's, and they're great from what I've heard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 00:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone please rule 34 this into existence. I didn't realise how much I needed a posh junkrat until now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst part is I stupidly bought it about three weeks before the iPad Air came out. I didn't really follow Apple back then so I wasn't aware of the release schedule 

And to rub salt in the wound, when I went to the Apple Store to fix my iphone and mentioned it to the genius, he said I could have replaced my iPad 4 with an iPad Air for free during a short window immediately after the Air  came out since I bought the 4 at basically the worst time. So I should really have an Air  \\_()_/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a serious note, how does iOS 10 run on the iPhone 5? I put it on my iPad 4 and it runs like absolute shit, completely regret "upgrading" it. The whole system is just ridiculously slow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 21:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This really worked for me. Good sound quality definitely helped. Nice :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 21:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And don't forget about the standard reply with a pun/joke to bathe in the easy comment karma from the promotion under your top comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoiler warning: it will </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/anticlimax  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 13:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, fair enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 11:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not how probabilities work at all

---

edit: unless blizzard has guaranteed that every 21 loot boxes you'll get at least one legendary, but I doubt this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 11:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I play two games, each played 40% as lucio, does that count as a rounded (80% - 1) full lucio game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 10:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [ITT](https://youtu.be/B759dzymyoc?t=1m1s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 13:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You surely mean:

 Justice rains fr- argh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 13:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you can get headshots that is. Unfortunately my aim is as bad as an obese sheep with parkinsons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 12:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> brb  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 11:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops - you've arrived at the wrong comment section. I linked to the main sticky from a couple of weeks ago, where you should go to submit your mod application or provide feedback about the recent changes to the subreddit. Here's the link again:

https://www.reddit.com/r/asmr/comments/5e6zf7/meta_new_shiny_flairs_mod_applications/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meta] Final call for mod applications! Decision will be made tomorrow. If you've not applied and you'd like to help out, tell us why you'd be an asset to the community! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 11:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 23:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great info, thanks! I'll look into everything you mentioned :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 22:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I watched the video too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 21:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand what part of

# don't feed the trolls

People don't understand  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is private. Only I and two other mods have access to it to read/write. It's running on a raspberry pi dedicated to running the bot, so if the hacker 4chan gets in I can just wipe it and start over - I have the source code and database backed up sufficiently.

Although that said, are there any additional precautions I can take when using eval()? I'm checking whether the result is a set of strings but I'm guessing it's too late to be validating by the time the function returns.

It's not a huge deal for it to be readable. It's readable if I go to the edit page anyway, because the text entry box is all in plaintext. It'd just be nice if it were possible, but looks as if it isn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 15:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just using [eval()](https://docs.python.org/3/library/functions.html#eval) on the entire wiki page to import a set with a comment next to each item in the set. The wiki begins with several comments too. So yes, this worked for the initial block of comments, but since python uses spaces as indentation I was gettin indentation exceptions when it wasn't indented as expected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 15:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried it but it only works on single lines apparently. Thanks anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know if it's possible to disable markdown on a wiki page? Perhaps with CSS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 13:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to store some configuration for my bot on a private wiki page so that any mod can edit it. The trouble is it contains a lot of python comments, which begin with hashes.. and hashes make the formatting go crazy on reddit because of their interpretation as markdown headings. The markdown also collapses multiple newline characters into a single newline, which also messes with my formatting.

It looks fine when editing, because the editor is in plaintext, but is there a way to cause the wiki page itself to show in plaintext rather than displaying using markdown? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 02:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh I hadn't watched this week's WAN show yet, nice surprise to combine Linus and asmr :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 01:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Help, help, I'm being repressed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 01:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mods don't have the power to remove the ability to downvote within the subreddit, nor can we see who has voted on a given post. It's a frustrating issue and has been discussed at length on the subreddit - see /r/asmr/wiki/downvotes. We wish there was more we can do, but all we can do is advise people not to downvote and hope they respectfully don't, but they do \\()/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 22:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What have I done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 22:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. I've always gone with the former, makes more sense in my head, no idea why. 

This calls for a straw poll http://www.strawpoll.me/11897901  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 21:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real talk: is that pronounced "100 dollars percent" or "100 percent dollars"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 12:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Op is Illidan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditor gets Bill Gates as her secret Santa and is very excited </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 10:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 10:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck everyone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 18:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> prolly

:/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 15:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intelli-gentlesir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 10:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed and banned. Rule 11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate when it's high noon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 15:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strange, yes. But it worked. Most asmr content is strange. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 09:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New submissions start on the front page unless they're downvoted. Three upvotes can put a submission in ~4-5th place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 22:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just new ones. It just checks for certain keywords which indicate a roleplay submission in either the reddit submission title, YouTube title, or YouTube tags list, and if it finds a roleplay post flaired as [intentional] it messages the op with a button to re-flair it. It's had basically a 100% hit rate which I'm quite pleased with so I might just bypass the confirmation message and re-flair all such posts. Anything flaired incorrectly will be caught by manual review or reports.

Edit: I could run a script to re-flair old submissions. It wouldn't be able to do the entire subreddit backlog, but I could do all top submissions and the past couple of months worth of submissions. I'll look into it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 14:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> emphasis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 12:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to find the image I was referencing but couldn't find it anywhere :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 11:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what the fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 00:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/asmr

Down the rabbit hole you go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 15:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See [1% rule](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1%25_rule_(Internet_culture\))

My interpretation of it wasn't that 99% of all users will never submit, comment or vote. I always assumed it meant that in any given thread, almost everyone who views that particular thread won't comment or vote in it. That is, I might visit an askreddit thread where I don't vote or comment, so I'm part of the 99% for that particular thread. But that doesn't take into account my participation elsewhere on reddit.

Someone can correct me if I'm wrong but that's the impression I've always had when discussions about it come up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean you don't have to, but you can if you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's common everywhere online, not just reddit. Approximately 10% of viewers vote on things, and only around 10% of *those* (1% of viewers) contribute by submitting/commenting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a submission is removed, you can resubmit it straight away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I were the owner of a library I'd make sure we don't stock your book because it's obviously all kinds of wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 15:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See my comment here https://www.reddit.com/r/meirl/comments/5hv704/me_irl/db3ggbc/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 15:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah a lot of people have the same reaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 14:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I should proofread comments before I press save. Not sure how the last few words got chopped off :\ Fixed now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 13:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to understand that 99% of regular users don't know this sort of stuff. If you've ever changed settings in an app or have the ability to recognise the differnce between album links and hotlinks etc, you're already more computer-savvy than 99% of users. I'm not exaggerating the percentage. It's well known in software development that around 99% of people will never change the default settings, and in the same way, almost every person will just take the imgur link they're given by default, which for a while now has been the album link for whatever reason. I'd guess that even those who realise the link is an album link mostly don't care; the extra click or two adds enough friction that people will just not bother.

I'd like not to see weird album links everywhere too, but you can't change people's behaviour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 13:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imgur creates an album by default now. So it's more effort to get the direct link, and people don't really realise I think. Almost everyone just goes with whatever the default is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 21:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the word "triggering"

HOLY SHIT DUDE YOU CAN'T JUST SAY STUFF LIKE THAT WITHOUT CENSORING IT THE INTERNET POLICE WILL SURELY BE COMING FOR YOU NOW

edit OH MY GOLLY i JUST SAID IT TOO I'M A CRIMINAL FUCK :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Handles were *ok* while you could change them whenever you like and it was optional to add your handle to your posts/comments. But tying them to your phone number, making them unchangeable, and requiring them on each comment and submission? Nope, I'm out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't. I'm also a casual onlooker and therefore have no idea how to value a company. People who know more about this stuff than I apparently valued it at $400M though, and I presume they didn't pluck that figure out of the air so they must have has some reasoning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "casual onlooker" doesn't really know how to value businesses accurately though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was good for a while. But they pushed a load of updates and completely ruined it. So everyone left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 12:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's be honest that wasn't the worst grammatical error </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [unintentional] Wrist Aiming vs Arm Aiming explanation. [male] [short] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 16:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 16:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zenyatta is great after they increased a load of his stats a few months ago
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever get that feeling of deja vu? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok well that's fair enough. So then I think the timer should be increased, maybe 5-10 minutes or something. What is it at the moment? 30 seconds ish? The tg shouldn't have pressure, including from the timer.

edit: Actually, on second thoughts. It would solve everyone's issue if they just count faffing in the menus as "action". If you're remapping controls or switching heros, that should count as action if you're in the TG. That way you can take as long as you like, but if you actually go afk you'll still get booted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm confused as to why there's an activity timeout on the Training Ground. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 14:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely love the idea of a training ground. The whole point of it is to give you a space to take your time, try out heros and abilities, and learn about the game generally. Although this applies less now that I've levelled into my twenties, several times I have been kicked from the training ground for taking too long while reading the hero descriptions. I carefully read about their abilities and compare a couple of different heros, and then suddenly I'm kicked. Why? I'm not sure if this is intentional or an oversight, but I'd like the pressure of the activity timer to be removed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What email or text message do you wish you could "unsend"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 12:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 15:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with this? Maybe I'm missing something but it looks fine to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 15:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like this purposefully to confuse people who aren't "good at computers". It's not at all obvious that it's even possible to close it completely. I had a fully competent colleague (a programmer and very good with computers) who has been using Task Manager - End Task to quit the program because he didn't realise there was another way. He thought, as I did at first, that the cog and the arrow were all one button. The cog goes to the settings panel, from which there is neither an exit button nor the option to actually close the program when the X is clicked, while the tiny 7x4 pixel arrow provides the Exit button after navigating a sub-menu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the only method to close Microsoft Lync. Anything else just minimises it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 15:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What email or text message do you wish you could "unsend"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 14:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 13:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \ using hours

\ not using kilosmoots per microfortnight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 12:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since you asked. I'm touching up my subreddit bot.

https://github.com/Theonefoster/asmr_bot/blob/master/asmr_bot.py </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 11:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you get these gifs from all the time? You always seem to have a relevant gif for every comment. Your gif library must be huge! Or you're really good at searching for them I guess :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aww boohoo downvote me for protecting your privacy for you aww cry cry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 13:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok let's close our eyes and pretend it doesn't happen so we don't have to address the issue. I'm sure the problem of undereducation leading to spread of STI's and teen pregnancies will go away on its own if we just don't think about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 13:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \ 2016

\ reading the Daily Mail

\ expecting anything other than full retard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 00:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. Right you are. Great minds think alike apparently. I'll remove this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 23:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real something something is always something something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 23:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Day After Tomorrow is dying for this to be photoshopped in. Perhaps even the South Park parody </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 23:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh fancy. Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 22:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ayy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 22:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, I'd vote for an orange shield. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 22:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like a link back to the main site from the modmail. Since it seems to function as a whole different website, I have to manually "return to reddit". It'd be nice if there were a button to, say, my user profile or the front page for example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever used iMessage? You're going to love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 14:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removed. No personal info allowed. See the sticky for details.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You swerve to avoid a squirrel. Unknown to you, the squirrel pledges a life debt to you. In your darkest hour, the squirrel arrives. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 11:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you've got some serious anger problems. What's going on bud? All ok? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 14:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't see how vote fuzzing stops people vote manipulating anyway. Just because they can't see the effect of their extra upvotes doesn't mean they can't still add the extra upvotes. You seem to put in a lot of effort to vote fuzzing so I guess you must have a good reason, but I don't know what that reason could be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 14:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe amateaurs like this still exist. It's " + current_year + " and there are people don't even have bionic retinal projectors installed. Jesus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 14:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/OutOfTheLoop/comments/5gpwvt/whats_the_original_post_for_the_how_many_upvotes/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 00:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly why it's one of my favourites. The whole keyboard section was done so well. I usually skip the "interview" in roleplays but this one is just hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (RaphyTaphyASMR) Cranial Nerve Exam Roleplay [humour] [whispered] [tapping] [object sounds] [roleplay] [male] [33:39] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would use [this picture](http://imgur.com/XeyI1y4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not, but AMA anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 13:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I just tested this and it works great. If only I'd known this months ago! So annoying to have to OK the location every single time I search for anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 13:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comedian? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually a manhole cover. The hole can't really have leaves **on** it. It's a hole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah that's unfortunate. I neer use it so didn't even think of jailbreaking it tbh, so I didn't know 32-bit devices don't have the jb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an old 4S lying around on iOS 9.2.x if that's any use to you. I can send it over if you need it. I'm based in the uk though so postage might take a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 19:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, it seems I haven't updated the bot's message yet. [roleplay] is also a flair tag, so having [intentional] and [roleplay] together counts as two flairs. I've approved your post though since we're in the trial period of the new flairs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 17:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was kissing sounds. There's a subtle difference and I think the sounds are acceptable. Videos which roleplay as actually kissing the viewer are more boarderline.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't agree. If the sound triggers people, then great. There's a lot of bizarre content in the asmr world, and that bizarre content can trigger people well.

I reviewed the video and it's neither sexual nor inappropriate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6th panel has incorrectly capitalised "A". Literally unreadable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been, but I find they're less effective. Sometimes if I really need to sleep quickly I'll give my phone a quick blast charge and then put the earphones in for sleep. It means I have to keep on top of my charge all day the next day though, so I have to plug it in in the car and at work. Not a huge deal but it's a little hasstle that feels unnecessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Lightning earphones work with any iOS10 device </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 01:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> albums </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 01:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> murica </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 01:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally disagree. Even as I write this comment I'm on FaceTime Audio with a friend using my earpods, and I'm on 7% battery. Soon I'm going to have to hang up the call so I can charge my phone.

I sometimes have trouble sleeping and find that certain youtube videos playing on my earphones can help me fall sleep in minutes. Can't do that any more because I need to charge my phone overnight. 

There are many occasions I miss the hpj. I'm disappointed that Apple moved in this direction. Unless the iPhone 8 is extraordinarily impressive, I'll likely switch to Android next year, which is something I'd NEVER have thought I'd say a year ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 21:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah it's fine here. Kissing sounds aren't sexual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 00:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> op pls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 23:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I ran `sudo apt-get install ldxe-core` and rebooted and my desktop is back. Thanks so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [raspberry pi, Linux] when I log in, I'm taken to OpenBox instead of the desktop and I can barely do anything. It wasn't like this yesterday. Please help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 22:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why it's doing this but I'm not particularly good with the command line so my pi is next to useless at the moment. Yesterday it was logging into the desktop fine, but it suffered a sudden power loss without safely powering down and now I don't have a desktop. I can right click the blank grey canvas and choose "exit" to get back to the login screen, or I can launch a terminal or a browser. There's an option on the right-click menu for "obconf", but selecting it yields an error: No such file or directory. There's also an option "reconfigure" which does nothing. I tried running raspi-config and selecting Boot Options  boot to desktop but it didn't make a difference. At the login screen I can choose "Openbox" or "Default Xsession" from the dropdown menu at the top, but both seem to do the same thing: log me in to openbox. 

Any ideas? I need my desktop back :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. I haven't seen a rofl in the wild for like 10 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't do it OP it's a trap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't fly. They fall. With style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two redditors find love in an unusual way over the course of three weeks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 12:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 12:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or `print("hello world")` if you're not a dirty 2.7 heathen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 00:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone had to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 00:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feels more link a "link in the sidebar" sort of topic than a sticky. But I agree that it should be easily accessible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 00:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Submitting a subreddit as an askreddit question has always been a karma goldmine. Instant frontpage. 

"Hey reddit, what's your favourite youtube video under 30 seconds long?".

"What's your favourite landscape picture with no roads or buildings in it?"

"What headlines sound like they're made up but are actually real?"

etc. Guaranteed hits. Try it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 00:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, you don't even suck *over* the trench coat? Amateaur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 23:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     public class HelloWorld{
        public static void main(String[] args){
            system.out.println("Hello World!");
        }
    }
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Haiku] I believe I can fly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 14:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 13:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that they're finally rolling out large-diameter mugs!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 12:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't convey my meaning very well, I just meant words which have programmatic meaning. You shouldn't use `integer` or `class` or `exception` or `for` etc as variable names </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 12:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh me neither. It's obviously a waste of time at best and a harmful scam at worst. But it works great as a trigger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 10:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the idea of "Thanks, Brexit" becoming the new "Thanks Obama" but for specifically Biritsh problems. Biscuit too big to dunk in your tea? Thanks, Brexit. Too much meat in your fiver? Thanks, Brexit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 10:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really need to learn how to copy and paste comments properly.

Pro tip: if you highlight part of someone's comment and then hit "reply", it'll automatically insert the highlighted part as a quote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 10:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You used "string" as a variable name?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you haven't already, I'd really recommend browsing /r/wooasmr/top. For me at least, they give some of the strongest tingle responses of any video category. I love them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really doesn't matter. Everyone agrees ASMR is a terrible name, but it's what we're stuck with. It's not possible to change the name at this stage. I think of it more as a made-up word than an initialism anyway, like "ayesemmar". If we can try to disconnect the initials from their intended meaning I think it would confuse people less, because it really doesn't mean anything significant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what y'all means. I just mean when you're yelling and screaming at hundreds of thousands of people, telling them they're all wrong and insisting that your completely different view is right... who is likely to be right there?

Also you've mentioned banning you multiple times. We don't just ban people we disagree with. Feel free to have your discussion openly, as long as you don't break rules or harrass/demean/insult people. Unless of course you *want* to be banned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha I'm now having to go through all your comments and manually approve the ones that aren't too ridicuous because reddit has flagged you as a spammer so everything you comment is being removed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I set up the bot to do it for us. Faster and less effort :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no problem. There is no "y'all". If you don't like how we've set up the subreddit for everyone's benefit then go and make /r/typeAAsmr or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 18:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not about arguing over the term. It's about labelling something in a consistent and predictable way. All videos flaired "intentional" are videos* created with the express intent to trigger the viewer's asmr. JK Rowling's movie was not created with the intent to trigger the viewers' asmr, therefore it isn't tagged as [intentional]. if it *happens* to trigger someone, it should be flaired as [unintentional]. The purpose of the flairs is not to fully describe the content, it's to give a broad category so that people can choose the type of video they'd like to see while browsing the subreddit. 

The flairs are supposed to broadly categorise the content to make searching and browsing easier and faster for people who want to find content that appeals to them. Some people like content which was created to trigger asmr, some don't, and both of those people can easily browse the subreddit and see their type of video. With that in mind, the rule is that anything submitted because it triggered the OP should be either [intentional] (ie it was *supposed* to trigger them) or [unintentional] (i.e. the video has a different purpose but incidentally triggers people). With that rule, people know that anything *not* flaired as either [intentional] or [unintentional] is most likely not going to trigger them. 

So if you want to discuss something, you can create a [discussion] thread. But the purpose of that thread type is for OP to start a *discussion*, as should be self-evident. Links aren't discussions, so [discussion] link posts aren't allowed. You are free to include links in the discussion post for reference though.

[intentional] posts should be links to triggering content, so self-posts aren't allowed. This is to keep them meaningful - if everybody applied their own definition and meaning to the flairs, they might as well not be there because their categorisation of posts would be different to different people.

I'm not really sure what you're trying to say to be honest. Nobody else has a problem with the categorisations. Their purpose is to keep the subreddit clean, readable, searchable, and on-topic. It sounds like what you're trying to do is have a discussion, so you should create a [discussion] thread. 

I also have absolutely no idea what a "type A self trigger" is.

---

*or any content, actually, not just videos. But since the vast majority of submissions are youtube videos I/we generally say "videos" when we mean "content" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 16:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries. You learn something every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 16:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure where else to put this since it's a little light-hearted. But I've noticed something that's **ruined** python code for me. Can't be unseen.

    def foo(bar): # - see it?
        pass

    foo(bar):

    (bar):

    bar):

    r):
 
    ):

There's a sad face on the end of every definition line. They pop up every now and then in ifs and whiles etc too.

CAN'T. UNSEE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
