<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2746</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to challenge my sci-fi writers' group to tell a space-based tale that takes place somewhere other than on a planet or in a ship. What are some options I can give them, if they need inspiration? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 21:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 23:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is not to be "super deep."  Few of the movies Rian suggested would be considered "super deep."  But those films tell a particular flavor of story.  Watch a few of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did people of the American "Wild West" drink hard apple cider instead of beer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 16:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read [this article](http://www.smithsonianmag.com/arts-culture/real-johnny-appleseed-brought-applesand-booze-american-frontier-180953263/)  about Johnny Appleseed that implied the drink of choice of the American West during the 1800s was not beer at all, as we see in every saloon depicted in the movies.  It's hard for me to envision a rough-and-tumble frontiersman leaning on the bar and ordering a hard apple cider.  Can this be true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 20:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I approve of your collection! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 04:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great endorsement! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 16:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good tip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 05:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can find super reviews on just about any Mora knife at Amazon, but here's one example:

https://www.amazon.com/Morakniv-Companion-Outdoor-Military-4-1-Inch/dp/B004TNWD40 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 04:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Kind of Magic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you know about Frost Mora knives? They are inexpensive but have stellar ratings at Amazon. Some reviewers there say these are BiFL. Yet so cheap? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 04:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 04:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why USAA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 03:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was given an Invictus as a gift. How would you rate that brand? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 19:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am completely dejected every time a race starts behind a safety car, because it eliminates what is often the most exciting lap of the race.  Not every race can be thrilling, I know, but nearly every time the safety car drives around and around for three or four laps to start the race, what happens next is boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 03:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you ever watch American-style football, either college or pro, you'll see that complaining about the commentators is half the fun.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are homes with 10-foot ceilings harder to heat and cool than homes with traditional 8- or 9-foot ceilings, if all other factors are equal (square footage, insulation, et cetera)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 00:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 18:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the info! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 15:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 05:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, this thread isn't leaving many brand names that are trustworthy. What's a consumer to do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 05:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your opinion of Henry? I have heard my father speak very highly of his Golden Boy .22. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 05:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Bear stuff gets a bad rap from the hardcore crowd. Remember, that stuff is made to sell at Walmart to fans of his shows, rather than at high-end shops to gear heads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 04:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't speak for Craftsman power tools, but their hand tools have never failed me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 01:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  I'll give it a try if you can vouch for it.  I'm just sort of overwhelmed by the number of those products on the market, each one sounding a little bit too good to be true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I use an engine additive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 21:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I drive a beautiful 2007 Chevy shortbed, and she just rolled over 100K miles.  I see a lot of ads for engine additives, fuel treatments, and oil stabilizers.  Does any of that stuff actually extend the life of my truck?  If so, how do I know where to start, with so much on the market? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 18:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's cool!  But it's probably because a sponsor was paying for it.  As they say in POLICE ACADEMY, "In America, talk is cheap!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 17:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, this America.  We are built on commercials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 16:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an American, my F1 experience is brought to me weekly by Leigh Diffey, David Hobbs, and Steve Matchett, and I find their commentary far superior to what I've seen here when watching NBA, NFL, NHL, et cetera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 16:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. I heard the term applied in RPGs long ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 16:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a word for those types of players: munchkins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 20:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not that guy in real life, but only in the classroom.  ; ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 17:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are not alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 14:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Allan with an "A" and not "Allen" with an "E," as I say about 22 times each semester. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using Honey To Cure Allergies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 17:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 03:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize that tone is difficult to convey in text, but OP wasn't seriously calling everyone crazy. Relax. If you're so easily offended, I'd hate to see how you react when someone genuinely insults you.

I for one admit that I'm a wee bit crazy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 03:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry about it. Some people take things too seriously and have a hard time making fun of themselves. I've seen enough beekeepers to know that we're an odd group, for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 03:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, but how will messaging function via Skype?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 01:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think OP was meaning to insult anyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 16:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally unimportant but totally mine: The older editions of Dungeons and Dragons are superior to more recent editions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is my favorite depiction of the demihuman races. Your opinion may vary. But I always come back to this illustration when I think of elves, halflings, and dwarves. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 01:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 20:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Ambush**! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 20:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any RPGs involving mythological figures such as Paul Bunyan and John Henry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 18:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 16:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 18:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most intriguing book I've found is THE BEEKEEPER'S BIBLE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 04:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Remove the reducer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 04:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compass, please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 03:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A compass seems like the first thing I'd add if making a mapping program.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
