<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2923</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NPD] SIB Echodrive, Diamond Vibrato, Mr. Black SuperMoon Chrome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 06:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FS: Alesis Bitrman, Mid-Fi Electronics Deluxe Pitch Pirate, Arion SPH-1 Stereo Phaser, Aria ACH-1 Analog Stereo Chorus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 21:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alesis Bitrman -$170
http://rvrb.io/2003-bitrman-d9s

Mid-Fi Electronics Deluxe Pitch Pirate -$210
http://rvrb.io/2012-deluxe-pitch-sp5

Arion SPH-1 Stereo Phaser -$50
http://losangeles.craigslist.org/sfv/msg/5552102021.html

Aria ACH-1 Analog Stereo Chorus -$70
http://rvrb.io/1980s-ach-1-stereo-jsc

Let me know if you have any questions. I'm open to interesting trades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 19:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much! I was kind of experimenting on this one, singing mostly in falsetto with a droney melody in kind of a weird rhythm and when I was mixing I definitely noticed the Kevin Parker influence (and a little Panda Bear). It's funny how that stuff seeps in. I love Currents, btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surreal/Dream Pop song I wrote and recorded yesterday. Thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 19:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surreal/Dream Pop song I wrote and recorded yesterday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 19:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meat and Potatoes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 21:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biv, Roy G </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 02:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 02:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! The switch on the left is the on/off for the pedal and the one on the right is the on/off for the photocell theramin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 23:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please post videos of you operating the Ipad with your foot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 23:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got the jupiter 3 very recently and posted about it on here.  Super fun synth that you can trigger with any audio source. Also talked to the guy who makes them and apparently it's just something he does in his down time. They are made in super small batches and very infrequently and he's not interested in scaling up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 23:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that Pick Cage I see?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 02:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DS-1 and TR-2 are both super sub par </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 05:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's actually one for sale for $250 in LA at Caveman Vintage Music (where I saw it in the first place and got obsessed with it). I don't know if they ship, but they might put it on Reverb or something if you message them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 23:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my hand clicked purchase right as my mouth said "you cannot buy another pedal" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 22:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> done did it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 22:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to hear it (not a full demo by any means, just one cool setting and chord progression I made up on the spot) with the settings from the photo
-----  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FR7KSuQNyl0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NPD] Mid-Fi Electronics Deluxe Pitch Pirate (feeling pleasantly woozy) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 22:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 19:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... I don't know how new it would be. There was a good bit of space oriented music in the 50s (pop), 60s (psych), 70s (psych, pop and prog, especially prog), etc... 

That being said, I am TOTALLY down for a more concentrated space music genre.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 06:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bravo, sir! I've only heard tell of the KoT, but I had an ARDX20 and they are stupendous. Way to circumvent that insane waiting list! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 06:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have also napped in my car on occasion... again, that's why this case is a nap goal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 06:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would think "Wow!  What is the likelihood that I would find a photo of my dad napping in public on reddit".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 06:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not making fun of him. I wish I was uninhibited enough to nap in public... aka nap goals. Things can be funny without being made fun of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 06:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's quite an assumption to make. Even if that's the case, I still think it's funny to do it in a donut shop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> #napgoals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 06:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 05:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can plug any audio source into it and it triggers the synth, or you can hit it (it has a pickup inside). Also: photocell theramin to control the pitch. I plugged a crappy yamaha dd-9 I've had since I was a kid into it and messed around with the pitch knobs. Everything sounded like funky old video game music. Started messing with the sweep, modulation and decay and it sounded like rototoms played in space. I couldn't be any happier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> tired and terrifying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 03:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 23:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't even say the make and model in the title... whoops! It's a Chamber of Sounds Jupiter III. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 23:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aesthetically, it is very well done, but I think that more graphic oriented pedals tend to sell better in the current market. That's just my opinion, mind you, but something to consider in the future. The eq is a good idea though, for sure! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NPD] 365 Million Miles Away From Earth (not a traditional guitar pedal, but one that can be triggered by guitar and one that experimental guitars players will no doubt appreciate) + it looks amazing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 23:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 07:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fletcher Munson! Never forget.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 22:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, the digiverb goes 100% wet and those x series pedals are nearly indestructible. I'm now going to stop talking about it and go play with it instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 22:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the Digitech Digiverb. Have had it for and used it on recordings and live for years. Many other high end pedals have come and gone, but funnily enough this one stuck around. Coincidentally, the digidelay is super flexible and fun too. I'm sure you can find both of them for very cheap on craigslist, ebay, or reverb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 19:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That old grey mxr 117 has a wide array of cool and insane sounds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 18:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure... I haven't seen any announcements about it or anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 18:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got it direct from Dwarfcraft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 10:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was so excited by the new pedals that I spelled "excitement" wrong and didn't notice until 11 hours later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 04:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either a dream or a very pleasant hallucination. Definitely what I was looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
