<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3415</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 13:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You notice Puma is always getting the shit beat out of him on LU?

I'm excited for the next season, Puma coming back from the dead is going to be interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 07:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all honesty does it make your sex life like tons better? No pun intended. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to re-roll that entire thing. It needs CDR and CHC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 04:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me uncomfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First book is great and has a lot of mystery too it and then the rest feel like fan fiction written by the author's child who had a vague idea what the book was about. 

The first book has a few mysteries but the second is like "HOLY FUCK WHATS THAT" every two pages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's prepare the "Lol things are more expensive in Australia!" 

Fuck off cunt, at your minimum wage you could buy your game than I could buy one in my country for less at my minimum wage. 

If you even out our minimum wages you're making more in Aussie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't like the film very much.

It doesn't explain anything and has a really weird rapey vibe to it. 

The first scene in the movie is the main character complaining how they didn't leave a woman alive for him to rape as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 12:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MMO's and Story Immersion really don't go well together. 

Most MMO's will be quest-hub fests because that is the design of an MMO. You want engaging you're better off playing a SP RPG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 12:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're waiting for an animation to finish at that point. I can see where /u/WarmBagels is coming from. At some point immersion does have t take a back seat to game play otherwise it's not much of a game is it?

In grinding MMO's it would just be inconvenient to have to wait for NPC's to drop in or spawn in a special way. Most players just want their kills so they can move onto farming the next area.

Changing a spawn animation CAN be a QoL improvement especially if you're cutting down on the over all time a player has to spend grinding in an area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 12:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That has to be on of the most click baity trashiest websites I've ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 05:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm...it could possibly be an anti-virus or program related issue. 

Try seeing if it may be an exterior program running that is effecting the game. I know Nvidia Shadowplay used to make me lag all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One is worth money to the restaurant the other isn't.

If you and I are out to lunch and the bill is $20 and I say, "I don't have ten, but I do have this 50% coupon! It'll be like I paid my half."

You're going to spend ten either way if we had meals that were even/close in value. Are you upset that I'm not spending money when I don't have to? 

Going somewhere cheaper and having a coupon are not the same thing. One has actual value one just has a value difference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of people can tell me I'm wrong but it doesn't change my opinion.

If a friend has a physical coupon worth a certain amount and it would cover/more than cover their portion if they were going to use cash anyways why not use it?

It's not like they are making you pay more they just aren't paying anything because bam coupon. That's frugality not cheapness. If they expect you to cover more than their fair share the coupon doesn't cover then that is pushing it and being cheap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> US here, https://www.retailmenot.com/view/dominos.com

No such coupons for us.  Also these coupons aren't always legit...see the success rates? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, if you had a physical coupon though like my original post suggest then I would.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on the US vouchers are normally special coupons that are priced higher and typically only handed out as special promotions by companies. 

I don't know anywhere I could easily find such a great coupon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please link me to a legit voucher code for that much. I can't find them would love to see where these great deals are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would because your discount cares for your half of the meal assuming we are splitting the meal as with a pizza. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A 40% coupon and a split between two people is more than fair. I fail to see how him saving you nearly half the cost of your pizza wouldn't justify him having a few slices. Coupons are treated like money by the business as well so in the eyes of the business they would be paying their share.

If we were hanging out and I said dude you got five bucks I got this five dollar off coupon we could split a large two topping you would be upset if I didn't have actual cash instead? If you feel this way your being real petty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? With that large of a discount using it as payment is well justified. Only an fool would turn down a 40% discount of pizza. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A large pizza around where I am is about ten dollars. You say house mates so I'm assuming there are at least three of you. If his coupon covered 30% of the pizza then it would be more than fair for him to use the coupon as payment. Would you rather pay the same price and have him not use his coupon? 

You sound like an ungrateful and condescending turd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom would do this in a heart beat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cousin's big fat dark areola when we were teens. She flashed me and I've had a thing for girls with fat saggy boobs and big ol' saucers for nipples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 13:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of internet are you using?

Are you wi-fi or direct cable? 

I get micro-stuttering from time to time because my computer is connected to Wi-Fi and sometimes it just doesn't work as well. Sun spots and all that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 13:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is in fact no difference between magic truffles and magic mushrooms. They are parts of one and the same organism. Sometimes it is said sclerotia contained a higher amount of active compounds than a fruiting body. Until today, this statement is scientifically not proven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 22:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can be cheap but jump scares have their place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 21:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if Young Metallica would hate Old Metallica. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 20:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where in China is this? 

Every time I've seen pictures of major cities they are always really busy and busseling with tons of people. Is this a more private neighborhood or city? Where are all the cars for driving on these hugs roads?

Video just seems real empty compared to all the other footage I've ever seen of China.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 20:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given what a hard on China has for censorship that would make sense. There is probably a whole lot we don't see because they feel it would ruin the countries image.

Really wish the whole world could get past the high school mentality and act like adults... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 20:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it's not. 

Fill up your inventory with Rares and click salvage all, takes one second to get all of them. 

Fill up your inventory with Legends and you need at least half a second to delete each one. I can click and hit return pretty fast but it's always going to be slower than an all button. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 20:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who said two buttons? Just have a salvage all button and make sure to remove the ones you want from your inventory. 

Or maybe we could get a favorites button and an auto-sorting button like ALL the other ARPG's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 19:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A warning window won't save you from that, he could of just as easily done the two click and been away with it. It's his own fault.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 19:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do, it's real easy for me to do a quick mouse over of my inventory and see what I'm keeping and what I'm not. 

After I get going I'll find myself with big inventories of legends only looking for ancients and everything else is instant trash. A salvage all button would be nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 19:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We used to have to salvage all items one at a time and it didn't require us to also hit enter. I think OP brings up a good point, especially for people who at this point are only farming for Ancients/Primals. 

On T13 you can rack up a whole lot of legends so I could see why someone would want a salvage all button for the legendaries too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 14:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope but your system sound will stutter for sure lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 14:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you've cleared GR70 with a Whirlwind Barb then you're good to go for quick-farming mats to build other characters. 

You could literally have any other class geared and ready for T40+ easy in just a few hours play doing nothing but collecting blood shards and then gambling them on a fresh character.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 13:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8====D~~~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
