<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3097</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes exactly And she basically volunteered two episodes ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but the difference is that people know about the Nazis, heck a whole channel( History Channel) broadcast are basically looking at the Nazis from different viewpoints  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm I the only one waiting for Tomoe (book shop beauty) to be drawn by Sagiri? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think an adult exposing themselves to a 12vyear old would still be pretty illegal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Japan's Imperialist (especially the war crimes) not as "publicised" as it should be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 07:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everybody,

I wanted to ask, why isn't Japan's past as well known to general public as say Nazi Germany and Fascist Italy? 

Most people I talk to seem amazed when I try to highlight the fact that Japan has not only a "victim" of WW2 but also one of the main aggressors both before and during the conflict.

This comes as a surprise considering acts which are just as  horrible were committed in Japan's Imperialist campaigns over a longer period of time than the other regimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 06:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll just add my two cents here, since you don't even have to be informed on anything to post on here.

1) OP from the review certainly went overboard in most in not all aspects, but I think it's safe to say that based on the Manga so far, the Author does at least like the  idea of a strong military state with a possible outlook on colonisation. 

2) The fact people even think that Imperialism, Colonisation and "Military" past are things to be celebrated makes me kinda incredulous. Sure it's fun to hear how great commanders "annexed territories after great battles" but I think *state condoned pillaging, raping, brutalisation, murder and many times enslavement of the new populace* describe the aftermath more accurately. 





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Odd but not wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 07:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this is sacred geometry as you claim, why mix it with something as profane as a fictional jolly Roger? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 07:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why be so heated though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 17:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yuiyui and Hyoizaburo would be so proud of this meme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I put on my glasses while talking to somebody </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 16:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is weirdly sexual </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 16:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of that Gear 4th drawing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 06:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe either one between 24 and 25 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Fate/Stay Night] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 04:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
