<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An interesting look at how, although the Germans were Christians too, American media (particularly Stars and Stripes, the newspaper for the military) affirmed that America's cause was Christ's cause.  It reminds me of Bob Dylan's song,  [With God On Our Side](https://bobdylan.com/songs/god-our-side/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Christian imagery was used to shape American perceptions of World War I, during and after the conflict </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 01:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I was thinking of! But I think by the time I go buy a ticket, I won't have saved any time off of taking the T.  Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the MASCO shuttle check ID? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 00:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I work in Central Square and have a doctor's appointment at BIDMC.  I thought I had read somewhere that anyone can take the MASCO LMA shuttle, but it seems from their website that only employees and students can.  But do they check ID? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, I would add that in both Croatia and Bosnia, Serbia cooperated with the ethnic Serb forces.  So they didn't have any natural allies in Macedonia.  And unlike Kosovo, they didn't view it as historically part of Serbia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, huge numbers went to Brazil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Obamacare Is Repealed, Could Mass. Fall Back On State Law? It Wouldn't Be Easy [From February but still applies] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a good story explaining what happens: http://www.wbur.org/commonhealth/2017/02/07/obamacare-repeal-massachusetts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mirror surface has to match the ideal, nearly parabolic surface to about 25 nanometersabout 3 ten-thousandths of the width of a human hair. Thats really, really smooth; if the mirror were scaled up to the size of North America, the tallest mountain would be one inch high and the deepest canyon would be one inch low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL scientists are building a telescope with mirrors that are 8.4 meters across but less than 25 nanometers of deviation from a perfect parabolic curve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Though the language itself was race-neutral, like many of the rights set forth in the Constitution, the patent system didnt apply for black Americans born into slavery. Slaves were not considered American citizens and laws at the time prevented them from applying for or holding property, including patents. In 1857, the U.S. commissioner of patents officially ruled that slave inventions couldnt be patented.

And what's really sick is that the slave-owners took credit and sometimes even advertised this fact:
 His slave master, Oscar Stewart, attempted to patent the invention. Because Stewart was not the actual inventor, and because the actual inventor was born into slavery, the application was rejected.

 Stewart ultimately began selling the cotton scraper without the benefit of patent protection and made a significant amount of money doing so. In his advertisements, he openly touted that the product was the invention of a Negro slave  thus giving the lie to the abolition cry that slavery dwarfs the mind of the Negro. When did a free Negro ever invent anything?



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL slaves in America, as property themselves, weren't allowed to get patents on their inventions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yipes, these things travel:
 studies conducted near the Mario Zucchelli and McMurdo   Scott research bases confirmed that chemicals in personal care products were even present in Antarctic seawater. Those reports identified the presence of plasticizers, antibacterials, preservatives, sunscreens and fragrances in the Antarctic marine environment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a new generation of water pollutants in your medicine cabinet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought this would be of interest to people liking history - I'm planning to visit Philadelphia to see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Revolutionary War Museum Aims To Illuminate The Past </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Since the ESA was enacted, the list of threatened and endangered species has grown to more than 1,600 U.S. plant and animal species. During the same period, the U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service (FWS) and National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA) have declared 47 species recovered. Twenty-nine of these recoveries occurred during the Obama presidency. Among the recovered species are some of our nations most iconic wildlife, from brown pelicans and gray whales to American alligators, Louisiana black bears and bald eagles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL 1600 animals and plants in the US have been protected under the Endangered Species Act but only 47 have thrived enough to be taken off the list, including bald eagles and black bears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Realistically, how close are we to melding mind and machine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [News][Link] Why losing a dog can be harder than losing a relative or friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A review of scientific studies on the dog-person bond.
 When people who have never had a dog see their dog-owning friends mourn the loss of a pet, they probably think its all a bit of an overreaction; after all, its just a dog.
 
 However, those who have loved a dog know the truth: Your own pet is never just a dog.
 
 Many times, Ive had friends guiltily confide to me that they grieved more over the loss of a dog than over the loss of friends or relatives. Research has confirmed that for most people, the loss of a dog is, in almost every way, comparable to the loss of a human loved one.

https://theconversation.com/why-losing-a-dog-can-be-harder-than-losing-a-relative-or-friend-68207 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And how many read it?  I certainly hope you did.  As a non-doctor, it was incredibly useful for shaping my thinking and behavior with my father. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Pope Francis need to rethink improvisational management? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Classic maneuver of the middling-manager: lower the bar on where you're starting out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ICA Plans To Expand Across The Harbor And Into East Bostons Industrial Shipyard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> H-1B Visas: Stealing American Jobs Or A Solution To A Tech Shortage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ### Submission Statement
An archaeologist explains how during the Enlightenment, scientists decided that empirical data would be how you evaluate 'alternative facts', instead of the appeal to the authority (of God, the king, or the ancients).  This evidence-based approach has also been challenged by post-modernism, which claims that all facts are subjective (so if Trump's view of his inauguration crowd is that it was the largest ever, that is true).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Science is about seeking truth among 'alternative facts' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
