<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2472</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's why I like her show as well. CNN programming, with their panels of 5 or 7 guests, are worthless if you're looking for meaningful discussions and broader look at the story beyond the headline.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MSNBC Viewership Surges Amid Trump Chaos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MSNBC Viewership Surges Amid Trump Chaos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the video of that [close encounter](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l6P2hyZyBlY)!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 21:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are they releasing it like that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 21:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good catch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  After Trump's election I've asked myself, "How can House of Cards compete with a reality this full of twists and turns?"


And after the first 100 days of non-stop insanity it's fair to say that we're living in a hyper HoC reality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless of the changes they made, both Bryan Fuller and John Van Citters the Vice President at CBS Consumer Products confirmed that the series will be set in the prime timeline.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Of Cards Star Robin Wright Says Trump Stole All Of Our Ideas For Season 6 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prime universe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Trek: Discovery First-Look Trailer Analysis With Screencaps And GIFs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   But with the White House in crisis mode, and Fox sometimes downplaying the seriousness of the situation, channel surfers are opting for MSNBC and CNN instead. So far this week, Fox has ranked No. 3 in prime time behind both CNN and MSNBC, which almost never happens.


 On Monday night, after the Washington Post broke the news that Trump shared highly classified information with Russian officials, MSNBC was No. 1 with an average of 662,000 "demo" viewers during prime time. CNN averaged 608,000 and Fox averaged 499,000. 

  On Tuesday night, after The New York Times reported the allegation that Trump asked Comey to end the FBI investigation into former National Security Advisor Michael Flynn, CNN was No. 1 with an average of 719,000 "demo" viewers in prime time. MSNBC averaged 650,000 and Fox averaged 539,000.


 Nicole Hemmer, who recently wrote a book about conservative media, "Messengers of the Right," said Fox's "inattention to the breaking news of the day was startling" on Tuesday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News losing out in prime time ratings race amid Trump turmoil: So far this week, Fox has ranked No. 3 in prime time behind both CNN and MSNBC, which almost never happens. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 01:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 23:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks different for sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 23:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Trailer - All regions](https://streamable.com/pmp54)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Trailer For Star Trek: Discovery, Season Extended To 15 Episodes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 23:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CBS Upfront Presentation 2017 Live Blog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 22:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, looks like we're getting mixed messages! Well, we will find out very soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a small clip according to [ CBS CEO Leslie Moonves](http://trekmovie.com/2017/05/17/breaking-first-image-from-star-trek-discovery/):


 you will see the first clip of Star Trek today. So we are ready to show you something. Its a small clip, but I think it is really impressive and we are really proud of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck McCain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secretary of State Rex Tillerson: 'I would have no way to know' if Russians bugged the Oval Office during President Trump's meeting with Russia's foreign minister and ambassador last week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a whiny little bitch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who Can Really Impeach President Trump? Fox News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fox News is a clear and present danger to the Republic. As long as they keep misleading the GOP base about basic facts, we will not see any meaningful actions from the Republican Congress.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 17:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So by prequel they actually meant that it took place a long time ago in a galaxy far, far away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 17:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So by prequel they actually meant that it took place a long time ago in a galaxy far, far away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Star Trek: Discovery' Reveals First Photo of Two Cast Members </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 16:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What last weeks Oval Office lovefest with the Russians demonstrated was that the adults are not, in fact, in charge: a 70-year-old man-baby named Donald Trump is. There are just too many ways in which the presidentany president, but especially this oneis beyond the restraints of those who serve him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Grownups Wont Save Us From Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry but he literally wrote a book about speaking truth to power and yet he lied to the American people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has lost all credibility with his "I was in the room. It didn't happen." bullshit statement yesterday and the performance at the WH press briefing today. 


Edit: Politico review of H.R. McMaster's book 'Dereliction of Duty'


 McMaster's takeaways: **Don't lie, don't blame the media, don't rely on an inner circle**


 Lt. Gen. H.R. McMaster, the president's new national security adviser, knows a thing or two about standing up to the commander in chief and his political confidantes  and the potentially disastrous consequences when you don't. He literally wrote the book on it. 

 "**The president was lying, and he expected the Chiefs to lie as well or, at least, to withhold the whole truth,**" McMaster wrote in the epilogue of "Dereliction of Duty." "**Although the president should not have placed the Chiefs in that position, the flag officers should not have tolerated it when they had.**" 

 "The disaster in Vietnam was not the result of impersonal forces but a uniquely human failure, the responsibility for which was shared by President Johnson and his principal military and civilian advisers," McMaster wrote.


 "**The failings were many and reinforcing: arrogance, weakness, lying in pursuit of self-interest, and above all, the abdication of responsibility to the American people.**" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I can tell you I have started shooting and it is absurdly cool. I feel like a five-year-old when I say those known words from the past that you have seen in shows. Anything I tell you would just ruin it for you.


 I think its out in the public domain that it is Star Trek, but not as we know it. Theyve changed a bunch of stuff in it. Its a new and yet familiar experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jason Isaacs: Star Trek: Discovery Is New, Yet Familiar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> H. R. McMaster: I was in the room. It didn't happen. LOOOOOOOOOOOOOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Frame Of Mind' - season 6 episode 21 or 'The Pegasus' - season 7 episode 12. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deputy Press Secretary Sarah Huckabee Sanders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched Dershowitz on CNN the past couple hours and while he was freaking out over the potential ISIS attack; he kept downplaying the Russia connections. As well as interrupting other guests to say dumb things like "Comey affair now in the wastebasket of history"; forget about the RussiaGate and just focus on this one issue! And ranting about leaks from the The Washington Post!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the orange buffoon said to his handler, can you believe the world we live in today? Isnt it crazy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [And yelling at each other!](https://twitter.com/Carrasquillo/status/864262056849092608)

 WH comms staffers just put the TVs on super loud after we could hear yelling coming from room w/ Bannon, Spicer, Sanders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A former senior Defense Department official in the George W. Bush administration emailed, simply, "WTF!!!!!!!"


 "If it were anybody but the Russians you'd think it's sort of juvenile, he's trying to impress them...but because it's the Russians, you've gotta wonder, is this a deliverable? Is he reporting to his case officer?" the same official said in a phone interview. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's handling of classified info brings new chaos to White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 01:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Orville - Official Trailer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yy9sKeCE8V0 t=11s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 00:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Eliot A Cohen](https://twitter.com/EliotACohen/status/864230521093730304); former Counselor of the Department of State.


 This is appalling. If accidental, it would be a firing offense for anyone else. If deliberate, it would be treason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 00:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The tweet](https://twitter.com/SpeakerRyan/status/751106162574053376):


 Individuals who are "extremely careless" with classified information should be denied further access to such info. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 23:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I get great intel. I have people brief me on great intel every day

What a fucking moron.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 23:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't think so. According to the original report by [Huffington Post](http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/lawrence-odonnell-msnbc-future_us_59162d8ce4b00f308cf5534a), "Four well-placed sources tell HuffPost that MSNBC has not been in contact with ODonnells team of representatives to negotiate a new deal." So it looks like MSNBC is the one dragging the feet in this matter. 



Then you have [ODonnell tweeting](https://twitter.com/Lawrence/status/863135251530252288) this on Friday:


 Last night @maddow was #1 rated show in all of cable tv, not just cable news. @TheLastWord was #2. Thanks for your support. We need it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 22:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rubicon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 22:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The forgotten *rich* men and women of our country will be forgotten no longer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 22:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NBC News chairman Andy Lack is an idiot. Lawrence ODonnell's 'The Last Word' is the second-highest rated show on MSNBC and Lack wants to replace ODonnell? Are you kidding me?


Rather than hiring people like Greta Van Susteren, he should bring back Keith Olbermann </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 22:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump keeps breaking all time records bigly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Fox News turned into the official American Pravda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was always ridiculous and most recently Fox News turned into the official American Pravda.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yellowstone is the first scripted drama series greenlighted by Paramount Network, Viacoms new general entertainment network and leading scripted brand, which will replace Spike in early 2018, The 10-episode series is slated to go into production in the fall for premiere on the network in summer 2018.


 The project marks Oscar winner Costners first major return to television in five years following his starring role in History miniseries Hatfield   McCoys, which earned him an Emmy, Golden Globe and SAG award.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kevin Costner is set as the lead in 'Yellowstone' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what will happen when Trump replaces Mattis with someone like Flynn?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 16:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. Which polls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 16:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ODonnell, who has been appearing on the network since its inception, has hosted his highly rated program since the fall of 2010. The Last Word is the cable networks second-highest rated program, according to Nielsen figures, behind only The Rachel Maddow Show. ODonnell has even been, on some nights, besting Sean Hannitys program on Fox News among viewers ages 18 to 49, the demographic that television advertisers care about the most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 16:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lannisters wannabe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 21:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No posters of Ivanka, [one of the great beauties of the world, according to everybody.?](http://www.politicususa.com/2016/10/08/grotesque-history-donald-trumps-sexual-comments-daughter.html)

Come on, there should be at least dozen posters of voluptuous Ivanka, I mean [shes tall, shes almost 6 feet tall and shes been, shes an amazing beauty.](http://www.politicususa.com/2016/10/08/grotesque-history-donald-trumps-sexual-comments-daughter.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 21:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [CBS Upfront Presentation](http://deadline.com/2017/05/tv-upfronts-2017-schedule-parties-lineup-presentations-1202092767/): **Wednesday, May 17 at 4:00pm EST** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 21:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they're all astronauts on... some kind of star trek.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 18:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Americans can't assume that the system will work. It will take immense political pressure on legislators in the coming weeks to make certain that our leaders use every mechanism available to discover and prevent abuse of power and to ensure the health of our democracy for future generations.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 18:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, your ball is looking at the wrong time! You should have seen naked Orion green girls instead.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 17:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would anyone believes a pathological liar like Trump? 


Democrats should stop giving him the benefit of the the doubt and act accordingly.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 17:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ted Sullivan is a writer, my bad.

It seems that he has taken on multiple roles. Beside writing, both TrekCore and Trekmovie are describing him as Supervising Producer   mentioned his heavy involvement in producing the second episode of 'Star Trek: Discovery'.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 16:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What else did you see in your crystal ball? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 02:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even close. Anyone waiting on the GOP to act is delusional.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 25 Best Sci-Fi Films of the 90s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 00:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV Ratings: MSNBC, Maddow Scoring Huge Wins With Comey Coverage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 00:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV Ratings: MSNBC, Maddow Scoring Huge Wins With Comey Coverage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 00:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 23:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paramount was already working on an 11th Trek movie titled ['Star Trek: The Beginning'](http://memory-alpha.wikia.com/wiki/Star_Trek:_The_Beginning) from a script by Erik Jendresen. But [the change in leadership at Paramount](https://www.trektoday.com/news/160406_01.shtml) led to the cancellation of the project.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 22:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this time they will find 18 *hours* missing from the Trump tapes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'SWAT,' 'SEAL Team,' 'Instinct,' 'Wisdom of the Crowd,' '9JKL,' 'Me, Myself and I' Score CBS Series Orders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 20:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 20:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "This morning, the president tweeted a thinly veiled threat to Mr. Comey, which could be construed as threatening a witness in this investigation, which is another violation of federal law," Durbin said. "To preserve his reputation as a credible prosecutor, Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein must appoint an independent special prosecutor to pursue possible criminal charges, or he must resign." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Durbin: Rosenstein should resign if he won't appoint a special prosecutor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 20:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 19:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 19:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be Fox News from Earth 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 18:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just seen it now at the bottom of the page, will delete this submission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 18:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't mind reading subtitles then check out the French series Engrenages aka Spiral.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ursula K. Le Guins 'Left Hand of Darkness' is being developed as a limited series </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump and his GOP enablers are turning America into a banana republic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 01:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That only shows the limit of your own imagination. 

Netflix is currently producing Altered Carbon a new science fiction series set in the *25th century*. A world where humans can store their minds to cortical stacks and regularly updated it via needlecast, then download their minds to new bodies if they can afford it. 


That's just one aspect of that future world that we will see in the upcoming show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 22:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut up, Wesley. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 22:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And with that I'd just like to add that Mr. Trump has my full support and I will be voting yes on any of his proposals before Congress.


Ha! All the way to the end of the republic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 22:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John McCain's former chief of staff says the security of America 'might now depend on electing a Democratic Congress' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 22:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 21:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Deputy White House Press Secretary Sarah Huckabee Sanders told reporters she did not understand why it is so complicated for them that Donald Trump this week fired the FBI director overseeing an investigation into possible Trump campaign collusion with Russian agents trying to impact the election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sarah Huckabee Sanders Blames Press For Making FBI Director Firing So Complicated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 21:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 17:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the media will admit the fact that the President is MAD? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 00:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been reported by Variety. They don't tend to publish unsubstantiated rumors, so that's good enough for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Valor Military Drama Pilot Picked Up To Series By the CW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 00:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ridley Scott Now Says There May Only Be Two More Alien Sequels; Talks Prometheus Shortcomings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 23:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 23:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing, not even a sex video of him banging Ivanka.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 23:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He [retweeted the news story](https://twitter.com/karlurban), I sure hope he will be cast as the Judge.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 23:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walk with the Prophets, my friend and watch the story of the Emissary in a non-linear order.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Foreign Minister And Trump Agree: No Need To Probe Election Meddling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 23:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 23:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it makes perfect sense. Also the results fit with polls that were conducted by the official Star Trek website: 


 [**POLL: Fans Most-Watched Star Trek Series Is...**](http://www.startrek.com/article/poll-fans-most-watched-star-trek-series-is) 

 Which series have you watched the most? More than 25,000 people voted, and the results are pretty surprising; not so much in terms of which series won  thatd be TNG -- but the fact that Voyager beat out TOS for second place. 

* The Next Generation  43%

* Voyager  20%

* The Original Series  19%

* Deep Space Nine  13%

* Enterprise  5%

* The Animated Series  0%



Other recent polls show that the majority of active ST fans are mostly TNG   its sister shows:

[Which series is the best for a new fan?](http://www.startrek.com/polls)

* The Next Generation 51% - 2342

* The Original Series 23% - 1071
    
* Voyager 11% - 501

* Enterprise 8% - 372    

* Deep Space Nine 7% - 324 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 22:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you read more news stories about The OA, a show that has been released for months and already renewed for a second season, than about Star Trek: Discovery? wow, Im shocked, shocked I tell ya! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 21:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walton Goggins has joined the cast of 'Maze Runner: The Death Cure' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [First official poster.](http://cdn.collider.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/judge-dredd-mega-city-one-tv-show-poster.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 19:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, Star Trek is not an obscure little show like 'The OA'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Live-Action Judge Dredd TV Series Planned: Titled Judge Dredd: Mega City One, the announcement comes as the character celebrates his 40th anniversary this year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 19:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't care about Fox, they're state media, but I hope that Lester Holt will ask him REAL QUESTIONS for once.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like a month before the release but there are some exceptions.

Netflix released a teaser trailer for 'The Defenders' in April, 4 months before the release date of the miniseries on August 18, 2017. 

And the full official trailer was released on May 3rd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Your question looks very funny for me.

Looks like Lavrov got his talking point from his boss.

[Politico](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/05/10/sergey-lavrov-jokes-james-comey-fired-238205?lo=ap_b2)
 Russian Foreign Minister Sergey Lavrov sarcastically acted surprised Wednesday when asked a question about the firing of FBI Director James Comey during a visit to Washington.

 Was he fired? Youre kidding, youre kidding,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They must be really happy with their puppet at the WH.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian foreign minister jokes about Comey: 'Was he fired? Youre kidding' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview: Chief OBrien at Work Creator Jon Adams On Chronicling The Ennui Of A Transporter Operator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A Senate Judiciary Committee hearing ended abruptly Wednesday morning after word spread that Senate Democrats were planning a slowdown of committee business.
 
 Sen. Dianne Feinstein (D-Calif.), the ranking Democrat on the Senate Judiciary Committee, planned to shut down a confirmation hearing in retaliation for President Trump's abrupt firing of FBI Director James Comey Tuesday.
 
 About an hour into the hearing, though, Chairman Chuck Grassley (R-Iowa) suddenly adjourned the hearing before Democrats could carry out the plan.


Fuck Grassley and fuck the GOP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate hearing adjourned to avoid Dem shutdown over Comey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stranger Things: Shawn Levy Says Some Season 2 Ideas Are Being Held for Season 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you aware that Star Trek: Discovery is a very expensive show? 


[It's going to cost between $6-7 million per episode](http://variety.com/2016/tv/news/bryan-fuller-showrunner-star-trek-discovery-cbs-1201901398/), that's close to 'Game of Thrones' cost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's far more important that they concentrate their effort on the product itself than on advertising it.


What would be the point of making a great show only for the show to fail to reach audience for lack of promotions? 

Thats why they have marketing department in the first place, to take care of advertisings while the production team works on the show itself.


 Or does anyone really remember (or care) what the marketing for DS9 was prior to airing The emissary? Most people don't.

Unfortunately were not in the 90s anymore. Its a different world now; most upcoming shows reach out to new audiences not just via TV ads like in the 90s but through social media as well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure but were they hired for being British or because of their talents?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Avatar' Sequels Cast Cliff Curtis in Lead Role </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martin Scorseses The Irishman Begins Shooting This August for 2019 Release </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm familiar with Jason Isaacs and his excellent body of work; and I believe that he's a great addition to the show. However, I don't see the relevance of his British nationality to the quality of the show.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Star Trek is an established franchise and the *producers should know what works and what doesnt*


Says who? 


 The USS Discovery has a British captain

What?


The "5 reasons" make no sense whatsoever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the end of VHS took the movie rental window with it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 8 Years Ago 'Star Trek' Restarted A Franchise: The 11th film in the franchise came six years and five months after 'Star Trek: Nemesis' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  When Mattel's Barbie dolls were introduced in 1960, Weston realized boys were an untapped market for the doll industry after noting that many of them played with Ken dolls. He conceived of the idea of a military action figure and in 1963 sold what would become G.I. Joe to Hasbro. The runaway hit would go on to be one of the most enduring toy lines in history, spawning hit TV shows and films as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stanley Weston, G.I. Joe Inventor, Dies at 84 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peter F. Hamilton's books 'The Night's Dawn' trilogy or the  Commonwealth series. The books are full of wonder, space warfare  and explorations of alien regions/artifacts in space. 

Fair warning, the books are very long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many news coming out today, it's flood day or what?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm relieved as well that Denis Villeneuve is directing BR 2049.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Blade Runner 2049' - Official Trailer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ['Blade Runner 2049' - Official Trailer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gCcx85zbxz4)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Blade Runner 2049' - Official Trailer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Former President Obama warned Donald Trump against hiring Mike Flynn as his national security adviser, three former Obama administration officials tell NBC News.


 The warning, which has not been previously reported, came less than 48 hours after the November election when the two sat down for a 90-minute conversation in the Oval Office. [...] According to all three former officials, Obama warned Trump against hiring Flynn. The Obama administration fired Flynn in 2014 from his position as head of the Defense Intelligence Agency, largely because of mismanagement and temperament issues.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Alien: Covenant': What the Critics Are Saying - The film is winning plaudits for its back-to-basics space scares approach. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it is not just France, other EU countries learned from our mistake.


[Politico Europe](http://www.politico.eu/article/merci-for-nothing-donald/):

 The French arent the only Europeans in recent months to reject the nuclear option in the wake of the U.S. election. In both Austria and the Netherlands, voters turned out in droves to head off a populist surge and elect liberal candidates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A great day for western democracy. And a very sad day for Russia, Wikileaks and their associates.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For people pointing to "Author claims" in the headline and screaming that it's just "hearsay" and there is no proof of Russian funding whatsoever.

 

[Donald Trump Jr. in 2008](http://www.eturbonews.com/5008/executive-talk-donald-trump-jr-bullish-russia-and-few-emerging-ma):


 If he were to choose his top A-list for investments in the emerging world, Trump said his firm would choose China and Russia. Given what Ive seen in Russias real estate market as of late relative to some of the emerging markets, the country seems to have a lot more natural strength, especially in the high-end sector where people focus on price per square-meter, he said.


 **In Russia, I really prefer Moscow over all cities in the world. Unlike other countries in the world, this country has five major cities where people would at least be happy being close to living in the metro.**


 In Russia, if one has made money anywhere in the country, you would want your place in Moscow.


 And in terms of high-end product influx into the US, **Russians make up a pretty disproportionate cross-section of a lot of our assets; say in Dubai, and certainly with our project in SoHo and anywhere in New York. We see a lot of money pouring in from Russia.** Theres indeed a lot of money coming for new-builds and resale reflecting a trend in the Russian economy and, of course, the weak dollar versus the ruble, he said.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that I think about it, perhaps they are going to follow 'The Godfather part II' example, with parallel plot lines in two different timelines.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who came up with that title, a 3rd grade studio executive?

Edit:

 As for that story that Limans so excited about, he previously told us that the film is actually a sequel thats a prequel, noting his intention to upend how people look at sequels in the first place


A sequel that's actually a prequel? Well, can't wait to figure out what the heck he means by that.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Donald Trump Jr. in 2008](http://www.eturbonews.com/5008/executive-talk-donald-trump-jr-bullish-russia-and-few-emerging-ma):


 If he were to choose his top A-list for investments in the emerging world, Trump said his firm would choose China and Russia. Given what Ive seen in Russias real estate market as of late relative to some of the emerging markets, the country seems to have a lot more natural strength, especially in the high-end sector where people focus on price per square-meter, he said.


 In Russia, I really prefer Moscow over all cities in the world. Unlike other countries in the world, this country has five major cities where people would at least be happy being close to living in the metro.


 In Russia, if one has made money anywhere in the country, you would want your place in Moscow.


 And in terms of high-end product influx into the US, **Russians make up a pretty disproportionate cross-section of a lot of our assets; say in Dubai, and certainly with our project in SoHo and anywhere in New York. We see a lot of money pouring in from Russia.** Theres indeed a lot of money coming for new-builds and resale reflecting a trend in the Russian economy and, of course, the weak dollar versus the ruble, he said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Donald Trump Jr. in 2008](http://www.eturbonews.com/5008/executive-talk-donald-trump-jr-bullish-russia-and-few-emerging-ma):


 If he were to choose his top A-list for investments in the emerging world, Trump said his firm would choose China and Russia. Given what Ive seen in Russias real estate market as of late relative to some of the emerging markets, the country seems to have a lot more natural strength, especially in the high-end sector where people focus on price per square-meter, he said.


 In Russia, I really prefer Moscow over all cities in the world. Unlike other countries in the world, this country has five major cities where people would at least be happy being close to living in the metro.


 In Russia, if one has made money anywhere in the country, you would want your place in Moscow.


 And in terms of high-end product influx into the US, **Russians make up a pretty disproportionate cross-section of a lot of our assets; say in Dubai, and certainly with our project in SoHo and anywhere in New York. We see a lot of money pouring in from Russia.** Theres indeed a lot of money coming for new-builds and resale reflecting a trend in the Russian economy and, of course, the weak dollar versus the ruble, he said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know, given the last election it seems that voters don't care about these stuff as much as they used to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From reading about him he comes off as a jerk but he's combative, ambitious and competent politician. After all Emanuel is the one that delivered the House to the Democrats in 2006.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rahm Emanuel should run for the presidency in 2020.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that's Chris Obi. He plays TKuvma, a Klingon leader.


Edit: [Actors pictured in the photo](http://trekmovie.com/2017/03/21/first-group-photo-of-star-trek-discovery-taken-at-james-frains-birthday-celebration/):  

 Going from left to right we can see Jason Isaacs (Captain Lorca of the U.S.S. Discovery), Michelle Yeoh (Captain Georgiou of the U.S.S. Shenzhou), Chris Obi (Klingon leader TKuvma), lead actor Sonequa Martin-Green (Lt. Cmdr. Michael Burnham of the Discovery) and her husband Kenric, Doug Jones (Lieutenant Saru, Science Officer on the Discovery), James Frain (Sarek), and Shazad Latif (Kol, Klingon protege to TKuvma). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We do, I'm 37 and we happen to be in the right demo as well, the 18-49 demo aka the holy grail of Nielsen ratings! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, they are going for a younger demo. And Moonves hinted that ['Star Trek: Discovery' will be an action oriented show](http://trekmovie.com/2017/05/03/star-trek-discovery-back-on-for-fall-cbs-ceo-talks-netflix-importance/):


 When asked specifically about how international sales influenced decisions for original content for CBS All Access, Moonves contrasted the two shows that have been announced for the platform (The Good Fight and Star Trek: Discovery):

 "You know that a Star Trek will travel. You know a The Good Wife [spin-off] might not do nearly as well. It is much more of an American show. There is much more talking involved as opposed to action-adventure. So [international sales] does affect your decisions, but not exclusively." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  that depends on how old the average CBS viewer is.



[About 59!](http://www.thewrap.com/cbs-network-courts-young-viewers/)

 While CBS wont release any numbers yet, Debevoise said, the overwhelming majority [Of CBS All Access subscribers] fall in the 18-49 demo. Our viewers [on CBS All Access] are skewing younger than even the audience that we already have [on CBS.com], he said. On average, our viewers watch twice as much content as our typical CBS.com or CBS app users.


 **While CBS has more viewers than all the other networks, it also has the oldest. CBSs median age is 59.9, highest among all network broadcasters.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  CBS also revealed some demographics for All Access, saying that subscribers were evenly split between men and women and averaged about 20 years younger than regular CBS television viewers. Moonves also predicted Star Trek will bring us even younger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moonves: We have already had a couple of 'Star Trek: Discovery' episodes in the can that weve seen. So we are very excited. It will launch later this fall. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yep](http://www.voanews.com/a/reu-prospect-of-offshore-oil-a-mixed-blessing-for-somalia/3586073.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ridley Scott directed both movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> William Shatner Says Hes Ready To Play Kirk Again: Im perfectly fit and ready to put on some makeup The problem I guess is what do you do with an aging captain whose youthful existence is already there?, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A US military member was killed and two others wounded in Somalia when they were attacked while on a mission advising Somali National Army forces, US Africa Command confirmed Friday.
The US service member killed in action was a Navy SEAL, a US defense official told CNN.
 A US military official confirmed that this is the first US service member killed in action in Somalia since 1993, when two Black Hawk helicopters were shot down and 18 American soldiers were killed in the Battle for Mogadishu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Navy SEAL killed in action in Somalia: A US military official confirmed that this is the first US service member killed in action in Somalia since 1993, when two Black Hawk helicopters were shot down and 18 American soldiers were killed in the Battle for Mogadishu. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A US soldier has been killed in Somalia, the first confirmed US combat death there since the disastrous Black Hawk Down incident in 1993.

 The soldier died on Thursday during operations against al-Shabab militants about 40 miles (64km) west of the capital Mogadishu, near the town of Barii, the US military says.

 Two other US servicemen were injured. US forces were on an "advise and assist" mission with the Somali National Army, the US military said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Somalia conflict: US suffers rare combat loss in al-Shabab clash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do we know about the current 'Star Trek: Discovery' showrunners? Are they active on social media like Fuller?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Highly illogical.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actors have been saying "theres no guarantee" for the sequel right after Beyond released? Since when?

After JJ made his announcement about Star Trek 4, they expressed their excitement for the chance to work again with Chris Hemsworth and kept saying that for months. 

Zachary Quinto's comment is echoing what Chris Pine recently told the media about the state of the sequel. And regardless of how you feel about it, his comment is news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must be on a starship traveling close to the speed of light! [The quote](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HlEtooMHeNE feature=youtu.be) is from 9 days ago, not a month. 

 [Not news.](https://www.cinemapolitica.org/sites/www.cinemapolitica.org/files/films/Surviving%20Progress%201%20.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Londo Mollari in 'Babylon 5' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened to the 'Tremors' TV series with Kevin Bacon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The constant delays from January to May and now to "sometime in the near future" are eroding my excitement somewhat for the show.

   

 I really want it to be good. Like the best of TNG meets the big arcs of DS9.

I'd love to see that too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Trek: Discovery Recasts Klingon And Adds Four New Actors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then resign, everyone wins.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says he misses life before he became US president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Famke Janssen Joins Cast Of Michael Caton-Jones Movie Asher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Mist is one of the movies that I tend to re-watch every once in a while. An excellent cast and a great horror/Sci-Fi plot.

There is an upcoming TV series based on the same Stephen King's story. After watching [the trailer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kya_uqiSQOY) it looks like it going to be very different from the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Wag the Dog' TV Series in the Works at HBO: Director Barry Levinson will adapt his 1997 political satire as a comedy for the small screen, with Robert De Niro attached as an exec producer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Wag the Dog' TV Series in the Works at HBO: Director Barry Levinson will adapt his 1997 political satire as a comedy for the small screen, with Robert De Niro attached as an exec producer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a Vulcan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News Jesse Watters Takes Vacation Amid Controversy Over Ivanka Trump Remarks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may want to read his letter about smoking!


[Why I'm Quitting Tobacco](https://youtu.be/Sh6-amWM82Q?t=13)


 For over 25 years we devoted ourselves to peddling a product for which good work is irrelevant, because people cant stop themselves from buying it. A product that never improves, that causes illness, and makes people unhappy. But there was money in it. A lot of money. In fact, our entire business depended on it. We knew it wasnt good for us, but we couldnt stop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Alien: Covenant | Prologue: The Crossing](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XeMVrnYNwus) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Alien: Covenant': The Crossing - Reveals the Fate of Shaw and David Post-Prometheus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ford should have hired Don Draper from Sterling Cooper   Partners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another troll post? 

Dude, if you don't like Star Trek that much then do yourself a favor and stop wasting your time on this sub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  James Cromwell and Star Trek seem to go hand-in-hand. The Oscar-nominated actor is a five-time Star Trek guest star, as he portrayed Prime Minister Nayrok in The Next Generation hour "The Hunted," Jaglom Shrek in the TNG two-parter "Birthright," Minister Hanok in the Deep Space Nine installment "Starship Down" and Zefram Cochrane first in Star Trek: First Contact and again when he turned up, briefly and uncredited, in the Enterprise pilot, Broken Bow. He also appeared, in archive footage, in the Enterprise episode "In a Mirror, Darkly." But the connections dont stop there. His ex-wife, Julie Cobb, guest starred as Yeoman Thompson in the TOS episode "By Any Other Name," while their daughter, Rosemary Morgan, played Piri in "The Chute" episode of Voyager. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Catching Up with 5-Time Trek Guest, James Cromwell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. The original characters (Noah, Audrey, Emma  ...etc.) were the main reason why I continued watching the show. Bring back that cast for a two-hour TV special; give the fans a proper end.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Handmaids Tale: Elisabeth Moss on the Dark Material of Hulus Timely Series - Plus, Moss talks about returning for Season 2 of 'Top of the Lake.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's time to break the glass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, that's why I find it strange to reboot the series without resolving the 2nd season cliffhanger first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M. Night Shyamalan Confirms Sequel for 'Unbreakable' and 'Split': Bruce Willis and Samuel L. Jackson are set to return for 'Glass.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the point of ending season two with a cliffhanger then?


They should finish that storyline first; give us a conclusion and then move on to their new storyline with a new cast.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy to see that Malcolm is back!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'The Thick of It' is a great British series from Armando Iannucci who went on and created 'Veep' for HBO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The series will feature an entirely new cast  which insiders say will be more inclusive as the series looks to put a new spin on a proved concept that has not been embraced on the small screen. [...] A premiere date for Scream and its new cast will be announced at a later date. None of the original stars  including John Karna, Carlson Young, Bex Taylor-Klaus and Amadeus Serafini  are returning. Meanwhile, former Scream leading lady Willa Fitzgerald has already moved on with a key role in Fox's Behind Enemy Lines pilot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Scream': Queen Latifah and New Showrunner Set for Season 3 Overhaul </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Production budget: $185M

Marketing budget: $120M

Total cost: $305M

Box office:  Domestic ($ 158M) + Foreign ($ 184M) = $ 342M </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was offered a small role in the movie and [he turned it down](http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/arnold-schwarzenegger-doesnt-want-a-rematch-predator-991892): 


 They asked me, and I read it, and I didnt like it  whatever they offered," he said. "So Im not going to do that, no. Except if theres a chance that they rewrite it, or make it a more significant role. But the way it is now, no, I wont do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox Delays Red Sparrow and Maze Runner 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I dont know I know that they are working on a script for another one and well see how that all plays out, but the nice thing about that experience is that the time in between those big tentpole films allows us to go off and cultivate a lot of different creative experiences for ourselves  being back on stage, doing independent films Im hopeful that well do another one, but theres no guarantee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zachary Quinto: Theres No Guarantee of Star Trek 4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Private time aka TV watch time.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edward Norton in 'Primal Fear'

Christoph Waltz in 'Inglourious Basterds' 

Ralph Fiennes in 'Quiz Show'

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Predator Release Date Pushed to Summer 2018 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks reminds Trump of time he said 'I love WikiLeaks' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Four 'Avatar' Sequels Will Be Released On December 18, 2020, December 17, 2021, December 20, 2024 and December 19, 2025. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Le Pen has put terrorism, immigration and criticism of the European Union at the center of her campaign. She was spotted in Trump Tower in January and is supported by Russian President Vladimir Putin. Critics of her campaign have accused her of xenophobia, a familiar critique of Trump.


Edit: The Russians are funding [her party](http://time.com/4627780/russia-national-front-marine-le-pen-putin/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
