<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3274</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 22:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the final stage of capitalism, the climax, and seeing how things are going today we might actually live long enough to see the pinacle of this whole thing come to life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember that during my senior year in university my class went on a trip (for group projects, not really vacations, unfortunately), and a friend and I ended up with 3 girls to do the field work, and oh my God...

They were making stupid jokes and laughing all day long, especially by making fun of other people behind their backs. When me and my friend said something (jokingly, we're not dickheads, or at least I like to think so) about them being really puerile comparing them to 5 years old children, they lost their shit and didn't want to talk for the rest of the trip. Pure-bred b*tches, the funny thing being they were mocking other people for their manners and looks, when they weren't especially sophisticated and eye-candies themselves: girl when your face looks like it's putting your body to sleep you have no right to make fun of other people's appearance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 01:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sense comtempt towards the game series in his sentence, the guy is just so salty about his decision to give the rights up to CDPR instead of getting a cut percentage of the franchise profits. I don't blame him, in 2006 nobody could have imagined than almost 10 years later CDPR would release the biggest success of the fiscal year (and the Game of the Year, two years in a row). 

I hope they put enough budget into the TV show, the worst thing they can do to the Witcher is making it cheap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 01:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell fucking yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but they don't have to swing swords and maces all around for several hours on end tho

I'm talking about Knights and professional fighters, not the everyday farmer equipped with rusty plates and blunt blades that was barely able to eat enough everyday.

My point is not to compare the soldiers of today to the swordsmen of the past, it's just to get an idea of the strength required to walk around in chainmail and plate (I didn't see anybody mention the mail in the comments), while having to swing your weapon and not dying.

Fighting a war has changed a lot, I don't see why you would want to compare, that's like putting up a fight between a knight and a prehistoric caveman. My question is not "who would win in a fight", it's about the amount of effort the Knights had to provide to be able to move around in their armors.

About the argument of "we are taller", once again it has nothing to do with the question. I'm talking strength to body ratio, of course the average human got taller, but our muscles are thinner compared to people in the past, even in pictures from the 19th century you notice a difference vs now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 00:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 23:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty cool video, thank you. Apparently most of my opinions about medieval armors were wrong, and now I want one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 23:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a pretty smart explanation concerning the actual weight of an armor, I didn't even think of that. I know bodybuilders are not the best comparison, maybe a strongman would have been better. It's "sad" we'll never know how strong fighters in ancient times were, I see a lot of people here forgetting that most of them were trained from the youngest age to be a fighter, whereas today soldiers and strongmen usually start their intense practice after 18. 

It could be assumed that everyday training in sparring, martial arts and cardio would ultimately have an impact of the physiology and capabilities of a knight/fighter. Not to mention the simple fact about the length of the battles, the ones who survived must have been either really lucky or really strong and resilient dudes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How strong were knights ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I was visiting in a medieval museum this afternoon , I was struck by the size and thickness of medieval chainmails and plate armors (and the size of weapons such as battlehammers and broadswords), and was wondering how strong were the guys wearing and wielding such equipment ?

Were they really really strong or was this is all a sacrifice of combat effectiveness in favor or pure defensive gear ? I know people in ancient times were likely physically stronger than us but hell, even a bodybuilder would struggle moving in all that steel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
