<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1358</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When did humans figure out how many of them actually existed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've all probably seen that graph of population growth over the centuries, and the sudden spike in the 1800s. But when did the world get a realistic, mostly accurate count or estimate of all the people alive at the time. Had the 1 billion mark already been hit? Were people shocked at how high/low the number was?

Edit: I understand that censuses have been a thing for some time now. What I'm asking is when was the WORLD population first known. That includes people in the New World as well as the Old, and everyone in between.

Edit 2: I don't literally mean an exact count of every individual human on the planet, since it's a bit unrealistic. Estimates are what I'm looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Riot Act - My Maria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is not a sandwich. It is an abomination and must be removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toshiba Satellite E45-B4200 won't connect to wireless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had this computer since August 2014, and I've had little to no problems with it up until a couple of months ago. The wireless will randomly drop out immediately upon opening the laptop. It will often remain disabled for long stretches of time, even after restarting, shutting down, and performing hard reboots. Eventually, the wireless will reactivate, and I can use the machine without issue. These deactivations occur randomly, and even closing the laptop for a couple of minutes will result in my losing access.

The ethernet port is functional and I can access the internet using that, but I would prefer to use the wireless.

The operating system is Windows 8.1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Early aircraft flights over Africa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was reading an article on the early attempts of people crossing Africa in airplanes, and it mentioned two South African pilots who were able to pull off a trip from London to Cape Town, albeit with two different aircraft, in 1920. The next attempt that article mentions doesn't occur until nearly 20 years later, in 1936. Did nobody else attempt the flight in between these two events?

Here's the link by the way:
http://www.sapfa.org.za/history/1920s-london-cape-town </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 01:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you could have a conversation with anybody, dead or alive, who would it be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
