<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3191</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Canada. If Russia invades we will bitch slap them for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you are the guy who randomly tries to hug Alex Jones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its legal to buy life insurance on other people and be the recipient. I would buy a policy on this kid. He is young so a million dollar policy is cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need to make trump eat urine soak witch cakes. I am sure he would like them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found the paid putin troll. Commy. I write a ling post and all ye wants to do is talk about the russian commies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn communists. We need to bring back the committee for unAmerican Activities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mods post got deleted in the dnald sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most reddit posts have nothing to politics. I have posted on /r/nfl more than anywhere else. During the season I shitpost all week. Im a giants fan, shitposting other nfc east fans is fun. The difference is that shitposting is acceptable there. I have been downvoted alot when I make fun of the snowflake fans of other teams. I dont follow them to other subs and troll them. That is a sub where shitposting is acceptable. 

I got cursed out on /r/fantasy for telling someone dude, its just a book move on. If your mad dont buy Rothfuss next one. Guy went batshit. 
 
The most interesting subs are the science and history subs. Lots of really knowleadgable on there. /r/askhistorians has the most nazi mods I have seen. You can open up a thread and see mass deletes of comments unrelated to the question. They are totally ruthless. For good reason, they want to keep the thread on topic. 

Btw, the libertarians are very friendly to chat with. They are farther to the right than trump on fiscal issues and yet are very friendly. I guess dope mellows you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have yet to die.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont forget the first bush being called a wimp when he was a VP. If I recall Thomas Jefferson called John Adams a child molestor during the 1800 campaign. 

Dont get me started on any of Putins opponents or People who fuck with Dhaenarys Targaryen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is a conservative. He can agree with issues and think trump is a corrupt sack of shit. Your post is frivolous and stupid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Pompey had his head chopped off in Egypt. Rhaegar Targaryan was murdered at the trident.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 nuts tried to assassinate Gerald Ford.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont forget julius caesar being stabbed in the senate. Hell king john was forced to sign the magna carta. Dont get me started n poor Rhaegar Targaryan. Murdered at the trident.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most democrats voted for his cabinet. The president has a right to pick his cabinet. You want republicans to block the next democrats cabinet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am proud to say democrats never questioned McCains patriotism or military record in the 2008 campaign. If anyone did they would have gotten lambasted by the party. The republican president did. 

We should stand up and say that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mods are likely on alt right publication payrolls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump would have done wonders for himself if he had come out and attacked Putin for this from the start. But I wonder why he didnt?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they didnt stop lying. Clapper clearly said he wouldnt know because he didnt work for the fbi. Democratic senators are not going to make accusations like this yet. This is like during watergate repeating there is no evidence Nixon was tied to the break in. It took 2 years before he resigned. You just keep saying noone is saying he is guilty as a way to blow it off to say he is innocent. Your screwed with Mueller there. If there is anything there, Trump is a goner. It wont come out right away, but as we get  closer to the midterms, if stuff is coming out republicans will start turning on him. They like Pence better anyway. 

All the Trumpys do is copy and paste the same BS. Mueller is going to see Trumps tax returns. Flynn is going to talk. If he has anything on Trump he will give it up. 

Here is the kicker. Congress can impeach for any reason. The supreme court wont over rule congress if they vote to remove him. 

The right wing have turned into communist sympathizers. Its pathetic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Define wrongdoing. It doesnt have to be illegal to be political suicide. If democrats did this the right would be calling them communists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are not disclosing because there is something there. Trump also hasnt disclosed how much investment and loans come from russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This appears to be recorded and leaked by a republican congressman. Were any staffers present? Someone needs to grill the reporter on this. He will want to keep his source safe, but we dont have to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tap doesnt suggest he knows or has evidence. Its a suspicion. This suspicion is why we need a law that requires all elected officials to release 10 years of tax returns and required by law to disclose payments from foreign governments ever received. There could be democrats on the tae too. Get them out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to watch the video. The headline is misleading. Graham is saying that now that there is a special prosecutor, I am off the hook from having to investigate and call witness. The special prosecutor will not want those witnesses coming to congress </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 22:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will flip it and say they are being threatened, bribed, or in on it. I hope they sue fox, infowars, and breitbart. The standard to prove libel is much lower if you are not a public figure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 22:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go oldschool. Julius Caesar was stabbed to death in the Senate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 22:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have the CIA go to Turkey and kneecap these assholes. Serious too. The protest had nothing to do with American politics. It was about the Kurds being oppressed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 22:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesnt want to have to investigate Trump. He will get a big raise at Foxnews and he can spit out his right wing bullshit. Supposedly he wants to run for Utah governor. If he gets out of congress he cant be blamed. If I recall he backed off his Trump endorsement after the pussy grabber stuff for a while before he was pressured to get back onboard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 09:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Natural born killer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 09:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He needed a rocket lancher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 09:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no evidence on pence at all. You are getting ahead of yourself. That is what Trumpster Trash does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 06:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live 25 miles outside dc. I am afraid to look out my window while Trump is overseas, I dont want to be blinded by the nuclear blast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 06:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont get the 1812 reference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 01:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have smoked the guy if I was there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 01:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rosenstein: Fuck you for using me as a scapegoat on the Comey firing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 23:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they have a brain of any kind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cucker carlson is farther right. So im surprised by this. There are 2 other right wing cable news stations. This is good they are canabalizing fox.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend using the realclearpolitics.com average. Im on an ipad so posting a link is pain, but its an easy google search. They use a number of polls and average them. This cuts down on outliars. This has him at 40% approval. Lets not act like trumpster trash and jump on outliars. He is at historic lows, but his term just started. Republicans wont jump off ship that fast. Its better to be accurate than to throw out outliars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Report them to local DC police. They handle crimes like this. They can turn them over to ICE. They may have diplomatic immunity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The turks are brown too. He is good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont get your fear. This isnt Turkey. Its local police. Trump has no power over them. They wont lock you up for reporting violence. What are you talking about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These thugs will likely have diplomatic immunity. Bring mace and put them down. You can get key chain mace cheap on ebay. Its cheap and you dont cause permanent injury. Note that if they attack, technically you can kick them in the face after they ate maced to make sure they stay down. 

Note: DC has very strict gun laws. Dont go suburban commando and show up armed. Also your libel to hit an innocent bystander as well. Mace is a goos non-lethal self defense tool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> George RR Martin writes all of his books on s command line only 35 year old word processor. Back in the day, there were stripped down computers than only did word processing. He doesnt use windows, etc.. Supposedly he had a problem this breaking and he had to get it repaired. He couldnt write for a while. It was before the current book. 

He has all the commands memorized so doesnt have to take his hands off the keyboard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did Jimmy Carter have the authority to force the US to boycott the 1980 Olympic Games when the US Olympic Committee is a private organization? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have wondered this for a long time and I cannot find it anywhere. Is it something in the Olympic bylaws? Is it a presidential power? Can a president of the US force a boycott of the World Cup?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The AG works for the administration so I would expect that Clinton okd this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What politicians have been treated worse than Donald Trump? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id rather see the money go into the set than famous actors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 16:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She needs Tom at home in a french maid outfit cleaning the kitchen. Not shitting himself in a disper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 16:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants have made the superbowl 5 times with 3 coaches. Each in his 4th or 8th season.

All 4 giants superbowl wins came with Bill Bellichek coaching the defense or the other team. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 16:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends how bad the Texans are. If they are losing yes, if in playoff hunt unlikely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 16:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Brady plays until he is 45 , he will be shitting himself in a diaper during his HoF speech. No one in Mass will care since he isnt playing anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 16:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Donna Brazille had someone whacked shouldnt these idiots be heading to their underground bunkers. If Donna Brazille could make someone sleep with the fishes, Chuck Schumer is from New York imagine what he could do?

This makes me want to invest in a bunker building company and make money by scaring right wingers into building them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 16:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wont be anyone famous. Too expnsive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This explains why women are so much louder in bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thee and thou.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its business. If fans like your characters they want to see them again. That means long series with a defined ending or serials. There seem to be more serials in urban fantasy. These are open ended series where each book is a new episode. They arent required, just popular and good for sales.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do people get hired to be air traffic controllers and what qualifies them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How was Clinton convinced to appoint a special prosecutor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 00:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The justice department is run by the president. Why did he allow a special prosecutor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 23:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Netanyahu is sucking up to trump. He expects trump to be ok with him seizing all of thr West Bank. He may give a private pretty please dont give out our intel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 23:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some wanted him impeached over Benghazi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 23:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 23:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sure she is better than Phil Simms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McFly from Back to the Future </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what looks like prostitutes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that part is if the president is incapcitated. For example if reagans gunshot wound was worse and he couldnt work for a long time. It might hve been a reaction to fdr. No one knew he was dying. When he got that sick Truman should have taken over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best way o make that happen is to do a dda style mod for dwarf fortress. I dont know how moddable rimworld is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I say we get evangelicals to test it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 17:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is on tillerson for being incompetent and not informing his staff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 17:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, when we get rid of trump we are going to need laws to restrict the power of the president on issues like this. Trump is setting a precedent that the president can be irrsponsible.

Trump is worse than Nixon. Nixon was a paranoid idiot. He stole DNC strategy docs during an election. That shit isnt real valuble. He won the election by over 20 points in a landslide. It wasnt even close. So the whole break in was dumb. If he admitted it and apologized it would have made it hard to govern, but we would not have gotten enough Republicans to support impeachment. It was stupid. You dont even need the other sides strategy. You can tell what it is from what they do. Seriously why would anyone steal something this useless? 

Nixon was moderate by todays standard. He created the EPA. Ended the war in Vietnam. Opened up China. He would be attacked as a democrat if he ran today. 

Trump is a fucking incompetent buffoon. He thinks he knows better than everyone else. Look at it like this, fucking Putin is telling Trump dont antogonize the psycho N. Koreans after they intentionally launched a missile near Russia. If fucking Putin who is a murderer, is the voice of reason, Trump has to go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the game moddable enough to mod this in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You said above that i7 is quad core then you said i7 can have 10 cores. I work fir a hosting company and we deploy servers with 8 cores. These are server class chips. I dont remember the line. 

So there are i7 with 10 cores?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have they given a roadmap to where the game will be when its final? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought the game last summer. .15 came out about 8 months after .14 and the game has been in development for a number of years. I think its well worth my $20. Even though it doesnt fully have an end game, there is alot to do. 

Have they given a roadmap beyond the next release? I am not sure there is a roadmap for .16 ( which I would not expect before the end of 2017) since they are still working on .15. 

Have they said what they want the final version to look like? Unless they add a subscription service they cant work on the game forever, eventually sales will top off. Even Minecraft added subscriptions for hosting on servers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do the on chip graphics matter? Most people who care about graphics have a video card? Every build site I have seen says the i7 doesnt really matter for gaming. Better off going i5 and getting a better graphics card? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Its illegal. However, they will probably fire her. As long as she is not in a 2 party consent state, I would secretly record all conversations with her manager and send an email to her manager confirming she did this. If she does the second they may fire her, so I would have the recordings first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a common difference between i3, i5, and i7 chips through different versions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having trouble adding a flair with the ipad app. Mod please add and dont delete. When I press add flair, all I get is close.

I know i3i5i7 . However, are there standardized difference along different versions or is this just a way for intel to have 3 different grades along the same version. I have a 4 year old i5. I dont remember the rest of the name. Not looking to upgrade

I thought of this question because I saw a post in /r/gadget about a possible i9.

Also is there a reason why they do t just use i1, i2, i3 ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im shitposting. Id figure a raiders fan should understand a shitpost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We fought a civil to take away states right to own slaves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Military officers are trained to disobey unconstitutional and highly immoral orders. Now theory and practice are two different things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought congress could only remove the president by impeachment. That requires a 2/3 vote in the house.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By that law trump could legally dox US spies with no legal consequences </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am the life black hole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember watching this episode when it first aired. Damn, I am old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am the life of the party. I suck all the life from the room and the life comes to me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No with in a few billion years all galaxies outside of our local group will be moving away from us faster than the speed of light, so the visible universe will shrink to just the local group of galaxies. With in a few billion more years local group of galaxies will be merged and have run out of hydrogen. So no new stars. The only stars left will be dwarf stars. It will be several trillion years before all the black holes evaporate. Black holes will be the last energy source. 

Not infinity. The universe will be a cold dead place for an infinity. So in the whole scheme of things, its a blink of the eye. There is no hope.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoken like a true physicist. Did you get your profound knowledge from a book with popup pictures? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck southern california girls. Indy girls have so e 150 pounds of extra meat on them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The eye shadow on the danes is idiotic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebody copped a feel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder if trump got a write down on one of his Russian loans for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that violates the principle of the conservation of energy. You are spitting out pseudo science </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are an evolution denier too? The continents Re nit moving because we were nit around to see pangea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the other possible end states? The universe is expanding faster and faster. Eventually all galaxies outside our local group will move away from us faster than the speed of light. Eventually all hydrogen will be fused into helium so no more stars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eventually the universe will suffer from heat death. All stars will go out. All black holes will evaporate. The universe will be a cold dead place for an infinite period of time. There is no hope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raptor. Take him to rural kentucky and fees him republican rednecks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems thin for a trump supporter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democrats should run on this. We need the house to investigate Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The original Pool of Radiance from 1988. Fir its time it was groundbreaking and I was a kid when it came out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldnt put money on him being alive in 2030 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grrm will never write all of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At its height in the 1980s. Announcers used to say Miami Hurricanes could compete in the AFC East. Bullshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jags are moving to orlando and will be renamed the Princesses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joe Namath. He had 2 good seasons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants/49ers nfc championship game in 1990. This is back when you can plaster people. Both teams were loaded with all pros as well. Parcells said it was his best game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Punters need big hands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This got cut off. He meant they have the best looking defense in the NFL.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jonathan Hankins: Indianapolis has the best weather in the US. Fuck Hawaii or Southern California </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Las Vegas raiders could have naked women on their jersey to advertise the Bunny Ranch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 14:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And ass fuck monday nights </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 49ers fan too young to remember joe montana </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just watch the games on the web. You dont need to pay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minnesota quit. I remember that game. Randy Moss wasnt even running routes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There hve been alot of good superbowls in the last 20 years. When I grew in the 1980s the nfc won 14 straight and 12 were blowouts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 04:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me want to play the Battle Hymm of the Republic. Hang all the traitors! See the tweets, The Russians are our friends? Time for treason trials. Treason is a death penalty offense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 04:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a democratic governor. I expect hm to veto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 04:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That added that or it could be unconstitutional to put people in prison </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 00:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is begging you for vet assisted suicide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 00:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Troll them. Its not about dismantling. Its about fucking with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 00:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How come they dont get charged with blasphemy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 18:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is seeimg dollar signs. He will make bank for this when he leaves the fcc from the telecoms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 17:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start calling him fat bastard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 17:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start calling thr, communists and call for bringing back the committee for unAmerican Activities to investigate the communist infiltration of the Republican party. This shit is clearly funded by Putin. When these assholes speak they use the same talking points. You notice how they go talk about how we dont want Russia to see us as an "existential threat". 

I mean this honestly. This is Putin and the people pushing this are traitors. Subpoena their tax returns see if they are etting paid by RT. 

Seriously. Hang the fucking traitors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 17:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you are from Kentucky you should be emailing this to someone elses mother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 10:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard a retired redskin say that into the 1980s guys had jobs during the offseason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 10:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Parcells being asked if he was afraid of the 49ers.

Let me tell what I am afraid. I am afraid of snakes. I am afraid of spiders. And I am afraid of the IRS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giant hockey stick with spikes on it. Have to be thick not to break.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contrived endings. The plots have things getting bad, then the protagonists win. Most of the time its contrived and total bullshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have Alien Covenent that is so new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blockbuster video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 04:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blog post translation: see the fun I had instead of writing the next book </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 04:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me want to go to ireland and pass out scientology bullshit to get them to charge me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 04:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rug stores constantly have these  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 04:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scientology </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 01:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Foxnews started making the case to fire McCabe the day Comey was fired. His wife ran for office as a democrat and got a donation from someone close to the governor who is a Clinton supporter. They called it conflict of interest. He wont last long. Trump will fire him. I expect the new fbi director to lots of people at the fbi. They dont get the same federal government protections.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 23:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they are married isnt the house joint custody so its illegal for husband to kick her out right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 21:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont sign anything if you dont work there. Why would you? They are not going to pay you to sign this. Just tell them to fuck off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tribulations before search and replace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 00:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump will just lie and say they dont exist. No e of his beta cucks will say they exist. If there is a reirding, its digital. Its easy to delete or hide. We will never see them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 19:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are nato members. War with them is war with the US. Well in theory. Depends what Putins cuck does. If putin offers to write off Trumps loans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 19:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turkey still denies the Armenian Genocide. When Nancy Pelosi and the democrats declared it a genocide about 10 years ago. Turkey through a shit fit threatened to cause trouble in Iraq. Republicans responded with why do we have to do this now? Armenians were christians. Not that it matters to me. You would think the party of the Christian right would want to call this genocide a fucking genocide. Onward Christian soldiers.

Who now remembers the Armenians? - Adolph Hitler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 18:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the hell is it not rape if an older guy has sex with an underage girl just because she has a ring on her finger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 18:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is there cost for electricity compared to the US? Anyone have a breakdown of just the cost to generate? If we do overall cost then we get into infrastructure such as power lines, etc and that doesnt compare the cost to generate renewable vs. fossil fuel. The cost to generate needs to include construction and maintenance costs to get real numbers. Prefer numbers from an academic paper or a reliable news agency. I dont trust advocacy groups.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typical of a loser fan base that has 1 playoff win in 20 years bragging about regular season wins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giants had the 2 worst tackles in the eague. Bobby hart had a pff rating in the 40s. You dont belong on an nfl roster with that. Center and left guard are very good, right guard is mediocre abd could probably start for less than half of nfl teams, but not garbage.

Most pressure comes from the outside. I think part of it is that the giants get rid of the ball so fast less time for pressure. Its too fast. Defenders can play press coverage since there is less time to cover. So the giants coach around it by getting rid of the ball fast. With press cover eli has small windows and very short pick ups. So you need alot of good plays to score. 

West coast is getting rid of the ball fast. However, of the giants had better blocking they could mix it up more so guys can run more in patterns and comebacks, but the terrible tackles made that hard. Its harder to cover guys in press coverage if you have to cover longer. The inability to mix it up and the shit run game is what killed the offense.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should get more upvotes and comments. A bush judge is going after him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your percent chance of finding marble? It seems low </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does not seem to be an even distribution. I just did 20+ explores without marble. I used 20 mine stones and did not get a marble mine. I had to blow 10 gems and get an advanced minestone to progress.

I think its a weighted chance. I think coal/stone are about the same. Iron is lower. Then clay, then marble.

Not sure if anyone else is like this but my refine bonus is much lower then harvest plus i need to make oil so refining marble is a slog.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That isnt wht he said. He implied i should keep going before resetting because it gets harder with each one. I did reset at ng+2 and it was faster.

I have a number of other recommendations in here such as banks are useless, workers dont do anything other than for paper or inns, its just too slow. Autotap should run offline and longer so i dont blow out my phone, artifacts give too small a bonus, and how about being able to upgrade them, a more thought out progress reset instead of the same bons, etc... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You almost have to buy a couple of levels of the finger artifact that autotaps and the xp bonus to progress </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 05:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True conservatives are embarrassed if democrats are more anti Russia than democrats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 04:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This wont last. Justice Department is already making the case to fire McCabe. Foxnews has been spitting out bullshit why he should be fired. His wife ran for state office in virginia and got a donation from someone tied to the democratic governor. Not sufficiently loyal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then the next generation of poor people wont have money for free education so the cycle continues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone named adolph hitler. They exist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting gold when you are already famous is cheating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
