<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1271</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Legion didn't happen Jessica Jones would still be my favorite superhero/comic book based series. It isnt just for superhero comic lovers, but also for TV fans. Unlike most superhero series the storytelling is unique, its much more adult and isnt afraid to explore dark themes of sexual assault, rape and abortion and it does so with taste. The tone of the show is dark and chilling, but is also mildly humorous. There were the occasional scenes that makes you feel youre watching a horror movie, and others that made it seem like a self-aware satire of superhero tropes. Oh and Kilgrave is undeniable one of the best TV antagonist.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bow Down to More Royal Thickness from Pleasantly Stacked Ms. Kingdom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bow Down to the Royal Thickness of Pleasantly Stacked Ms. Kingdom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Lucifer, the best show I have ever seen.

welp. I suggest you check out some more shows, but if that's your thing I won't judge.

Good news tho. Lucifer is renewed for a 3rd season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  jessica jones for example, that show is so cliche in the dark way that to me is boring.

please don't force me to say anything against the rules here man. I'm trying to be good. 

But why in god's earth would you think Jessica Jones is clich? Well maybe het whole broke down alcoholic schtick, but otherwise Jessica Jones is an original show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supergirl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 1 - Season 2 - Twin Peaks: Fire Walk With Me (1992)

also, pay close attention to the interrogation scenes in season 1. It'll be interesting to see how it actually played out in the prequel film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 15:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have high hopes for this one, being a FX original and all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
