<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2797</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 07:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> interesting. I just don't know any programming yet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 06:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yezzir  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> have any modern philosophers produced material concerning the political correctness phenomenon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> sources for information on United States investments in El Salvador/ Guatemala? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> more specifically pertaining to the civil wars. I can't seem to find any good sources on this. most of the sources reference more current events like 2012 or more recent. I am interested in the economic motivations of the US for its involvement in the wars. thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im aware that the dot product is not a linear transformation in the way I stated and I apologize for not having pointed out that this is what the prof said and likely meant something else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats what I was confused about when he said it. I know its not so Im wondering if anyone can help elucidate what he meant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> how to prove the dot product is a linear transformation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 00:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe my teacher told me this will be a definite question on the final. cant seem to find a good answer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 00:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great response  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: why are some people light sleepers and others heavy sleepers ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 07:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you single lol? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> feet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im thinking about getting the poincare disk model on my shoulder  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fight Club. Sherlock Holmes. Catch me if you Can. A beautiful mind. Pi. Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: why is reading "good for your brain"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> am I the only one around here that thinks life is actually... NOT short? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its fucking long. this semester has felt like a million years and its still not over. a 6 to 8 hour work shift is so painfully long its unbelievable that its only part of a day. who the fuck says life is short? its long, mostly boring, mundane and painful. it is rarely exciting or SHORT seeming in any way  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same it sucks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> psychology/neurology question: why do we get sleepy when we're bored? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the implicit function theorem  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> beautiful answer lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> does the study of differential geometry involve a good bit of PDE's? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this is a stupid question. But I'm just curious. I don't know very much about diff geometry at all but it sounds interesting. I have calc 2 under my belt but have not yet taken ODE's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> any good books on the real projective plane? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> are there jobs for mathematicians which involve alternative energy research ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Book of proof by Hammack. it's got a lot of exercises and describes the thinking behind proofs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's what I seem to have trouble with right now. not knowing what to assume  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that answers my question pretty well thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> when practicing proofs, how long will you typically spend on a proof? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the answer varies a lot. But say its a class like analysis or linear algebra. and you want to spend an hour or two practicing proofs. how long will you spend on each one?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 04:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> alright thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> has anyone read Antoni Zygmund's book on trigonometric series? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> would you recommend it? I have recently become interested in set theory and sequences/series  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sick ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try Steve Coleman and the Five Elements? they have a very unique sound in my opinion, really makes you think while listening to it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow apparently redditors all have amazing taste in music, the only thing I haven't seen that I like so far is the classical genre. I pretty much love anything by Felix Mendelssohn, or Tchaikovsky.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: why is Islam considered the "religion of peace"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OHHH lol gotcha. thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the whale shark is the worlds largest fish? hm guess I was wrong  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to be a research mathematician. I am comfortable with linear algebra and calculus. I love proofs. I like set theory, topology, analysis... etc those types of subjects. However... I know absolutely ZERO programming whatsoever. I am afraid of it and haven't been required to learn any yet. I am not yet a grad student so that may be why.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> um what? first of all how do you know Im an undergrad? 2nd don't tell me what to fuckin do  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a drinker and smoke a lot of herb and love psychedelics. I'm somewhere between intro and extrovert. Sports are ok, but I'm not super into them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> oh so only men do these things but not women right? the hypocrisy of SJW's amazes me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://braininspired.net/every-single-one-10-things-emotional-abuse-yes-really/   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fine don't fuckin read it I don't give a shit?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the cliche frat boy look. nuff said  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ill look into it and yeah elements is a must  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow that's a wild looking paper. thanks a bunch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sick ! thanks a lot ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> will I be able to watch this if I live on the east coast US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> now that I think of it I would love a link or source for Poncelet's work on projective geometry if anyone knows of any. thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
