<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2159</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you tired of your BBs sniping from the backline? Do your DDs ignore the caps? Are your cruiser players the reason cruisers have a low winrate? Well come join us with Supremacy and may your opinion of random battles forever be tainted by what you see coordinated teams accomplish! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 01:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the show is based on the books, she'll have a much more minor role. It'll be all Yen all day baby. :D:D:DD:D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 16:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Geralts body is made to age 5 times slower than a normal person and be top tier human levels of strength and endurance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah and Gandalf was thousands of years old. Why do fantasy ages have to correlate to actors?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Yennefer is also around 100 but it'd be a bit odd for Hellen Mirin to play her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the books recently got their official translations so its time to get caught up, people!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand how this is possible. Roon is straight up better than hipper and Hindenburg is a Roon with an extra turret.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 04:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The captain respec helped them a lot (priority target, 10pt CE, AR is the titties kitties), steering gears helped a couple of them a lot, all the US CAs have received serious buffs, the concealment mod now increases dispersion to help against BB fire, German CAs got some armor buffs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 23:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. Through the process of buffs or, in some cases, several buffs, ships have been brought in line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 23:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Power creep doesn't make old cruisers bad when old cruisers have received several buffs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cruisers are in a better spot now more than ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe cancer isn't the right word. Obnoxious then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This subreddit is just as cancer as T_D. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone on the outside of this whole thing, I think both of you are fucking obnoxious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, you are confused.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U stupid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minotaur is a cruiser?

Edit: jokes are hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DM is the least tanky T10 cruiser.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least reddit is becoming slightly more self aware.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something tells me their engine wouldn't like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You make one line have good MM and it fucks it up for everyone else. The system that is in place for MM is the only way the game works. Sometimes you're fucked, sometimes they're fucked. 

Really though, even against a lot of T10s, you can still make a difference as T8. You just have to play a little different. Keeps things interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game is in a pretty good state right now. Get those CV re-balances out and holy shit we'll be livin right.

Keep up the good work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you guys aware of the interesting implications of the spaced armor on French cruisers? For instance, HE shells do 0 damage penetrations as they only penetrate the outside layer of armor (even very large caliber HE). And some AP will detonate between the plates doing zero damage (Royal Navy AP specifically).

Details can be found in this thread.

https://www.reddit.com/r/WorldOfWarships/comments/6669wo/unusual_effects_of_spaced_armour_in_the_french/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bismarck has way more AA on the mid range guns, not just the close range. 

Sitting higher = eating more shells regardless of whether you take citadels.

Torps that get knocked out frequently vs hydro is a toss up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Well yeah the 20km sucks so don't use them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shima still has the worst detection, but not by much, and the highest damage per torp by far and the biggest ability to saturate an area. You can't just look at one stat to compare her torps to other boats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah she's the only ship I have spec for FP. Maybe I'll give her another go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the T9/10 IJN BBs are struggling. Yamato still has her strengths, but she's more susceptible all the fire spam.

Even so, if you think IJN BBs are still great, that's less of an argument that power creep has been negatively affecting the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolute hardcore you forgot about it having worse AA, worse speed, sits higher in the water, and oh yeah no hydro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the only old lines that don't hold up as well are the IJN DDs  (but they were OP way back and now they're getting small buffs) and IJN BBs. Everything else is still very competitive. 

Power creep has entered the game, but most old lines have received buffs along the way. US Cruiser buffs have happened, US BBs got their accuracy buffed a while back, etc etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> , .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's huge! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't envy SO's job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 18:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So not only does this subreddit regularly overreact and speak out against things (that was presumably the reason SO left), the subreddit ALSO overreacted to his comment about taking a break and spoke out how we're all going to miss him.


Hahaha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The downvote button is not a disagree button.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure. I don't see why not. DDs also kill other DDs too. And while I would like to see more cruisers every match, it would also get quite boring with the exact same team layouts every match. Sometimes it's BB heavy, sometimes cruiser heavy, sometime DD heavy, sometimes balanced. 

Quit bitchin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BBs can kill DDs too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we trade notser for Sub Octavian? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/mOnvOJG.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With every reaction, there is an equal and opposite reaction. 

Statement remains true everywhere I go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Ellie doesn't toss ammo to you on the harder difficulties.

And yes, you were very condescending.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The execution of the gameplay in parallel with the story is what's so good. The gameplay has narrative to it and I don't just mean that story elements are told through it. I mean that when Joel stealth kills and beats in the heads of 10 guys in a room, that's canon. And stress of that, the frustration of it, the brutality that is demonstrated exists in prefect cohesion with the characters and the story. The gameplay is hard, it wears you down, it's not necessarily fun, and it's perfect for The Last of Us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The context of the gameplay was to drive the narrative. Comparing it to other games is tricky,  because the last of us has gameplay that exists in prefect cohesion with the story.  The gameplay is not separate from the narrative, it is canon with it. It is stressful, frustrating, resourceful, and mostly grounded.  It's prefect for what it accomplishes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A funny meme,  but the amount of people who assume and consider this the norm are vastly mistaken.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first I thought it was funny, then you torped the friendly Fletcher, very much on purpose. No warning; no nothing. Stopped watching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A little luck, a little skill. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should take every reaction of this subreddit with a grain of salt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zao, Hindenburg, and Moskva can bounce Yamato AP off the deck. Doesn't overmatch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's several circumstances that differentiate the two. You may go undetected vs a Yamato. Torps don't care if you're spotted or who the intended target was. Assuming you're not sitting still, you can also dodge the shells as you can see them coming as they're fired. Angling works vs shells. Des Moines has a particular weakness with it's poor deck, but most cruisers can mitigate Yamato fire. Angling vs torps does nothing. In fact you lose out on torp belt protection  (not like it helped much but still). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it *feel* good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cruisers don't die in one or two Yamato hits. Hyperbole doesn't help discussion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Granted, a lot has changed since then and I don't really expect Shimas to go back the their prior dominance. More ships run as counters to DDs and Shimakazes will still be missing their super long range torps

-subject2159 from the post you didn't read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I stated as much in my post. The majority of what I said is unrelated to what you're pointing out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand your point but I still think it's a little different. A good cruiser player can avoid taking huge damage from a BB very well. And while a good cruiser player can avoid torps, there's still a little less counter play to it, especially considering walls of 15 torps. Sometimes it's very hard or impossible avoid all of them and when they do half or more of your HP, it's very devastating. 

DDs are the biggest sufferers though imo. Cruisers have hydro a lot of the time to see torps but DDs act mostly reactionary to them. So a zone being flooded with 15 torps that pop up really close to you, oops you misjudged the turn, oops your rudder was the wrong way when they were spotted, oops those torps luckily were packed in too tightly together to dodge. Insta kill. I just don't think having insta gib mechanics with such a high variability of outcome and response is very engaging. Which goes back to the suggestion of lowering the alpha to begin with, but I don't see WG considering that for some reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah well let's buff the speed too then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My opinion is just to buff the detection and nerf the alpha damage. The torps are still the fastest torps in the game, so hitting more consistently but for less burst seems reasonable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More accurate and easily accessible information is always a good thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Regarding Shimakaze Torps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when seeing 4 Shimakazes per team was not out of the ordinary. You guys complain about the passive meta now, but perhaps you look at the past with rose tinted glasses because I remember it being much worse. Granted, a lot has changed since then and I don't really expect Shimas to go back the their prior dominance. More ships run as counters to DDs and Shimakazes will still be missing their super long range torps, but there's an element that is often overlooked when dealing with ways to buff their current underperforming torps. 

The individual damage of them. There are arguments to be made about total DPS and how other DDs fire torps more frequently at less damage, but that's only part of the way to look at them. What is important to consider is this higher alpha makes them particularly more deadly against cruisers and DDs when these torps can one or two shot them. People always meme about BBabies crying about torps but I assume it's the DDs and CAs that will be most affected by any spotting range buffs. Any slow moving BBs might take one extra torp to little effect because of a detection buff, but a cruiser taking one extra or a DD being hit at all is a big deal. I don't think WG wants these dramatic consequences. 

So, while Shimas are currently underperforming, it's a careful topic to consider as their torps are dangerously close to meta defining. More dangerous Shima torps mean more dangerous and game ending consequences of a single mistake or a single case of bad luck from random torps spreads. And its not BBs that will suffee the most, imo. Be careful what you ask for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're all products of confirmation bias.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a dead BB.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but even making a lower caliber shell do the same damage as a higher caliber would be the first time that's happened (I think). And for what Flamu was calling for would do way more damage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They would probably not want to give 240mm guns much more alpha than Scharn 280s though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A high alpha cruiser sounds awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dodging torps and maneuvering in tight spaces are severely limited. Often I was confident enough with Khab to contest tight points like C cap on Hotspot. Not anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my experience of not only playing different competitive games,  but also following them to an extent,  the successful games balance around the top players and the competitive scene. 

As far as power creep, there are certainly cases of it and I hope the duca duca doesn't go through as is,  but as far as main ship lines,  I think have been very balanced. German DDs are a good spot,  Grrman BBs are a great example of balance, RN cruisers are weird but situational, French cruisers are probably a little weak but still interesting (which is okay).

All they need to do is remove Belfast from the game and we're in a good spot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mosvka is the better BB.

Joking aside, both are great. They offer different things so its hard to call one better. 

Mosvka is a bit more static in it's play with poor options for disengaging but very strong when played to it's strengths. 

Zao is much more versatile and can freely move around the map in an active way. The stealth fire removal didn't hurt it too much. 

Personally I find Mosvka more fun to play because oh how well you can bully people with your insane deck armor and Russian bias guns. Zao is a bit easier and while it does have more freedom for map positioning, it's a bit easier to play and less interesting imo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many opinions reflected flamu's from other testers. His opinions were just the most publicized.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah big weakness still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CVs aren't dead at T7 and below.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But my Russian bias :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would probably be okay to give every cruiser enough deck armor to not get overmatched by BBs of it's tier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even so, you should keep it in mind as a longer term goal. Once you get a 19 point captain it will begin to help out every other captain you have. It's great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a 19 point captain on a T10, play that ship a lot (T10s generate more xp), use it's elite commander xp to level other stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give Henri more deck armor and give the whole line more krupp and 3 kts more speed. 

Fixed and not op.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very well said. I like your point about situations where the poor torpedo detection plays little to no role. A lot of people use that detection as their main argument against the ship's effectiveness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make them faster (the ships), give the shells some more krupp. The line still wouldn't be top tier, but they'd be good enough to be relevant.  

Wargaming, hire me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> VMF CLs dont get 9.4km detection and 10km torps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think people forgot there exists a turret rotation module. It's certainly still slow, but certainly very playable. 

You fire 15 shell salvos. Gotta be careful how you buff that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> German DDs have proved to be reliable BB escorts in NA competitive. They use their hydro to detect torps from way far out, are good at spamming torps towards enemy lanes and their smoke is long enough to be useful until a benson can come back for the big smoke.

Detection mechanics could still use some work as you say, but I have seen plenty of people criticize the lack of stealth firing directly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are things as bad as people want them to be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright alright. I don't intend to say this game is above criticism or that the devs are infallible as they certainly aren't, but holy shit this echo chamber can be a bit exhausting. I won't say that I know everything but I have been playing this game for a long time now and have a decent enough understanding of game mechanics that I feel my opinion should carry some weight to them and not be immediately discredited behind the echo chamber. And some of these opinions being contrary to the general opinion I think makes them worth hearing.

I'd like to list a few heated topics and give my opinions on each. Some I agree with the populace, some I come at with a different point of view.

* Ranked was complete shit and an obvious cash grab on premiums. Every ranked season will obviously push premium sales, but T7 having only premiums with radar and enough smoke going around to make Snoop Dogg cough was painful and I hope it doesn't happen again. 

* German DDs being "shit". Are they shit? Maybe they're not the best, but they're certainly better now with the stealth fire change. The T8 German DD has made its way successfully into competitive play in a lot of comps but I'd also like to make a point of power creep. WG went to odd measures to make the RN cruisers relevant and the sense of power creep can be felt everywhere. Not every line has to be the best new ships, they can be kinda meh and still be relevant. Otherwise you get continous power creep.

* Russian bias? Maybe? I mean they are generally strong ships, but so are other lines. Russian ships have a pretty unique playstyle that I think adds to the game balance in a positive way. They separate themselves from the role of other ships without relying on consumable power creep. 

* Stealth fire change. Look guys, I remember a time when people were asking for stealth fire to be removed. I know that things change and with radar and hydro it's more scary now for DDs but even still, stealth firing was a hugely situational tactic for the majority of DDs. If you were relying on it I question whether you were playing correctly and the couple ships the change did affect greatly like akizuki, it was needed. Stealth firing akizuki lacks counter play and it's not fun. 

* New French ships, stop freaking out, just politely voice concerns and move on.

* ~~Russian T8 BB premium. I don't like it having radar but will 305s will be that good? I imagine they will do fuck all agaisnt a NC and even a lot of cruisers should be able to handle them. It's a Scharnhorst without turtleback sooooo not sure how good it is minus the radar.~~ 

I've been duped. 

tl:dr don't hate me

edit - formatting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erik is fucking hilarious. Dude trips me up every time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right on time for T8 ranked season. If the bow can be over matched I'll forgive it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not great but it's long enough to be useful.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair heal on Khab isn't inherently OP. No smoke is a pretty big tradeoff for both yourself and teammates. I play with heal just because it's full adrenaline fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks bud </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Miss(ouri commentary) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't really about the Black vs CA/BB. It's about Black vs other DD being instant win.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't maintain your distance against a ship you can't see. It's detection is shorter than its radar range.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [My friend's list.](http://imgur.com/ZH5LZnN) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played Chivalry for 1600 hours (mostly conpetitively) and enjoyed my time despite the game's huge mechanical flaws. At a fundamental level, Chivalry offers an insane amount of depth with its swing manipulation. It makes an interesting mind game and reactionary game when you not only have to read the direction of your opponents moves, but also the speed and timing of it (since blocking is a timing based reaction). However, while dragging was an intended mechanic, this depth does bring out exploits that might not necessarily be *as* broken as people think, but certainly take a lot of mechanical understanding and experience to deal with and even for an experienced player, still get tiring to deal with. Players with an over reliance on reverse attacks took away a lot of depth and it was just a game about your ability to react quickly, ping be damned.

Mordhau looks fucking brilliant. Not only have they fixed the reverse attack issue, they also added more depth in the ability to deal with your opponents attacks. In Chivalry, you can parry and that's about it. Some fast weapons can interrupt an opponents moves, but you mostly can just parry. And with feints being so incredibly challenging to read, the person on the offensive has a huge advantage. Mordhau gives more defensive tools to take back the initiative and limits the effectiveness of feints with the counter attack system. It's no longer safe to spam feints hoping your opponent bites, as they can simply queue up their own attack as a counter to any potential swing, feint or not. 

tldr looks alright tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well according to them CV rework is a wip. With this patch a step in the right direction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hyperbole never helped anyone. Low tier cvs were unfair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All you need to do is kite! Don't need smoke! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ognevoi is probably alright. Won't be super good though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kiev and Benson serve different purposes. Both are excellent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If by viable you mean random battles, I think every T8 ship is viable. Hipper and NO being the worst, but still viable. If you mean competitive play, Edinburgh is great and chapy wasn't using stealth fire in comp anyway so no change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not every ship has to be completely viable. That's how power creep happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your opinion on the upcoming stealth firing changes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's ignore the fact that the devs have been pretty communicative up until this point and [have stated] are actively aware of the major balance issues the community dislikes and are looking for ways to fix it. 

But nah, the cosmetics cost too much so let's shun the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People really *really* **really** want to be upset about things these days. More than anything, it seems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should run CE regardless of being able to stealthfire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Akizuki is getting a 2km range buff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 10:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angel of pride and unseen. Pride is my favorite and has a Berserk reference in it.  Want to get an angel of war but he's out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have two of this guy's prints.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even close. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Standard battle is succ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yeah, can't really argue against BF1. Frostbite is a monster which makes ME:Aook even more amateur.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the game looks pretty incredible maxed at 1440p. I run full AA at 1440p (gtx 1080) without hairworks for solid 60. Iirc I can turn hairworks on geralt and it's 50+. Not many games I can do 1440p and AA for 60 fps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confirmation bias is a helluva drug. Instead of branching out and discovering more of his content and his attitude, let's just isolate your only experience of him to a negative one so you may hold on to your opinion of him. 

I hate him and I'll never not hate him!

Boohoo his ME3 wasn't even that bad. Somebody sounds butthurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's an open map vs high tiers, not much you can do. And yes the range buff WILL help a lot. Otherwise the NO has pretty good concealment and should be playing around islands when possible and radaring shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 14:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Witcher 3 is incredibly optimized  (hairworks aside). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 08:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reload mod pls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 08:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bit too much hyperbole for serious criticism. I agree with a lot of it (especially the first point) but the point about how there are still passive games so why not give Shima their old torps back is completely asinine. Passive games may not have completely disappeared, but it's way better now. You're criticism has a bit of anti logic going on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
