<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject366</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5000 square feet isn't enough to influence anyone politically, so I think he won't get any subsidies.  Also, he won't be creating any jobs, so you won't find much interest in helping him tax wise.  

The issue with being inside the city is that the police don't want to spend their time following up on property crime, so when your shop is broken into, they won't help catch the person who did the crime.  This will effect your insurance rates and may cause all of those toys to disappear.  Someplace outside the city will get better services for not much more money.  If you are north of the city try Warren, Hazel Park, if West try Westland, Inkster, Dearborn Heights, etc.  The difference a few blocks makes in distance is enormous in city services.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neiman Marcus sells a pair of "distressed" sneakers for $1,425. I wonder how they smell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll see what the weather brings.  Sandy soil, dirt, puddles, not too much rocky stuff.  If there is a lot of rain we'll see lots of mud, if not, just dirt.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 06:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it!  You should think about entering a Gambler 500 event if one is anywhere near you.  They are on/off road rallies for $500 cars.  Your Fiero would be a great choice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  I posted some more photos on the Detroit Gambler page here:  https://www.facebook.com/detroitgambler500/posts/409094682822507 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty cool.  Around here 2000 mustangs aren't real popular and explorers are everywhere, so why not combine them?  I like the 4x4 decal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here in the Detroit area it isn't too hard to find running cars for $500, they are all on Craigslist.  This one had its share of problems.  It had been rear-ended so the body has some wrinkles and the rear bumper cover was all cracked and dangling.  The rest of the body has some decent visible rust spots too.  The trunk didn't open and the driver's door pins were so worn that you couldn't get the door to close.  I repaired the cracked rear bumper with hunks of wood and some screws.  I replaced the door pins, which only cost $12 but took about 7 hours of labor.  That job was a serious pain the butt.  I'll probably grind and bondo the rust spots too.  So, it's possible to find a good $500 donor car, especially if you are patient and can do some work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 04:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could only do so much with my budget.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 04:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished the build, so I've only put less than 100 miles on it as is.  Before I take it off road I am gradually taking the tires up to higher and higher speeds.  They were a bit age-cracked when I got them, so I am worried.  In two weeks it'll hit the trails.  For now I've been playing in dirt lots and driving over curbs.  Before the Gambler I'll also weld up the rear differential to get 2 wheel drive.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 04:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The $500 thing is a suggestion.  The grand champion of the event is the person that completes the entire rally with the shittiest car, so spending more ensures you lose.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  So far I've bartered for a bunch of stuff (the tires and the installation of the tires).  Including electronics, fixing the car, and suspension parts I'm right around $1,000.  Before I put the tires on it was fun to drive, but honestly they are too noisy so it isn't much fun to tool around in.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  Those are stock mustang wheels.  I never liked them with the skinny stock tires, but I love them with the mud tires.  They were also in my budget because they came with the car.  15" wheels are not too hard to find mud tires for. 

It didn't take much suspension work.  I started with a v6 mustang which had tires that were way too small.  I wanted tires that were the same width as those on a Cobra, but with my budget I could only find some that were a little bit bigger.  (I wanted 29x10 but got 31x10.5).  That meant I had to lift it a bit.  I but a 1.25" lift spacer in the back, it was just and aluminum puck and caused about a 2.5" lift.  I also put in new, slightly longer, air assisted shocks in the back.  (monroe hi-jackers).  That installation wasn't tough.  For the front I put in 3/4 in. spacers, which were good for about 1 1/2 inches of lift.  The front spacers were a complete pain in the neck to install.  The stock springs (I kept them all) were already fairly long in the front, so to get the spacer in, I had to use a spring compressor that I needed to cut down in length, as well as use a special mustang spring installation tool.  That took me a while to get right.  It's now about 10" to the bottom of the weld flange of the body.  It also seems to have a better stance.  These mustangs seem to naturally squat rearward, which I don't care for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a v6, you can't get a GT for $500.  I am avoiding the roof rack by just bolting stuff to the roof.  The spare is mounted and the fake machine gun, for the Gambler I will be toting a chain saw and possibly a shovel.  I'll be making mounts for each of them out of some scrap wood.  I'll use the "Screw it right through the roof" method of installation.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It didn't take much suspension work.  I started with a v6 mustang which had tires that were way too small.  I wanted tires that were the same width as those on a Cobra, but with my budget I could only find some that were a little bit bigger.  (I wanted 29x10 but got 31x10.5).  That meant I had to lift it a bit.  I but a 1.25" lift spacer in the back, it was just and aluminum puck and caused about a 2.5" lift.  I also put in new, slightly longer, air assisted shocks in the back.  (monroe hi-jackers).  That installation wasn't tough.  For the front I put in 3/4 in. spacers, which were good for about 1 1/2 inches of lift.  The front spacers were a complete pain in the neck to install.  The stock springs (I kept them all) were already fairly long in the front, so to get the spacer in, I had to use a spring compressor that I needed to cut down in length, as well as use a special mustang spring installation tool.  That took me a while to get right.  It's now about 10" to the bottom of the weld flange of the body.  It also seems to have a better stance.  These mustangs seem to naturally squat rearward, which I don't care for.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a link to the Detroit Gambler 500 event.  It is on April 29th-30th, 2017.  It is free to participate and there are not too many rules.  Come join us.  https://www.facebook.com/events/364793720550098/?acontext=%7B%22ref%22%3A%223%22%2C%22ref_newsfeed_story_type%22%3A%22regular%22%2C%22feed_story_type%22%3A%2217%22%2C%22action_history%22%3A%22null%22%7D sharer_id=346585665740076 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I turned a $500 year 2000 Mustang into The Mudstang - I am organizing the Detroit Gambler 500 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 05:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red Coat Tavern on Woodward avenue between 13 and 14 mile roads has a great prime rib.  It comes complete with potato, vegetable or salad, and yorkshire pudding (sometimes called a popover).  They offer three sizes, I think the small one is $17.95.  A lot of people go to Red Coat for the burgers, but the prime rib is excellent.  They offer it every night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi!  I'm just reminding you that persistence does pay off.  I hope all is well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm in a race against time! I've got to eat all of these holiday cookies! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 20:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If necessity is the mother of invention, laziness is probably the father. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There you go!  It is definitely time to dust it off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to put some thoughts into this, so that I would give you a good reply.  This is my best shot PrivilegeCheckmate.  

My personal experience is that if you can keep a project moving forward, every day, you will eventually accomplish something.  Sounds kinda over-simplified, but I swear by it.  

No matter what the project is, you have to keep it moving forward every day.  It might be leaps and bounds, it might be a small step, it might even be a slow crawl after the project has been set back significantly, but you (or me) as the person leading the project has to make sure that you move forward every, single day.  

You have to do this with one project.  The other projects can play around on the sidelines, but one project has to move forward every day.  

You mentioned that you have a million ideas, so how do you choose?  I start by discussing all of the ideas with the smartest, most successful friends I have.  I find that successful people love to talk about ideas, and they can help you figure out which ones have potential and which are duds.  I have always tried to choose the best, or my favorite idea, and kick it down the road daily.

My personal mantra has been the same for 17 years now.  "Every day I move forward." 

That was a hard question to answer.  It took most of my morning to write write and it still seems stupid.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
