<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1499</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 10:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shame on them... I'm totally not clicking on it for myself, I'm doing it for a friend  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 09:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My area often doesn't pursue unless it's ~10+ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem the subreddit in my eyes in one of the best, though don't post bad advise (aka don't advise anything batman would do) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there is reason to believe that was what a reasonable person would do in an emergency is your best course of action, vigilantes often get into trouble with the law because often what they do is not reasonable. However if cops are running after someone and you tackle the culprit you probably won't get into trouble.

 for more accurate advice head on over to /r/legaladvice the mods there are great, active, and can explain in layman terms  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I was referring to how to this zombie looking human, sure he is kinda creepy but that's ok, and suddenly this horrifying monstrosity pops up 

It's my first DS game, and I stopped playing after hitting me my first OH WHAT THE !!!!!!! zombie dog.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of us are not dark soul material. Mid way through the first boss of DS3 I put down my controller, said nope, and walked away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 22:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Train til it dies, then train the next one til it dies. Bone-breaking work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 22:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pupil did well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 07:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was just a little too morbid for me, a pun and a pun indeed, but a morbid one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 07:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be afraid that my house would catch on fire from the aftermath  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 07:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad thing is he believes it blatantly without even a Google search... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 01:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinking along the lines of questions such as "why did the Spanish not remove Sutter from a position of authority in California after he threatened to raise the French flag over sutters fort?"

Questions that are really specific or obscure. Overall general research insight is great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 01:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in a similar situation, if you still can't recover losses, I was suggested that I could write some of it off in my taxes as "loss not covered under insurance" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best way to research lesser known historical events? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 23:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While it is quite easy to grab information on a well known topic such as the civil war, it can be difficult to find information on more obscure or detailed topics. I would normally just wiki the topic and find the references underneath for more information, if more information was needed a google search with multiple criteria. But I couldn't find a mega thread on researching history and tips do so and was wondering if anyone has insight and tips on research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad career move </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of necessity I once had to hook a TS cable (just call it an instrument cable) through 4 adapters t fit an XLR port. Sound quality was crap. Would this particular set up lead to loss of some data? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a fun fact </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So pretty much like holding a mic to a speaker? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 12:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screw that, the mechanic did barely anything and would reset often, too often for it to make a sizeable impact on draws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 12:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can imagine why that the solviet soldiers were well behaved in comparison to Germany  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess some sort of mental disorder that they don't seek help with, with a few genuinely evil people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 22:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an easy slip up if you are used to one way and see it another way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 22:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 57% of solviet POWs died 

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/German_mistreatment_of_Soviet_prisoners_of_war

Granted it's wiki but the sources in wiki cited seem reliable enough  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it's the ~wannacry ransomware. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To back up his claims, only around 40% of solviet POWs survived German prison camps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You've got ice... and more ice..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 12:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird that poison removes sap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 11:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now ff12 intro is beast, immerses you deeply into the story and the world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 11:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did I know it was Seymour before I even clicked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 06:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frankly my problem with trump is he is slow, very slow to denounce supports of his that do things like this.

I don't remember exactly his name but there is one right wing radio talk show prick that once hosted trump that spawns things like sandy hook conspiracy (Google that)

It's Alex jones he hosted trump in 2015, would it be too hard for trump to say "screw this guy"? This Alex guy is really screwing people's lives over and more. And he is not the only one just a prominent one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 23:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dog was an idiot who just couldn't realize that no, the cat doesn't want to cuddle, and yes she will scratch you if you try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 22:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nationalism is a weird and dangerous thing, I am Russian used to have a sense of pride in being Russian strangely enough, despite being far removed from Russia and having nothing good out of it. (Nothing bad either)

A psychologist or biologist could tell you more about this, but it's little more than a tribal instinct. A terrible one to have this day and age though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 11:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 10:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go be useful... this is why you can't have freedom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 10:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until now I was confused why a larger more powerful empire (but not by much) was not already attacking me. I just kept being a bigger douchebag hopping it wouldn't attack me just yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 10:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From reading some of the shitty "tenants" (some guy squats for a while and voila) some landlords had to deal with on this sub, I can imagine why he would be so cautious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 10:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that mean as a Russian citizen I must file for Russian taxes as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 21:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have not read that in years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 10:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one gain for the Americans would be the issue of forts and arming Indians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 09:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Japan nukes didn't leave as much radiation as one would think, they popped them mid-air (to increase AoE) and as a side effect less lasting radiation than a ground explosion. But not saying the radiation released didn't have any immediate-long term results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 09:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mistakes happen, just 2 weeks ago paramedics declared a women dead only for police who arrived to make a report to revive her with CPR. If with all our modern technology we cannot 100% determine if one has died I doubt innpast ages they could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screw it, slave empire here I come </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fit four 2" by 4" that were 20' long into a Prius once. Not on top, I mean into the car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Power came back up a little while ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Power outage in natomas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently a power outage in natomas, looks like summer truly started now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last stand saves the day. In fact it makes the fight much easier, I clear it with 6 champs on multiplayer.

Last round was: cloud and Mif XIV, Fang and Ystol, zidane and zack. The kicker? Ystol did not have a wall (only asylum) and we still passed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it opened my eyes to last stand. Before this week my Mif XIV was lv 35 and neglected, now she is lv 99 and half dived. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should be enough, you can ultra cure the other white mage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it was more, the boss can do as much as damage as he wants, it will charge our SB gauges faster, and no one will really die with so much back to back last stand and reraise spam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She didn't do as much damage but I didn't need to heal her much as I kept her in the air with leaching jump. I think dragoons are some of the best bc they can do that atm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is fang considered bad (I have her Burst and over) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ours did more akin to 9999, but we had a "shout" (Mif SSB gives attack up large and last stand) and onion BSB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My father got pickpocketed and he spent $60+ On a pay phone before the various bank accounts he has could be frozen (please hold dam it)

To be fair he tries to take advantage of all these open account bonuses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My set up was lv 99 Firon BSB, lv 99 Ramza shout/chant, lv 82 Faris USB, lv 80 Cait Sith toy soldier, and lv 99 Aerith BSB. RW wall

Pretty much I debuffed the crap out of the boss and (should have) took my time to build SB for Firon. I got lucky with one of my Firon Burst, but I recommend putting silence resistance on your why mages and screw the rest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last stand was a godsend this fight, bc last stand is not triggered by the (send your character to 1 hp ability) only by an ability that would actually kill. Even so the reraise was used, often, probably around 9 times total but in the end still mastered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The OK, Cid, and to a smaller extent Vannile were nothing more than meat shields in my team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firion BSB is pretty sweet, I have it too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow the synergy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 man team, (the cloud did 3/4th of the damage alone on my team, everyone else where more of supports) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dismissal blade on mif was important to get rid of the haste (otherwise she did nothing but wrath) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The XII hardest level MP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally beat it after a 30 min battle of Mif XIV last stand, Lenna Reraise, 2 ystols, a vanilla XIII, Cloud, Cid (tactics), and an OK who wisely did nothing but use his burst. (He afked so I controlled him and the ystol). How did others beat it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firon II BSB, its really one of the Best BSB (instant cast, mag blink to all on team) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There a visitor center for the old Folsom powerhouse museum, I got a nice angle and fairly close while on a small guided tour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A worst case happened </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> alright will go for the stone shooter banner bc I will be the least disappointed in a worst case scenario  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh side note, is fran or mustidio better as a damage support (if they have their Burst) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best banner out of the 4 to draw </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently I am really looking at FFT stone shooter and Fran's burst, I would go for Fran, and the USB Pennelo but my XII synergy, while not perfect is better than my FFT. And I already have the Burst for XII gab. On the other hand I have CID Burst (and only that for cid). The other FFT banner I would love the USB for Ramza and the pole for the witch, but already have the genii gloves. The 2nd banner for XII has not been released so I don't know anything about it. What's the best one to grab? (I have a ton of heal and physical Burst, no support Burst, ok amount of mage Burst)

Edit: QQ, I got crap. 1/11 headband, feels bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 10:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last thing I want is squirrels to pop in my car, most of these squirrels are non-native too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 10:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine trying to measure a tree with a tape measure. If it's big you are not going to have a good time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 10:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god I remember Yosemite squirrels and I hope it won't come to that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> syphilis Hit Europe really hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just care, I am not familiar with new models but older models can force enough electric current into you to kill you.

Even unplugged </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to deal with this shit, but isn't the 3 white strips the factory adhesive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> XII as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you link a good version? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marking this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your story puts a bit of fear in my heart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your story puts a bit of fear in my heart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly was a bit surprised that FDR, crippled from polio, had an affair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just driving through the park to reach the interior takes time, it can get congested at times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try local subreddits such as /r/Sacramento as well.

They often have posts or sidebars for people coming in to see the sights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guessing they needed a suitable punishment for the crime  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The east lasted longer and in years before the breakup had the majority of the economy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While for me I have to ask didn't they stop after encountering stiff resistance, I have forcibly done some pretty stupid stuff that would be obvious to others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Error 404 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine a horror game where in the middle of a tense part, they turn on a blue screen of death for a few seconds, and then right after some horrifying jump scare  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Japan and Russia were going to go to war eventually even if the mess in Europe didn't happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting is there a specific website for sac radon gas levels? The best I found was for the country  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downtown is ok, most of the streets are ok but there are some serial offenders. Watt comes to mind, but that's not exactly capital </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Lol' uh I wouldn't say exactly funny, sorry if I'm pedantic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is one in natomas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a pedestrian I walk 3-4 steps away, as a bicyclist if they really don't get the hint, I get off and prop the bicycle up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in some locations a spikes stripe sounds ok but shredded tires would make you lose control of your vehicle, particularly I am thinking of short ramps or ones that descend onto the high way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds awesome. What's the details on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are Sac radon levels high? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well not axis but as a semi-neutral  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you (that's kinda what I actually did, transplanted the engine and transmission.) overall I should be fine as the DMV and CHP (CA highway patrol) inspected and signed off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I under stand the British won the battle, and then afterwards the storm hit the Spanish.

Part of the reason why the British won was their cannons were better and kept their range and during the main battle a brilliant but risky move by the British paid off:

Normally during a battle between ships of the line there is a tactic called "crossing the T" where your ships would perpendicularly cut through the enemy fleet, that way your port/storport cannons would be hitting the enemy while the enemy would only be able to fight back with their few front/back cannons, and even then might end up hitting their own ships...

...But the British deliberately allowed their T to be crossed! The wind was blowing at the Spanish backs and half the Spanish ships quickly crossed the T... and realized they couldn't rejoin the battle bc they would be sailing upwind. With that move the British effectively cut the effective Spanish fleet in half in that battle.

Note this is just information I absorbed from various Reddit posts so feel free to correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What made it wrong? From my understanding this is a grey area with no strict rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I learned from the same source  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I feel like a psychopath who is a serial killer. To be fair, a good portion of them were to strengthen the cursed katana </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
