<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2621</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much to sell my paintings for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm new to this and people just started asking to buy my work. Need help with the price. https://m.imgur.com/a/ebxpZ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 22:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ex looks like a more attractive version of me. I'm bi and get hit on by both genders a lot, he does too though he's gay. One time he decided to see the what all the fuss was about and slept with a girl. He didn't like it and he's only bottomed since, to my knowledge (haven't spoken With him in a couple months)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 21:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between ten minutes to ten hours honestly. Though I have been dating a guy for a bit over a month now and we haven't fucked yet...it's weird for me lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a trick to the colors. 


Blue: everyday wear 

Green: clubbing or parties 

Brown: weddings and the like 


The best companies only carry those colors and as long as you're paying around fifty for the bottle you're probably getting some good stuff  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disk golf 

Painting 

Gym 

Tennis  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 05:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I've been getting healthy I've started getting more attracted to myself so I think it's normal lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 05:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a bottle of wine (moscato is a safe delicious wine everyone will love) get Bella Bolle (the best tasting and cheep) pick up sone acrylic paint and brushes from Walmart. Grab a two pack of canvas. Open Netflix and paint along with bob Ross the joy of painting. 

Total cost: about 20-25 dollars  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 04:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm for abortion without limits so I would definitely look down on someone who did this but I will defend their right to do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 04:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get hard whenever I find out my partner is hard :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd give you a hug and buy you a drink of this wasn't the internet! 

You are awesome :) 
I admire you for doing this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 01:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd giggle, if you're cute I'd laugh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cuddling with a guy and feeling him slowly get hard against you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The confusion that comes from not knowing if you're attracted to a guy or if you want to look like the guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can only do it on festivus after feats of strength  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm cute, monogamous and left wing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really glad you are in a good place now man. I just cried a few tears for him too. Take care of yourself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am to a very sweet guy that I met six months ago. I'm known to get into relationships for a couple months at a time  then something happens and we break. I met this guy right after one break and I asked him to go to steak and shake with me (I only had $10 on me but I was lonely). It took some convincing but he said yes, we stayed and talked there for sure x maybe even seven hours. Turns out we both have degrees in applied mathematics and there were a lot of other things we had on common too. We went on another date (we were both seeing other people at the same time too) and the second date was fun too. Then the other guy I was seeing wanted to get more serious with me (this guy was drop dead gorgeous) so I asked the first guy what he was interested in and he said that he's about to move away for his phd so nothing serious. I said yes to the other guy. We dated for a couple months and then broke up. The first guy and I remained friends, we hung out and text all the time and somehow while doing this I stopped seeing him as anything other than a close friend. I just don't have the feelings to be with him anymore. It turns out that his dream school (he never thought he'd get in) accepted him. It's only an hour away. So Joe every couple weeks I get a drunk text about how messed up with the perfect guy for him and how no one is ever going to compare. I feel bad about this but the feelings just aren't there for me.  

Now I'm seeing a wonderful guy and we are coming up on three months (I think) and we haven't split yet. My relationship with the guy I'm dating now is different than any other I've had before. This time it really does feel like I'm with an old friend every time I'm with him, I never feel the need to impress him and there aren't any topics that we avoid :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol it's all good now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww thank you lol

That's the most unique compliment I've ever received :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You replied in your regular account and not the throw away you posted with  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are really two approaches to this and it depends on what kind of person you are. Method one is for a confident outgoing personality, two is for more reserved. 


1: text him saying you're coming over and will be there in five minutes. Be by his place when you text him. Bring your twos favorite food. Force the conversation to happen. Don't give him enough time to say no. He is confused and you're confused, might as well be confused together. 


2: text him saying you two need to get together and discuss these feelings. Say you don't like what the awkwardness is doing to the relationship and you'll wait until he is ready to talk but you definitely want to talk about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't like him just say so. Sounds like he really likes you though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone's feelings are going to be hurt here bro. You have to let him know you don't feel the same way  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to talk with him. Air of grievances. Then decide if you wanna still be his friend  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Early in college I dated some people who worked in the admissions office with me. A ton of drama and I wouldn't recommend it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my go to pic lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a liquor store that has a beer selection from every state, it's pretty wonderful lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww thank you :) 
We have a vacation together in five weeks, I'm so excited  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a big easy from Abita and that was some good shit!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was drinking one of those not your fathers sweet teas. They are amazing! But if you're gonna drink beer then you have got to drink Guinness  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I posted it a while ago lol 

It's my go to pic, here is one with my boy so you know it's me  http://i.imgur.com/PRAduXo.jpg 

Edit: my boy wants me to clarify that he looks much better than that and I'm just shit at taking photos lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try r/GaySnapchatimages 

Here we just occasionally post pics of ourselves in the comments...like this lol http://i.imgur.com/rlJOB3n.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 06:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Pepe's in Frankfort! 
I'm in south bend these days  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 06:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Growing up in Indiana being gay was considered the worst thing so it became taboo. Taboo turned me on  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 04:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in the same place as you last year friend. 

You are not who your family thinks you are, you are not who your friends think you are, you are under no obligation to be the same person you were five minutes ago. You are loved. There are people who'd give you the shirt off their back, these people are your friends and all they want is for you to be happy. 

Don't run from yourself, embrace your desires. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 04:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've hand a few fractures and cracks. I didn't notice a couple of them, sometimes it just feels like a sprain or like a bruise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 04:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll find that it's a lot easier to date really hot guys than it is to date really hot girls. 

It looks like you're trying to get us to tell you it's ok for you to go out and cheat on your girlfriend. Cheating isn't cool but it's a personal choice. Just have to decide if you're that kind of guy or not. Once you start cheating though you'll find it's hard to stop, my ex gf cheated on everyone she ever dated after her first time cheating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 04:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry anyone would say something like that. You deserve much better than that man :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 04:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, usually with pizza and talk about going to rallies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have friends say they love me and call me babe...it's not concrete evidence  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk to him and tell the truth. You both need to know where the other stands.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm bi, a top, with women I'm switch, with men I'm dom. I dont think there is a general statement that can be said about sexuality like you're looking for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only been three months so just try and put the conversation off for now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What super power should you choose?

How many fourth graders could you take in a fight?

Helen Keller or Susan b Anthony?

M Ms or skittles?

Pretend you voted for trump, now defend it. 

What color of car just screams old people? 

Bowling or getting drunk and eating pizza at a bowling alley watching other people bowl? 

If you went back in time and your mother was about to have an abortion so you'd never be born, how would you convince her to keep you in five words. 

Favorite movie from before the 90s  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start going to bars with live music. Everyone becomes friends at those. 

Ask your old friends if they know any gay people. Everyone of my friends have tried to introduce me to their gay friends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somewhere around Chicago but not in Chicago. I live in south bend Indiana and my family is from Chicago. City life is great there and there are a ton of jobs everywhere out here. I'd definitely not live in the city though. I drive or take the train into town whenever I want to and I don't have to pay crazy city life costs. Plus Illinois is in major debt so it's not fun to live there. I like south bend. It is the most gay friendly city in Indiana with a gay mayor who was just running for dnc chair. We have a bunch of colleges, like Norte dame, and there is some fun to have in town. I road trip every weekend to Michigan or Illinois and we have Lake Michigan so there are some nice beaches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my experience the LGBT straight alliance was full of really far left minded people who couldn't shut up about politics. 

That being said, some of my closest friends in college regularly went to those meetings. I got along with everyone there individually but when they are together they start playing off eachothers energy and then we don't get along. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say something like "he was really nice but I'm sure your next guy will be a bit easier on the eyes." 

Every time you refer to Patrick compare him to Matt's future partner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 00:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's a pistol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free concert tickets to almost any performance, my sister's best friend owns a well known concert review site. I've taken advantage of this a few times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf just because your taste in bi guys cheats doesn't mean we all do  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell!? I'm bi and I've never cheated....wtf  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with being bi?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really late to the show but you have to know about Hero of Alexandria. 

He was a mathematician and engineer in the first century. He created an early wind turbine and a steam engine in THE FIRST CENTURY!!! Only he didn't see the value in these for anything other than temple artifacts...we could be 17 centuries ahead if he had been less religious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same thing happened to me. My best friend even said "I take it you're playing sone sort of cruel prank because you'd make a disgusting gay man" he has apologized a ton of times since, he honestly thought I was pulling a prank on him. Still stings a bit though. 

Don't let this get you down. Remember that you are not who you spend time with. Do what makes you happy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black suit with white pin stripes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last weekend a guy asked me to come over for a date. It was a two hour drive but I said what the hell and went. The date was him, his dog and I walking on the beach and he got my favorite meal from Burger King lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, I have a Midwest voice (not too high, not too deep). I play disk golf, paint, listen to alternative music, my tv shows are the political and superhero ones lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went skinny dipping with my high school friends a few time during the summer. It was a little awkward at first but we got over it quick  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im bi but probably a bro...I'm pretty masculine and all though  http://i.imgur.com/JohBblA.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
