<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1497</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Bacon Tree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 10:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two Mexicans are stuck in the desert after crossing into the United States , wandering aimlessly and starving. They are about to just lie down and wait for death, when all of a sudden Luis says.........

"Hey Pepe, do you smell what I smell. Ees bacon, I theenk."

"Si, Luis, eet sure smells like bacon. "

With renewed hope they struggle up the next sand dune,   there, in the distance, is a tree loaded with bacon.

There's raw bacon, there's fried bacon, back bacon, double smoked bacon ... Every imaginable kind of cured pork.

"Pepe, Pepe, we ees saved. Ees a bacon tree."

"Luis, maybe ees a meerage? We ees in the desert don't forget."

"Pepe, since when deed you ever hear of a meerage that smell like bacon...ees no meerage, ees a bacon tree."

And with that, Luis staggers towards the tree. He gets to within 5 metres, Pepe crawling close behind, when suddenly a machine gun opens up, and Luis drops like a wet sock. Mortally wounded, he warns Pepe with his dying breath,

"Pepe... Go back man, you was right, ees not a bacon tree!"

"Luis, Luis MI amigo... What ees it? "

"Pepe.. Ees not a bacon tree. Ees

Ees

Ees

Ees

Ees a ham bush...."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it dimethylethylamine and not ethyldimethylamine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 08:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought -eth would come before -meth. But that doesn't seem to be the case. Why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 08:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus christ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are those viewing ports(?) for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add forced induction and you're easily past 100% VE, straight away. Thermal efficiency is what's being discussed here. Big difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big diesels can get thermal efficiencies past 50%, which is huge. Turbines can do better in some cases but there's no need to write off big, slow diesels, yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now I'm thinking of that fucking music. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man. Much appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I think I'll continue the way I am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, true - I was mainly getting at the ridiculous taxes on alcohol here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 15:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm. Never thought of that. I will look into it. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 15:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then they need to keep sufficient quantities of change on hand. There is no excuse for that. It's not that hard to work out what denominations you need for the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 15:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you talking about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 15:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, they 'failed' when they were asked to do something they were not designed to do, coupled with technical faults. Amazing. And look at that - alternative sources made up the deficit, very nicely. Anyone would think the operators don't know how to manage such a situation. The situation was adequately managed and homes and businesses were NOT left without power. Wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 15:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares? Take it to politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 14:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roobarb and Custard - Aussies will get this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 14:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very interesting. Are talking blocks of AC, powder or some other form? What were you removing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 14:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you slick you hair back using the grease from your face? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 14:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I'm a little off topic but it makes me wonder how I can buy a case of 500 mL Oettinger cans for less than $2 a can, when it's imported from Germany - and I'm paying far more than that for any of the big names in Aussie beer, even on special. It's fucking ridiculous. I want to see the big names reeled in and start selling beer for a realistic price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 14:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers, mate. I was thinking that perhaps an equilibrium was set up with CO and O but that is not the case, apparently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 14:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically harmless, unless you inhale it. The vast majority (by percentage) of uranium isotopes are alpha emitters. Alpha radiation won't even go close to penetrating your skin. Absolutely safe to handle without even wearing gloves.

The real danger is inhalation. Alpha radiation damages exposed, dividing cells. Inhalation of alpha emitters can be a serious problem. So you would want to wear the proper safety gear with regard to respiration when handling uranium.

Take, for instance, polonium-210 - the substance used to kill Alexander Litvinenko. Po-210 is basically harmless when in contact with your skin. But it emits so many alpha particles that it is absolutely deadly when inhaled or taken into the digestive tract, where nice, fresh cells are exposed to the alpha radiation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 14:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking cut that mofo off, the first chance I get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 14:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Won't whatever the fuck it's cut with crystallise out, once the solution cools down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 14:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not Asian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 14:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry - I meant normal as in engines without this energy recovery bullshit. I'd like to see turbocharged engines of ANY capacity - so long as they can compete with the same fuel allowance as everyone else. I simply do not understand the idea of limiting *specific* fuel consumption. No one has ever been able to explain it. 

You have some allocated quantity of fuel (xyz kg) - why the fuck would you need to limit the *instantaneous* consumption of that fuel allowance? I really don't get it, at all. Every team must get to the finish with xyz kg. Why penalise them for using more than abc kg/hr at any point in the race? It makes absolutely no sense, whatsoever.

Look at the old 80s turbo cars - they were managing that specific rate in real time. The driver had to back off, and/or limit boost to finish the race, in many cases. Far, far more exciting than just saying you have 160 kg @ (max) 100 kg/h. I hate the FIA and their micromanaging bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers mate. I'm really thinking about just dropping the cash on Steam. I'm sick of this shit - I just want to get past this bug. I might try one more pirate version. If it won't work, I'll go legit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah - fucking camphor laurel or something! I think you know what I mean by that persistent, shitty after taste. Seriously, I have bought bottles of that garbage that cost more than a hundred bucks, hoping for some revelation - and it's just the same shit. The same. Fucking. Shit.

And don't get me started on that Red crap. My cat could piss a better bottle of spirits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers, mate. I thought it would be something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too much, really. I want to drink more than one glass before I'm shitfaced. I never understood the attraction to spirits much more than about 60%. It's like that one bloke who insists you try his home brew and before you even taste it, he's bragging that it's 9% or some shit. Who the fuck wants to drink 9% alcohol beer?

Inner Circle Black dot is still 75.9% and Green is 57.2%. That's plenty for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't care how they sound - I just want to see this energy recovery crap gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you just assume... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just happened to have the right hex key to undo the very first bit of bodywork... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you guys mean by fly-by-wire in this context? I know what that means with regard to cars but what does it mean with aircraft? Surely no modern jet could be operated with pedals and levers directly linked to the control surfaces? Or do you mean something entirely different? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have not tried it, yet. I looked it up and I'm discouraged by the light colour and the reviews of light, vanilla and buttery tastes - looks like it might be closer to some kind of spiced rum. I dunno. I like darker stuff but everyone is different.

My problem with Bundy is the strange and persisting after taste. And furthermore, the fact that no matter how much you pay for it, that taste is always there. I have dropped some serious coin on the more expensive bottles of Bundy and I honestly couldn't taste the difference between them and the standard stuff. Extremely disappointing but I learned my lesson - fuck Bundy. Only drink it if nothing else is available. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a semi-legal idea to fix my bugged game. Will it work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I downloaded Witcher 3 and I have a bug that breaks the game. I just need to talk to one NPC and it will be fixed. I have tried for days and nothing I do works.

So, what if I buy it on Steam (so it's the very latest version), load my save file, play it for the five minutes I need to get rid of the bug and then say I didn't like it and get my money back?

Could this work? I don't really have 70 bucks to spend on games right now but I could cough it up if I was sure to get it back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks how it should look - half an inch off the ground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read just yesterday that Apple have exclusive rights to use some kind of material - I think it was the 'molecular trampoline' - in *any* device. And that does not expire for several years. If that's true, it's just a cunt act by Apple and further proof of why the entire patent system needs overhauling.

I always did hate them from day one - the one button mouse. I will never, ever willingly buy or use their shit. Hate their marketing and pretentious feel of their whole existence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't a boost limit mean they are air limited? Personally, I'd love to see these energy harvesting contraptions and fuel flow limits completely gone. I don't watch race cars to marvel at their fuel efficiency. Everyone is always carrying on about keeping costs down - wouldn't normal engines help with that a great deal?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have a flute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where OP is talking about. Different parts of the world and even within countries have different rules and all that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just downloaded it (the GOG one) from TPB and the files did not pass the integrity test. I can only see three torrents for Witcher 3 with the skull next to them. And I already have one of them - it's got a game breaking bug. Should I trust a torrent with no skull? Should I reinstall the one I have? I don't know what to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 11:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forget Bundaberg. Fucking garbage. It's nothing compared to the original Australian rum, Inner Circle. Get some of that up ya and see for yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone help out a noob with regard to SkidRow torrents? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 11:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I found the SkidRow site and I notice people talk about it here. I want Witcher 3 - found it on this page:

https://www.skidrowreloaded.com/the-witcher-3-wild-hunt-game-of-the-year-edition-v1-31-repack/#more-31398

Looking at those torrents is sort of making me nervous. Never heard of zippy share or any of the rest. Are they trustworthy? I've only ever used TPB before, where you can look for the little skull that signifies a trusted uploader. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 11:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you even talking about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 10:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucken oath. He is an absolute disgrace - but so is the entire organisation he works for. Yet every time the fucking Pope opens his mouth it gets posted on places like reddit and everyone says what a great guy he is, how 'progressive' he is. Fuck all that - he presides over a network of paedophiles. Who gives a fuck what he has to say unless it's an admission of guilt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 07:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever heard of international law? See the bit about summary execution. And torture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 07:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evolutionary backwater. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 07:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Islam in action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 07:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another islamic triumph!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 07:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 07:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Catholic Church should be declared a criminal organisation and any person found to be giving them monies considered complicit. It's good enough to do that for bikie gangs. I don't really see why the CC should be any different. Confiscate their money, properties and anything else they own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 07:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have said this so many times - if you want to see just how devious, untruthful and disturbing this man is, just look up his 60 Minutes interview on youtube. 

He basically incriminates himself. And by the time he realises, it's too late to backtrack. It really is worth watching - the longer it goes on, the bigger the hole he digs for himself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 06:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slugs out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 06:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that is one massive front-bum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 06:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the CO2 being turned into charged particles, at all? Is there some sort of equilibrium like CO2 -- CO + O in play? Or is it a strictly physical process? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a quick question on reinstalling the same game but from a different source </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 06:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Witcher 3 game is bugged, so I downloaded a different version (newer) from a different source. Can I just install the new version without deleting any of the old one? The one that's already installed doesn't show up in Control Panel at all. 

The .iso for the one that is bugged is in Program Files (x86). I was planning on putting the other one in Program files. Is that a good idea? 

Can I realistically hope that installing a new version will fix the bug?

TL:DR - do I have to remove the old one before I can use the new one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 06:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you find it at the bottom of the sea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 06:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have wondered for years why some of the Soviet/Russian jets have such a wide spacing of the engines. This is the first reasonable explanation I have seen. But how exactly, does that spacing create active lift? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 06:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you for real? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 06:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 175 L/day? There are natural leaks worse than that. This is nothing but a beat up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 06:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, we can only look at so many pictures of Camel cigarette packs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 06:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's that odd looking part of the exhaust system you can see at exactly 3:07? It's on the right hand side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is supercritical carbon dioxide so good at cleaning and extracting things? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 05:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wiki basically says that it is but not much more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 05:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, sure it's common. There must be three pools with curtains or something. You're trying to tell me it's a coincidence that they suddenly need curtains in what's become the muslim capital of Australia and there's no ulterior motive. Why can't men who feel self conscious join the women behind the curtains, then? All groups, remember? Is pathetic that people are pandering to their separatist ideology. Go swim in the pool like everyone else or go home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was only implemented at the behest of muslims. This shit did not exist before their numbers got large enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, what if men want segregated hours and areas? In my day, you went to the fucking pool and everyone saw everyone. Why change that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why has this happened in a muslim hot-spot? I don't see other areas implementing this garbage. It is solely down to muslims demanding their own place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought as much. Just keep shifting the blame/responsibility around until no one has any overreaching authority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when surround sound was the next big thing - and it really didn't do much for me. More annoying than anything, actually. I almost never watch movies and I sure as shit don't need it to listen to music in surround sound. Two speakers with a decent range is more than enough for me. I even question stereo sound for music. I have songs in mono and I really cant see a reason to find stereo versions. I can't tell the difference, apart from (for example) when they deliberately alternate a drum line from one side to the other - I find that quite annoying, to be honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A very touching song and melody. I can only listen to it occasionally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asking GPs - just how many conditions/diseases/syndromes/etc do you realistically remember? How often are you forced to consult some medical dictionary when faced with something 'unusual'? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 14:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 14:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly is a pinched nerve? Pinched between what? Bones? Muscles? What's happening when I wake up and my neck hurts like shit because I 'slept on it wrong'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 14:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuckin' gold, cunt. Fuckin' gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 14:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take your moral platitudes somewhere else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 14:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, maybe not... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 14:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So are they fired? That would make me believe they didn't support those actions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A gentleman will walk but never run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always loved Part Time Lover </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shout At The Devil was pretty good, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cold Chisel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gimme Gimme Gimme has always been a favourite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dooo, do do, do! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Motley Crue - Kickstart My Heart

Guns 'N Roses - Nightrain

The Bee Gees - You Win Again

Australian Crawl - The Boys Light Up

Billy Idol - White Wedding

Cheap Trick - Surrender

Fleetwood Mac - Go Your Own Way

Fuck, too many to name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub is about moral guidance, now? Shut up. No one needs to hear what your view on that shit is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My house is very close to the node. Could I somehow pay to have fibre installed for the last 50-100 m? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 12:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct. I remember that, too. Then you have the quarantined subs - basically because the admins are worried it might damage the image of this shithole. It's pathetic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 12:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same reason the admins won't reign in mods of large subreddits being complete fucktards - they're fucking useless and they don't even try to hide their vested interests/political-social leanings. That's why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 12:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, how am I only half right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Auburn pool gets swim screen for Muslim women </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 12:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 11:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, this sounds encouraging. Thanks very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 11:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had that a lot as a kid. I would turn up to Camp Quality hoping to see a friend or two I had made at the last one or at the Childrens' Hospital. But so many times, the adults would tell me he's not coming - ever again. Sometimes I would see their names in the newsletters (this was the mid 80s) - and you can guess what that meant. I still remember them, 30 years on. I saw too many people fr the last time, even before I was 10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 10:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does plugging in and switching on such a device draw no current, until a load is applied to the 5 V side? Or is there always a small current flowing through the HV side? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 10:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I get you keg of beer, Teenwolf? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 10:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit logo, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 10:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And fuck pinterest, anyway. I am NOT making an account, just to look at stupid shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 10:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Sony Ericsson one is shit. Fucking terrible logo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Witcher 3 game has a game breaking bug. Need some advice on an alternate version. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 09:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I downloaded it ages ago - V 1.21. It's got a game ruining bug and I'm wondering if installing a different version and using my old saves will be able to fix it. 

I'm looking on TPB and I see two versions that are 1.31. Is that the latest? If not, does anyone have a suggestion on where to get the latest edition? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 07:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers, I'll check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Win 8.1] Is there a way to stop tabs down at the bottom of the screen showing a preview of what they are when you mouse over them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 07:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, I have a spreadsheet, a Word document, several internet windows and so on at the base of the screen. 

I don't want to see them pop up a little window showing me what's displayed in that tab if I accidentally hover over one with the mouse pointer for more than about one second. 

Is there a way I can stop this shit?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a mod out there which will allow me to complete a bugged quest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 06:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't give the acid to Yoana so she can make the armour. I've tried previous saves, going to and from places and all that shit. Nothing works. This is a major point in the game. I need this quest completed. Are there any mods that will allow it? [Witcher 3][PC] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is there a mod to let you complete quests? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 06:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got a bug where I can't give Yoana the acid for the armour. She won't interact with me. I'm extremely pissed off. This is simply not good enough. I've tried reloading previous saves and all of that bullshit and it won't work. This is a major part of the game and I'm stuck.

Is there a mod that will let me get around this bullshit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 06:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asbestos filters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 06:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many years did it take? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 06:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch your tongue, Mister. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You will pay for your insolence! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how the reggae bit at the end plays on that childrens' rhyme - 3, 6, 9 the goose drank wine... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monkey pack 'im rizla pon the sweet dep line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheaper and you need to smuggle a much smaller amount. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not knocking it - if you like it, then that's good. I just don't see what all the fuss is about, really. I've never bothered with it. Two speakers are good enough for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It existed in the first place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh. I don't get the appeal, to be honest. I could easily set up such a system in my home. But no, I use high quality stereo speakers - two big fuck-off speaker stacks. That will do me, just fine. And yes, I have experienced such 'surround' set-ups in various places. It's just not that good. Not really exciting, at all. The sound should never outpace the visuals. Surround sound is a novelty to me, at best. And at times it's actually annoying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The tide turns. Finally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you find that Effexor made you have an insatiable thirst for alcohol? I felt good when I was on it but my alcohol consumption was absolutely staggering. I just could not get enough. I quit the Effexor and now I don't suffer from he level of alcoholism I used to. It's very strange. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
