<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3727</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 08:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could be trained up in any profession of your choice by top professionals what profession would you choose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 08:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 08:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not at all, student and daily wages worker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 08:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot drive because of my vision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quotes From Great Books </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 08:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
There is some good in this world, and its worth fighting for.

 J.R.R. Tolkien, 
The Two Towers

Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things that you didnt do than by the ones you did do.

 H.Jackson Brown Jr., 
P.S. I Love You

It is better to be hated for what you are than to be loved for what you are not.

 Andr Gide, 
Autumn Leaves

Who, being loved, is poor?

 Oscar Wilde, 
A Woman of No Importance

Every human life is worth the same, and worth saving.

 J.K. Rowling, 
Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows

Get busy living, or get busy dying.

 Stephen King, 
Different Seasons

The goal isnt to live forever, the goal is to create something that will.

 Chuck Palahniuk, 
Diary

Travel far enough, you meet yourself.

 David Mitchell, 
Cloud Atlas

None of us really changes over time. We only become more fully what we are.

 Anne Rice, 
The Vampire Lestat

Most people are nice when you finally see them.

 Harper Lee, 
To Kill a Mockingbird

All endings are also beginnings. We just dont know it at the time.

 Mitch Albom, 
The Five People You Meet In Heaven

When someone leaves, its because someone else is about to arrive.

 Paulo Coelho, 
The Zahir

Its no use going back to yesterday, because I was a different person then.

 Lewis Carroll, 
Alices Adventures in Wonderland

The only limits for tomorrow are the doubts we have today.

Pittacus Lore, 
The Power of Six

It is our choices that show what we truly are, far more than our abilities.

 J.K. Rowling, 
Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets

If we wait until were ready, well be waiting for the rest of our lives.

 Lemony Snicket, 
The Ersatz Elevator

Fear doesnt shut you down; it wakes you up.

 Veronica Roth, 
Divergent

When you are imagining, you might as well imagine something worth while.

 Lucy Maud Montgomery, 
Anne of Green Gables

The worst enemy to creativity is self-doubt.

 Sylvia Plath, 
The Unabridged Journals of Sylvia Plath

Yes: I am a dreamer. For a dreamer is one who can only find his way by moonlight, and his punishment is that he sees the dawn before the rest of the world.

 Oscar Wilde, 
The Critic as Artist

I dream. Sometimes I think thats the only right thing to do.

 Haruki Murakami, 
Sputnik Sweetheart

If I got rid of my demons, Id lose my angels.

 Tennessee Williams, 
Conversations with Tennessee Williams

It is sometimes an appropriate response to reality to go insane.

 Philip K. Dick, 
Valis

If youre making mistakes it means youre out there doing something.

 Neil Gaiman, 
Make Good Art

Even a stopped clock is right twice a day.

Paulo Coelho, 
Brida

If my life is going to mean anything, I have to live it myself.

 Rick Riordan, 
The Lightning Thief

To define is to limit.

 Oscar Wilde, 
The Picture of Dorian Gray

Art enables us to find ourselves and lose ourselves at the same time.

 Thomas Merton, 
No Man Is an Island

If you dont imagine, nothing ever happens at all.

 John Green, 
Paper Towns

Everything is possible. The impossible just takes longer.

 Dan Brown, 
Digital Fortress

So many things are possible just as long as you dont know theyre impossible.

 Norton Juster, 
The Phantom Tollbooth

We are all in the gutter, but some of us are looking at the stars.

 Oscar Wilde, 
Lady Windermeres Fan

Pain is inevitable. Suffering is optional.

Haruki Murakami, 
What I Talk About When I Talk About Running

Above all, dont lie to yourself.

 Fyodor Dostoyevsky, 
The Brothers Karamazov

Some infinities are bigger than other infinities.

 John Green, 
The Fault in Our Stars

You never know what worse luck your bad luck has saved you from.

 Cormac McCarthy, 
No Country For Old Men

We must all face the choice between what is right and what is easy.

 J.K. Rowling, 
Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire

Nothing thats worthwhile is ever easy.

 Nicholas Sparks, 
Message in a Bottle

Its only after weve lost everything that were free to do anything.

 Chuck Palahniuk, 
Fight Club

Time you enjoy wasting is not wasted time.

 Marthe Troly-Curtin, 
Phrynette Married

It is never too late to be wise.

 Daniel Defoe, 
Robinson Crusoe

Appear weak when you are strong, and strong when you are weak.

 Sun Tzu, 
The Art of War

When you want something, all the universe conspires in helping you to achieve it.

 Paulo Coelho, 
The Alchemist

One day I will find the right words, and they will be simple.

 Jack Kerouac, 
The Dharma BumsAnything worth dying for is certainly worth living for.

 Joseph Heller, 
Catch-22

All we have to decide is what to do with the time that is given to us.

 J.R.R. Tolkien, 
The Fellowship of the Ring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get inspired by the worlds most recognized book quotes  and make sure to read or re read the books they come from. Internet users share hundreds of thousands of quotes every day. Not too many people know that many of these great thoughts come from books. Even fewer know which books. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 08:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as a passenger 80 KPH. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats the fastest you've ever driven (as driver or passenger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't think so but not sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> serious Could you ever have an affair with a married person? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much would it cost to buy your love? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> most of you aren't telling any reason of your atheism and changing religion . you are talking about just superficial things.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you discovered a new species of dinosaur what would you call it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You go to school, study hard, get a degree, and youre pleased with yourself, But are you wiser? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and after sometime again. it will stop when i will shutdown laptop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Serious You go to school, study hard, get a degree, and youre pleased with yourself. But are you wiser? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I open Internet, first I see Have I gotten any reply on reddit than I do something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Porn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Science fiction novel"1984" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats your favorite fiction book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nothing, I cannot see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats the most interesting thing you can see out of your nearest window? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Razi Alvi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were a wrestler what would your stage name be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sherlock Holms, Tarzen, a man called X, Shadow, madame story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which fictional character do you wish was real? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who was your favorite teacher at school and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> dear European and American reddit readers, in third world countries there is a concept that you do not care about family. including old parents sibling etc. Is this write or wrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Madame story" detective </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> which animal do this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to faithful like a dog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could have any feature from an animal what would you want? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I choose comfort instead of fashion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what do you like stick to conventional fashions or like to try and be original? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
