<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1563</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the first joke on here that I actually laughed out loud at in a while. Nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you tell an optimistic tree from a pessimistic tree? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's negative, its roots are imaginary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that one was really weird </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the equations you get in physics come from calculus, so if you don't like calc then you won't like physics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We call those other ones deformities  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah exactly. Never breaking the law is lame. Doing illegal stuff is cool. Getting arrested for doing illegal stuff is not. Same concept; you want the fun without the consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How exactly would half-eaten cantaloupe seeds smell different than uneaten cantaloupe seeds? I'm curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 22:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took me forever to spot the difference  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link confirmed Jon Snow. He's even resurrected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black people can't be racist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 06:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's just an easy target. You can't miss her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 06:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I'm not being sarcastic at all. Completely serious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 06:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah because sarcasm is always subtle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try watching Game of Thrones. If you want justice, you're gonna have a bad time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never watched Mr. Show but i just binged all of Bob and David two nights ago. Absolutely hilarious. Definitely need to check out Mr. Show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 02:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of like how Batman has a fear of bats. I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 01:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Why can't you just lettuce be right!? You don't carrot all about health, you just have to prove how smart you are!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 01:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [this](https://youtu.be/CSav51fVlKU) needs to be played over it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because it's introducing voice acting into a game that didn't have it before. Even if the voice acting is decent, what does t really add to the game? You know what bowser says through the captions. Everything leads up the final boss fight, and you're ready to fight this evil creature that you've been waiting so long to finally face, and then he just talks like a goofy pirate. It's odd and it's a massive letdown. Really takes away from the gravity of the moment. Besides, Bowser in SM64 was just so much more menacing because you never heard him speak. 

Also, it's not just Nintendo I criticize. I hated FO4 for using a voice actor for the player character. Totally ruined immersion and made me feel disconnected from my character. Sometimes voice acting is just the wrong way to go. Introducing it to a series that never had it is a big risk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 17:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't explain voice acting. They could have saved time by not doing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That final boss bowser in Sunshine was just all around odd. The voice acting was horrendous. Why would they do that?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like food. You can go to a 5 start restaurant and have the best food you can imagine, but does that mean you'll never eat pizza again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reaching into his wallet and handing me money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's nice that he's getting better at commentating because after he fights Jones he'll need a new career. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 06:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want this game, it looks incredible. However, I really don't like how Mario looks in a city with somewhat realistic people in it. He looks horribly out of place because the art style doesn't match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah they really ruined Andy by the end of it. I hated his guts in the final seasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 17:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is that selfish? Are you supposed be concerned about your nonexistent siblings' nonexistent kids? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 17:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There has to be an AMA now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 17:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get annoyed that there's just so many holidays in general, not specifically just mother's day. But actually mother's day was kinda nice. I just don't like the idea that you're supposed to do something that day. It would be much better to just do something nice for your mom just because. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 06:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you actually read my comment. I'm not opposed to it. Just don't make a mountain out of a molehill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 06:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nigger is way different than ladyboy. Ladyboy isn't a nice thing to say but it's nowhere near as offensive and vulgar as "nigger." 

I'm not saying you can't be opposed to the term and tell people they shouldn't use it, but getting overly upset over it and acting as if it's deeply offensive when at worst it's mildly insulting is just being a crybaby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 03:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go cry. Yeah, it's shitty for someone to hate on trans people but if you can't handle a comment like "ladybody" on the internet, you're not cut out for the real world. That's really tame compared to actual offensive things people say about trans people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 02:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *applies cocoa butter* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 00:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it was Asian men remind them of their sisters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 00:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe, but that's not what she wrote. That's like saying goodbye Ohio, hello Cincinnati. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 20:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has to be a troll  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 20:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean that is pretty stupid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 15:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice repost  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 08:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You kill animals. This person killed an animal. It's essentially the same. You don't get to feel morally superior. You don't care about animals, don't pretend you do. I don't. That's why I eat meat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 08:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do people act like they care about animals when they have no problem eating animals that have been tortured and live miserable loves every day? I'm not being a hypocrite, I eat meat too. But i'm not gonna lie and say i care about every animal that suffers. It's just so gross to me to see so many self righteous cunts act like they care about this animal being killed while they stuff their faces with beef jerky or bacon. Quit acting like you care. It's so fake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you tell a muslim terrorist from a regular muslim? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 08:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm honestly asking, because it's a difficult issue we have to deal with as a society. We can't just stereotype an entire religion, however it's no coincidence that many acts of terror are done in the name of Islam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 22:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you actually have a chance at losing your virginity in a way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 19:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know why you're being downvoted. Ham is salt and fat, cheese is fat. Put it on bread with condiments, it's not any healthier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 19:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does Rousey being a bad striker have to do with what I said at all? I'm simply saying it's fun to see fighters that Reddit circlejerks over, like Rousey, get beat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I'll be so happy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He might want that to happen, but it won't. He'll lose again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll honestly be so happy when he does. DC fans are so annoying. "He's such a good guy, he's a family man, he works hard, such a role model..." It's like this sub has just become a giant PR machine for DC. It's always satisfying to see a fighter that everyone circlejerks to go down in spectacular fashion (e.g. Rousey).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cormier isn't the "good guy." He's a self-righteous, insecure cunt who wants so badly to be seen as a stand up guy and wants people to like him. Dude just rubs me the wrong way. Yeah i'm sure he's a decent person, and he cares about his family etc., but once you start getting upset that people boo you, and you feel like you're entitled to praise because you're a "good guy" you're just displaying how fragile of an ego you have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ain't gonna happen. Jones is gonna win. He's a better fighter no matter how much this sub hates him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 16:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean a korok mask. Casul </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 16:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless the parents always dressed exactly the same, they'd be stuck in an infinite loop of trying to dress like the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 04:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/titlegore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did you hear that the Energizer Bunny got arrested? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 03:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was for public masturbation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 20:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  pertend
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 16:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically as in "technology," since C3P0 is a droid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 16:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not with celebrities but people I know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 15:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying he doesn't believe it, I'm saying it doesn't make sense to call him Christian. Does he ask himself to be forgiven for his sins? Does he worship himself? Is he his own messiah? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 15:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How could Christ be a Christian? He's God in the flesh. Are you saying God worships himself? Are you saying Jesus accepts himself as the messiah and asks himself to be forgiven? That's nonsense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 05:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. It takes me about 10 seconds to take a piss. Not worth taking my phone out. Shitting on then other hand takes me a lot longer now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 05:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean is experimenting with drugs really all that crazy? I feel that's kinda normal, especially in college. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 04:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hate the trend of redefining words like this. Racism is the belief that your race is superior and/or other races are inferior. No more, no less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 04:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you implying Christ was a Christian? That makes no sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 20:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuuuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 18:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *gets modded to look like Woody from Toy Story* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 18:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *gets cracked over the head with a super sledge* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 13:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. I think it's because I can explore a game world without being bothered or having to worry about people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 13:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never have. Smoked cigars, hookas and even had pipe tobacco. Cigarettes smell absolutely disgusting to me. I have no interest in trying them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 13:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't run for a bus, especially one that's going up at a 90 degree angle! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 05:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chuck violently knocked her phone out of her hand with no explanation other than "it's rude to talk on the phone when you're a guest." That's a very aggressive thing to do. She didn't know about the illness because he hid it. 

She was quick to fly out to him once she heard about it and she wanted to make sure he was okay. This makes me think she really does care a lot about Chuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 04:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really can't see Howard doing that at all. Way out of character. He didn't even feel comfortable with Chuck's scheme to catch Jimmy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 04:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot the part where Nacho finds out he is, in fact, a McGill. He has his name legally changed to McGill and begins practicing as a lawyer. He threatens to have Hector kill Jimmy if Jimmy doesn't change his name. That's what makes Jimmy become Saul Goodman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ugh this guy is a total dumbass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facebook is a private company. They can do what they want. If you don't agree with Facebook don't use it. That said, this is really disgusting and we should continue exposing them so this doesn't happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're mixing up a bunch of shit there. All undead go hollow eventually when they run out of humanity. The chosen undead chooses to sacrifice himself to rekindle the flame. The Ashen  One was an undead who tried to link the flame but wasn't powerful enough so they just died (along with the other Unkindled). In DS3, the Ashen one is awoken by the bells. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh look at your face! You're practically hollow. But who knows, going hollow could solve quite a bit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sure kid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Parent Trap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't stand when faggots spoil movies like this. God fucking damn it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 22:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *whoosh* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you normally this retarded? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it. Was Ralph a child? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Checks original post*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not rocks, they're minerals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean this person has a pretty valid point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've reached a point where now it's not enough to accept other people's sexuality and gender expression, but you also have to take part in it, otherwise you're some kind of "phobic." As long as you're consenting adults, fuck whoever you want. Express yourself however you want. I'm not interested in dating men or transgender women. Sorry, I'm just not into it. Having preferences is fine. That's the entire point -- we all have preferences but we should accept that other people have different ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIII'm just checkin in on ya. Just checkin in ya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the point is that it's clearly a mental illness and that's why there is inconsistencies. I also thought that it was weird Chuck could sit in a car when clearly a car has a giant battery in it, and it powers the dashboard, windshield wipers etc. Even if the radio is off the battery is still on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you here?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just thinking, what if Frodo an Sam are gay? Just randomly thought of that on my own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus was apolitical. He didn't speak about how to govern. He spoke about how to treat others, how to be moral, and to get into heaven. I'll never understand why people try to make Jesus into a political figure. This is coming from someone who is atheist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just stop breathing. Pretty simple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For your Mac? Who games on a Mac? /r/pcmasterrace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ugh I hate people who go try to go into a bathroom without knocking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emma Watson is so damn hot that I don't care </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE always shut and lock the bathroom door even when home alone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was gonna say donkey is gray, but then I realized that there was that part where donkey becomes a steed in Shrek 2. I shouldn't know this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moondog. For some reason I really like that. Sounds like a cocktail I definitely wanna try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably on the environment/renewable energy. Something like a world where we've become extremely environmentally friendly, only use renewable energy, animal farming practices are extremely humane etc., but the drawback is complete and total authoritarian government. Something like burning gasoline or using paper would get you thrown in prison, and this is made even worse by mass surveillance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's by far the worst episode. I couldn't even finish it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I agree this really broke my immersion. They should have picked a really scrawny old guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> defiantly

first time in a long time I've seem that and it wasn't supposed to be definitely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is E3? Does it look promising or does it look like it will be a disappointment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That give me an idea actually, I could name my horses after dictators! Looks like I need to go and find new horses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but "horse" sounds more like "dorf" than "hoof" does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
