<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject398</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 19:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.wikihow.com/Tell-a-Horse%27s-Age-by-Its-Teeth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 19:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From buying a horse and telling it's age from it's teeth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 19:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I jumped on it. PM sent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So they got a room and got down to business. After a while the man asked for a blow job. The woman tells him she has something better for him and pops her fake eye out and uses the socket to get him off. It was THE most amazing sensation he had ever felt. As they were leaving he told her that he hope they could meet up again. She said she'd like that and would keep an eye out for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Micro fiber sheet](https://www.amazon.com/Best-Linens-Ever-Flat-Sheet/dp/B01EQP1MCO/ref=sr_1_2?s=bedbath ie=UTF8 qid=1484157733 sr=1-2 keywords=microfiber+flat+sheets refinements=p_n_size_browse-bin%3A362281011) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Jumbo Hammock](https://www.amazon.com/Sunnydaze-Portable-Hand-Woven-Hammock-Capacity/dp/B00TFOEYAO/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 qid=1484157488 sr=8-1-spons keywords=jumbo+hammock psc=1 smid=A3VCRITOBCN68L) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Jumbo Hammock](https://www.amazon.com/Sunnydaze-Portable-Hand-Woven-Hammock-Capacity/dp/B00TFOEYAO/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 qid=1484157488 sr=8-1-spons keywords=jumbo+hammock psc=1 smid=A3VCRITOBCN68L) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 00:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been a few years hanging inside. 64m Don't even have a bed anymore. I used to have an under quilt fashioned from a blanket , a few wire ties and some of those cheap bungies with the ball on one end. Worked fine but now I just have a double size microfiber sheet that is large enough that if I roll one way then the other it sloughs down behind me and I never get a chill. I also recommend getting away from the camping style bag. I used one to get started but bought one of those jumbo size woven types from Amazon (around $80 on sale). No more back pains, no more heel pain. No more tossing and turning trying to find comfort. No moe CBS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As I near my twilite. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 02:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this on Craigslist in Ohio. Thought someone may be interested. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 04:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have never heard a woman say "I feel great! I LOVE my man!! Life is wonderful!!!... It must be the hormones." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 16:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 15:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time can be hard to pass also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 02:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice find! I'm going to one up you though. Driving home through town one evening I past a house that was being cleaned out. Huge stack of household items at the curb. I spy 2 desk chairs so I stop. [Two Herman Miller Aeron](http://store.hermanmiller.com/Products/Aeron-Chair) desk chairs!!! Exactly like the one linked. One was missing a castor, the other was complete. I am driving a Geo Metro so I can only kind of stuff the best one in my open trunk for the mile ride home. Immediately did a 180 for the other but it was gone when I got back. Cleaned it up, working perfectly, gave it to my full stack son that spends his life in a desk chair. One of my better garbage finds. 
Second thought: After looking at your chairs value I take back my "Oneupmanship". You kicked my ass. On hella find fella! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 18:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://badoo.com/profile/0532821396/?r=2lUA1 p=6 from_search=1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever noticed that the older a man gets the more he looks like Sean Connery and the older a woman gets the more she looks like ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 20:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  uuuuummmm.....????? Sean Connery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 05:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many shades of red in natural red hair ranging from light strawberry blonde to dark auburn. Ginger is just a lighter shade of red with strong orange tones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> True redheads are born, girls with dyed red hair are just girls with red hair. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 03:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went to my local coffee roaster to get a pound... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 19:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cute counter girl ask how I'd like my grind.
Me, "Slow building to unbridled anger." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 21:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it is a thick item you have to allow the internal temp to get to 113f.
Edit: word
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 21:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put your larger items in a black plastic bag and lay it in the sun. Bed bugs and their nymphs/eggs are destroyed at 113 F / 45 C in 60 Minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 06:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to say this also to peel them under cold running water. The water helps by getting between the shell and the whites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 04:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, I was wondering how many. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many times is this mosquito in my room going to bite me tonight while I sleep? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 03:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
