<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1239</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was left over of a body after a funeral pyre and what did they do with whatever charred remains were still there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking of a traditional wood pyre where a body is placed upon a mound of wood and set alight. I know that this is a notable practice in both old Norse and Hindu culture, at least as far as I have been taught. It's also a common movie trope (the funeral of Vader in EP6 comes to mind as an example) but I doubt the movie depiction is an accurate one.

Anyways, I was struck by the thought that there must be some sort of mess to clean up. Wouldn't you have a charred husk of burnt bone? What did people from cultures that practiced this do with all of the mess? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 16:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem is there is no feasible way to remove these without destroying the frosting unless you sacrifice the box </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That hand model has some nasty looking nails. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 04:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There honestly needs to be legislation to hold judges accountable for this sort of thing. I'm sick of hearing about these people who hand slap-on-the-wrist sentences to murderers and rapists. It's nothing short of aiding and abetting criminals, and you should answer for it. If nothing else, it's a plain declaration of your gross incompetence to handle the judicial process. 

I haven't been this infuriated myself since that judge let off the Brock Turner kid with a 6 month sentence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 02:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet to be made aware of women being murdered, jailed, beaten etc. in the west for wearing hijabs. 

You can see scores of daily reports of the horrors women are subjected to outside of western society.

Why we have to insist the situations are equatable is absurd, and I honestly believe it's actively contributing to the undeniable patriarchies that exist abroad where women are treated like cattle and subject to brutal, socially condoned violence on a constant basis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Friend wants to do 531 but has joint condition that limits shoulder movement, cannot physically lift arms above head. Any alternatives to the OH press? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend has a bone growth condition that prevents his shoulder joints from being able to lift his arms above his head. This is a permanent condition that flexibility exercises won't be able to fix. He has enough range of movement to do incline presses, but I'm not sure if that will work as a substitute. Does any have any ideas, or can he just not do the program? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Guy Love!

That's all it is!

It's Guy Love!

He's mine I'm his!

There's nothing gay about it, in our eyeeeeeesss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> View of Boston from the Madonna Shrine (Taken by me) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet you're fun at parties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game is frustratingly hard to navigate. Doesn't give any reasonable indications as to where to go to progress. Had to look at the walkthrough just to figure out where the tiny hole was in the room I was stuck in for 20 minutes so I could crawl out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not gonna need that. You're gonna need a stress ball. Game was more frustrating than anything. Game gives no sense of direction. Was always too annoyed to be scared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every single online walkthrough for Outlast 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'll throw in my two cents on this because I 
[removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprise surprise, a man lost a custody case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title made me think your cat was an artist and now I feel lied to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently people thought this was serious and not sarcastic.

I give up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 18.6k retweets and counting. What was that about "fake news" again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Summon Signs for Dummies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's not very obvious and Dark Souls is a pretty new series so I wanted to let people know how summoning works since it doesn't seem people have figured it out yet. It took me a while but I finally figured it out through lots of trial and error and doing data collection. Here's what I found:

Basically, when you put your sign down, you get summoned by another player because they see a sign appear in the same location they can interact with. Some of you might have figured this part out by now.

Now once you've been summoned by another player, next comes the important part. You see, just like you, that player has to fight enemies during the course of the game (this blew me away when I found out. I can back this up with video) . This is in fact the reason they are summoning you. Most likely it will be for a boss fight. 

Now we all know bosses are scary, so your first instinct is probably to follow the host into the fight and then run in circles around the edges of the room making no attempt to actually attack the now health-boosted boss, but this is actually the OPPOSITE of what you're supposed to do. What you actually want to do is one of the following:

1. Attack the boss. You can literally do this in any way you like. Melee, magic, you name it!

2. Stop putting your summon signs outside of Midir and then running laps around the arena the entire fight.

I hope this was helpful because I know the game is really new so there hasn't been enough time for people to figure all the complicated aspects of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I see.

Still, I'm well aware how it works.

Marxists start with suppression of dissent by censoring.

Later comes the Gulags, and then the mass murdering. It's the same old routine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd expect nothing less from a Marxist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Capitalism allows corruption and greed!

The only possible alternative is to reinstate a system that has killed over 110 million people and systematically led to widespread genocide, poverty, and oppression! 

After all, none of that was *real* communism. If *I* was in Stalins place none of that would have happened because I'm morally perfect and I understand the doctrine of socialism better than anyone else!

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read books. Either great classics of fiction or philosophy or even poetry. Books that teach meaning.

Exercise. Get your body moving.

Go outside. Find whatever aspect of nature you can and immerse yourself in it.

Get out and experience. Doesn't have to be specific, just exist in as many interesting places as you can.

Talk to people. Be candid. Let them prove you wrong so you can really learn what's outside of your subjective mind.

Get out there, do something difficult, take on some responsibility for something, and above all, be honest, all the time. The core of life is suffering, so go make it worth something instead of sitting around praying for eternal happiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you seriously expect anyone on this sub to tell you not to? Lol.

Honestly if you get it used it can be a fun game, especially if you play with other people. I bought all of the Soulsbourne games  only after they dropped in price. I'd never pay a full $60 for a Souls game, as I just don't see them as the AAA Mona Lisas they're hailed as; too many issues that haven't been patched/fixed for me. To be fair, that's not unique to the series, it's just sort of how it goes with games nowadays. 

My only tip for actually playing is to have fun, experiment, and not get caught up in he whole SL 120 meta elite community (the "git gud" crowd) that likes to tell people what they can and can't play as. Just be you, and you can make almost anything work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd actually love to boiled alive, honestly. It sounds pretty hot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So am I the only person that got those tokens through PvP or what? I hate the PvP in dark souls with a passion, but I don't recall ever getting a single one of my proofs from a silver knight when I got my Darkmoon items. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thing is, as someone who has been in a group home/ dealt with CPS, it won't be much better for them if they get taken away. It might even be worse. The state, as far as I ever saw, is *abysmal* at caring for children they "rescue" or putting them in good homes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it was Thomas Szasz who wrote how mental illnesses don't really exist for the most part. All these things we constantly call "mental Illness" and insist on treating with drugs is, in reality, just a symptom of a problem in the way a person is living their life. I think we vastly underestimate the ways our mental health can deteriorate when we develop poor habits, such as our societies new obsession with constantly burying ourselves in social media and internet usage. What we mistake for mental health problems is mostly just us having really bad life habits that we don't take the responsibility to change, as opposed to some random, sudden pandemic of mental illness that is appearing out of the ether. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
