<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3232</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This scene from the Adult Swim dark comedy series Moral Orel on always hits me in the feels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds tasty. I've recently come around to using cake mix as other things. I made what I can only describe as the best chocolate cookies I think I've ever made when I was in a pinch and only had a box of yellow cake mix, an egg, some butter, and some bittersweet chocolate. They turned out amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't do that, we both like football. Except I'm a Steelers fan living in DFW, so I'm basically a pariah.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most mellow song about couples suicide I've ever heard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of their music is similar, I'll admit. This song, however, has a special spot in my heart. I enjoy it, and I wanted to share.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Regina Spektor - Carbon Monoxide [Indie pop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 113 - Tonton Du Bled [French Hip Hop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tegan and Sara - Downtown [Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Gray - Babylon [Folk Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cat Stevens - I Think I See The Light [Folk Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I'm not sure about that--most meta subs have rules against posting stuff that you're a part of. I would block the guy if I were you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Penn - Walter Reed [Alternative Pop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey addpulp! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* You may only post links if you are not the source of the drama or directly involved in the drama. Do not submit drama you have commented in



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My advice is don't be afraid of being "bitchy." It's all about your delivery. If you talk about it is in a straightforward and caring way, you're not going to be bitchy. If you've set boundaries with him before and he's made an effort, that's a great sign. I would just be honest with him in a moment when you're both feeling calm and have the time to talk about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is she in therapy? If someone gave her the diagnosis of BPD, then I would assume she at least has access--most professionals will not give that diagnosis without extensive contact and testing. She should work on this issue with her therapist. 

She always needs undivided attention or else she feels neglected and unloved

This is a hallmark symptom of BPD--and it's something she can address in therapy. She should look into doing Dialectical Behavior Therapy to address her interpersonal and affect regulation problems. If she's not willing to do so, then you might want to take a break from the relationship. Borderline people often attract either narcissistic or dependent personalities, and you sound a little like you might have issues with the latter. Don't get sucked in--you are not responsible for her feelings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't like roleplaying, tell her. If it's a deal breaker for her, then she has to deal with it. I can understand why that would make you dread the encounter. I would start with just having a talk with her about it and tell her how it makes you feel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's....awkward. If it makes you feel uncomfortable, I would just tell him. See how he reacts. Could be that's how he's showing affection and he doesn't know any better. If he corrects the behavior, that's good. If he gets defensive and refuses, that's a bad sign, IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh look, it's bait! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chill out--if you usually post the source what's your problem with someone pointing out the real source? You should say "hey, thanks for the source!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would love to see that cross section!

Just a small note, in the future get your pan just a little hotter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not like it is easy to carry.

I would beg to differ, I used to carry two in my purse and I wasn't even that active. Just change them out every 6 months to make sure you are accounting for wear--but it doesn't sound like you'll go that long without using them. Keep one in your wallet or have her keep a couple in her purse. It's easy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice for a first attempt! It's medium, and could have used a little less time, but this is the first try--you'll nail it next time! Did you butter baste? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish you had left some of the crust visible so we could see it! What cut of meat did you use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then I'll dump a bucket of ajvar on your head and call you a naughty boy and leave you wanting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oven? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, just remember that having a kid is a big responsibility--a HUGE responsibility. It's not just a matter of child support, it really changes your life (whether you're wanting a child or not). Probability is on your side, but it's that one time that it fails that can really change everything in your life if abortion is not an option. 

If you don't mind me asking, what are the times when having a condom aren't realistic?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should know by now that I'm typically overly nice as a mod, even to the jerkfaces that cut up in /r/food.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was a defensive lineman, but I think he wants that vicarious glory. 

Seriously, though, concussion research and the weird culture of "play through the pain" here in Texas gives us both qualms about high school football at this point. It's just not worth it if you end up with brain damage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey now, don't make me spank you with a wet noodle. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, this really boils down to the degree of trust in your relationship. Have you talked through what you would do if you had an accidental pregnancy? if not, I would say double up. If you've had the conversation and she's taking her pills responsibly, then there's a very small chance (and I mean very) that she'll get pregnant. 

When she takes it every day at the same time of day, it's going to work 99% of the time. It's closer to 91% on average because people don't usually take their pills perfectly. My then boyfriend (now husband) and I didn't stop using condoms until we were at a point at which we were very clear about what we would do with a pregnancy. Communication is key! The pull-out method is not sound, statistically speaking, so do not rely on it as an alternative to condoms. 

Finally, regarding her getting tested--you should both get tested. 8 Is not a super high number, but the number doesn't matter. Both go get the basic tests and then you'll know for sure. If she's mature, she won't take it personally--this is something that adults do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama in /r/pettyrevenge when one commenter says the U.S. just isn't set up for bike travel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, we'll play Settlers and I'll lie about what resources I have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do, actually, it was always a limitation when I played piano because octaves are challenging for me. 

My husband said he will blame me if our kid isn't able to be a quarterback.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's best to anticipate and plan rather than react, IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then we can have hot dog sandwiches and grilled cheese with bacon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's take this outside!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey folks,

This is just a reminder in advance to please follow our rules while commenting in here. Do not insult each other, do not ping users, do not post obvious bait comments spoiling for a fight, and try to keep the circlejerking to a minimum if possible. And, of course, **do not, under any circumstances, vote or comment in linked threads!** Thank you for being an awesome community and we hope you enjoy this drama as it unfolds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they actually leave Reddit, I'll legally change my name to Donald.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather make a frittata. I make them a lot--butter a baking dish, use whatever tasty ingredients you want, bake it until it's delicious. Boom: breakfast party food.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like an awful lot of work to me--and I'm a lover of butter in my omelettes, not oil. I can make a thin omelette that I roll up in much less time than it takes to make this, so I just don't see why anyone would bother. One of the things I love about omelettes is that once you get them down, they're *easy*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All flower syrups are pretty much the same--they are simple syrups, just with flowers for flavoring instead of vanilla beans or orange zest or whatever else you might be used to. Here's how you do it:

Dissolve two cups sugar to one cup water sugar in water over medium heat it is completely dissolved. Get it to a simmer but do not let it boil! Put your gardenia flowers in a ceramic baking dish or bowl. Pour the syrup over and steep for about an hour. Strain. This is, of course, assuming you are not using any pesticides or other chemicals in your garden. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use mine every time I grill chicken breast in order to get the breasts to be an even thickness--helps it cook evenly! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love eggs. I think they are one of the perfect foods. But whatever, be a heathen and eat your nasty ass eggs however you want.

He makes it sound dirty somehow. "I love her, she's the perfect woman, and you made her a whore!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun tip: you can keep eggs shelf stable for longer at room temp by rubbing the outside with mineral oil. A lady at a gun show taught me that. Good times! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Archive](http://archive.is/GUBm4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since a lot of people have already said chicken, I'll suggest goat or lamb--both can work really well with the jerk seasoning. It couldn't be easier, just marinate it for a decent chunk of time (at least 3-4 hours if not overnight) and roast it. Or do lamb chops on a nice hot grill--fast and easy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true. I always either do a side-to-side or a figure 8, depending on what I'm mixing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Who the fuck made this? A college freshman?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really, really does not make a noticeable difference to the final texture of the eggs. I follow the [America's Test Kitchen](http://www.wgbh.org/files/eggs.pdf) approach for scrambled eggs, which calls for presalting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 21:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GMO free, gluten free, organic and cage free! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was sold on the creativity of cake in an orange. I'm probably not going to make that on a camping trip, but I don't care--it's awesome. I think I'd do it in a back yard firepit scenario with friends, you know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying reposting it. Sorry it didn't work, hopefully I can get it working because it's pretty great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 Fun Campfire Desserts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Next step: world domination.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Archive](http://archive.is/7NCqG) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The basic components are garlic powder, onion powder, cumin, chili powder, oregano, salt, and pepper. But it's faster to just say "taco seasoning." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commenter in /r/GifRecipes is deeply traumatized by Americanized onigiri </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, very true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP Vincent Schiavelli. Fine actor, wine expert, and all around cool guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow, I'm sorry, I didn't recognize your username! Congratulations on your sobriety. 

I don't get why so many people are projecting stuff onto your photo--I think it's human nature to try to paint whole pictures with limited information. Basically, a bunch of people are arguing over whether or not you were more attractive on drugs. I think any time someone posts a picture on Reddit, particularly women, there will be commenters arguing over how hot the picture is. Don't let it get you down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, our way was a little backwards. It's because we have an "interfaith" marriage of sorts--I'm sure we would have done things a little differently if we were both religious. I wanted to do one ceremony at the venue to make everything more convenient for the guests, and of course a priest won't marry you outside the church. It all worked out really smoothly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Am I suppose to be mad too? 

Only if you invest way too much in the photo of a stranger on the Internet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that the guy sees littering as a form of protest. 

As a side note, my husband and I decided to stop shopping at Wal-Mart a few years back, ad the change has been easy to maintain. That's not as much of an option for rural folks, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other than an alternative to reddit without the shitty admins, vote manipulation by said shitty admins (and users who they agree with and allow to vote-brigade certain subs), editing users comments by the shitty admins, etc.

If you don't support voat the terrorists literally win.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That does not surprise me. I worked with drug addicts for a while as a counselor, I've seen some absolutely bonkers behavior, mostly from people on meth and PCP. 

I actually think this guy's sentence was a little extreme. Obviously kidnapping and injuring police are both serious crimes, but 160 years? Dude needs some serious drug treatment, and he probably won't get it in prison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C'mon now, no bait.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure! Risotto is supposed to run on the plate a bit--if it mounds up on on the plate like that it has "seized." This means that the starch in the risotto has thickened up to the point at which it is making the risotto more gluey than creamy. Risotto uses the rice starch to make the creamy sauce--it's not supposed to hold its shape on the plate. I hope that helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 05:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boy, for women who struggle with sufficient milk production, having a lactation consultant sure is helpful though. We survived many thousands of years *as a species* but there are a lot more babies surviving now that we have experts helping women breastfeed effectively--and now that we have formula to supplement in cases in which mothers underproduce.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 05:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's overly simplistic and a little off (although you're right that larger orchestras are a defining part of the shift from classical to romantic). 

You should review the text for your course. Surely there are lecture notes or a book that has these basic concepts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 04:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some cheater hints for if you get really stuck: 

Classical pieces generally have much more variation in rhythm vs. more static rhythm in baroque pieces. You'll also have more key changes in classical pieces vs. baroque. Classical vs. romantic guideline is you have more diatonic harmonies in classical and more chromatic harmonies in romantic. I'm afraid I don't know much about Medieval or Renaissance period music. The contemporary stuff should be very easy for you to discern.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warren Zevon - Excitable Boy [Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 04:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rancid - Ruby Soho [Punk] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 04:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Andrew   Polly - Grapes [Children's Music] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 04:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 03:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 03:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not the way to change people's minds about their eating habits. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 03:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Catholic one was small because it was our immediate family only. The later one was everyone--about 175 people. Because it wasn't a full mass the Catholic ceremony was pretty short, actually. The non-religious one was super short--15 minutes tops. I'm a big believer in short ceremonies and long buffets at weddings. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 03:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, solid cream cheese?

By the way, those flavors sound awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 03:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm of the opinion that seeking attention is not an inherently bad thing. People need validation. I think how you *seek* that attention is what matters. Obviously, if you hurt someone else or yourself in an effort to seek attention, that's a big problem. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 03:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Classy? Nah.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, that's up to you. Next time read the sidebar before posting, it will save you time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canned tuna, mayo, lemon pepper, diced celery, green onion, lemon juice, a little garlic powder, and a teensy bit of mustard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I archived it for you OP, in case they do a mass delete. Please repost it as a self post. Thank you. 

http://archive.is/ILfU4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Rownik! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* Surplus Popcorn: All surplus drama threads must be linked as self posts. See [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules#wiki_surplus_popcorn) for more information. 

Surplus popcorn:

* racism drama
* gender wars
* social justice drama
* Trump drama



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Green stuff = pickled cucumber

White stuff = fresh onion

Flat brown stuff = sliced brisket

Hope you get a chance to visit our lovely state some time and try the wonderful barbecue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a big tradition in Texas. You use it to mop up any sauce/juices. 

Personally, I don't eat it when I eat at BBQ places here--I'm just not a fan of it. But it's a beloved part of the spread here--it's tradition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, that's part of the requirement, too. 

It's funny, though--our priest is one of the few married priests out there because he was an Episcopalian priest and then converted, so he has a wife and kids. There aren't many of those around, but we have one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's required in order to be married in the church. You have to meet with the priest and also a married couple in the church who provide a counseling session. You are also required to take a test that analyzes your values and goals, and you have to go through a series of classes to study and discuss the sacraments. 

I should stress, I am not Catholic--I'm actually not religious at all. But my husband is, and he wanted to get married in the Church. A non-Catholic is allowed to marry a Catholic with some conditions--I just wasn't allowed to accept communion and the church that married us does not allow a full mass since I'm not Catholic. We ended up having two ceremonies--a Catholic one in the morning and a larger, non-religious ceremony in the afternoon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's kind of projection, don't you? We really don't know anything about her based on either picture. Honestly, I couldn't even tell she was on heroin specifically in the first picture, she just looks out of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell, just post a "Philly" cheesesteak and put peppers on it. That will get you enough drama to last you for hours. And then link it to /r/iamveryculinary, we love that argument there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 22:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "She has that far away gaze in her eyes, I can't put my finger on it..."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently, what he wants is a social climate in which people can be complete jerks and there are no social consequences whatsoever. And that women somehow encourage a climate in which the men don't get to have fun ripping on each other and on women because they get "shamed" for their jerkiness. Or something. That's what I took away from the walls of text.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait...but you're here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Oh, it's an argument](https://www.reddit.com/r/GifRecipes/comments/6b9mpy/cloud_eggs/dhl488z/?st=j2tdy8pt sh=51a5dac3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IME, it's the heat from your hands and the compression that affect it more than the salt. This is why, and I'm not kidding, I get my hands ice cold before I form my hamburgers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This does not exist in a marriage. A marriage means implied consent.  It's called the Marital debt. 

That's funny, the priest that counseled my husband and me before marrying us in the Church must have glossed over that part.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Unless you have such poor self control that it's a struggle to not be an asshole to people. 

I think this is a significant problem for a lot of people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 17:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, I would worry she would say something damaging to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 17:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There is a problem with seeking validation if it is manipulative and comes at the expense of the free will of others. 

This doesn't make a lick of sense to me. I do not see how her post is hurting anyone or imposing on anyone's "free will." But quite frankly, I don't think we're going to see eye to eye here. I've learned my lesson discussing [social skills stuff with you before](https://www.reddit.com/r/SubredditDrama/comments/4hxb4c/is_deodorant_oppressive_heated_slapfight_in_a/d2uqk7q/?context=3 st=j2t64iso sh=8169daff). I get that you find social expectations and pressures frustrating--I think they're harder for some people than others. You might run into some interpersonal difficulties as a result, though. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 17:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still don't get it, but I'll accept that's how you identify. 
To me it seems like an arbitrary distinction is being made between desire and arousal, but whatever floats your boat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 17:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except no one is telling you that you have to applaud. You can just not say anything at all. Or you can say something nasty, but then there will be social consequences. 

Human beings, regardless of gender, are all motivated by the same thing: to get their needs met. Emotional and physical needs. There's nothing wrong with trying to get those needs met as long as no one else is getting hurt in the process. People need validation--you don't have to give it to them, but there's nothing wrong with them seeking it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 17:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're mad that we have social mores in general? That there are social consequences to being an asshole? I don't know what you tell you, man, that's just part of being an adult in society.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 17:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think a Reddit post is "coercing" anyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 16:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a venison meatloaf with bacon around it once--it was ideal because venison can dry out. It was delicious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 16:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then he says 

jesus this is a very serious issue to a lot of you

I love it when people get butthurt about a food issue and then when they're losing the argument turn around and say "Gee, why do you take this so *seriously*?"  I had a guy do that the other day about eggs when he tried to start the "don't salt your eggs" argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 16:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a fellow Texan, I would say the only thing they're missing in addition to the pickles and onions are pickled jalapenos. That's a key part of the BBQ restaurant experience for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 16:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Helpful tip for making great mashed potatoes: after you drain the taters, put them back in the hot pot in which you boiled them, and let them continue to cook for about a minute. They will steam a lot. This gets excess water out, which will lead to fluffier, tastier taters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's one of my baby's favorite things, which is great because I can add veggies to it (spinach, broccoli and carrots are all good bets) and have kind of an "all in one" entree for him--very easy during the week when we're busy. One version I do is turkey meatloaf and mashed sweet potatoes--it's slightly healthier and he loves it so it all works out well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The biggest difference between a burger and meatloaf is the presence of binders. Meatloaf has eggs and breadcrumbs so the texture is totally different. Where I live the meat you use to make them is the same, though. You might use a coarser grind for burgers, if you have a butcher who grinds your meat for you. 

I like the idea of selling a fried egg burger on a bun as a "deconstructed meatloaf" though--very clever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I have a feeling she has much more unflattering pictures of herself from when she was a heroin addict.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's a burger vs. meatloaf debate in /r/GifRecipes, and the chefs in this drama aren't mincing words </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a similar split happen with people who are recovering from eating disorders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can understand that--addiction can turn people into real assholes, and they can hurt a lot of the people in their lives as a result. It's hard to reach a point of forgiveness--if you ever do, which is by no means a given. I think that's why they put "asking for forgiveness" so far along in the 12-step process. 

I have a lot of empathy for addicts, but at the end of the day, regardless of how you feel personally I think we can all agree that addiction isn't good for us as a society. It's hard on families, the healthcare system, and the criminal justice system. So even if you have a personal issue with them, I think it's good to support recovery in general.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why would an asexual person want to have sex in the first place? It seems if the desire is there, that's sexual attraction is it not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I can understand why she'd want to share her success. It's really hard to give up opiates, and sometimes people need the external validation from others as a motivation to keep on going. 

We're having an opiate crisis in the U.S., so whatever helps that lady keep safe and sober, IMO, is a good thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you liked it! I was very impressed by Christian Bale--he is a very committed actor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm not sure why she didn't just take a plea deal. It would have probably just been a fine and maybe some community service. It's a misdemeanor, so it's not like it will ruin her life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Archive](http://archive.is/mQyDv) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The comment "You looked better when you were on heroin" gets a lot of people itchy in /r/pics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait wait...how can you enjoy sex if you don't experience sexual attraction? That's very confusing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I'm good. My sex life is fine. I was with a LL asshole who shamed me for wanting to fuck, then I dumped him and now life is great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The question is whether she should go to ~~prison~~ jail for it.

FTFY. 

EDIT: it's an important distinction that some people don't understand, I was just pointing it out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the judge needs to get creative here with some kind of social service volunteering or something--just a fine won't teach her anything IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C'mon, you know the rules.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not everyone calls them Swiss rolls, though. I think that's a British/U.S. thing, but in other areas they are called roulades. My mother always called them "jelly rolls." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So a roulade? Actually, that would be a good base for a Bche de Nol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey BritishBurrito! Thank you for your submission, unfortunately it has been removed from /r/SubredditDrama because:

* Surplus Popcorn: Due to a lot of stale politicized drama crowding out niche posts and dominating the front page, certain categories of drama face greater scrutiny and greater rates of removal. Your post fell into one of these categories and was not exceptional enough to be approved. See [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules#wiki_surplus_popcorn) for more information. 

Surplus drama categories include:

* racism drama
* gender wars
* social justice drama
* Trump drama



For more on our rules, please check out our [detailed rules wiki](https://www.reddit.com/r/subredditdrama/wiki/rules).  If you have any questions or concerns about this removal feel free to [message the moderators](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FSubredditDrama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What...is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh gosh, *that's* what he means? Those sites are terrible. They look like you've put an article through google translate a bunch of times and then given them to a person with a traumatic brain injury to rewrite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 05:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't really paid much attention to Seth Meyers but I've watch his past couple of shows and the writing and delivery have been strong. Of course, with all this material it's kind of like shooting fish in a barrel... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 04:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can use cooked pineapple, just not fresh pineapple. Heating it denatures the enzyme that keeps the gelatin from setting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 04:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chicago, IL, the 3rd largest city in the US, is 8% more expensive than Houston, TX

Yeah, I'll gladly pay that tax to not have to live in Houston. 

I haven't lived in Chicago in a long time, but when I was there it was very much affordable--especially if you had a bike and skipped having a car. I didn't make that much and I was able to save quite a lot. 

EDIT: My two cents on a cheap, gay-friendly city: Pittsburgh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 04:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White wine has enough acid that it should work. It's pretty traditional in fondue, too. That said, I'm not sure how it will work with pimento. Failing white wine, you can use a little lemon juice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out The Machinist. It's a really jarring, moving film IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Playboy model Dani Mathers is in hot water over her locker room pic, but people in /r/news can't agree over whether or not she deserves it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playboy model Dani Mathers took a photo of a naked 70-year-old woman in a locker room and posted it on social media with insulting comments about the woman's body. She plead not guilty, but if she's found guilty she could theoretically face up to six months in jail and a $1,000 fine. People in /r/news are discussing this, and some commenters think the punishment doesn't fit the crime. 


[Is it wasted tax payer money?](https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/6biah5/playboy_model_dani_mathers_faces_jail_after/dhn49dc/?st=j2sbm6ff sh=de8eef85)

["Sure, that does make you a hypocrite..."](https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/6biah5/playboy_model_dani_mathers_faces_jail_after/dhn5v01/?context=3 st=j2sboaup sh=43f498a7)

["Yay gender equality!"](https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/6biah5/playboy_model_dani_mathers_faces_jail_after/dhmt1sf/?st=j2sbpc6v sh=25b70c09)

[Should it even go to trial?](https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/6biah5/playboy_model_dani_mathers_faces_jail_after/dhmx1pn/?st=j2sbqxoi sh=a7bfb6e6) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A big problem is parents don't understand how unhealthy they are--their kids want them so they buy them. I'm a therapist who currently works with kids--many of whom have anxiety and sleep issues. I always assess for whether or not they're drinking these garbage drinks--and lots of them are! 

Part of the problem is the idea parents get that if they give their kids caffeine it will help them focus. This idea comes from the recommendation from some doctors to use caffeine to boost the efficacy of ADHD medication (which is true--for people with ADHD it can help with focus). The problem is, the vast majority of kids don't have ADHD and shouldn't be consuming vast amounts of caffeine--let alone large amounts of taurine and other additives in those drinks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never tried this! What are the taste and texture like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slightly dampened cheesecloth works well, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's a matter of personal taste. Sometimes I like it on the thicker side, just as OP has made it here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he claims he's *29*. I would have thought 19.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 01:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, he's like "I can go down on you for hours!" and she's like "no thanks, I'm good."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then how about you use "I said I needed to impress her sexually?" Or how about "love is more then getting a woman you've been dating for a couple weeks a balloon to huff nitrous with."

Honestly, this part just killed me: 

We then went back upstairs, and I put on Janis Joplin and began eating her out again...This lasted for a good while, her body moving in time with Janis, the tension rising with the music, and multiple orgasms later she said, "Ok, I'm impressed!"

I love Janis Joplin, but that's not the first choice I think of when it comes to music to have sex to. Also, I don't think I've ever told a guy "okay, I'm impressed!" Like he just demonstrated a really neat space-age vacuum cleaner or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We then touched each other, kissed, hugged and held, before the oral and piv sex began again.

"I sexed her with my sexy parts! I'm a published author!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a published author balls deep in a beautiful woman who loves me so I will get over your disdain

I'm guessing self-published.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  soign.

Oooh, this made me think of Marcel from Top Chef.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It had a key lime mousse and whipped cream as the filling layers, and then just simple meringue. I piped the meringue into disks, so it was a round dacquoise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely love dacquoise. I made a key lime one once that was out of this world. They're so easy and pretty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your mac and cheese is dated! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I [27 F] am three months pregnant after stopping my pills without telling anyone and my boyfriend is angry wants me to get an abortion. He said he never wanted to have a baby, but I know if he just had the chance he would be an amazing father. What should I do?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He keeeps telling girls he's single n dosent mention he even has a kid

Yeah...sounds like it's time to end things. I don't usually advise people to end their relationships, but he sounds like he's disrespectful and emotionally abusive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say it's probably significantly fewer than the number of double A batteries his gf goes through a month.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, third account that I know of. We try to keep track of his alts because he's banned here and has showed up with other accounts to evade the ban (which is probably why he PMd me instead of commenting here).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be a recent change, because in the past when I've seen the MGTOW types pop up there they got downvoted to hell (kind of like this guy in the linked thread).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is his third account dedicated to it, too. Dude's committed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just don't want OP to feel obligated to a bitch who's too selfish to suck his dick when he's pent up.

No projection there whatsoever. 

I'm good, don't worry about me sugartits

It's like Ford Fairlane got a Reddit account.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the biggest difference is that it's a smaller sub. I definitely prefer it to /r/relationships. Sometimes you get "delete the lawyer hit the facebook" responses but generally it's more rational than that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I'm good. My sex life is fine. I was with a LL asshole who shamed me for wanting to fuck, then I dumped her and now life is great.

The guy probably cries himself to sleep on a regular basis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually /r/relationship_advice, not /r/relationships, and it's actually a pretty good sub overall. The advice in there tends to be much more practical and people are more realistic and respectful. Usually. That post seems to have brought out some of the crazies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emotions run high when libido runs low in /r/relationship_advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For posterity, here is the original post from /r/relationship_advice in case it gets deleted:

I've been with her for almost 3 years and I don't know what is going on. We are both 22 and I honestly want to have sex at least 3 times a week, at least, but she always says that she's too tired, or when we are in bed she just says that she feels bad. I swear that everytime we're in bed her head starts to hurt, or her stomach, or just falls asleep, idk what to do, I told her my issue months ago but she stayed the same. We used to have a lot of sex, but now it's only once a week if I can manage to convince her, and it has to be in a bed, otherwise she can't do it. Any help is appreciated. 

[How should you handle low libido?](https://www.reddit.com/r/relationship_advice/comments/6bfp6o/gf_wont_have_sex_with_me/dhmdnq3/?context=3 st=j2rr761r sh=e7e4e979)

["All her excuses are bullshit..."](https://www.reddit.com/r/relationship_advice/comments/6bfp6o/gf_wont_have_sex_with_me/dhman0h/?st=j2rr6dal sh=0e759646)

[What if she's asexual?](https://www.reddit.com/r/relationship_advice/comments/6bfp6o/gf_wont_have_sex_with_me/dhme4we/?st=j2rr94nq sh=c87be672) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 17:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if I let her know of this, she is going to say that I'm crazy, and she will get mad.

Has she done that before? 

Realistically speaking, you can't do much about this if you don't talk with her about it. I mean, you could just break up with her as some people are suggesting, but I think communication should be your first intervention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 17:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice looking chicken and asparagus! I love charred lemon slices.  The risotto looks like it seized a little, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, there's a tinge of Aesop Rock in there, too. Aesop Rock actually writes really good lyrics, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has she started a new birth control? Or any other new medication? Sometimes that can kill libido. 

Ups and downs in sex drive happen--the only way for you to work through this is to sit down and have an honest talk with her about what's going on. Just reflect to her that you've noticed this significant change, and see what she says. And you can let her know in a non-threatening way that you have certain needs and expectations about the physical aspects of your relationship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that's a tall order for people in their early 20s. And it sounds like she was into it before, just now she's had a drop in libido. But still and all, they need to have a long honest talk about their expectations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd totally beat up a kid for damaging my car! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm trying to backpedal my /r/iamverybadass comment but I'm not sure how so I'm just deflecting onto you!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Scriabin had neurosyphilis. There's nothing philosophical about it. 

He also had synesthesia, which influenced his music quite a bit--he saw notes as colors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, heck no, I think there are a lot of problems in both parties. But I also think the propaganda was really strong against Clinton, and has been for a long time. So much spin. A big part of the problem are media related, IMO--they just want a sensational story, no matter what the consequences. And I think a big problem was in how Clinton chose to run her campaign in such an old-fashioned, buttoned-up way--but she learned to do that after 25 years of attacks, so it's hard to teach an old dog new tricks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "If me fantasizing about slugging a child is a violent fantasy to you, clearly you're mistaken!"

--You right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, it's the opposite with me and my husband. I hate shopping, and he talks me into going into stores I normally wouldn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no, I am--I find your violent power fantasies about beating up kids to be entertaining. Do you also ask police officers "am I being detained?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You bought the lies they sold you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my favorite! I always do it in cast iron. I've noticed that the prices have gone up since it became more popular, which is disappointing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, okay, whatever you say.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you linked to the wrong place, but I know what post you mean (the CB2 one, right?). 

I mean, it's unwordableweirdness, that's what he does--starts fights about veganism, follows people around, gets way too caught up, etc. 

I had been watching the /r/grilling argument because I'm a mod of the sub--I finally decided to post it because he got a second wind and added even more crazy to the slapfight. /r/grilling is a small, happy little sub and we don't get a lot of drama, surprisingly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds amazing, I love asado. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really wouldn't matter if they did stop, internet sluts are common. 

Lol these girls are about their $$. She's even trying to scoop an extra 4 racks for the face pic.

This attitude makes me sad. It's like they're pissed that women in their lives don't want to be hot and naked for them for free, so they're directing all this resentment towards the ones that charge. Hey, they're still people--selling nude shots of yourself doesn't make you sub-human. And no one owes you tit pics for free, you muppet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I figured--no other vegan on Reddit is *that* nuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you imagine the Sausage Party   business pitch on Shark Tank? 

"I don't really understand the sausage industry, so I'm out." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in Texas, U.S. Grilling is like a weird competitive sport here. 

The upper rack is positioned [like so](https://cdn.shocho.co/sc-image/6/7/1/f/671f22280e6541d8be540f21d2cd08ca.jpg). That's not the kind I have but the design is the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it either. Eminem worked full time and overtime at minimum wage jobs while he was honing his craft. Not saying you have to do that, but it's definitely possible to work and produce music because lots of people have done it. 

Honestly, I think you have to treat your passion like a hobby until you're good enough to earn money at it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that would be your choice--and your choice might land you in prison, or at the very least probation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be more generous and call it thoroughly mediocre. His delivery is a little stilted and sounds a bit like he is reading his lyrics off the page and the lyrics are pretty damn uninspired.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 12:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only way I'm up North is if you're in South America. 

It's a four burner natural gas (yes, I know, judge away) grill with an upper rack when you open the hood. It's smaller than the bottom racks, but it gets the job done. 

In addition, I have a smoker, and I've had some great luck with smoked veg (tomatoes, potatoes, mushrooms, etc.).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 05:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grill has an upper rack, and that's what I use specifically for vegetables. So in theory if I had a vegan over who didn't want the veggies touching a rack that had touched meat, I'm prepared. 

Also, I make fucking delicious grilled portobello caps. I brush them with a soy and balsamic mix and they're out of this world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 05:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, I would eat those components, just not all at the same time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Op here

Well that's simply not true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually have no problems whatsoever with vegans. I dislike people militantly telling other people what they should eat, though. I don't think that's the best way to facilitate progress in our food industries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone in /r/Music tells OP he shouldn't have quit his day job, leading to an argument about following your dreams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's one of the lamest products I've seen on this show. Pheromone spray? What is this, the mid 90s? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently watched the movie *Joy* and this lady kind of reminded me of the protagonist in the film. She clearly has a good idea, a good prototype, people don't believe in her, and she's a divorced single mother.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genius invention. I had a really simple gown that wasn't too hard to use the bathroom in, but I would have still loved one of these just to keep it from touching the bathroom floor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, now that's a sausage party I would like to attend. Sounds like fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess so? He just sent me the message with "Nice" as the title and "Try" in the body. I don't know what he thinks I'm trying, but he seems like a highly passionate vegan so maybe he sees it as an act of aggression against his ideology.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, the person [sent me an angry PM](http://imgur.com/a/ScdsN). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five day slapfight about vegan barbecuing in /r/grilling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 23:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, I completely missed that connection! Obviously they made a deal out of him being a photographer because of his eyes, but I forgot that was her job before she moved to Stepford. 

I read that Peele is planning on making a bunch more social horror movies--I, for one, cannot wait.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 23:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's a really good comparison--in fact, I think Jordan Peele must be an Ira Levin fan, because his sardonic writing style seems really on the same wavelength.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 23:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? That family (and the other people involved) didn't seem conservative to me, at all. They present themselves as being down with Black culture but not accepting of him as a person--they literally see him as a thing, but I think it's also commentary on how even well-meaning White people who think they're being accepting and liberal and open-minded can still end up fetishizing and co-opting Blackness. 

EDIT: This is a horrible comparison because it's not a good movie, but I think of them like the socially liberal couple in *Amos and Andrew*. The ones that were bragging about being civil rights lawyers but who, when push came to shove, saw a Black guy moving in to their ritzy neighborhood and thought "robber!" That's the kind of White liberal I'm talking about.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
