<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3787</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 08:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 08:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm down haha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 08:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love his work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 08:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was there and this painting too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 08:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that's really touching. As I sit here alone in front of my easel and struggle at times with the solitude of artmaking, comments like this are really nurturing for my heart and soul. Thank You.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My artwork titled Black Madonna </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use psychedelics as a catalyst for creativity, a tool for art production, and a source of inspiration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My artwork titled Black Madonna </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My artwork titled Black Madonna, I thought r/Psychonaut would like it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black Madonna, gicle print of digital painting, 24x36 inches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My artwork titled Black Madonna, I think r/Heavymind would like it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 23:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha Andrew. I'm glad I found this subreddit. XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Struggling to Install my Vive can you help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 03:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got my vive with the HP Envy bundle last week. I've been working at it the past few days to install it and I'm really struggling. The computer isnt recognizing the Vive's headset. My computer has a Raedon RX 480 Graphics Card that has 1 HDMI and 4 Display Ports. By the recommendation of some google searches I bought a mini-display port to display port cable and I'm attempting to run that as the output for the headset. It doesn't seem to be working. I could also buy an  HDMI splitter if that would work. I know the computer is recognizing the usb part of the headset just not the visual output on the card. I am sure I have the latest graphics card drivers. I also tried starting the computer without anything plugged into the HDMI just the Display Port. Also it seems like one of the controllers isn't working, that maybe it isn't holding a charge properly and the computer says its firmware isn't up to date. Did I just get a bad system? The computer otherwise is working 100 percent fine. Can you help me?

Thanks guys!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 07:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a psychedelic artist who created a psychedelic work of art in tilt brush and thought that the people here would appreciate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Psychedelic Art in Virtual Reality - First time gettin' Tilt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 06:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First time gettin' Tilt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 06:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 21:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's 1-1, the exact size of the plates. Though the plates are made bigger than the ones in the book. About 11x17 inches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 04:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure he used to teach there also.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 04:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy to answer. You work from a more generalized version of the image, to a more specific and detailed version. And you work in a manner which is very methodical and sequential. The method is set up so that you are accurate at every stage, always checking as you go, and you make corrections as needed as things change subtly. You can use a ruler a bit towards the end for final minor corrections, when things may be off one or two millimeters. Most of the measurement is done by eye, but also using a piece of string or a knitting needle on occasion. Any other questions I am happy to answer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 20:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The darkest values are patiently handled with a 2B pencil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 05:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corel painter  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 04:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's relevant because it was painted under the influence of psychedelics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A self portrait I painted recently (digitally) reflecting inner turmoil, much of this was painted on LSD. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 04:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inner Turmoil (self portrait), Digital Painting, 5000 pxls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 04:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A digitally painted self portrait I finished recently to reflect a state of inner turmoil. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 04:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Collection of my work from the Angel Academy in Florence, Graphite. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 04:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enter the code SANTA for 30% off of my art prints. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 01:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enter the code SANTA for 30% off of my art prints. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 01:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SPECIAL HOLIDAY SALE! For the holidays I am offering a 30% off sale on all of my paper prints! Enter the code SANTA during check out. The sale expires on the first day of the new year. $25 prints are only $17.50 with this sale! http://subject3787.bigcartel.com/category/prints </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enter the code SANTA for 30% off of my art prints. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 01:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
