<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3313</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-26 06:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tell me about it! they're not even related; they were both too small from separate litters and now, you can't separate them. :] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Reddit, I need ideas on how to convince my mom to let me adopt my last two foster kittens! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-26 02:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chunk: A foster kitten with the cutest little face. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-26 05:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I fits, I will sits. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-27 06:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-31 02:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ditto! haha... but we're considered an important country... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-31 02:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i wish i could upload this forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-16 15:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry for the late response, I haven't been on for a while. I would look into the program if you're interested for sure, come in for a tour. I'm interested in the same things you are, and there is one mammology class here that's phenomenal. Whatever you want to do in the future, though, here is a great place to start, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-26 06:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I understand, a lot of the best zoology programs that have to do with marine biology are on the east coast. But according to the head of our department, MSU's zoology program is one of the strongest off the east coast. Personally, I love it here, but obviously I'm biased.

Basically, make sure to do your research based on what you want to go into and what research professors at your future school are involved in so maybe you can work in one of their labs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
