<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2840</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most enjoyable film I've ever seen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've actually been ordering in bigger portions so that I can use the leftovers for a few meals lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We're the Czechs and Slovaks raped by soldiers during its occupation by the nazis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In school were learning about the Czechoslovakia occupation by the Nazis, and I was wondering if the Nazis had treated the Czechs and Slovaks the same way the soviets had raped the German women when Berlin fell. Obviously the raping would've taken a smaller scale than the 2 million women that were raped in Germany after the war.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We're the Czechs and Slovaks raped and tortured by soldiers? Like what happened to the Germans when the soviets occupied them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 06:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That plane in German is flight thing. I nearly fell out my seat laughing in the bus lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 05:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eating food. My entire family looks at me like I'm an alien when I claim to be hungry enough to eat an elephant, and then can't even finish my curly fries(which I eat before the wrap). I'm always hungry, but there's just too much, no matter how hard I try. Don't even get me started on trying to diet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 05:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I come from a fairly respectable school, so the biggest "scandal" was when we protested against cutting down a tree. We didn't want it cut since we always hung out there and we had "emotional attachments" to it. We do, however, have legends. 

Our school takes civics books from the government at the beginning of the year, and returns them at the end. My friend fapped in class, came on the book, and forgot all about it. Shit storm when the government got the book back. 

The second one is my brother. He's known for being a fucking pain in the ass for teachers. This year alone, he's been called out for skipping school every Tuesday, except for the last one. My school has a system where you can't redo a test, but they average your score and apply it to all missing tests. 23/25 on his last test LMAO. In the morning we would go to the cold store and he would buy shit. We had to go to the coordinator of were late so she can mark us in. She's chewing him out about why he was late, all he said was "spite is good for the stomach" and went to class.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/unexpectedrunescape </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoyed the sex scene. There are some things that I would like to point out though, in the paragraph where he describes her he says "her wanting eyes, her goddess tits." The use of tits instead of breasts threw me off balance. The rest of the scene was more of a romantic vibe, but this made it seem like a hook up. 

The line with "like a metronome in a hypnotist's office." Sounded extermely forced and out of place. I think that if it were omitted, the reading would've been much better. I don't know what a metronome is, and I don't believe that many people do, all it's doing is making us confused. 

You're doing very well with the build up, at first it was all romantic but took a turn to making me feel uncomfortable. I knew something was off right off the bat, when he said "what the fuck is wrong with me?" I assumed this meant that he shouldn't be fucking a friend and felt bad about it. As the scene progressed, it was revealed that it was actually built up feelings to her(I think, I'm slightly lost on what's happening in the previous chapters) 

The build up was good, but the actual sex wasn't. The scene was basically Ruby having sex with someone who was just lying there. Karl also lasted really long, while at the beginning you were describing it as if he was going to cum really quickly. There wasn't any foreplay, which made it much less believable. You kinda skimped over the part where they were undressing, what was she wearing under her shirt? Was she wearing any panties? 

The crying was really weird, I don't know if that's because we missed something since we don't have the entire chapter, it added something to the story, but without any explanation. If you elaborated on why they were crying, it would've flowed much better with the story. 

The end of the scene, after ruby and Karl are done fucking, they say things like "I'm never gonna leave you baby" sounded like it's a bad romantic comedy. You could've shown it instead of outright saying it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 17:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What're you gonna say? No? That means you've beaten your wife in the past. Say I've never beaten my wife, sounds like you're denying. The questions is designed to assume your guilt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 14:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Runescape. Trading, patience, integrity, and honor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 06:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Logical fallacies. A logical fallacy is when there's something wrong with an argument. There are 5 types Ima talk about. 

False cause: Correlation doesn't equal causation, or, just because two things happened in sequence, doesn't mean they caused each other. "Vaccination and autism levels have increased at the same time, therefore, vaccines cause autism." 

Loaded question: A question that has no right answer. Ex: "John, when did you stop beating your wife?"

Ad hominem: Attacking the person not the argument. Ex: Person one: "I think that medical marijuana shouldn't be legal" person two: "says the person who was held back last year."

Bandwagon: Everyone says it's true, so it's true. Ex: a few hundred years ago, everyone thought that sperm was just little human bodies that'll grow into bigger humans until they're birthed. 

Appeal to authority: A person in charge says it's ok, so it's ok. Ex: "Trump says that all Muslims are bad, and he's the president so he's right."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 05:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simpler explanation: it's when you only look at data that's confirming what you already believe, while ignoring data that disproves what you believe. Ex: antivaxers: "there have been proven increased levels of autism when vaccines have become widespread, thus vaccines cause autism." If you try to get to the root of the problem, you'll see that the way autism is diagnosed has been altered at around the same time vaccines have become cheaper, so more people will be diagnosed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear Germany, 

You have tried to take over Europe, twice by force and have failed spectacularly. You tried once by peace and look at you now! You have conquered all of mainland Europe and Britain! Well, besides the Swiss.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 05:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find other people to pay for me. There was this trip to Hong Kong about how to protect human rights, school paid in full.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 05:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They could have either a weakened dose of the vaccine, or they have a weakened immune system. The virus could still get through with enough exposure, like if they're in Disney land with swarms of tourists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 15:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice soviet flag  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 06:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The infamous Falador mines the grueling work we had to do just to get a bit of coal :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 04:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because not only their kids are in danger. There has been multiple times when an unvaxed kid spread his disease to vaxed kids. Some things should be forced upon people, and this is one of them as it could spread the disease a lot faster which is what we're trying prevent. Have you ever seen polio? Me neither, thanks to vaccines.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 21:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vaccinations should be a law. There should be an insane penalty for not vaccinating your kids. The antivaxers are only looking at one side of the argument, and completely ignoring another side. People have too much control over their kids tbh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 21:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3rd world doesn't mean anything. Just means that a certain country wasn't aligned with the US or Russia after the Cold War. Bahrain is a 3rd world country, but has the 16th highest GDP in the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mattress business is really weird. Every store in town will claim "the lowest prices in town!" Which seems like an obvious lie to snare you in, but it's true. Let's say mattress store 1 buys model A mattress, and so does store 2. Store 1 advertises it as "cloud mattress 3000" while store 2 advertises it as "cloud mattress 4000". Exact same mattress, different names, different names, lowest price for air mattress 3000 in town.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 19:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes my sister works at citi and says that it is NOT a good place for an account. It's an international bank and the charges are ridiculous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 15:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I know(Shia Islam) you're allowed to pray duhr and asar one after another. When I hear the Duhr athan I pray Duhr then Asar, instead of waiting for the Asar athan. I also do this for mughrib and isha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 15:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get married islamically, but not officially. That way you are abiding by Allah's laws but you won't lose anything if you get divorced.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
