<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1417</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 10:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russians of Reddit, what is the general view and consensus on the whole Trump/Russia scandal? How is your media covering it? What do the general public say about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was out there shortly after his Dad died and I was shitting myself the Army would throw a coup because he was clearly not up to the task and had previously named his dog the head of the Airforce or Navy or some shit. It was a tense time but thankfully they figured the GoGo dancer in the hot pants and vest was indeed the holy appointed head of state, so I ended up having a lovely trip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cloning the First Human (2001) - "This powerful documentary looks at the controversial attempts to clone a human being. Including the first televised documentation of the formation of a ten-cell human embryo!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Swan and Paedo - Peep Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 19:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 15:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I regularly call it Malk to my girlfriend and she never knows what I'm going on about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Have a Boyfriend - Snuff Box </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 15:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> England v Ireland Highlights - Royal London ODI </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Richard Ayoade and Noel Fielding bully Jimmy Carr about his Mum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that Rich Fulcher? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a limit to how many times a player can bowl in a match? Is there a rule or is it just too physically demanding to have one/two players bowling all day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> England Cricketer Moeen Ali swaps jobs with Heavyweight Boxing Champion Anthony Joshua </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This is great, look forward to seeing more from this guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Club from Bang, Bang, It's Reeves and Mortimer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Space Shuttle: The Human Time Bomb (2003) "the disaster of the orbiter Columbia. 200,000 feet above the skies of Texas, Six American astronauts and Israel's first spaceman died when their spaceship literally broke up around them. Was it a genuine one-off disaster or an accident waiting to happen?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not going to lie, I'm HYPE as fuck for this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thor: Ragnarok Teaser Trailer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That made me laugh. 'Dry Cheese Sandwich' is what my friends and I call someone who is really dull or boring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North V South Series - Match Two Highlights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love the olive oil one as a ring tone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Giant Of The Skies - The Making Of The Airbus A380 (2007) 'The story behind making the Airbus A380, the world's biggest and heaviest airliner ever built. The Airbus A380 is a double-deck, wide-body, four-engine airliner manufactured by the European corporation Airbus.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gordon Ramsay Tasting Prank </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 11:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was lovely but if I'm honest I think I put too much oil in it and should've started the pasta sooner. Had to take the garlic off the heat and wait for the pasta to cook, which meant the garlic was a bit overcooked. I know I'm making it sound like I fucked up every aspect of it (and maybe I did) but it was still really tasty and I want to try it again but get the timings right.

It was just like the scene from chef except I don't remember Jon Favreau swearing at the pasta as he was frantically stripping the parsley from the stalks.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No thank you, I can't wait to make 'Sexy Jon Favreau Eyes' at my Mrs. :)

I have to ask, are you the head chef at a restaurant? I find your knowledge of food and cooking styles astounding. I love to cook but I have to follow a recipe or I'm completely lost. I'm hoping by constantly cooking I'll just start picking it up by osmosis and eventually won't need the recipes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mate this is my favourite channel right now on YouTube. No kidding, I'm trying the Pasta Aglio e Olio from Chef tonight with my fiancee. Looks so tasty and only a handful of ingredients, I'm hungry now just thinking about it. Keep up the great work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mate... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best of Father Dougal - Father Ted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2010 I Think  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This post is almost 2 days old and still reposted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Noel Fielding's Bake Off Experience - The Big Fat Quiz of The Year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 10:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's fucking adorable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man, he's over the moon with the support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend is the director Sam Ashurst, I met him through doing stand up comedy. Really funny guy and huge horror nerd, it makes me so happy he's finally making his first feature.

As for the film this is all I know... 

Following his excellent short film Hells Garden, which played at FrightFest last year and won Total Films Best Scare award, Ashurst has made the jump into features, and heres the plot synopsis

Arcadia State is the story of Sarah (April Pearson), a timid nurse bullied by her boyfriend Paul (Mike Beckingham) and her Arcadia State Hospital colleagues in equal measure. But when Sarahs tasked with caring for a new coma patient, Simon (James Swanton), she starts to experience weird visions and dark dreams, until her life changes forever

Arcadia State stars April Pearson (Skins, Tormented, Tank 432), James Swanton (Double Date) and Mike Beckingham (Subconscious). No release date has been announced yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome, thanks mate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After winning Total Films Best Scare award, a buddy of mine has directed his first feature, a horror film called 'Arcadia State'. This is the teaser trailer and I cannot wait! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't help but admire the guys honesty, on national TV no less. Good luck mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When the Cast Can't Stop Laughing - Whose Line Is It Anyway? US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Series 1 Episode 1 of British comedy 'Campus' is up on YouTube, starring Sara Pascoe and Andy Nyman. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 08:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 17-15 to England but yeah  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 11:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It pretty much goes like this "Ooooh a person, nom nom nom." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 13:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Derren Brown! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a comedy show. I think the point is just have fun with it and not a social experiment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 11:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was starting to get a bit tired of the amount of video essays that are popping up on YouTube but this one is great, really enjoyed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How easy is it to create fake news? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 10:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colin Mochrie and Ryan Stiles's Best Scenes From Season 10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 10:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fascinating. You usually only hear about the US side of Scientology and don't think about its effect on the rest of the world. Great documentary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 11:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, it's astounding really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Churchill's Traitors (2012) "The shocking true story of the individuals who betrayed Winston Churchill and Britain in WWII, as the Japanese went from friend to foe - culminating in the Pearl Harbor attacks." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 10:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well this is probably the best video I've seen posted in this sub-reddit for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Nazi Temple Of Doom (2012) "Examines the case of the Chiemsee Cauldron a large gold cauldron found at the bottom of a German lake. It appearance suggests an ancient artifact, but closer investigation reveals it to be a modern relic that may have links to a secret Nazi SS cult." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 12:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stand up comedian tells funny story about a social worker and a dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers mate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a comedian and I need to write my 3rd hour of comedy before August for the Edinburgh festival (I have 20 mins so far) which is stressful. I still have a day job where I manage 15 people but because of the comedy I can feel myself slipping and not doing as good a job as I used to. I worry I'll eventually lose the job and won't be able to pay my mortgage, which is stressful. I have to plan my wedding and find the money for it this year. Which is stressful. My Mum is an alcoholic and suffering from depression and it makes all my interactions with my family incredibly stressful. 

Other than that I'm pretty happy. The comedy and the fact I'm getting married make up for the stress.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Reason Ewan McGregor   Danny Boyle Didnt Speak for Years - The Graham Norton Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 13:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 02:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Sick burn bro' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wayne Brady's Funniest One Liners from Season 10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patient Has To Lose 11 Teeth Due To 20 Years Of Not Brushing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 12:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 11:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a fair point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And this is how you make a shit child. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run that channel! Dead Parrot is my online baby and we're working with production companies to get fully licensed episodes of UK comedy shows on YouTube. We're trying to get a load more British shows on there but I was over the moon to get Catterick. We should be putting 'The Club' on the channel soon too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 01:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at that show! I'd never rated them until that performance and it blew me away. They were amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Think 3D Printing Human Tissue is cool? Wait until you find out where they get the human cells from... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 10:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's more a regional thing, the US have access to everything first and the other regions play catch up. They've made a few original videos like the piracy one, the react parodies and also the UK [AS] bumps. I'm just grateful for the additional content. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 09:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the idea is this was made by someone who doesn't understand women... or dogs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 23:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that was the whole point. The food is OK and affordable but there are quite a few similar restaurants on that street. This is the only one where they really take time to treat you like shit and it's brilliant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bloody love Wong Kei's. They would always force you to sit on a table with people who definitely don't want you there and regularly shout for your order and then sigh loudly when you said what you wanted. I still go there now but it's less rude these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 11:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just a rip off from the official channel with the end board cut off? The guy even burnt his own channel name into the top right corner?!

Here's the original - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MpCqYs4VzFE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 14:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 7 years, although I really threw myself into it about 5 years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 14:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks mate, appreciate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 08:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They say if you're good at something don't do it for free. So here is my second solo hour of stand up on YouTube... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 01:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 13:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to Finland once with work and it was insane, all the women were so incredibly hot and all the men were just getting smashed. They all sat in a circle passing round spirits and singing whilst the women all just stood at the bar waiting for someone to talk to them. I had some of the best sex I've ever had that weekend and all I had to do was be able to stand on my own two feet and not dribble when I talked and that made me attractive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeremy Wade and River Monsters crew do The Mannequin Challenge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 12:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeremy Wade Does The Mannequin Challenge - River Monsters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 12:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most anticipated show of the year, surely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Derren Brown Persuades A Stranger To Steal A Baby </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 15:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Catterick: Series 1 Episode 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 18:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 23:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alcohol. I'm a stand up comedian and at most gigs there's a good bar tab for the acts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Catterick - Season 1 Episode 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 17:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pockets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 13:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump: The Apprentice President? (2016) - "A candid look into the trump campaign to be the next US president." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 10:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weirdest Football Rules That Never Caught On </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 12:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pun Detective </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 13:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Best Football Kits of the 80's </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 10:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 12:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I REALLY wanted to like this. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
