<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3297</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely understand and I respect your opinion. I just don't like the channel, and I find the writing to be very terrible as either comedy or film analysis. [this is why I don't like them](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=qnTZbZw1JPQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's also a Blade Runner reference in Alien Isolation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS TACTIC TO RUN AWAY FROM CRASHING HELICOPTERS HAS BEEN PASSED DOWN IN THE ARMSTRONG FAMILY FOR GENERATIONS!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Characters have an emotional stake in a movie cliche"

I absolutely fucking hate CinemaSins as either comedy or film criticism  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cowboy Bebop. I'd argue with that show and Trigun (another short run series) it changed the way Americans saw anime and helped launch Adult Swim as a mainstay of television.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Fantastic news. Season 4 was different but still great. If you didn't enjoy season 4, I highly recommend multiple rewatches. It all works better when given another look.

I did, but I still thought that it didn't reach the stratospheric heights of the original seasons. A combination of the family members lack of interaction, the writing not being as sharp, the editing allowing for too many jokes that probably should have been cut (Michael and George-Michael one-upping each other's lie comes to mind), and character changes that I consider to be mistakes (mostly in them making Michael a REALLY unlikable jerk).

Don't get me wrong, I enjoyed the season (and if you love it, more power to you). I just didn't think it's close to being as good as the original run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I felt like the showrunners should have played TellTale's adaptation of "The Walking Dead" or watch "Stranger Things" to understand how to write well-written kid characters in horror situations, but I do genuinely enjoy The Strain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 15:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Samurai Jack - Tartakovsky proves he's a master visual storyteller once more with Jack's final season against Aku. With only one more episode left, I feel so happy to see that we got one more season of Jack and I hope that the finale lives up to the anticipation.

* Justified - Just starting out and I'm really loving it. It really scratches my itch for a "modern-day western" series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Although it's a bit of a mixed series, the Eichorst/Setrakian discussion in the first season of "The Strain" remains one of my favorite moments in television </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 15:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 15:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For animation: A full season of Thundercats (2011), Spectacular Spider-man, Moonbeam City, Clone High, or Chozen

For live action: A full season of Jericho, Surface, or Almost Human.

It's weird how many revivals of old shows we have been getting (Prison Break, Samurai Jack, Twin Peaks, etc.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 15:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prison Break - Michael's video tape at the end of the series.

"We're free now, finally. We're free." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 15:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked the film (including those amazing designs, the casting, and the fantastic soundtrack). I feel like it's a perfect visual companion to the "Hitchhiker" universe. I think it could have benefitted from a second ghost writer to tinker with the script (somebody from a witty rapid-fire writing background), and a bump up in maturity rating to cover more of the adult subject matter in the first book. But I like it as it stands. 

Watching the '81 series is nice, but MAN are some of those production values and acting rough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 14:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the love of....WHY is there still so much damn lens flare?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 06:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they'll update every other year now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 00:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries. I was more commenting on the fact that somebody down voted me at all for asking a question not really pointing towards you. Thank you for the response! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nearsighted gynecologist  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You poser </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, let's not say things we can't take back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least we got one last adventure with Jack and friends :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, Jack's parents as well. Not to mention all of the returning characters for the most recent season of Samueai Jack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 05:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I read that they didn't want to pay his huge salary, and that while the show had decent ratings it wasn't worth paying Allen that much.

Do you happen to have a link to the article?

post-edit: Did I get downvoted for asking for an article? Some people have thin skin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 04:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Man, that's an incredible shortlist. DC has been killing it on their director shortlists.

True and I hope that they have good films, but their track record does not give me hope.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 04:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NTSF:SD:SUV:: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 04:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's strange because it's the second best show in terms of ratings for ABC prime time television. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 04:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which character was the toughest for you to get psychologically into? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 02:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just personally don't like how they've written Superman and wonder woman in this game. But I guess they have to continue with how they've written him in the first game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully they won't do the Arrested Development  route and try to have the older actors try to play their younger selves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The weird thing is that it was second in ratings on the channel for prime time TV.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the first suggestion, I'd recommend the following:

* Daredevil, Jericho, The Expanse, Band of Brothers, Prison Break, Cowboy Bebop, 24, Dark Matter, The West Wing, Samurai Jack, Twin Peaks, LOST

For the second, I'd recommend the following:

* Archer, the first three seasons of Family Guy, Police Squad!, [Smart Guys](http://smartguysshow.vhx.tv/), Harvey Birdman: Attorney at Law </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. I'll give it a shot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The magic asshole? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Deadpool. Specifically, it's the usage of the song in Deadpool by DMX </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might like Cowboy Bebop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend Jericho, Dark Matter, and Cowboy Bebop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really like Rick and Morty, but I recognize that I'm clearly in the minority of that opinion. But if you want to watch it, it's on Hulu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 01:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, there's some good stuff with Anakin (mostly in Revenge of the Sith). I think the big problems involve the writing and Lucas' direction, but I Think that Anakin does have some genuinely good aspects to his character . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 00:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps going to a place online that houses episodes of the show you want. A COVE of some sort </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 00:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You forgot an X

That's right. After all, X is gonna give it to ya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 00:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I love the games on my Xbox one, but I do feel like this year seems to be a bit of a drought in terms of "Microsoft" exclusives for the consul. So, I'm thinking about getting a PS4 in addition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 00:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a good number of games on the Xbox, but I have to agree that this year, Microsoft has really been phoning it in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. Well, you can either buy the series on Amazon (only the DVD), or you can watch it on Youtube. Here's the [first episode](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uzY1D1n9zvY)

For Moonbeam City, you can buy the entire series for about 20 bucks on Amazon. Here's a link to the page: [link](https://www.amazon.com/Mall-Hath-No-Fury/dp/B014PYYV2E/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 qid=1494874069 sr=8-1 keywords=moonbeam+city)

Did you have a bad experience with a web series? Because, I LOVE Smart Guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it may be my favorite show ever made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend Daredevil for a law and order show through the prism of vigilantism. For good character development and mystery, I'd recommend Dark Matter, LOST, The Expanse, The People vs. OJ Simpson, Prison Break, and Justified. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cowboy Bebop might be a good show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For 'off-kilter' comedy (with animation recommendations), I'd recommend: 

Chosen, Childrens' Hospital, [Smart Guys](http://smartguysshow.vhx.tv/), Moonbeam City, Police Squad!, Metalocalypse, Harvey Birdman: Attorney at Law, Black Dynamite, Mike Tyson Mysteries, Aqua Teen Hunger Force, Space Dandy, Red vs. Blue: The Blood Gulch Chronicles, American Dad!, Farscape (this is a weird one. It's a sci-fi show but is so oddly experimental and hilarious that I would near call it a sci-fi dramedy), and the first three seasons of Family Guy (which I still hold as a great comedy because of the pre-cancellation episodes). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A show full of action, conspiracy, and heroism.

With these stipulations, I'd recommend: Daredevil, Jericho, Dark Matter, The Expanse, Prison Break, 24, Trigun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smart Guys (it's a hilarious online 6-part web series), the first three seasons of Family Guy, 30 Rock (post season 1), Arrested Development, Police Squad!, Moonbeam City, Archer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Gritty" with no graphic violence might be hard. I'd suggest Prison Break, Daredevil (this does have graphic violence, but it's a great show and given that you have a Jessica Jones icon, I think you can expect that level of violence/gore),The Night Manager, Dark Matter, LOST, and Jericho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Band of Brothers and John Adams. Hands down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brian saying goodbye to Pearl in Family Guy (the original run; seasons 1-3). It's a hilarious episode that becomes something rather tragic and heartfelt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything to impress his father. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jericho, Surface, Prison Break are some not mentioned that I feel had good mystery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Foy battle is also terrific. I just think that the tempo of the battle here, utilization of filmmaking techniques, usage of space and perspective, and the ability to switch between emotional beats so effortlessly makes it the most harrowing fight in the series for me.

This show is damn good from every angle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 21:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Careful with that joke. It's an antique. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 08:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Band of Brothers is at the top among my favorites. Especially in terms of writing, storytelling, and cinematic techniques.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 07:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BAD FOOD PREPARIN' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The attack on Carentan in "Band of Brothers" is still one of the most intense battle scenes ever shown on TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 07:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vader has that affect on people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take that, racism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 04:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MR. BODY'S BODY'S GONE!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like we got a winner, David Schiwmmer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 00:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is there a picture of Dune sandworm? Don't these people research the topic anymore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 22:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you're an alligator

Whoah now, Mike. Let's not say things we can't take back  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gotta disagree here. He's Anakin with none of his positive traits and Vader without competency or menace, in my point of view. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 15:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, Satan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 04:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree. The joke of George-Michael and Michael one-upping each others lie should have been cut out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 04:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything in your first paragraph is literally something Trump has done IN OFFICE

Did I SAY that I support what Trump has done in office? You seem to be missing the main argument point that blaming Trump's supporters with racism is like blaming Clinton's supporters for the worst of her world. 

WHILE YOU LUMP ME AND OTHERS INTO A BUCKET;

I'm calling you a deplorable when you do lump people into a bucket. The complexity of the argument isn't complex. Claiming all the supporters of Trump hold the same beliefs or condone the actions or words he's said is idiotic. I'm saying the identity politics YOU preach is evil of judging everyone by some "all or nothing" perspective is intellectually dishonest, and you trying to turn that back on me is just plain baffling. 

 if you vote for Trump, you ostensibly agreed with his anti-Muslim policies (can you explain how you could possibly vote for him and not support them? He made them extremely clear during the campaign)

That's idiotic. That's like saying you couldn't possibly support a candidate because you don't support 100% of their stances. It's like saying that because you voted for Clinton means you fully support all forms of abortion.

 Clinton can be a anomalously moral but effective politician that would make a decent president despite the fact that she made some mistakes.

She never admitted to ANY mistakes. She thinks everything else is somebody else's problem, EVEN NOW with Trump. 

 Trump campaigned on racism and despicable offensive populism and has demonstrated he has no understanding of how to run a government or even what the basic function of the three branches of government are.

He campaigned on economic policies that weren't about shipping jobs overseas, that partial birth abortion was wrong, to repeal Obamacare (I support this given how much much premiums have raised with the coverage), stopping TPP, and ran a campaign without Super PACS. Here's a list of promises: [list](http://www.politifact.com/truth-o-meter/promises/trumpometer/). There's a plethora of ideas he supports that not everyone will be behind, but some may see that as a better alternative to Clinton's proposed promises. 

 He was the worse choice, hands down, and his supporters are guilty of voting for him. They're never getting forgiven for that, sorry (not sorry).

Your moral outrage of the man doesn't change the fact that not all of his supporters are evil monsters (given that many of them are the same people who voted for Obama). Your inability to listen to other people's perspectives is horrendous and you should honestly be ashamed of that. Your stigmatized point of view rather than sympathizing with other people's perspectives is only going to encourage people to go to anyone who listens to their concerns (especially when economic issues are at the heart of their problems). 

 Further, he's made it clear he's only interested in using the presidency to enrich himself and his children. 

Well, given that he's advocated for causes outside his family I'd say that that statement is a factual lie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 03:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yeah, those people don't have good judgement.

In comparison to a woman who has done nothing but lie to the public, unethically collaborate with the DNC (against their charter) to beat Sanders, treats the constitution like a suggestion in how she wanted to choose justices, changes opinions with the strongest breeze, committed several felonies, used drone warfare to kill unarmed civilians, and (once again) killed an ambassador and several marines for ego.

 Sorry, I'm not about defending racist assholes. If you are, that's cool. I'm not.

People like you are the reason why Clinton lost the election. The only people who deserve to be considered among the "basket of deplorables" are people like you, especially when you lump an entire group of people with a candidate's worst traits or words.

 his supporters think Muslims are subhuman so they don't really consider that to be a problem.

You didn't say it was Trump who considered Muslims sub-human. You literally said that it was all of his supporters. Your "all or nothing" attitude is sickening. 

Once again, as a reminder: I voted for Clinton, and even then I knew she was a terrible candidate.

 The fact that they blame Clinton for Benghazi despite four Congressional investigations that turned up zilch and the fact that the GOP congress denied the funds to man the embassy proves they're even dumber than previously thought.

Not CONVICTING her of zilch isn't the same as committing a horrendous act. Especially since Obama was lying about having contact with her. The Youtube video starting the entire incident? That was an entire lie propagated by her supporters. [Benghazi and the aftermath](https://www.louderwithcrowder.com/benghazi-everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-attack-and-its-aftermath/). I don't like Trump, but Clinton was absolutely no saint and the "lesser of two evils" doesn't excuse her actions. I don't blame her supporters for her sins, neither do I blame Trump supporters for Trump's sins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 02:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also think that the writing just wasn't as on-point as the original three seasons. i think it's also because they included every joke they thought of rather than just the cream of the crop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 02:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  People who voted for Trump voted for a person who had dehumanized Muslims. They must be pretty proud of that fact if they voted for him.

Or, crazy thought, maybe they thought he was a better choice in terms of other issues than Clinton. It would be like saying the people who voted for Clinton voted for someone who let an ambassador and several marines get killed over ego. The people that voted for her must be pretty proud of the fact that she killed American soldiers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 02:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, being "in" the bushes is technically being "among" them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tarnation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope it's better than that fourth season. They really lost a lot of the charm of the show by removing so much of the family dynamic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like both, but I prefer Samurai Jack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh stop it. Vilifying supporters of a particular politician is what cost Clinton the election, and I voted for her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scene of The Master killing [the air traffic controller in the basement](https://youtu.be/1Xu5cSZU37o) in "The Strain" is pretty damn violent as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK. I can see that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 00:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest, I love prison break, especially with the different seasons. For myself, I didn't mind the shift in terms of what kind of genre they wanted to be every season, as I felt that really changed up the pacing and dynamics of the story, which I liked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 00:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Not counting one season shows or currently running shows):

The West Wing, Spectacular Spider-man, Jericho, Metalocalypse, Stargate SG-1, Justified, Avatar: The Last Airbender </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 23:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion, I think the story in alien isolation has more plot to it than in the original alien film, especially when you look at the backstory of the Svestapol station </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 21:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now THAT'S what I call music, Vol. 87 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 21:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In my opinion, the horror version of Alien is done, they perfected it in the first film, and it can't ever be replicated. 

They did for Alien Isolation, and showcased that a particular universe can still thrive with new ideas or takes on the motifs of the series. It's a prequel with Ellen's daughter, uses a new location, still keeps the Xenomorph around, and it totally works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 21:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't agree, but I respect your opinion on the matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 21:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually really do like the film (if you watch the extended edition that's less of an action film towards the end).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 21:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everybody in "Lincoln." It's kind of an unfocused film, but the writing and acting is just so damn good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 19:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Strain, Jessica Jones, Daredevil, Game of Thrones

Also, Band of Brothers is EXCELLENT and showcases the horror of combat in extreme detail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 06:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For Green Lantern, it's a case in terms of wondering how the HELL it was considered worthy of release. That and "Jonah Hex". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 06:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh.

I'd recommend seeing a movie like "the dark Knight", or avengers: age of Ultron before you see the live action adaptation of Green Lantern. I hear that's nothing but a disservice to the great comics it was inspired by. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 05:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Green Hornet made it clear that the most "in-shape" Seth Rogen can get is a young "Kevin Smith". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 05:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked the movie (for whatever that's worth). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 05:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. I can respect that rationality. For myself, it's a question of good narrative, which I can't possibly recommend with this movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daniel Day Lewis in "Lincoln". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's going to be hard to do after the craziness of their movie franchise problems </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Green Lantern

Post-edit: to the people who downvoted me, what did you actually think was worth having in the theater? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I respect your opinion. For myself, I loved the first two acts and thought the third act was alright with good action but less interesting character development 

Post-edit: why did I get downvoted? I just politely disagreed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe they just didn't like it. I love the film, however I know a number of people who were bored to tears by the film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really do like the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely start it! Even if it's one at a time, it's an EXCELLENT series </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that the one where it's like Wolfenstein: The New Order with Nazis winning World War 2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I don't think others are watching (some have also ended):

* Dark Matter, Smart Guys, Justified, Motorcity (underrated animated series;), and Samurai Jack (which I feel is one of the best shows on right now. 

What I'm considering:

* American Gods, The X-files, Agents of Shield </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I think a better word for the channel should be "Speculative Fiction TV." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 23:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really do think they dog pile on Christian Slater way too much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 17:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that animation and the weird split between the cartoon world and reality (with the strangely separated plot lines).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 16:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was sad to read that this was not a new continuation of "Osmosis Jones". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 16:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The West Wing, Cowboy Bebop, LOST, Jericho, Daredevil, Band of Brothers, the first three seasons of Arrested Development, the first three seasons of Family Guy, the first five seasons of Supernatural. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 15:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In some iterations, he can even rip Tony's armor off with his bare hands!

Okay, well that doesn't always make for a good character, which I thought was the case for Killian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 14:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Killion never claimed to be the Mandarin

[Here's Killian claiming to be the Mandarin.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gv2bGsdizhM)

I loved the differing away from the source material as the adaptation was so much more interesting than just "magic guy with rings", especially in the area of tying into the movie's themes of status, identity, and perception.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 07:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Yes, we can. That show was so terrible, that it retroactively bumped up "Spider-man Unlimited" and MTV's "Spider-man" adaptation in terms of quality just by comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 06:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy both series, in my own opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 05:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll just have to wait until they make a movie about [this guy.](https://www.vice.com/en_us/article/after-isis-killed-his-close-friends-matthew-vandyke-founded-a-mercenary-security-firm-to-fight-back-253) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 04:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who really isn't feeling this movie from the trailer?

The tone, jokes, and focus remind me a little too much of "The Men Who Stare at Goats" which had potential but squandered it horrifically.

This...isn't really gelling with me so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 04:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Has any other show/movie ever topped this show and The Last Airbender in this regard?

Well, there's a good number of great fight scenes in both TV and movies, but they'd might not have the same concept of "super powers" as Avatar and Korra have in mind. 

Here are just some great fight scenes that utilize "a form" of superpower or another (with either one or both sides of the fight), that I think are excellently intertwined in a fight scene:

* The Wolverine: [The Bullet Train fight](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2cBz_TUmOrE)

* The Amazing Spider-man - [The School Fight](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=10fno5Qpm7w)

* Avengers - [The Forest Fight](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b41-cDJ5TUw)

* Fullmetal Alchemist - [Metal vs. Fire](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ikowZCwmx-s)

* Captain America: The Winter Soldier - [The Highway fight](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qXPOl6EjbWg)

* Captain America: Civil War - [The Airport Fight](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uArWAMAmLDI)

* Trigun: Badlands Rumble - [Vash vs. Gasback](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lvk5H9foyi0)

* Spectacular Spider-man - [Spider-man vs. The Sinister Six](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B4cUf8N86Fg)

* Cowboy Bebop - [Spike vs. Pierrot](https://youtu.be/-6nmTundSn4)

* X-men: Days of Future Past - [The Sentinel Attack](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Y2TlrFVTDc)

* Spider-man 2 - [The Train Fight](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VUsssa6ArAY)

* Samurai Jack - [Jack vs. Scaramouche](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ony8OIuBVw0)

* Samurai Jack - [Jack vs. Demongo](https://youtu.be/FEw7npcRalU)

* Doctor Strange - [The "Reverse" Fight Scene](https://youtu.be/60QNLyGpFl0?t=51s)

* Star Wars: Return of the Jedi - [Luke vs. Darth Vader and the Emperor](https://youtu.be/YZ_j3s5xj8I)

* Ant-Man - [Ant-man vs. The Falcon fight](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EIrsOg9Wqp8)

* Iron Man 3 - [Tony vs. The Mandarin](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TZIAaKIsXDw)

* Star Wars: Clone Wars - [Anakin vs. Asajj](https://youtu.be/W19l3rt8HSI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an animation fan and as someone who wants to see more action oriented American animation, I've been loving how much Motorcity has blown me away. The Duke of Detroit is one of my favorite antagonists  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of great action scenes, stories, and characters, I'd recommend these:

The Spectacular Spider-man, Thundercats (2011), Cowboy Bebop (I see you didn't love it), Trigun, Fullmetal Alchemist, Samurai Jack, Gargoyles, Batman Beyond, Motorcity, The Real Adventures of Johnny Quest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That just reminds me of FOX's "Justice" show that only got one season but was pretty good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
