<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1120</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good history channels that still upload? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love history and have found several new channels as of late about history. I really can't get enough of them. Any channels that deal with Vietnam or anything from Roman times up until the War of 1812 in Europe or American History (since I know little) would be great.  

A google search told me this had been done, but it was a few years ago, so I was wondering if anything had popped up since then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh nice find, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, I will check Kaptain Kristian out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Lindybeige

I love history, I will check him out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Kurzgesagt

I have seen some of their videos I love the host. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will check those out, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent I love geography and History! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to love Vsauce, they don't seem to upload much anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have heard a lot about them and will check them out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will look into him :O) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone read, and enjoyed, books about books (the nonfiction kind)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been hearing a lot lately about books about books. This one caught my eye: ***My Life with Bob***: by Pamela Paul, mostly because I have always wanted to keep a book journal and have no idea how to do it. I was thinking though, could a book *about* books be interesting and not dry. I love video games, too, but I imagine a book about all the technical details would be boring for me to read. What have your experiences been like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do any of you keep book journals? would you care to share a picture or at least how you make it work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, those sounds like great channels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi, CC! i am looking to switch from creepy/horror themed YouTube channels to more light hearted or even educational channels, what would you suggest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am trying to make the things that come into my head a little more healthy and positive and beneficial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
