<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1143</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandpa'a brother died on Dady

*D-day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen this short film, called [2+2=5](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EHAuGA7gqFU) ? I though it was a reference to that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you read the whole thing, props to you - it took me at least an hour to read that. 

It's funny, how we react much more to stories than statistics. Say, if I told you 10 million Russians died in the Eastern front, you probably won't react much. Ten million is too big a number for us to comprehend. But if I told you for every step you take from the Soviet border to Moscow, 10 people died, now that's a different perspective. Same goes if I showed you the diary of a soldier. 

I wasn't very sympathetic towards the Japanese in the atomic bomb issue. They deserved it, in my opinion. But this article shifted my perspective. It showed how human suffering is universal, whether they deserve it or not. I still believe the atomic bomb was the best solution to defeat Japan with the least number of casualties, but that doesn't excuse the number of civilians killed. A nessesary evil, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 04:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know those industrial grade ear plugs for working in loud environments? I use them while vacuuming, and every time I take them off there is a brief sensory overload. Everything seems so loud all of a sudden.  Once I took them off outside, and I can hear the wind rustling leaf and grass, birds chirping in the distance, the distant sound of a car motor; all these background noises that I wouldn't have usually heard seemed so clear and sharp. Unfortunately my superhearing usually only lasts for a few minutes before things go back to normal :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 00:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an article from the August 31, 1946 issue of The New Yorker. A really nice long report on what Hiroshima and it's aftermath was like and how people responded to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hiroshima - the story of 6 survivors on the day of the atomic bombing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 00:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Why haven't we thought of that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 21:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tre-bu-shet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 20:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> happy cake day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 03:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the amount of people you step over and are marginalized is real

Yes, they shouldn't be ignored, or you end up with shit like this:

"The death of one man is a tragedy, the death of a million is a statistic." ---Stalin

Of course Elon and Stalin are totally different people, the point is you can't use an end result to justify the  suffering of many people.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, their regime might be terrible, but the Russians have the best anthem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 23:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll need proof, your account is new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 23:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pass compos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have Instagram? Your art is full of emotions, I love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deutschland?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not poland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Switzerland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Einstein is German. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can't look on the bright side, I will sit with you in the dark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems someone is already helping you, but I will try my best none the less :) Fire away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a kind soul OP. Here's a quote that fits you: 

Do not assume that he who seeks to comfort you now, lives untroubled among the simple and quiet words that sometimes do you good. His life may also have much sadness and difficulty, that remains far beyond yours. Were it otherwise, he would never have been able to find these words."

Rainer Maria Rilke

If you need anything, I'm willing to help, or listen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, that. But conspiracy theories are always fun :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting tidbit, Apple's logo was once rainbow coloured before they switches to silver. A theory is that Steve Jobs was paying homage to Alan Turing who played an important part in decoding the enigma, who was basically the father of modern computing. The guy was gay and died from a cyanide poisoned apple (he was also a chemist), but ppl suspected him of suicide because being gay wasn't accepted back in WWII. So ppl think the original Apple logo was a nod to Turing's homosexuality and how he died. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a punching bag and punch it whenever your angry :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either drawing or origami. Will most probably maybe update a week later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Origami could be cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not OP but sure. As someone famous probably said: "good composers borrow, great composers steal" ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, your like 16. Many people dream of starting that young. Go find a guitar teacher now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are well aged pianos better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up with tintin :') Instant upvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, but it's not your fault, it's just how cities roll. Big cities are usually more competitive, people are more stressed, suspicious and less likely to chat. Most of the time people are too busy to bother with you, they just want to mind their own business, and we see so many ppl every day, smiling and chatting with everyone would just be tiring.

I wouldn't gauge how rude people are based on how big the city is, on average people are about the same, you see a more diverse spectrum of society in a big city, so you're bound to have more unpleasant encounters. I'm living in a high tech area right now, and even though it's a fairly big city, most people here are really nice.

imo, to put it bluntly, how rude an area is depends on the average education and income level.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, but it's not your fault, it's just how cities roll. Big cities are usually more competitive, people are more stressed, suspicious and less likely to chat. Most of the time people are too busy to bother with you, they just want to mind their own business, and we see so many ppl every day, smiling and chatting with everyone would just be tiring.

I wouldn't gauge how rude people are based on how big the city is, on average people are about the same, you see a more diverse spectrum of society in a big city, so you're bound to have more unpleasant encounters. I'm living in a high tech area right now, and even though it's a fairly big city, most people here are really nice.

imo, to put it bluntly, how rude an area is depends on the average education and income level.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's DnD? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that Aland's flag on the wall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the difference between this and fencing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's also one where US made a nazi pun after WWII and put on sunglasses, and he refuses to take it off until someone laughs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would assume it does somewhat, at least on political subreddits, but most of the traffic comes from NA, so I don't think votes will be affected that much. A bigger factor is that most ppl here are asleep when you post on Asia time, so it's harder to hit the front page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're an Asian, not a Csian!

...I'll see myself out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is an exoplanet out there made of mostly diamond. It's called  55 Cancri e. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you can choose any superpower, what would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it the animated french one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pmed someone a poem and they didn't respond :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a really great question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah it's just weird </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, my writing is probably easier to understand than Shakespeare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you go to a school in a eastern country, there is the same pattern you see in the West. There is an equal amount of students with bad grades in the West and East. It is true that eastern cultures place more emphasise on academic achievements, but I think there is a more important reason to this stereotype. Due to the nature of immigration processes in the West, you can only immigrate if you are smart or rich. Thus Asians seem to be averagely smarter, and seem to do well even in poverty, but it is because their parents were allowed in due to having a high level of education. The reason Asians tend to have high marks is because only the smarter, or richer, or the ones that have more connections are allowed in, and that is not representative of the general population. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP care to give update? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck, I tell you you'll be awake at midnight scouring the fridge for food! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peace. I want people to be at peace with each other, world peace and all that. Imagine how much more efficient we can be if we just stop fighting each other! Not only that, I want inner peace. The ability to accept who you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Won't you be severely jet lagged for the whole trip? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you speak Cantonese or Mandarin in HK? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USSR ---- US

US senior ---- US </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know either lol. I also don't know why the comment below me has 450+ votes. Is there a joke I'm missing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hotel you mentioned is called Nishiyama Onsen Keiunkan, it has been around since 705 AD. There is actually an older company, also Japanese, a construction company called Kong Gumi, it has been around since 578 AD. The thing is, it liquidated in 2006 and now operates as a subsidiary of Takamatsu. Depending on how you define 'operating company', answers will differ. So I don't know.

Correct, a more concise definition would be "an idea, behavior, or style that spreads from person to person within a culture".

Correct, the other one is the flag of Indonesia and Monaco.

Correct

Correct, I hope to see it too, hopefully with my grandchildren </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the world`s oldest operating company?

Who coined the term 'meme'? (bonus points for definition)

Which [flag](https://qph.ec.quoracdn.net/main-qimg-fd51dc59fbe7be7bb7081d336e1da819) is [Poland](http://cdn2.list25.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/2130-610x360.jpg)?

What is the origin of Shakespeare's quote: 'to be or not to be'?

What comet will come near Earth in 2061? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like a flowing flag in the shape of Australia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Want more? :D It might take me a while to think of nice questions though, it seems hard to stump you.

E: too tired, maybe tomorrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
