<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2746</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you talking about something like this?

https://www.royalcollection.org.uk/collection/61944/arming-sword-and-scabbard
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ran a search on "side-sword" and found this:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spada_da_lato

Is that accurate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What type of sword would have been carried by Hernn Corts during his time in Central America? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm working on a mixed-media project for school. A search on "16th-century Spanish sword" results in many images, but they vary wildly. I know that we'll never know exactly the look or name of Cortes's weapon, but can you offer a logical possibility?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What type of sword would have been carried by Hernn Corts during his time in Central America? I'm working on a mixed-media project for school. A search on "16th-century Spanish sword" results in many images, but they vary wildly. Can you offer a logical possibility? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find this to be an interesting phrase in the article: "a chop-shop for beehives." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. So how can I watch my movies? Is there a workaround? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have many movies purchased through the Microsoft Movies and TV app on Xbox. I don't see this app available in Google Play (most MS apps are present, except this one). What's the best way to access and play my movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I'll need to investigate that.  My contract expires in November, and alas, if there's no phone future with Microsoft, I guess I'll have to switch.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see both sides.

My real-life career requires that I occasionally delve into academic journals, so I am familiar with navigating jargon.  Generally, jargon serves two purposes: (1) it conveys content to those who understand the lexicon; (2) it serves as an artificial divider to keep pesky laypersons at bay.  It's that second function of jargon that causes the lay reader to label researchers as stuffy and arrogant.  In English lit circles it's all particularly annoying, because--as Kuntz's detractors on G+ will attest--sometimes the writer would be better served by using simpler language; clouding the topic with buzzwords and technical terms is often unnecessary.  There are definitely some writers out there who substitute vocabulary for real substance. I'm not saying that Kuntz is one of those types, but the arguments against his cumbersome prose do have some merit.  If only 5% of your readership can understand your thesis, then you've wasted a lot of time.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you suggest a scope mount for my father's Winchester Model 94 .450 Marlin carbine? I know little about guns but would like to purchase the correct mounts (and possibly scope) for my dad. Thanks! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT: Apparently it's a "Short Rifle" rather than a carbine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far it seems that Kuntz's prose style is being discussed as much as the book's content.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are some snippets from a recent exchange from the North Texas RPG Con Facebook group:

Frank Mentzer: The lineage [of D D] as commonly credited seems to be as follows. Does Rob address this sequence?

a. Wesely's Braunstein sent individuals into a castle (modern warfare system), Arneson a player;
b. Arneson then sent individuals into a dungeon (Chainmail combat variant), and told Gary about it in detail;
c. Gygax wrote up and published the combination of ideas.

Tim Kask: Once again, Rob is talking through his hat.

Mentzer: In the [Kuntz book] cover text, the term Dungeons   Dragons is misused and uncredited. He needs a competent editor before he gets a C D from WotC... or maybe they'll just ignore him. We shall see.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the sound of the term "design workflow," but I'm not really sure what it means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TSR Games.  You know they published about half a dozen issues of GYGAX MAGAZINE?  Eventually Luke Gygax amicably left the company, so they stopped producing the mag and now focus on OSR products.

http://store.tsrgames.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The creator of the original Top Secret RPG is soon to launch a new, updated edition. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said.  I certainly admire him as a game designer, as "Mordenkainen's Fantastic Adventure" remains one of my all-time favorite modules.  As I mentioned, I'm very interested in hearing his thoughts on the evolution of the game we all know and love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in total agreement with you that Arneson's contributions to the hobby are both very important and quite different than Gary's.  The game would not exist without Arneson.  But reading the blurb on the publisher's site, I get a distinct sense of bias.  Or maybe it's not really bias, but just a desire from the author to elevate Arneson a bit higher up the ladder.  But it may be hard to raise up Arneson without knocking Gary down a bit.  

At any rate, I'm interested in reading the author's discussion of how D D is not descended from Chainmail, since that's counter to every bit of history I've ever read on the subject.  

(It may also be worth mentioning that Kuntz was literally a teenager when he was gaming with EGG and Arneson, and 45 years have passed since then. I wonder how that affects his perception of those long-ago events . . .) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After reading the introduction to this book, I get the feeling that the author is trying to knock EGG off his pedestal.  Right or wrong, there's definitely an agenda here other than exploring Arneson's contributions to D D. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the detailed reply! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By not counting D D, I hope to avoid any possibility of edition wars.  : ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Runequest 3rd edition?  I own the boxed set, but that is my only experience with RQ.  How do those two versions compare? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> " . . . 5th is just another fantasy heartbreaker."

In what ways?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ". . . I stick to more rules light smaller systems . . ."

Such as what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is it bad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder why the writers would remove the setting's backstory? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it?  I own the old books but haven't looked at them in ages.  What's different in the newer version? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, that's cool, me too!  We stick with 3E simply because we have all(?) of the books from 1st, 2nd, and 3rd edition, and the rules changes between those and 4th are too much for an easy conversion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not counting D D, what RPGs do you still play in an older, discontinued edition, preferring it above the currently supported edition? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. I just recoiled when i heard the word " censored." It doesn't sound like I'm missing much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, okay.  Yeah, I don't need that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. 

EDIT:  So the Kodansha ebook version is uncensored?  I'm looking here:

http://kodanshacomics.com/series/ghost-in-the-shell/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's finally time for me to read GHOST IN THE SHELL, but I'm confused by all of the many editions and reprints. I would like an uncensored, English-language (or bilingual) version. The latest "deluxe" version on Amazon is censored. : ( Can you help me sort it all out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favorite novelist is William Goldman. His thrillers are without equal. He hasn't written any book-length fiction in 30 years. He turns 86 in a few months . . . so I remain hopeful. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 04:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have no need to apologize for being too young to appreciate old Craftsman quality. Don't feel bad for assuming new ways are the best ways. Wisdom will come with age. You'll get there, lad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd take OP's old Craftsman against your hip and modern version any day of the week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ELI5 the many different editions of RuneQuest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dewalt, like Craftsman, is owned by Stanley Black   Decker.  Makita is a Japanese company.  There are a lot of interesting dynamics in the tool world, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stanley Black   Decker is "committed to bringing Craftsmans manufacturing back to the United States." I know that Craftsman has fallen off the BiFL radar in recent years, so maybe the Stanley buyout is good news for the brand . . . ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 04:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds cool. Pics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.  8000 watts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the helpful commentary! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, okay.  I need to look closer at the specs of the inverters.  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My miter saw requires 1800 watts. Will a 2000-watt inverter be sufficient, or does the saw have a "start-up" energy requirement beyond 2000 watts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In those cases, I always blame the song that was playing when the problem occurred. I really do. "Damn you, Billy Idol!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! Upvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
