<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3359</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snoop Dogg gives heartfelt speech while inducting Tupac into the HOF </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 15:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 23:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a big fan of it myself, the only trap album I honestly really like is Travis Scott's Rodeo. I'd give it a try if I were you, even if you dislike trap a lot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 02:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah agreed his album is actually really good, went way past my expectations. Went into it thinking I'd be unimpressed just like when Zayn came out with his solo album, but this was a pleasant surprise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disliked One Direction a lot, gave Zayn's solo album a listen and wasn't impressed at all. This album however... Wow, not something I expected. I'm blown away tbh. Never expected something so good to come out of a former 1D member. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Run The Jewels - Legend Has It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out her Cheek to Cheek album. It's a collaborative album with Tony Benett, pretty much just jazz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lady Gaga comes to mind for me. Started out doing pop music, was insanely popular, then just went to do Jazz for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stfu my nigga </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wholesome joji is best joji 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah which is exactly why he doesn't break character that often and why he deleted joji vlogs. Such a shame tbh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to be like you tbh, it took me a while to really understand why it isn't just trash. The Money Store was my first introduction to them, took me multiple listens to start enjoying it but it definitely grew on me. Their production is absolutely insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I honestly love seeing him out of character, seems like a really lovable and chill guy to be friends with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you don't believe those songs I mentioned convey their meaning in a unique and interesting way? Because in my opinion they do. To each their own though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you decide to pick out two lines from one of his most mainstream and banger tracks? Also those lines do fit the message of the track to be humble, but I admit that it's not his best work.

But lyrically he is in my opinion one of the best, if not the best, of this generation. Listen to To Pimp A Butterfly, a few tracks I'd check out purely for lyrics: These Walls, How Much A Dollar Cost, Black the Berry.

Even if you don't like his lyrics, you gotta admit there's a good message behind most of the songs he puts out. 

I will say that a lot of people rate his lyrics TOO highly like there's a really deep meaning behind every line, but just ignore those people. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just trying to be nice man lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get where you're coming from. Most mainstream music is really mediocre, but there's a few great songs that gain a lot of popularity every now and then. But it's been like this in every generation. 

I'd check out [THIS](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=be_HVMwiBAM) video which talks about that subject. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I highly recommend listening to The College Droupout, Late Registration and My Beautiful Dark Twisted Fantasy. Those are in my opinion his three best records and each one of them has some of the best production ever. I'd avoid a few of his other albums, but music is subjective. I for example hate Yeezus, yet there are lots of people loving it.

Kanye's personality may be annoying, arrogant, egotistic whatever, but he sure as hell can produce some amazing music. 

Hope you end up checking out those records and at least enjoy them for the extremely good production. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're a Hip Hop duo who gained a lot of popularity after their debut album Sremmlife. Their music falls under the genres pop rap, trap rap, southern hip hop etc. You could basically describe it as "turn up" music, so music to just party and get crazy to.

A few songs by them which you could check out if interested are: Black Beatles, Shake It Fast, By Chance, No Type etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's part of his appeal in my opinion. Not every artist has to go hard as fuck or really aggresive with their voice. And honestly even Kendrick can go hard if he wants to (DNA, m.A.A.d City, Blacker the Berry), but he just decides not to on every track he produces.

What else don't you get about him? Why people love his albums/music so much? Go listen to the entirety of Good Kid m.A.A.d City and To Pimp A Butterfly. Read the lyrics while listening. It's way different from any other hiphop artist of this generation. Especially To Pimp A Butterfly, it's a damn masterpiece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wholesome Joji (Filthy Frank) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly love seeing how different Kendrick looks here from how he looks now. He always has a new distinguishable look with every album. And also always a new sound.

I love this Schoolboy Q song too, but there's so many better ones he's come out with in my opinion. Not saying it's a bad track though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would DEFINITELY check out Injury Reserve - Floss if you're a hip hop fan, such a shame that there aren't many people who have heard it before. One of my favorite albums from 2016. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Outside feat. 21 Savage](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iQgvrzmal6o) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Death Grips - Hacker

Mac Miller - Two Matches 

Brother Ali - Sleepwalker

Desiigner - Panda

Nas - The Message

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already follow GaLm and most of the derpcrew, love those guys :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to go back and watch Seamus play some Fallout 3/Vegas or Borderlands 1, those were the days man.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I often see Cole being criticized, but this is probably the first time I've ever seen this sub shit on Joey. Usually this sub is really positive about Joey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Favorites: Submission, Busted and Blue, Ascension, Charger, Momentz, The Apprentice

Least favs: Halfway to the Halfway House, Out of Body, We Got The Power, Hallelujah Money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, all of sudden his album isn't great anymore and he's too pop for this sub lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me Against The World by Tupac is better imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Illmatic and To Pimp A Butterfly are the two best hip hop albums of all time imo. Couldn't really argue with anyone saying either one of those is the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good track, but other outshine it imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who feels like the only reason this is getting upvoted so much is because of Thorin?

Nonetheless, good fragmovie. I enjoyed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoulda kept the "you smelly cuck" in your comment then lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think he'll give it a 7, I'm feeling more of a 5 or 6 from him tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't enjoy that song, it's just so corny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> k.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He liked The Let Out and Ascension, but I honestly don't think he'll like the whole project. Should be an interesting review though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://open.spotify.com/album/0NvirtaDCaZU5PAW1O5FDE

Should be out now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gorillaz - Humanz (Deluxe) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been listening to it since it came out for me over 5 hours ago and my opinion hasn't really changed. A few tracks are skippable for me like We Got The Power, Hallelujah Money, Out Of Body, Halfway To The Halfway House. They're not really growing on me. I feel like the first half of the record is great, but it definitely falls a bit flat in the second half.

That's just my opinion though, hope I don't get bombarded with downvotes or anything lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> midnight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally out in the US, have fun listening boys! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly think Vince Staples feature is still one of the best. Danny Brown's verse is awesome too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listened to this earlier this night when it came out in EU, anyway I think the album is solid, but it's not amazing or anything. Definitely a few stand out tracks like Ascension, Busted and Blue, Submission, Charger etc. but then there's also a few skippable tracks like Hallelujah Money, We Got The Power, Out Of Body.

So overall I'm feeling a strong 6 to a light 7. (Fantano will probably give it a 5 lmao)


Edit: Guys I get it, some of you like We Got The Power, Hallelujah Money etc. this is just my honest opinion. Everyone has their preferences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually dude check out Mortal Man, all the verses on it are clean and you could use his poem and the thing at the end of the track. 

https://genius.com/Kendrick-lamar-mortal-man-lyrics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out some stuff by Aesop Rock, dude has the biggest vocabulary in rap and I'm pretty sure a lot of his tracks are relatively clean.

Check out [None Shall Pass](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yeh6jhHLgtg) for example </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah bro, not clean at all lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Midnight like the rest of the world I assume, so a bit less than two hours for you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a Drake fan or anything, but with him it really just depends on the song. If we're talking If You're Reading This It's Too Late kinda tracks than he ain't boring at all, if we're talking Views... then well yeah, he's pretty boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly thought The Heist was a very enjoyable album. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean each album is different, but I'd give Demon Days a go first.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted a thread over an hour ago when it came out in EU, got removed cuz it's not out in America I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finished the whole album and honestly I don't think it was amazing or anything, but it was still a very solid album. 

EDIT: Elevator is a BANGER btw, like holy fuck that track goes hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't finished the full album so I may edit this:

1. Submission

2. Busted and Blue

3. Ascension </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that track is fucking insane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where you from? America? If it's not available for you guys then you gotta wait til midnight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UK? :p

I haven't listened to the leak yet so this is gonna be great :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 12:09 am, it got released at midnight on spotify for us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Humanz released in Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much all of To Pimp A Butterfly by Kendrick Lamar in my opinion.

EDIT: BLOOD into DNA on DAMN. also by Kendrick Lamar and honestly most of Good Kid m.A.A.d City goes well together since it's just one big story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chance the Rapper - Same Drugs [Hip Hop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Excuse me sir, do you have a moment to talk about Corey Feldman?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G_OJhSGG078) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goddamn Australians and their early releases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can people stop comparing these two to each other already? Jfc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FRESH] Joji - I Don't Wanna Waste My Time (OFFICIAL) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda hard to fuck up a WWII game, but you never know I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't imagine that they'll fuck this up, but if they do I'm giving up on CoD for good. CoD 2 is probably my favorite game in the franchise and this is looking promising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Kendrick  Lamar - For Free?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_ZTYgq4EoRo)     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realise 8 hours a day is almost the same as a full time job right?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who actually likes Joey's album more than Kendrick's? Don't get me wrong, Kendrick's abum is great as well but I just enjoyed this record more. I'm sad it didn't sell that well though, it sold even less than Joey's last album, didn't it? He deserves much more praise imo.

Joey and Kendrick have the two best hip hop albums of the year so far imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tyler, the Creator is legit the funniest artist out there. His music may not be the best, but his personality is awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, that's probably the only great Nicki verse out there lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright I'll try to find it this week and will reply to you again once I find it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 16 year old here, looking to get into vinyl


So before you roast me for being a hipster or something, no I'm not. I'm really just a music lover and would like to experience the real warmth of vinyl and to own physical copies of my favorite records rather than listening to them on spotify.

My birthday is coming up on the 6th of may so I thought this would probably be a good time to get into it. Anyway, which starter turntable would you guys recommend? I was thinking the Audio Technica LP120, but I still find that kind of expensive if I'm gonna be honest.

Also I think my mom has an unused Pioneer from the 90s stashed away somewhere upstairs, I'm not sure what exact model it is, but I heard old Pioneers are usually pretty good right?

One final question: Would you recommend just getting a second hand amplifier or would a new one be way better?

Sorry if any of these questions seem stupid, I've read a bit into it and know which red flags to avoid (Ahem crosley), but it'd be nice to get some help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't this posted yesterday? Why'd it get removed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I couldn't get tickets in time, so bummed out. Could get them, but I'd have to pay a lot more which sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I'm aware of that, but in every couple tracks Kendrick reads the poem and adds a couple of lines. Those last few lines usually tell the theme of the upcoming tracks. The poem get's longer and longer throughout the whole album and then is read in its entirety on the last track.

The part I mentioned is the part of the poem he read just before the track U on These Walls, with those last few lines saying something about the theme of the track U. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhm no, they're from the end of These Walls, leading up to the track U. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came out on January the 13th, 2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda like "Omg I can't get enough of this it's so amazing" I guess? I'm not a professional emoji translater lmfao. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People definitely do this, especially older people believe it or not lol. They spam emojis instead of just using one or two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Death Grips, Kendrick Lamar, Danny Brown, Run the Jewels, Clipping, Kanye West (his older stuff though), A Tribe Called Quest, Tyler the Creator and many more.

Also would like some R B recommendations, want to get more into that genre.

Recommend me shit fam, would love to listen to some lesser known artists. But feel free to recommend anything and I'll give it a try, will edit my post to say what I thought about some of the recommendations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, in the poem leading up to this track it also mentions him being depressed and screaming in a hotel room, so the video fits it perfectly. Here's the part of the poem leading up to the track for anyone wondering.



"I remember you was conflicted

Misusing your influence

Sometimes I did the same

Abusing my power, full of resentment

Resentment that turned into a deep depression

Found myself screaming in a hotel room" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I decided to post this music video here because it is pure art in my opinion. I have no idea how it only has 9 million views, it deserves a lot more than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kendrick Lamar - God Is Gangsta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't call his music amazing myself, but it's fucking awesome as turn up music when you just wanna get crazy and dance or whatever. I was a bit disappointed by his New English album since it just felt extremely rushed, but the singles he's put out since then have all been very enjoyable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. When he gives something a 5 it's mediocre, a 6 means he liked it but there's still a lot of flaws, an 8 means it was great with few flaws. 7 is right in between that and I can agree with his rating tbh even though I would've given it an 8 myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the reversed part was very creative, I don't think I've ever heard an artist do that before on an album. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 11:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 18 comments but none are showing? The shadowbans are real lol

EDIT: I love this track btw, top 5 for me on the album. But I've yet to look up what the reversed part says, could anybody tell me what it says?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have fun being banned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're not funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what the fuck is your problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Injury Reserve aren't underrated, they're just not well known. Most people who've heard their music would rate them highly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got removed rip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats wrong with track 8? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck dude I'm on the bus right now and I cant download it, anyone confirm if it's good? Any more bangers like humble? The features actually any good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cant watch rn, what does he say about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People probably forget about it since it's not on spotify, I forgot about it as well for a while. Listened to it for the first time a few weeks ago even though I listened to Tyler way before that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chef Ramsay has an Awkward gay Moment with a Contestant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 13:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. What I've done instead is just download albums that aren't available on spotify and put them in my playlist from local files, then sync it with my phone and it works perfectly fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey dad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard the release got pushed back because of some samples he used or something and they had to get some shit fixed, but I'm not sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 12:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Ascension
2. Saturnz Barz
3. Andromeda
4. Let Me Out
5. Hallelujah Money
6. We Got The Power

This is my ranking. I honestly hated We Got The Power, so corny and just bleh. At least Hallelujah Money was interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have listened through the album a few times since it leaked and it's solid. Personally don't like it as much as his last project, but this is still very good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know any other Nicki verses like that? Because that's the only time I've ever really heard a Nicki verse and enjoyed it. Then again, I haven't really bothered listening to her albums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly would've never thought these two would form a rap duo, but boy am I happy they did. Can't believe how consistent they are with their music, all three albums have been like an 8 or 9 out of 10 and they started in 2014. Just crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.redd.it/7e31fgkvddpy.png - cowchop logo is missing the black pixel on knife and handle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://streamable.com/kqiri </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this one was still better than part 1, but agree on the rest you said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally not a fan of Hopsin, but I thought this was dope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pm me too thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
