<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject375</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My uncle committed suicide believing he wasn't needed. A few months later, his widowed wife had an asthma attack in the middle of the night and couldn't find her inhaler. The kids found her the next morning. If he was there he would've been able to help her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not about finding someone you agree with 100% of the time. It's about finding somebody, anybody, who isn't doing the bidding of their big donors. 

Our politicians are puppets being controlled by oligarchs. Our politicians do not fight for their constituents, they fight for the people who give them the means to continue lying to their constituents. 

Corey Booker received more money from Wall Street than any other politician, Democrat or Republican. Corey Booker defended Mitt Romney, against Barack Obama, when Obama criticized Romney for his connections to Bain Capital. You really think that guy is going to fight for you? Maybe if you pay him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 14:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe in the Wikipedia it says that people who were sentenced to death by beast would have to fight beast after beast. If they killed the first lion, a second lion would be released. And a third if needed, etc.

But there are three types of Bestarii, as far as I can tell. There are the animal trainers who were considered Bestarii, there were Bestarii who were sentenced to death by beast, and then there were Bestarii who were affluent people that were given favorable conditions to fight in. That's what I gathered from Wikipedia though, I might be wrong and if I am I'd love to know what's true! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How legit were the Roman Bestiarii? Did Carpophorus really fight a lion, tiger and bear fairly? Did Lysimachus kill a lion with his bare hands? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am interested in some of the gentlemen who fought as Bestarii in the Roman Colosseum, and other arenas by extension. Those being, people who trained, fought along side, or against animals in the arena. 

With the limited resources at my disposal, I am having trouble finding concrete claims about what transpired there. From what I gather, most of the time that animals were involved in the arena, there was a large handicap utilized either in favor of the fighter, or the animal. For example, I have read about how Commodus would fight wild lions. And I have read less about how he did it while standing on a platform above them and shooting at them with arrows. Not exactly heroic, but quite exactly Commodus. Likewise, I am wondering about how exaggerated these other claims were:

*"As a punishment, damnatio ad bestias is mentioned by historians of Alexander's campaigns. For example, in Central Asia, a Macedonian named Lysimachus, who spoke before Alexander for a person condemned to death, was himself thrown to a lion, but overcame the beast with his bare hands and became one of Alexander's favorites."* - Is this story legit? Did Lysimachus get sentenced to death by lion, only to defeat it and become a king? His Wikipedia doesn't mention, and you think it would.

Similarly, I have found this excerpt *"Martial (Spectacles, XVII, XXVI) noted that Carpophorus, who was renown as a bestiarius, as having killed a bear, a lion, and a leopard. In fact, Carpophorus is said to have killed twenty wild animals in one show."* 

I truly wonder if any of these accounts are correct, or if they are embellishments. 

Do we know for a fact if there is any evidence that there was ever a "fair fight" held between humans and animals, or were they always favored one way or the other, by either heavily arming the men, injuring the men before combat, or injuring the animals before combat?

Was there ever a notable contestant in the arena who did manage to survive the ferocious onslaught of a hungry lion, leopard or bear on equal footing? It seems to me that most of the time the winner was determined before they stepped on to the arena. 

Also, were there women bestarii who fought with or trained animals for the arena? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 22:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think anybody is beyond political bias, regardless of race or education.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 22:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "He writes from a libertarian conservative perspective", which is fine, as long as we all can acknowledge that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 22:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WND and National Review? You do realize these two sources have no more legitimacy than their leftist counterparts like HuffPo and ThinkProgress, right? Smh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another of the reasons was that she lost $30,000 that was supposed to help save her family's business. In the grand scheme of things that sort of loss is obviously not worth taking your life over but in the perspective of a teenager who only knows a life in which her family depends on keeping the business open, it's a significant setback that could be reversed with life insurance and/or suing the school (neither of which I think would be fair to exploit though) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean "you people"? Is that people who don't defend political propaganda? How is asking for common sense divide   conquer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The universal translator did kick in when communicating with the alien species. It translated the language literally, for example "his arms wide" is an English translation of their language. But simply knowing the dialect couldn't help to explain the methodology they used in communication.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a sizable crossover between KiA subscribers and Breitbart subscribers. Doesn't make any sense, really. Just prepare to be downvoted by them, because they'll never admit that Breitbart is propaganda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
