<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3750</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British office vs US office? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Want to start one of them, along with 30 rock. I absolutely love Ricky however I feel that the US version has the better cast  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He barely breaks the top ten for me. Behind Curry, Harden, Wall, Westbrook, IT, CP3 even Kyrie and Kemba. Id even take Conley over him since he isnt a mist in the playoffs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao Smart is one of the toughest guys in the league, just tries too hard to get an edge over the opposition. And Delly was/is one of the dirtiest players in the league </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 22:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it comes to trashing Juventus, it is entirely relevant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 22:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are forgetting that Crotone and Bologna will wreck Juventus with a 5 goal difference each, and Juan Jesus will score the hattrick to lead us to the Seria A title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jokic, although his development may have not been the same. However hindsight is 20/20 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We will have atleast 5 guards next year, which one would you consider trading </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 11:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between IT, Bradley, Fultz, Rozier and Smart there are big decisions waiting to be made. I dont count Green here cause he plays mostly SF and will be probably gone. I would trade Smart, he is gonna get paid in 2018, cant shoot, questionable decision making and even though I love him to death can still kill me sometimes. Rozier would be a bench booster and I would give atleast 20 mins to Fultz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What popular and widely appreciated movie do you hate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Live perfomances of "Love is a laserquest" on a concert? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 00:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep finding videos infront of a studio audience but I want to see this kind of a performance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 21:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for clearing that up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 20:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still not a pair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 03:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time Tony Brothers is motioning for a foul he looks like hes having a seizure  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 23:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shouldnt be, you would have had a better chance against Celta than United </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 22:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah my bad, I didnt read your question right, I thought that you could voluntarily quit and get like a pension or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 22:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh crap, I didnt see it was a discharge, I thought it was you can voluntarily resign with benefits, my bad  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 22:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know anything about the actual number, just that I feel that even one suicide witnessed would leave a big trauma on the conducter or however the guy that is driving the train is called  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 22:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> certain number

I feel like that number should be one 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 12:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got the Celtics spread and got them over, on a double so thank you James Young </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Played my second MTT, cashed out for the first time, here are my best hands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I entered the freeroll 150 bankroll booster on bet365. The field had approx. 200 players and started as a shove fest but calmed down soon. I started like a nit with 5k and got down to about 4300 when I woke up with kings. I got it all in pre against A9s and doubled up because everything missed him. Few hands later I got AK suited and called a 3BB raise(240) from the MP. Flopped an ace and raised 560 on the flop, 480 cause the straight got there on the turn and 320 cause the board paired on the river. However he had AQ and i won 3k. 
Then came to the hand of the night
Woke up with jacks 2 spots behind the dealer, and called a 3bet from the UTG+1 and went three way to the flop
H:12220
UTG+1: 5780
BB: 9330
The flop comes 4s7h3s 
UTG+1 bets 665 
Hero calls
BB folds
turn 7s
Board paired and the flush got there and the villain bets 1596
His bet sizing and preflop raise made me put him on an AJ or KQ so I called
The river comes 6 of clubs and the one carded straight is there
He goes all in for around 3200 and I figured its either a pocket pair or a hand like i said above that has completely missed
I call he shows KJo and I get up to 18 k
From there I called a couple small all ins and got to around 23,4 k 
Fast forward to 35 players left and 27 paid and im hovering around 17 to 18 
We get to thirty players and I cant fold fast enough in the fear of bubbling and not getting my 1.5 (One for one drop aint got nothing on me) I fold hands like 77 and 10s
Finally I survive the bubble and get into a threeway all in with A10 of spades for 14 k
I hit the runner runner flush and triple up. Im down to 30 k when i get AJs and flop a jack and double up again, and the next hand i get 15 k more with queens. So now im folding and i get to the final hand of my tourney. I have like 2bb and go all in with 86, opponent has A10
I flop two pair he makes a runner runner straight and with a sick feeling in my gut I go out in 7th out of 198 and get 7.5 euros
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its okay, im in a better place atleast mentally in that aspect, thanks though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That part of the lyric is really painful for me, so I chose to understand the first part as an existential crisis that im currently in lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you look into a mirror to remind yourself you are there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking hate Amir Johnson, the 6foot9 man that looks like a homeles ww1 veteran trying to be a stretch five that has no shot and cant rebound for shit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesnt seem probable. It takes like 1.5 seconds to press the button, are you trying to tell me that the boat sank in two seconds, or maybe the skipper slipped or whatever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah if only the game didnt last 4 quarters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its okay, Smart cant hit a free throw anyway...or a jumper...or a layup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone needs to tell the ref to take the whistle out of his mouth when he breathes out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its the first half and we aint losing by 17 what timeline is this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats George Segal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at a swimming competition and we were watching the race for the special needs and handicapped kids. In my team there was a guy who lost the bottom half of his leg in an accident, so he was competing in the event. When they were waiting to start someone whistled and the guy on my team jumped in the water. I started laughing cause I thought he got startled and thought the race started, but I realized his only leg slipped and he fell into the pool when I opened my eyes to 200 people staring disapprovingly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the landing spots now for Cutler? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the Texans might get him but now with Watson thats seems out of the question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brady throws for 5k  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldnt a steal still be a TO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can spell his name without Bradley </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont know why you are downvoted, you are saying the truth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His injury was such a JR injury to me. I can see JR going "yea boi this rim gonna get it now" like TA did when his knee  spontaneously combusted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isnt really, its more like saying "Hey, can I get an advanced look into that stat you just offered"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally the last fucking line of my comment was that I am not taking anything away from him, are you that retarded? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am curious to know the ammount of those that come from drive and kickout or just pass to LeBron and let the dad dicking begin. 
Not to take anything away from him just would be cool to know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would count Green in the starting five since this is in reference to the playoff statistics, I dont know how he is as opposed to the league average </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clippers cant get a defensive stop to save their lives  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCK YES THE ROOK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fuck wrong wit you boy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like everything beside the placement of the bands name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His mechanics dont look broken and I like his energy but I dont see us keeping him if we get Fultz unfortunately </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terry is like a discount Westbrook, questionable shooting but will go 160 miles an hour down the court every fastbreak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
