<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1137</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 09:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next Generation Meme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come at me nigga </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pubs in Cork? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 10:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,

Which pubs in Cork has the 18 year limit?
Here in Norway most pubs have an 20 or 21 limit, but im wondering how it is in Cork? :) 

Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 10:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hper det er greit at jeg er transe da, har hvertfall veldig stor penis 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 10:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mt meg p Politistasjonen i stavanger baby 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ja det er jeg kom  knll meg n baby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skal vi ha sex? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nei det er dere ikke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha yeah :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh sorry lol didnt catch the meaning of being "Grand" hahahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sexy, and im in my area :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well ofc i would imagine meetups in pubs every night, but I was thinking of something more sepcific than just pubs. (Dont get me wrong i enjoy drinking) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you guys!! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not the biggest on sport (i go to the gym every week) but i have not done actual Sport in years. But thanks for the tip :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meetups in Cork </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,
Im from Norway and from 1. September to 1. December im going to Cork to work as an IT-apprentice. Im 19 years old.

I'll be living with a host family, but I was wondering if there are any Social meetups in Cork? I feel like i might not want to "hang out" with the 40-50 year old dudes I will work with and I would love to meet new people a bit more around my age! :) 

Any tips? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahah thanks, gonna tell everyone how much better Cork is than Dublin ;)

And ofc i wont throw any rocks xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 12:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! :) Im really looking forward to this!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 12:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info! Sorry if my post is one of those that gets posted millions of times, I'll make sure to read the top! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apprentice Exchange in Cork. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 10:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,

Im from Norway and from 1. September to 1. December im going to Cork to work as an IT-apprentice.

I'll be with a host family and the program here in Norway pays all the travel expenses, etc.

Im just wondering, as a 19 year old Norwegian dude, how is it to live in Cork or in Ireland?
I have no idea how stuff works over there or knowledge of any norms, etc.

And ofc, i gotta ask to be sure. Is the drinking age 18? ;)

Any tips on cool stuff to do in Cork? ( I love History WW1-2, and hunting and ofc i like Computers).

Any info and tips is appriciated! Really excited for this trip!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 07:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah!

Thanks for the info! :)
I'l make sure to use the spreadsheet! 

Thank you for your help, I'll do my best! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 07:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the help! I'll try my best! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can I pass the 70-410 Exam? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,

So i've been an IT apprentice for about 8 months now. 
First my company sent me to take the ITIL cerification, wich was hard.

Im getting really worried about this Server exam, it seems to be so freakin hard, and i see people saying they practiced for 11 Weeks, and 5 hours per day. I just can't do that and my exam is not 11 weeks away at all.. :(

Does anyone have any tips on how i can practice? At work i have a Server i can use to for Labs. I took the 5-day course but i didnt really pick up what we went through since its so much to go through in just 5 days :( 

I still have the 13 Module doc from the Course. Wich contains insane amounts of info and Labs.

Can anyone help me? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didnt like season 2 at all, the 2nd arc was the worst </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks i'll still use that site all the time tho  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well.... it's Naruto </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahha yeah i agree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SAO Season 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always use Kissanime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, The anime does not HAVE to have insane animation, as long as its got a cool storyline thats not retarded and is unique. Im not a fan of the "Cute school girl eccchi anime", i Like the animes with awsome badass characters, fighting, crime, mysteries, epic shit thats exciting to watch.

I've tried watching a couple "Standard Anime school girls" series, and i Just could not enjoy it. I forced myself to finish them, they even make me cringe. Some of it is just plain stupid to me.

But thats just me, i know alot of people enjoy these, but i cant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
