<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's see what they've got! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the one thing you've done that has made you realize "Wow, I'm poor." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NUMBER OF PEOPLE WHO UPVOTED THIS ON MOBILE ----------------------------- </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is very high quality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> very relevant username  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: This dog that is way cooler than you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spirit Airlines. Upvote this so that whenever anyone searches Spirit Airlines, this comes up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spirit Airlines. Upvote this so that whenever anyone searches Spirit Airlines, this comes up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens if I pour spot remover on a Dalmatian? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL rolling joints and wrapping joints are two very different things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "TWO CHRISTMASES BITCHES" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about you study that photo for the next hour or so and give us a report on it when you finish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I test to see that I'm not immortal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I'm traveling 6.7 million miles an hour in my car, what happens if I turn my headlights on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I legitimately had to zoom in to figure out if you were a guy or girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite part about the entire history was that it included that he graduated high school in 1870, *five years* after the Civil War had ended </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a similar note, playing video games. As uncoordinated as I might be in real life, multiply that by 100 and that's how uncoordinated my guys are in the video game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A membership to Augusta. Take that you rich elitist golf fucks, I'm a member at the best golf course in the world now too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew wedding vows are sometimes cheesy and make you want to vomit, but this is some next level shit right here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was your goal here OP? Get your gf to have an emotional breakdown so you can be supportive and then have sad sex? We all know it's the only way you'll ever get pussy you sad excuse for a man(or woman, who knows, this gf looks like she might be into girls) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't either, the last thing I remember is fleeting memories of October 2015 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy pointing at the camera is also having a great moment, his expression is as if he's telling his ex-gf "HA ERICA, I TOLD YOU HE WOULD COME!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just made Karl Marx roll over in his grave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why OP asked for this fuck's consent because obviously he has never let consent stop him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have uncovered the love triangle: girl is into guy on left, guy on left is into guy on right, guy on right is into girl. If there's a market for ugly bisexual porn, you three have it nailed down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oklahoma: there's a reason Andrew Jackson used it as reservation land: it's complete shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My paternal grandfather was a radiator-repair man, and he was one of the top notch ones. Good enough to he point that he was the only certified Rolls Royce radiator repair man in a 12-state region, and whenever he got them in, they made him be super secretive about the repairs in order to protect the brand name and the idea that Rolls Royce's will run forever. He also custom made a radiator for a Bugatti Royale, of which there are currently 6 in existence.

My maternal grandfather was raised on a farm and had to drop out of high school to keep up the farm when his Dad died when my grandfather was 16. With that being said, he was very good at baseball, and played for his local independent league team, where he was the star pitcher and hit over .300 on days he didn't pitch. He once struck out 23 in a game. After that, he became an iron worker, where he got knocked off a 3-story building by a crane, and survived, and in his time off, he learned to play golf one-handed because his other hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When killing your victim, ask yourself "How would a Canadian do this?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grammar books. Gives me a rush every time I read about the difference between commonly misused words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sarcasm. I am a fairly sarcastic person, and when a sarcastic comment is treated at face value, the conversation tends to descend into a hopeless pit of awkwardness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girls of Reddit, what is one thing a guy could do to melt your heart? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I am serious. And don't call me Shirley."

-Leslie Nielsen as Dr. Rumack in Airplane!

Total power move. No coming back from that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily a joke, but a pickup line

"Hey girl, are you a 90 degree angle? Because you looking right."

*silence*

"I'm sorry, was that not acute pickup line?"

*silence*

"Ok, I'm really sorry, I'm just being obtuse."

*silence*

"But honestly, I think we'd be complementary together."

*silence*

"Okay, I get it, you don't want a long term relationship, just let me supplement that ass." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Professional Golfer. I would never be good enough to make any money, so if I'm guaranteed a healthy salary, I would totally hit the links every day for the rest of my active life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/kindofwholesomememes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Charm. You better believe I'll be with some fine ladies by the end of the week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm all dried up, but I still blow" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet the Padres wish they could just cancel the next few seasons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best part of this is that the press release makes it look like a jeopardy tile.

"Yes Alex, is it 'Who are the infallible buffoons known as the Mets?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Ron Howard's daughter Rebel Alley could work on that one in her next PSA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "On the next Arrested Development: 'Genius' director with bloated confidence destroyed by accidentally sarcastic comment." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here in Kansas City, we do things right. Fuck adults! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a bully you have four options:

1. Military 
2. Reliving high school
3. Unemployment. 
4. Drugs

Convenient that OP got one of each  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She might be 8 years old, and I know a lot of 8 year old cats don't get too much attention, but dang it she's a good cat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could have sex with anyone, but they had to be a historical figure, who would you choose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why one invention would revolutionize middle-age society the most if they had it 1000 years ago? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put all of your money in the stock market for the next ten years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Go on a parade in Dallas in a convertible to show people your face!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tuberculosis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *guitar shreds in background * 

F*** YEAH, MURICA

EDIT: FUCK, THERE, I SAID IT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will my download times be better if I add on 1759 more consoles to my PS4? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trigeorgemichaelatops. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't believe everything you see on the internet! I once tried to poop on Ben Bernanke's car because the Internet told me he was behind the OKC bombings! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot to mention that you live with your parents, because there's no way you make enough money for that apartment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Pi badge? Are you trying to ward off the evil spirits known as females? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I don't know what Missouri is like to you, but here's some meth and some Dutch baked goods." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't let the media tell you otherwise! Now is the time to buy taxidermied kitten! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 06:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You won't believe what this guy did when he found out she was transgender! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "He had the doggonators" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jayson Stark on the baseball side was great too. I don't know what ESPN's long-term plan is here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who put pineapple on their pizzas. Get out of here you savage, we don't want your kind here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related: the pubes the somehow start creeping into the crease in your thighs and are impossible to trim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eat Arby's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look like the kind of girls that try to be sluts at gaming conventions, but somehow you still can't get laid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, we know you're absolutely fucking braindead when you talk about how much sex you have to distract people from the test that you're totally about to fail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because you fucked a sheep doesn't mean you're not a virgin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the IRA: Irish Repugnant Arsehole </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Why, did you want me to?](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [FTFY](https://imgur.com/gallery/EqFJF)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @Estan247. Why else would he have put it in the bottom corner of his text? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well we all know what kind of plug is on the end of those things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was about 8 and my brother was 4 and I had so much progress on backyard baseball. He said he accidentally deleted my progress, but I, to this day, know that little shit knew what delete meant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wipe that laughing emoji off my screen you hopeless fuckface </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because you created an AI, gave it a female name, and strapped a fleshlight on it does not mean you have a girlfriend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell, even go join AC/DC. I bet you'd fit right in and be a total rock star. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A purpose to life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad always told me not to be a hooker. So I became a stripper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe you should ask your piece of shit ouija board how to get a life  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any girl you're with could be in the fucking ocean and you still wouldn't get her wet

EDIT: Forgot he was in the navy, so he's never been with girls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is it a Mexican or a Cuban Armadillo? I MUST KNOW I AM NOW EMOTIONALLY INVOLVED </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *thicc*adillos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, you have subscribed to Armadillo facts! Every time  time an Armadillo gives birth, they give birth to quadruplets. Reply UNSUBSCRIBE if you no longer want to receive these messages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, I never thought an armadillo should end up r/aww, but here I am linking the sub  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The former U.S. Secretary of Defense, Robert S. McNamara, was aware that there might be objections raised by the international scientific community but said in a memo to the president that such objections had not in the past been a basis for prevention of military activities considered to be in the interests of U.S. national security.

yep sounds about right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's the little things in life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A boy's mother once told him that if he saw a naked woman he would turn to stone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One day, the boy and his friend accidentally came upon a nude beach, but the boy immediately ran away.

"Why did you run away?" asked his friend, who wanted to stay to enjoy the view.

The boy responded "My mother always told me that if I saw a woman naked, I would turn to stone. I felt something get hard in my pants, so I ran." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/circlejerk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but still, it's not like a robbery or something where your professional life is essentially over </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> safe sex and paychecks kiddos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ironically, you've probably been the biggest break from his YouTube channel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I could probably break up with the love of my life for a full ride to Yale. I'll just go meet some smart fuck there and make smart babies and help the gene pool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still, one DUI is recoverable from and will largely go down as a bad mistake, but people are generally willing to forgive to a certain point. It's when you get your 2nd or 3rd DUI is when you're getting in some deep deep trouble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the US postal service </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lightbulb that is turned off above you is symbolic: this roastme was not a good idea, you've never had a good idea, and you will never have a good idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aaron Hernandez has figured out a way to save the US prison system millions in incarceration costs! We need more heroes like him! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you love dogs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jet fuel can't melt steel beams </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FIFA. If I lose a game because fucking Sokratis let a ball go between his legs in the 89th minute and my brother makes a snide little comment, I am prepared to rip his head off and face the consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to real life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> found the midwesterner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/shittyaskscience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, here in America we just look for any extramarital affairs or any history with the KKK. If neither exist, then *we make them exist* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best part about this entire bit is that our Slovenian First Lady had to remind THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA to put his hand over his heart for the national anthem.

EDIT: words and such </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> does this mean I can contact the DoD whenever PS servers are down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait you people exist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if you ever need help, go to r/relationships, they have so much advice that absolutely never backfires and totally always helps so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [MOM, WHY WONT THE TV TURN ON](https://imgur.com/a/1reM5)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not looking at explosions. Cmon man, explosions are awesome, everyone looks at them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marshall Tucker Band - Can't You See [Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why is this happening in American minor league soccer smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a good one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way I remember it is that the light comes on top of the PS4, so the top button must be the one to turn it on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did people in the Industrial Revolution use to wipe their butts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, this may seem like a rather immature question, but I was thinking, what did people used to wipe their butts with? I understand that there is almost certainly going to be a difference between social classes, but I'm just curious as to how different people did their business in the years immediately preceding the rise of toilet paper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is this actually bacon or the Canadian kind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Checks out, OP is Canadian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We get it, you shot heroin into your dick and had to replace your old weiner with one on your shirt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not too expensive, but tortillas, pizza sauce, cheese, and toppings makes a dank-ass pizzadilla. Costs like $10 and it makes you 5 meals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You too? I thought I was the only one in here who did shit like that! High five!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2ND MISTAKE: NEVER TALK ABOUT FIGHT CLUB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just don't get married. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must say, it's a hell of a lot easier to try those kinds of pitches when you've only recorded 4 outs but you're still up 12 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making out with a girl a couple times in the bar, her telling me she has a boyfriend, having morals kick in, and go back to my room by myself. *Turns me on so hard* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I was so confused, I thought these kids were working on a subterranean rail system, not at a sandwich shop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dire Straits - Money For Nothing [Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
