<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1565</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did any of the German machine gunners who shot Allied forces during the beach landings on D Day ever get interviewed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it was war, but one would have to think the human element is still there in some form. To carry the burden of knowing that you were responsible for so many deaths that day cannot have been an easy thing. We hear so many stories from the Allied perspective, but I would be very interested to hear from the Germans too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 14:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can i upvote this more than once? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 14:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know where you live, but in Ontario our teachers are overpaid (in some cases grossly) and the quality of education is less than stellar. I think the problem with paying teachers so much is you can end up with an education system full of people who just want the money, as opposed to a system full of teachers who are genuinely interested in the success of our future generations and who love to teach.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After this long, Fowler had better arrange a goddamn ticker tape parade down Yonge Street for the announcement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 12:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Um we object to the term urine-soaked hellhole, when you could have said pee-pee soaked heckhole." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 12:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, thanks. What's a cross-buy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 12:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently purchased a PS4 and loved BF4 so much that I bought it again, however, none of the DLC that I bought for the PS3 version was there. Am I just SOL? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect! More Speights and sausage sizzles for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 23:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last part of your reply to me really isn't necessary at all, and completely ruins your credibility. Citing news from 3 years ago is also really stupid. Have a lovely weekend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 23:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prove that it isn't HC. You made the comment that Fowler et al are terrible, so the burden of proof is on you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 23:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't disagree at all because he is. Technique-wise KWS is a very good guitarist, I think, but some of his solos rip off SRV almost note for note at times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 23:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His fingers were like sausages as well. Most people just don't have the finger strength that he had, which is also why his strings were so heavy and added to his unique sound. You have guitarists like Kenny Wayne Shepperd who do a good job of keeping his style alive, but his true sound is all his. RIP Stevie. 

By the way, for those SRV fans  who have not seen his El Mocambo show, it's a must watch. Yes, he was drugged off his head, but it's one of his best shows in my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
