<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2240</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 23:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "There was just another piata inside it?!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 04:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I've always dreamed of abolishing the Make-A-Wish Foundation..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Picks For The 2017 Stanley Cup Playoffs: Third Round By Abraham Lincoln </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WASHINGTON, D.C.  We meet again, earnest reader! After yet another round of unsuccessful predictions, and Im not sure why, I am here to give you my predictions for the third round of these hockey postseason games. Apparently the winner of these games gets to vie for the whole thing! What an exciting time. Lets take a look:

Ottawa Senators vs. Pittsburgh Penguins: Well, I predicted both of these teams to lose. Twice! That is, frankly, impressively bad. Well one must win, so lets see if I get it right this time. I choose the Penguins of Pittsburgh. They defeated the good Union boys and the representatives of this nations capital, so these flightless birds are clearly vicious and unstoppable. Im afraid these Canadian boys dont stand a chance in this round.

Anaheim Ducks vs. Nashville Predators: No questions here! The Ducks will be victorious! Yet again Gordon Bombay will lead them to the championship! Stellar play by Ryan Getzlaf, Fulton Reed, Charlie Conway, Corey Perry, Dave Karp, and Ryan Kesler will surely lead this team to victory! Go Flying V and go Anaheim!

God bless,
President Abraham Lincoln </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hi, I'm Sean Spicer-"
"God, this is already a travesty!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jobs that definitely shouldn't make house calls. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Picks For The 2017 Stanley Cup Playoffs: Second Round By Abraham Lincoln </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WASHINGTON, D.C.  Hello again, kind reader! After my first round predictions were met with mediocrity, I was asked to give my predictions for the second round as well! Again, I have a very limited knowledge of hockey, but Ill do my best. Here goes nothing:

New York Rangers vs. Ottawa Senators: One of my few correct first round picks, I think Texs Rangers will do it again! These Union-allied boys will certainly clean the rink with those northern Canucks! Theyve shown what it takes to win on the battlefield: strength, determination, good leadership, and a lack of dysentery. The Rangers will win!

Washington Capitals vs. Pittsburgh Penguins: Washington must win! They represent our nations capital, and we need to show the countrys strength! Also, those Penguins defeated the Blue Jackets, so I have reason to believe theyre aligned with the Confederates. Its precisely for reasons like this that I suspended habeas corpus! The Union must be preserved, so I call this series for the Capitals!

St. Louis Blues vs. Nashville Predators: Well, I predicted that St. Louis would come out victorious, but I did not predict victory for Nashville. They defeated my boys from the land ofwell, me, Lincoln! Maybe theres more grit there than I expected. A young, feisty bunch of rebellious boysI dont normally support the rebels, or rebs, but I am going to choose them this time. You cant fool me twice, so Nashville will win this series!

Anaheim Ducks vs. Edmonton Oilers: Ducks again! Ducks again! I told you Gordon Bombay would win them the first round, and hell do it again. Break out the Flying V, boys! Ducks will win!

God bless,
President Abraham Lincoln </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions that will always be answered with a 'No.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd watch this for hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I planned the whole thing!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Picks For The 2017 Stanley Cup Playoffs: First Round By Abraham Lincoln </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WASHINGTON, D.C.  Hello, America and beyond! It is I, the 16th President of the United States of America, Abraham Lincoln. Today, I am here to give you my break down for the first round of this years Stanley Cup playoffs, whatever that means.

When I was asked to do this, I was quite confused. I was never much of a hockey person, and I know so very little of it in todays times. Regardless, Im not one to disappoint, so heres my breakdown for this years first round matchups:

Montreal Canadiens vs. New York Rangers: Now, I have to choose Texs Rangers! Im so confident that our American boys can beat this team to our north that I dont even care their star player is from Sweden! Habitants or not, Im calling this one in favor of the Rangers.

Ottawa Senators vs. Boston Bruins: An American team named for a bear? Why, Ill definitely have to choose the Bruins! Besides, when was the last time anyone saw a senator get work done? In my days, that was known as a political zinger! I call this series for the Bruins.

Washington Capitals vs. Toronto Maple Leafs: A third go-around for an American team taking on a Canadian team? What a world we live in! And this American team plays in and represents our capital? These boys really seem represent our Union and what it means to be American! What? Their star player is Russian? Ah, well, Ill still call this one for the Capitals.

Pittsburgh Penguins vs. Columbus Blue Jackets: Blue Jackets?! Blue Jackets?! Why even bother holding other contests? These Union boys will go all the way! No Penguins or Confederates can keep these men down! I call on them to win the whole shebang!

Chicago Blackhawks vs. Nashville Predators: Blackhawks and Predators. Both are fierce warriors! A fine, tough people versus a very general representation of beings that hunt and feast on other beings. This will be a tough series, but Im going to have to pick the team that comes straight from the Land of me, Lincoln: the Blackhawks!

Minnesota Wild vs. St. Louis Blues: Two American-bred teams in one series makes it difficult to predict. Sure, Minnesota is the State of Hockey, with passionate fans, a hard wilderness, and strong players like Zach Parise and Devan Dubnyk. But St. Louis represents exploration and creativity. With strong goaltending from Jake Allen and equally strong players in front of him, such as Vladimir Tarasenko and Alex Pietrangelo, I think St. Louis is going to best Minnesota in this series.

Anaheim Ducks vs. Calgary Flames: You wont find a bigger fan of the 1996 movie The Mighty Ducks than yours truly, which is why there is no doubt this series will end with an Anaheim victory! I mean, with powerhouses like Ryan Getzlaf and Corey Perry, not to mention the brilliant coaching of Gordon Bombay, I dont see how they could lose! Go Flying V! Go Ducks!

Edmonton Oilers vs. San Jose Sharks: Well, truthfully, I dont even know what an oiler is! Steam is the way for me, so I cant imagine theres a team named for a person who is involved with oil? Sharks are intimidating enough, so Ill choose them. Frankly, neither team sounds like winners. Can they both lose? No? Okay, San Jose then!

God bless,
President Abraham Lincoln </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Little Miss Muffet...I grabbed her by the tuffet." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm going to ride this thing straight to Uranus!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unlikely side jobs for Darth Vader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "...so I don't have to tell you."
*walks away* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islanders Ho-Sang Enjoys Hockey Better Awake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BROOKLYN, NY  Joshua Ho-Sang, the rising young prospect for the New York Islanders, recently discovered that NHL hockey is an even better, more fast-paced experience while awake than it is asleep. Sleeping through that first practiceit was kind of nice to catch up on sleep. But having that great game against Carolina? Boy! Way better!

Even Ho-Sangs teammates are commenting on the youngsters skill. He was a phenomenal sleeper. It took three guys to get him up! But having him set me up for that goalI think thats where the kids real talent lies, said Islanders captain John Tavares. With a hefty schedule still ahead, Islanders coach Doug Weight knows the stakes for Ho-Sang. Wait, for real? asked coach Weight. Hes a professional hockey player: of course he needs to be awake! If he pulls this (expletive) again, I promise you hes gone, finished the optimistic coach.

So what lies ahead for the newbie? Im contemplating not sleeping again! said an excited Ho-Sang. Ive been awake for everything: games, practices, meals, parties. Its changed my life! The future looks bright for this young talent.

At press time, Ho-Sang was seen guzzling cups of extra-caffeinated coffee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 04:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 04:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
