<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1397</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How effective, or what were the major accomplishments of Nixon's 17 month second term? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering how much, and how quickly did Watergate paralyze the government from governing. (also Agnew).

In my research, it looks like the things he was most remembered for, policy wise all happened in his first term. China, gold standard, epa, Paris accords etc. 

Was he able to do anything in his second term? Did events unfold slowly enough for him to do anything initially. If he was able to govern, when did that stop?

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similar topic, but not quite.  My brother is autistic, developmentally delayed (mental capacity 2-3 yrs old)  etc. 

He is super flamboyantly gay and a cross dresser. 

Thing is he can't talk all that much, and doesn't know really know what relationships are. 

It's just that he's sometimes found naked in bed with torn out magazines with male underwear models. And loves his male staff and not his female. 

And sometimes he's dressed in my sister's clothes. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pay Ryan needs to play it safe without seeming to excited about it. 

Because when Trump and pence go down, he will be president. Which was always his ambition. 

No way he gonna screw up his own best chance at that office </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If trump and pence go down, Ryan becomes president. No way he wants pass up that chance. He always wanted to be, and this is likely his only way in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 15:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread is going to get pulled so fast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 05:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also a constellation and/or zodiac </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 05:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd think that since stunts are often during the midst intense or climactic or perhaps hectic parts of movies, and you want to show them off well that you'd have first unit oversee that? 

Unless most of the with you're referring to after the simple stuff, like falling off a chair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 04:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Melania will get deported </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 04:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watergate caused 40 indictments or jail sentences. 

Trump will be at least that, as well.

 Including manafort, Flynn, page, maybe sessions and  Could expand to pence, preibus, maybe even nunes, and chaffetz etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 04:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Mueller, and everyone else, knows coming in to the job is that the only thing that matters is whether or not trump goes down. I think he is ready for that responsibility and to make that happen. 

When you come for the kind you Best not miss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 04:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbf Most episodes that ate mentioned in any grade level history book will have multiple college level courses on that specific subject </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A conspiratorial tale of murder, with Fox News at the center </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it supposed to be blindsided? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wapo is the only media company with experience bringing down a president. They'll trying for 2-0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 14:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tigerpig? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 14:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While we haven't yet gotten to it, I wouldnt be surprised if a former president who gets improsened would be held in a military one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leakeymaster mcmasterface </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the other hand, coupled with an ignorant electorate, no one has shown that this situation has any consequences. So why shouldn't he be confident? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 16:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There also was an article that oreilly was in negotiations with Sinclair media </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 19:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The show should have centered on Colleen wing. Better back story, better motivation, better fighter and most of all a better actor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 19:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fine if you skip a lot of the dialogue. It's not even exposition, just a lot of filler. 

Also just gloss over Danny's super cringey Buddhist ramblings and tai chi. Very bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 19:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that was iron fists. Danny is only iron fist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 19:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BUT HE HAD TO CENTER HIS CHI, GIVE HIM A GODDAMN BREAK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 18:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not letting dissenters against sitting senators. So, no blocking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 17:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A casually dropped sentence in there is a bot worrying. About Sinclair developing a rival conservative network. 

Sinclair is trying to be worse than fox. They hired Boris epshteyn as chief political analyst. Rumors ate they're hiring bill oreilly. 

And they're in middle of acquiring Tribune media which gives them some of the largest media outlets in the country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 17:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. That is for retirees with nothing better to do than watch TV to see how they're retirement is doing. 

1% use their Bloomberg terminals. Ain't nobody got time for stock prices if they're the ones that set them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 02:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While true, they will simply be pulled together, not held individually responsible. 

Can you name any congressman/senator from the seceded states? Can you name any anti-civil rights leader outside Wallace and Thurmond? Can you name any of the huac members?

The GOP know exactly what they're doing. 

It's a disgrace. But will never be held accountable. Thurmond was a senator through the end of the millennium  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 07:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using your logic to answer the question "when does the past become history?" Ie are newspapers history books because they talk about yesterday's events?

You answer, technically any moment in the past, no matter how recent, is technically history, then by using the same definition, then archeology would be studying your scissors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Knives Are Out for Lt. Gen. H.R. McMaster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The issue at that point isn't the car or motor, is the tire and road surface. Current theoretical maximum is 1.9 seconds 0-60, based on friction and tread deformation etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By law, it's not part of the budget. I can only find a liberal source, but it's true. 

http://m.huffpost.com/us/entry/2286462
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a big way, especially also it would jeapordize it's place as first in primary, because the whole election dynamic would change </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Social security is not usually part of the budget. It's a self funding program. It's part of federal spending, but not budget.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like what penis pump might do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly his baby want livinga good life and therefore deserving of healthcare </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a bit shaky reporting. 

Check my comment history, I'm no supporter of the orangutan president or any of his allies. 

That said, rennaisance technologies main CEO and founder, Simons is a major donor to progressive causes. I don't think this is about the company, Mercer simply believes in it or whatever. It's not about the 6 billion that the hedge fund owes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is hard and unpopular doing the right thing and making difficult decisions in the face of overwhelming adversity and evil people to accomplish them. Then there is disastrous 100 days because you're a deranged oompah-loofah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why Lindbergh is famous. 

He wasn't the first pilot, the first solo pilot,or the first transatlantic pilot. Or anything. He was the first transatlantic solo pilot. It's a niche accomplishment if there was any. 

Plus he was a Nazi. 

So he confuses me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting you mention Jew as a term. It is etymologically from the tribe of Judah. Which David was part of, and likely identified himself as. However, traditionally, when referencing Jews of that time, Israelites and Hebrews are more common. Israelites being descendents of Israel(Jacob), the last forefather that bound the 12/13 tribes. Hebrew, meaning from the other side (of the Jordan River) refers to their ethnic origin and language, but also includes ishamelites, moabites and ammonites, and a couple of other tribes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you say that your emphasis on libertarian economics (chicago, Austrian etc) and other ideas primarily stem from a practical or moral concern?

Ie, if you were somehow convinced that the keynsian model worked better, would you say that it's ok, or still be against for moral principles that the government has no right to interfere?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of the software engineering do have engineering implications (as you mentioned, not all). 

A lot of life safety these days rely on network and security engineering, or even as basic as signal processing from things like self driving to cell phones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And a Edmund Burke said, Evil happens when good people allow it to happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's funny, cause now I see them as an enemy, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> with no foreskin comes great foresight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we over-value the intelligence of previous dictators.

Kim-song-il was just as batty as today's, mao was not super-bright, and neither was hitler or saddaam.

smart dictators would have a close circle of advisors that tell the truth and are un-afraid of the leader. but thats not how its been. general's too scared to wake hitler, i.e. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loeb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't mention sub-subsidiaries. 

For example, Mariano's in Chicago is owned by Roundy's, which is apparently owned by Kroger's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't clear, but the article suggests that the people fighting the cameras here are not against cameras, but in fact the opposite, that the feel the cameras aren't enough, and that the policy over review and release of footage is tipped in favor of police instead of the people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are traditionally 5 reasons for "punishment":

Revenge (punitive)

Repay debt to society

Remove danger from society

Penitentiary

And rehabilitation

Death penalty fulfills a couple of those </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish the military would get on board as well. 

Don't need a fort Hood or the like. Why not just name it for actual heros </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Architecture by Jeanne Gang (Studio Gang).

Watch her. She will probably be getting a pritzker in the next 10 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your rhetoric is a little harsh. Many real Americans avoided the draft. Whether for being against a stupid pointless war, or because they were against war. 

Or they just didn't want to die. 


What makes trump (and other neocons like George w) spectacularly and uniquely hypocritical is that they were too good for war for themselves, but actively promote war and violence and sending other people's kids to war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't read the article, did you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably flying from mdw to mke or some shit. No need </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Private people don't have the moral right to defend themselves in any circumstance where the only possibility is to kill the attacker? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Papa no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And buttery males </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fu10ck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Grassley: A SCOTUS justice could resign this summer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Appointed to the administration </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not because he grew a conscience. More likely he will be appointed to the administration in thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They wanted to change from helping poor people of color and some covert racism to helping white people, getting rid of poc and explicit racism. 

That's what is meant by change. Change from Obama to Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. It didn't in 2016, and won't in 2018. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The flight was actually a republic airlines flight, which also happens to operate uniteds shuttle service. So it was their own employee, but not united </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News Poised to Drop Bill OReilly Amid Sexual Harassment Scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember when a bunch of armed white supremacist terrorists occupied a federal building in Oregon for like a month?

They were then sentenced to real serious time. Real time. 

I remember. Good times, good times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He does realize, but he also realized that no one is *really* going to hold him accountable, so why would he care? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He fits in on Reddit, not in public policy and governance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not unfortunate *she* abandoned it. She tried in the 90s, it lost, so she pushed for a workable alternative in 08 and 16. 

Just a history lesson, in 2008 election, Obama said that Hillary's then plan was too timid. Do you know which plan became Obamacare? Hillary's. Do you know where the individual mandate came from? GOP alternative plan in response to hillarycare (90s). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No time, just stay here and hope for ubereats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it does even out representation. Because you would be roughly equal to a Wyoming citizen, even in California </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deli meat+penis reminds me of a certain odd FRIENDS storyline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what the Republicans did when they finally got the office back after FDR. Until then it was only tradition that limited presidents to two terms (because Washington did it), then they codified it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said this yesterday. 

Seeing the quick development and prioritization of the semi, it almost certainly going to be a class 6 or 7 local hauler that will share much of the technology with the X. 

Given a gvw of a model X 100d pulling it's max (hitch), of 11,000#, and running at 168 Miles (per range factoring), I'd say we are looking at no more than 200kw battery pack. 

That could be a haul of 11,000# (gvw 16-17k#) for 150 Miles. 

This short haul could serve most deliveries, have more downtime to allow for standard charging. Also, by keeping the vehicle in the same weight range as the x, you can share a lot of the mechanical parts. 

Remember, every 400# or so of curb weight needs a redesign of the suspension, ball bearings, brakes, axles and drive trains, etc etc etc. 

It wouldn't make sense for Tesla to prioritize a completely new vehicle with new technologies (ie fast charging) before doing things that do share, like model Y.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people here are looking at long haul semis. While those are some of the biggest fuel hogs, and most benefit from self driving, I think the current logistics and policies are too large a hurdle in the near term for Tesla to have prioritized that. 

I think they're aiming at local deliveries and short haul semis (think distribution center to retailer). 

These require much less range, and more downtime to charge (ie while loading/unloading), and see most of the operating expense savings in the idling costs. 

Therefore, I'd say that we are looking at class 6/7 trucks, at most, not class 8 tractor trailers. These take into account load of the vehicle+payload. The class 7 being a gross weight of 11-15 or so tons.

A class 7 Mack can carry 8-11,000 pounds. 

Assuming a range of 150 miles (Greenfield distribution centers to City center retailer), And 30mph average (in City), I think there are more that electric could offer here with current technology and industry and regulations. 

The model X curb weight is 5,300lbs. And can tow 5,000lbs. The model X range while towing is 60% of its maximum of 280 (at 50mph avg) source: https://www.teslarati.com/tesla-model-x-range-impact-towing/amp ), which gives it a total 168mile range. 

This means, that with a 100kw motor, and a curb weight similar to X (all that suv weight converted into trailer weight), means that it could be a a class 3 without much Change in technology, or even production line tweaks. (bigger cars mean bigger everything, from axles and suspension to ball bearings and headlights), and keeping it in line with current makes it cheaper and faster to design and build. 

Therefore, I don't see larger than 200kw (to get a class 7 to 150 miles) battery in the immediate offering, perhaps later, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, you mean like the founding fathers didn't intend separation of church and state? We need to incorporate religion in our government?

Absolutely! Free healthcare and basic income for everyone, just like Jesus! Some wine, too! Oprah.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you want?

Guamer? Guamite? Guamish? Guamen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I needed 12.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10pm on a Saturday night? Great customer service, your urgent Care has.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10pm on a Saturday night? Great customer service, your doctor has.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He just got rid of regulations that prevent mentally ill people from buying guns; prevent isps from selling your info; requires oil companies from disclosing payments to foreign governments; companies from keeping better records of on job injuries; prevent companies with extensive billionaires violation history from getting federal contacts among others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just last month I was in er for 14 hours to stitch up my thumb. That's suburban Chicago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And a massive crumple zone like that could probably make it the safest supercar in front collisions, even small overlaps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That or the selteab deal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 06:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gomez? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 06:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Al Capone. 

And also corrupt politicians </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 06:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's a movie about a movie about a guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. Til </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that he did that film because he was in position to do what he wanted, and he wanted to act in movies his daughter wanted to watch- and she was like six at the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep watching </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're fun at parties, I bet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are multiple methods of gerrymandering. Only one of them produces this result.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 more and you've got 7 sins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red solos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a pyramid scheme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Nunes and Issa  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The GOP have a nearly 60 seat majority. Even if all 23 go Dem, and double that and another 23 flip, the GOP would still have a significant majority - and that's on top of the current incumbency when rate. 

In 2016,97% of incumbents won, with and average 35% margin. Previous elections have 85-90% incumbency won rates. 

Even if you double the average flip rate, and win 70% of open races (usually 40 seats),  it's still cutting it by close. 

It's a serious uphill battle that requires fundamental shifts in voting behavior.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 06:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You weighed less.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 06:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America has borderless entry and free movement from Alabama through to Vermont, and West Virginia to New Mexico.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mummy marketing team knows their audience.


Who cares about plot? Tom Cruise is zero g own stunt!!!

Of course we'll see it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worse than Doocy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Latimes and Chicago Tribune both. 

It isn't coincidental that the change happened when they got sold to Sam Zell. You should see he his speeches to reporters. Crazy MF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 05:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun Fact, one of those impeached, is currently a sitting Congressman. Alcee Hastings (D). 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Speaker Ryan Should Quit Congress Before He Gets Rumbled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 15:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a banned PED.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My then 4 year old daughter out of the blue gave my wife some advice, "mommy, when you die, try to stay asleep, it's easier that way"

:/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm jewish, so, rabbi, merchant or money lender. Sounds about right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 14:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her father is Lebanese </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 14:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How old were you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 14:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is, but they know you can ship a pebble, and then claim it was $1,000,000. Being that they would have no way of verifying this after the fact, they insure your stuff, up to a maximum of like 3.50. (above delivery charges, that they refund).

Any more money, you must declare in advance, and to prevent everyone from declaring everything at 1,000,000, they charge you for more. 

It makes sense to most people, if you're shipping cheap stuff, you don't have to buy insurance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 14:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My city, too. Though it's a volunteer ambulance company (chicago), so it's like free advertising or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, there is no way scotus won't wait until Gorsuch is confirmed. 

And based on Gorsuch's originalism and precedent worship, he will vote against judicial overview </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that's heavy bubbles. Common misconception </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just noticed now that artesian water is not artisan water, Witch sounds more pretentious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is their internal geometry that creates the cubic shape? Or by what mechanism is this accomplished? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And fire trucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like this? https://youtu.be/UngE0qn3VRY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a sea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's where the airbag goes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is Devin Nunes not on the bracket?

Or Jared Kushners, Chris Christie, Carl Icahn or Kelly Anne Conway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you me? Though I guess it's the industry. I do food production inspections. Most on a monthly basis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buttery males </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's ignorance like the comment above you that really irks me. 

Citizens United was literally (in the literal sense) about her. 

Citizens United was an anti-Hillary group. 


Of course she isn't pro citizens United.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this in a year crazy for sports. From GSW vs Cav, the no-name win in the premiership, pats SB, and real vs San germain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calling a bluff is standard negotiation tactics. 

No way a republican will vote against a bill touted as repealing Obamacare, even if it isn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From a negotiation standpoint, it's calling a bluff. 

He's gambling that the freedom caucus (primary holdouts) are just bluffing on the no, and that they would be vote for their anyways. 

Additionally, he's gambling that the freedom caucus would rather vote for a bill they don't agree with than vote against Obamacare repeal. A) they've promised repeal for so long, it's hard for them to imagine that they would vote no on the one Chance they got, and B) the freedom caucus is no longer the popular wing of the party - trumpism is. Trumpism is a cult of personality, not ideology, so he's gambling that he is more popular than the representatives in their districts, and they wouldn't be able to stave off primary if they vote no. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House, in gamble, demands make-or-break health vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lincoln was a Republican, slavery is bad  and more discoveries by President Obvious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then why would the article fucking link to the list?

This is exactly the media bring complicit and in collaboration with this fascist government.

If the list is a nazi tactic, then dissemination of the list is collaboration. Without the press showing you the list, then the list of meaningless. 

This is why the press is losing credibility.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a local business, large, but not nearly large enough to think that that would pass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brother spent 100K building an alcohol collection over six months, along with 300k in other spending.  


While spectacularly stupid, not to mention criminal, I wonder why it took the company so long to find out. Don't they pay it each month? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This would be a good time to do something about the red menace of Vladimir Putins Russia. Instead, were talking about the Red Raiders of Texas Tech.

FBI Director James B. Comey, testifying Monday about his agencys investigation into Russias attempt to tilt the 2016 election to Donald Trump, explained why it was a fairly easy judgment that Trump was Putins favored candidate: Putin hated Secretary Clinton so much that the flip side of that coin was he had a clear preference for the person running against the person he hated so much.

But Rep. K. Michael Conaway (R-Tex.), a senior member of the House Intelligence Committee, was having none of it. Yeah, that logic might work on Saturday afternoon when my wifes Red Raiders are playing the Texas Longhorns. Conaway doubted such reasoning all the rest of the time.

So, Putin wanted Hillary Clinton to lose but didnt want Trump? Maybe he was for Gary Johnson?

Comey tried to be patient. Whoever the Red Raiders are playing, you want the Red Raiders to win, he explained. By definition, you want their opponent to lose.

Conaway was fourth and long. He scrambled to formulate another question, then punted: Well, let me finish up then.

Comeys testimony confirmed what was widely suspected: The FBI is investigating whether the presidents campaign colluded with a powerful American adversary in an attempt to swing the election. But instead of being shaken from complacency and uniting to make sure this never happens again, the Republican majority on the House Intelligence Committee mounted a reflexive defense of Trump.

The partisan response made it plain that there will be no serious congressional investigation of the Russia election outrage, nor any major repercussions for Russia. We were attacked by Russia  about this there is no doubt  and were too paralyzed by politics to respond.


Trump, whose claim that President Barack Obama wiretapped Trump Tower was dismissed by Comey on Monday, continued to fire his weapons of mass distraction Monday morning, tweeting about ties between Clinton and Russia and claiming the real story is who leaked classified information.

This is to be expected from Trump. The disheartening part was that most Republicans on the panel, which is supposed to investigate Trump, instead slavishly echoed his excuses.

Chairman Devin Nunes (R-Calif.) underscored that there was no evidence that Russia cyber actors changed vote tallies. (There was also no allegation that they had.) He also pronounced himself extremely concerned about the widespread illegal leaks (much more so than the potentially illegal actions that the leaks exposed).

Reading from Trumps cue card, Nunes asked Comey to regard as serious the alleged Clinton campaign ties to Russia. In one exchange that sounded more sandbox than hearing room, Nunes asserted that its ridiculous for anyone to say that the Russians prefer Republicans over Democrats. The chairman urged Comey to tell his investigators not to believe that somehow the Republican Party watered down its platform on Russia.

Rep. Thomas J. Rooney (R-Fla.) pronounced himself concerned about the unmasking of Gen. Flynns identity, which denied him the constitutional protections that we all enjoy. (The unmasking of the former Trump national security adviser was in the service of demonstrating that he spoke falsely about his contacts with Russia.)


Rep. Trey Gowdy (R-S.C.), who led a multiyear Benghazi investigation packed with innuendo and damaging leaks, repeatedly denounced the felonious dissemination of secrets, supposedly by the Obama administration, and the hearsay that is impugning the Trump team.

Comey may have handed Trump the presidency with his announcement just before the election that he was reopening the Clinton email investigation. But he redeemed himself somewhat Monday with a lyrical defense of our wonderful, often messy, but free and fair democratic system. Said Comey: When theres something from a foreign state to disrupt that, its very serious. It threatens what is America.

The Russians, Comey warned, will be back to disrupt future elections. And one of the lessons they may draw from this is that they were successful because they introduced chaos and division and discord and sowed doubt about the nature of this amazing country of ours and our democratic process.

The chairman seemed more concerned about the political threat. Nunes told Comey flatly that we dont have any evidence of wrongdoing by Trump and his associates and asked the FBI director to hurry the investigation. There is a big gray cloud that you have put over people who have very important work to do to lead this country, Nunes said.


But the FBI director didnt put the cloud there. The Russians did. And if Nunes would consider country before party, hed recognize that the cloud isnt over Trumps White House; its over all of us.
 
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehe yeah. I forgot about that. With wapo, just open in incognito, and you're in. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Selektzia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans read Trumps cue cards on Russia and wiretapping </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grassley gets testy during CNN interview: I thought you wanted to talk about Gorsuch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF. This makes no sense!!!

Jews killed Jesus. So they would probably use Jew nails, not Christian ones. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Buttery_Males </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, we already lost respect, because the election had happened. And we also lost respect before that because of how popular trump was, anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if.

the jury is still out on Heidegger. yes I know his gf, arendt, defended him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, its that they know they don't have much of a black vote anyways. 

ie. they don't have the elderly or poor black vote, so they can afford to piss either demo off. however, the white vote is one that they can't piss off - and in particular the elderly white vote who vote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> either way, won't matter until 2020 (senate), or even 2022 (2020 is the redistricting, and if we can ungerrymander stuff, we might see a groundshift in 2022 elections). if trump loses 2020, then it wont matter. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ryan already figured that out. he is updating republicare to include more protections for seniors. 

remember, one of the prime changes republicare will implement over Obamacare is changing the refunds to be determined by age instead of income. which on its face is really stupid, but its smart strategically because now they can adjust refunds according to their preferred demographics (because the poor are both white and black, and poor whites are GOP, so they don't want to piss them off by taking away their healthcare. So by age it allows them to slice it the way they want it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no. they don't care if theyre caught. they already won. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care for impeachment, except in terms of removing him from power. Which is why we also need both houses (not likely until 2020), instead of just the house of rep. (2018) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, the GOP will just point at Bill Clinton. Need more than perjury, or at least win both houses.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> once you're having to explain your naziness, you're already in a bad position </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my experience, it's just an easy out for the supporters to acknowledge that they recognize her is crazy, and that as a supporter it's not for that, but for his ideas. 

Dont kid yourself that the supporters are therefore somehow reasonable. His Twitter is like 1/10 of Trump's total craziness. The craziest things he has said, were during speeches and policies. 

It's like saying I support Jeffrey Dahmer. I just wish he didn't keep the body parts in the freezer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope someone at the hearings will ask what his opinion on the "advice and consent" part of Constitution, and whether or not the Senate had derelicted it's duty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather not rebut by showing this evidence. 

It moves the conversation to their court. 

In no way should we be even entertain these notions. 

We should let them believe that there is no evidence. Fight them there. Say, ok, the is no evidence, but we aren't evil pieces of shit that will cut off these services to poor kids. 


Let them debate that. Don't give in to their wiles, you are going to lose. 

Let them argue that we can't feed starving kids because they don't get good grades.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not gonna happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone who realizes she isn't credible, is effing miserable that she and her band of crazy train are in power. 

So I guess she's right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tracking the special treatment media get when they play nice with the White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Age of the world picture. Meaning coming from narrating into history etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Middle Eastern </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idris Elba as Mufasa. 

Also, there is no way they will have a movie set in Africa without a large African or black presence. And there is no shortage of voice talent there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They took about 100. Also, they treat wounded Syrians who make it in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Edmund Burke said evil happens when good people allow it to happen, it doesn't mean bystanders, standing by while watching someone do bad things does not allow you to retain the title of 'good'. 

What he meant were people who use their moral conscience to make choices that allow evil to happen. Ie,I can't bring myself to vote for Clinton because she might have voted for war once, so, sure trump is Hitler, but I just can't do it. 

It's those people who use their "good" and actively choose to allow evil to happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, Texas, you can't blame everything on Alabama. You plentycrazy on your own </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm ready for them to give it another try </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jello shots don't count </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It happens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it is counterintuitive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In general he talks, behaves and this like he is still in the 80s. He also looks like it, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoosh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom yelled at my wife for not dancing with her before my wife danced with her friends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, a Heideggerarian existentialist. My man. (though I'm no nazi) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Albert hippocamus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *could* care less, but I care so little that I won't expend the effort to care fewer. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Systematic vs systemic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Says the man convicted of drug trafficking and DUIs, party of personal responsibility, worried about being politically correct as equivalent to Nuremberg laws and Holocaust </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Tim Allen, being a non-liberal in Hollywood is like being in 1930s Germany </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a different genre of good movies. And it's good for that. It's not a thriller or a drama. It's a good comedy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many companies have the top of the lower model be more expensive then the base of the step up. 

Loaded corrollas cost more than base Camry. Loaded Camry cost more than base Avalon. Loaded Camry even cost more than entry Lexus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside Trumps White House, New York moderates spark infighting and suspicion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No, Feeding Hungry Kids and Seniors Isn't a Waste of Money </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also was fired for being a bit whacky. Something must have happened a bit before. 

Also his son is full blown kooky, so he might have raised him that way, and always been unhinged.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then who was gun? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a feature, not a bug. In many places in the UK, that is. Other places, too. But in UK, also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is more the availability of screens of each. Especially in smaller venues and towns. It just reduces overall each movie's possible showing times. 

Even a 10% fewer slots/screens can be $50,000,000 off each movie's gross </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve Inskeep is seriously one of the best interviewers out there. 

No gotcha questions, but knows how ask the right questions and a master of the follow-up. Tough, but asks tough questions of all sides.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if the word "wiretap" shows up in an article, it has a very narrow and specific definition? It means Obama wiretapped Trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they for or against cancer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McConnell didn't shut down McCain for impugning another senator, I see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird. Cool. But weird too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. Cool. You're probably right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The White House thought CBO estimates would show GOP health-care bill would cause millions more to lose insurance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why 1/3 height instead of midpoint, where you might see the most combined vertical, and horizontal forces, plus moment? 

Assuming pane is supported on all sides, and not hung? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bipartisan 'Bromance' Blossoms As 2 Texas Congressmen Make D.C. Road Trip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And a split decision at the supreme Court would let the lower ruling stand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was in Hawaii yesterday. 

http://www.politico.com/story/2017/03/obamas-spotted-in-hawaii-236029 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you knee-jerk call people racist, it just makes them ignore you. Not everyone is racist!

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, you know, the East India Company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long term it would save us money, but we don't have the upfront  capital to implement it. Plus, being the AMA headquarters makes it a wee bit difficult.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DOJ asks for more time to address Trump's wiretapping claim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 10:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also many considered it anti-Semitic. Which he vociferously denied. 

Didn't help that shortly thereafter Gibson was caught saying some bad stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Trumpism an existential threat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Graphic user interface interface </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 07:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many of Googles experiments. From googlwave to plus to selfdriving cars and glass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's just trying to emulate Reagan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not their fault. Their just following orders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Percy is textbook Ned. Perfect goody two shoes, following rules, at the expense of everything else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 13:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a tribute to the greatest photo ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
