<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3318</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To add to the responses, you may notice that many stores are  automatically defaulting to Debit payment, where you enter your pin code.  They are not charged for taking the money out of your bank account because it does not involve credit services. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not an expert at all, but I read kissing comes from the feeding of premasticated food.   i.e. Mother bird feeding its young.

Take a look at this page and you may get where I am coming from.  It even kind of supports what I am saying in the section "Human kiss precursor"

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Premastication </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did leaders of Army's really jump into the front line mix of battle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 01:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen it many times on TV programs, just now on a story about Genghis Khan.  Seems to me the enemy should swarm on the leader to leave the enemy without a leader and destroy the moral of the troops.  Is this Hollywood or did they Genghis Kahn and really jump into the heat of the battle on the front line?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 15:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anybody tell me what evidence this entire Russia thing is based on?  Not what you think or circumstantial rumors, where is any evidence at all.   Documents, video, audio, hack.....Anything?  What was the smoking gun to start all of this?  Not a notion, a fact

Why did people want Comey fired when he hurt Hillary, but now he is fired and those same people are complaining he is fired? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 15:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People like you make things suck in the military. The sailor wants some help and turned to us.  Its a bit stupid to assume the sailor did not try to look things up, or is in a position that references are not handy, or even hearing some scuttlebutt. MeatShit really fits, I'm betting your a Chief.  How about your lazy ass helping somebody? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 14:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to add that when struck the aircraft becomes the same potential in energy as the lightning. (obviously)  however, there is no difference in potential for the flow of energy.   
Birds are OK on a wire because there is no difference in potential (path for electricity.)  If the bird was on a wire had one long leg and touched the ground it would be fried because the electricity has a path to flow.  The same for an aircraft, but if the aircraft was dragging a really long wire on the ground, the electricity from the lightning would flow through the plane and electrocute everyone and everything.

One more - those guys working up on the high voltage wires.   They can hang on the wire all day and the have the same potential as the wire, if they were to reach out and touch the tower they would get electrocuted.  Electricity would have a path to ground through the worker.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I begin, its important to know this was in the 90s

I have been living with my girlfriend for a few months which was a good thing because I realized even though she was hot, she was crazy..not rational at all.

Im in the military and we are going out over the weekend for exercises. The Thursday night before I leave, I decide to break the news to her that I think it would be best if she moved out while I was gone. She agrees - great its mutual. I thought it was good plan; I would not have to carry anything or go through the drama. Friday morning Im out the door with a good times goodbye kiss and things are going great. When I get back; I will have the entire place to myself.

A little bit into the deployment the boys ask me what was going on with the girlfriend. I told them the story and one of the fellows points out more than likely she will trash the place. I was pissed and started to worry the entire time we were away. Of course, I caught all kinds of crap form everybody the entire time regarding my calculated error. Things really sucked, there was nothing I could do but wait it out.

Along comes Monday night  the night of reckoningtime to go home and see how bad things are. I open the door an inch at a time and could not believe my eyes. This was the cleanest I had ever seen the place. Im thinking, what the heck is going on? Sure enough all her stuff is gone and the place looks great! No notes, and no sign that she ever existed. Heavenly!

The next morning the fellows are waiting with bated breath to find out how bad I was suffering because of my decision. Broke their hearts when I told them what had happened. They were disappointed; some couldnt believe it and figured something had to be up.

Fast forward a few weeks, my mail comes to my unit address so I can receive it when I am away. I get a big manila envelope from AT T. I open the envelope and it is a bill for thousands of dollars! I start looking at the charges (This is a good time to tell you that her brother was in the Navy in Japan). I think I remember putting the phone back on the receiver when I returned. Well, she got me. Time and Temperature recording in Japan! From the day I left until the time I got home and hung up. You could see the minute charges for the overseas calls  a few pages of 45 cents, 75 cents, over a dollar etc. 4 days straight. You get the picture. (For those of you that are not old enough to remember we paid by the minute in the 90s for our long distance calls.) I have to give it to her well played, well played indeed.

As far as the bill I had to payThe phone company was pretty cool about it. They averaged that bill with the last 12 months so it was a manageable punishment for messing around with crazy. Most of the pain came from the guys at work, never lived it down until I transferred. Young and dumb good times!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the classiest/creative way someone has "gotten revenge"..so good you have to respect it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I begin, its important to know this was in the 90s

I have been living with my girlfriend for a few months which was a good thing because I realized even though she was hot, she was crazy..not rational at all.

Im in the military and we are going out over the weekend for exercises. The Thursday night before I leave, I decide to break the news to her that I think it would be best if she moved out while I was gone. She agrees - great its mutual. I thought it was good plan; I would not have to carry anything or go through the drama.
Friday morning Im out the door with a good times goodbye kiss and things are going great. When I get back; I will have the entire place to myself.

A little bit into the deployment the boys ask me what was going on with the girlfriend. I told them the story and one of the fellows points out more than likely she will trash the place. I was pissed and started to worry the entire time we were away. Of course, I caught all kinds of crap form everybody the entire time regarding my calculated error. Things really sucked, there was nothing I could do but wait it out.

Along comes Monday night  the night of reckoningtime to go home and see how bad things are. I open the door an inch at a time and could not believe my eyes. This was the cleanest I had ever seen the place. Im thinking, what the heck is going on? Sure enough all her stuff is gone and the place looks great! No notes, and no sign that she ever existed. Heavenly!

The next morning the fellows are waiting with bated breath to find out how bad I was suffering because of my decision. Broke their hearts when I told them what had happened. They were disappointed; some couldnt believe it and figured something had to be up.

Fast forward a few weeks, my mail comes to my unit address so I can receive it when I am away. I get a big manila envelope from AT T. I open the envelope and it is a bill for thousands of dollars! I start looking at the charges (This is a good time to tell you that her brother was in the Navy in Japan). I think I remember putting the phone back on the receiver when I returned. Well, she got me. Time and Temperature recording in Japan! From the day I left until the time I got home and hung up. You could see the minute charges for the overseas calls  a few pages of 45 cents, 75 cents, over a dollar etc. 4 days straight. You get the picture. (For those of you that are not old enough to remember we paid by the minute in the 90s for our long distance calls.) I have to give it to her well played, well played indeed.

As far as the bill I had to payThe phone company was pretty cool about it. They averaged that bill with the last 12 months so it was a manageable punishment for messing around with crazy. Most of the pain came from the guys at work, never lived it down until I transferred. Young and dumb good times!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the classiest/creative way someone has "gotten revenge"..so good you have to respect it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you try to smell your farts when nobody is around?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girls on a one night stand with a wig -  Do you take the wig off before sex (hair pulling etc.)  or do you try to keep it on for whatever reason you are wearing it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skuttlebutt

Now, if there is an infection or loss of limb due to the tattoo that's a different story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anything happen to the soldiers that shot the students at Kent State? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope this is a good place to ask this question.  Was the shooting at Kent State a military action and the killing was "justified" or were the 29 soldiers reprimanded.
A little background.....
Members of the Ohio National Guard on May 4, 1970. Twenty-nine guardsmen fired approximately 67 rounds over a period of 13 seconds, killing four students and wounding nine others, one of whom suffered permanent paralysis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dust - This is what the ghost hunters claim are "Orbes"
Your flash or light source is hitting the dust particles in the air or on the lens.  

Or, its your aunt Mable trying to contact you
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lens Hood? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That small cotter pin holding your kid's seat on an amusement ride. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I investigated these crazy prices on cameras, but was not a victim.

The folks I dealt with had the item I wanted $300 cheaper then the other listings.   Ends up you will be asked to contact them for availability of the product, which is how they get your information.    I could go on with a e rant but the  bottom line as time goes on they want you to pay with $50 I-Tunes cards.   If its too good to be true, it isn't true.  Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
