<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2482</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: The Presidency </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President Orrin Hatch.

You heard it here first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. :)

The post does have a little factual-ness to it.  I've gotten Halo Top maybe 6 or 7 times total at a store across town, and maybe half of those times, someone was already there with the freezer door open browsing the flavors and checking the nutrition labels.  Their carts were full of meats and cheeses, and I asked if they were on Keto.  Every time, they said yup!  I just said Awesome, and that was it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh, I disagree. 

Trump would have just ran in 2016 on the Democratic ticket, claiming to be a life-long Democrat, and saying his values have always aligned with the Democratic party.  

The only allegiance he holds is to himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even joking...but if you want to meet fellow Keto'ers, just hang out next to the Halo Top section in the freezer section.  When they go for the Halo Top, you can check out their cart, and 95% of the time, you'll see a cart full of Keto-friendly foods.

Then it's a quick "Oh, are you on Keto?"  "Yes!  Yes I am!"

Source: Not a stalker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 04:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Purple drink would like a word with you. Oh yeahhhhhh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 02:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hide all my carbs underneath baggy shirts. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 01:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's not lose sight here. This is only the first mile in a marathon. 

Now, we find the motive of Trump willing to obstruct justice to protect Flynn. Why does Trump do anything?? To serve himself.  Trump tried to protect Flynn, in order to protect himself.  

From what?

Let's keep running this race.  Let's connect Trump with a willfull Russian collaboration via blackmail to assume the Presidency. Knowingly becoming a puppet of a foreign power, selling the entire country down the river in the meantime.

Impeachment is nothing. Prison. That is the goal here. The finish line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noticed they didn't mention Johnny Galecki's character though.  Hopefully he shows up in a cameo or two...but I'm sure he's pretty busy (and financially set) from Big Bang Theory currently.  He may even have a rider that he's not allowed to be in other shows while still under contract with the BBT.

Would be pretty awesome to see Darlene and David (Sara Gilbert and Johnny Galecki) as a couple again in this new show.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great question!  

They may ignore that, and just go with a "20 - 30 years in the future" thing, like the *spoiler spoiler spoiler* stuff didn't happen from the last episode.  

I have to admit though, that last episode was amazing and a perfect conclusion to the series.  (I do like dark endings, though) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched about 45 seconds of the first show, and shut it off, never thinking about it again....it had an audience cued laugh track, for goodness sake.  No thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny because it's true.  Also, because he says it's true.  Believe me.  Everyone says so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Roseanne' returning to ABC with the original cast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see you also like to live dangerously.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GoT blows it out of the water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sir, you have 21 already.  I recommend you stay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, no one noticed that at all.  You are a Master of Observation.  /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even deeper showerthought...If the clock started counting down 73 years.  72 years 364 days 23 hours 59 secs...etc.  

That would be even more motivating. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 07:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, sure, but I have to ask, how do you find something with that much fiber? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 06:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of them.

For decisions you've made that kept you alive, you're batting 1.000.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 06:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, so YOU'RE rubber and HE'S glue? Whatever you say bounces off....ok, got it.

I'll be on the swings if anyone needs me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa...they CHANGED that then. Whoa. 

That was always my go-to. 6oz Victoria Filet Mignon, roasted asparagus and that blue cheese wedge as the sides.

When I looked it up long ago, that meal was SUPER carb friendly.  I've probably had that meal 10 times in the past 6 months. Sigh. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....but you said in your post not to argue it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 16:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh, I'm O pos...grew up in South FL. Mosquitos would never really eat on me, and always chose others around me first. So, your mileage may vary on that bloodtype theory.

Could be that diff region mosquitos like different blood types, too. *shrug* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 20:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My co-worker (a Caucasian family) got back from an awards ceremony at his daughter's school, where they announced the rankings and scholarships of all the graduating Seniors.  His 17 y/o daughter was 2nd in the class of 286, salutatorian.  She was in numerous after-school curricular activities.  NHS, Band, Debate, etc etc.

Even though she had applied to over 20 scholarships, she received nothing, no scholarships whatsoever.  There were numerous students in her class that received full-ride scholarships from minority-based grants....many of these students were ranked in the 60's through 100's in class rankings, and did not have any extra-curricular activities.  Even more students were given very large one-time scholarships, also minority-based.  Mind you, these were scholarships that his daughter was not eligible to apply to, due to the color of her skin and her ethnicity.  

There were also students that received scholarships from the same ones that she had applied to, but had been rejected from...but the other students had no where near her grades, or her extra-curricular activities.  His daughter of course comes to the only conclusion that she can in that situation...that they received the scholarships over her simply because they were a minority.

This country's advancement is currently based on ideology, and not merit.  That is wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 15:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 19:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You also walked under the same moon you will die under. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 19:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP should change their title to "When the first person is able to return from Mars we will...." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like OP just saw the latest episode of ["It's OK to be Smart".](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mnYSMhR3jCI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhhh nice one.  I say Gilly Ad in my head.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From being a child watching 80's and 90's movies, I still sometimes brace myself when I turn the ignition in case the car explodes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IT wraps up very nicely, in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.  So much original here.  /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would hope that we wouldn't have to have it passed before we knew what it was going to do.  Sigh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes!  That's exactly how I have always pronounced it in my head all these years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I think you were downvoted because your statement wasn't in the least bit funny, nor creative.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhh, that does make sense. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, that's not what I asked.

So, the new bill doesn't mandate everyone to purchase insurance?
The new bill doesn't punish people for not being able to afford it?
The new bill isn't very expensive?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it appears I did miss the point of your post.  

And here I was, thinking the point of your post was to get as many down-votes as you could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Billy-bumbler is not equal to Dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that was true...then why aren't they just repealing...instead of adding the replacing part into the creed also? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my experience, the more non-sober you are, the more sober you think you actually are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simple question, but one I've never thought about before. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you pronounce Deschaine?  

As a lifelong fan of this series, and reading each book as they were published....I've always imagined Deschaine in my head to be pronounced as 'Da-Shane'.  

I was watching a "reaction video" to this trailer last night, and the lady in the video kept calling him Roland "Dess-Chain"...with almost a hard stop between Dess and Chain.  It made me CRINGE every time.  

So, have I been pronouncing his name wrong in my head for the past 30+ years?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] How is the U.S. Health Care Bill being voted on today such an improvement over the currently in place system? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How is the U.S. Health Care Bill being voted on today such an improvement over the currently in place system? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, what?

Do you not know that the ant colony has a queen?  That they care and raise their young?  But yet we wouldn't care if the entire colony dies.

When you create a Sims character to play with and it "falls in love" with another Sims character, do you really care if your character dies in a house fire?  
You think that you know the Sims character isn't really feeling those feelings....because you are looking at the Sims characters life from your human point of view.  The Sims character is a creation.  It's not "real"...even if we programmed it TO SIMULATE FALLING IN LOVE and SIMULATE BEING HURT OR DYING.  To us, the human, any tragedy that befalls the Sim isn't "real", because the Sim isn't a human.  And, that's the crux of it.  We, humans, can create a most life-like and detailed simulation that mimics and replicates all sorts of feelings or emotions in the simulation...but at the end of the day, we would unplug that without a second thought, because it's NOT human.  

In much the same way, if we are simulated...no matter what feelings, emotions, or whatever, that we might think we feel....we are not insert Programmer here.  It's most likely that they could very well think the same about us...an experiment.  A form of entertainment.  Something else we couldn't even imagine.  

Stop attacking my "argument", and start thinking about the issue itself.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drugs are bad, kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's Dossier might disagree with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I didn't know there were so many formulas, etc.  Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the what?!  

That's a thing?!  

I'd fast for two days just for the chance to go crazy on my calories for an event like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China to U.S.:
Hold my beer, watch this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about "smart" scales. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My scale does all the normal bells and whistles of scales these days, and gives all the info about BMI, etc, via an app.  

The thing is, it's telling me my Basal Metabolic Rate is only 2064 Calories.  I am wondering how accurate that would be...since all the online calculators have much higher numbers.  I'm not a little guy....currently 39 yo, 6', and 275 lbs.  Most BMR calculators online give me a number closer to 2300 Calories.  

Does anyone have any thoughts on this?  Would a scale actually be able to tell my real BMR like that (maybe it really is low or something), or are they just using a simple formula to give me that BMR? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I wish we were in medieval times sometimes, she needed a good bop to the chin that one. 

Wait, what?  Everyone is ok with someone saying that a person deserves to be punched in the face, because they have an opinion that differs from yours?

Have my downvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, you're not wrong.  You share the blame with the other 300 million that didn't watch it.  

Go hang your head in 1/300,000,000-th of a semblance of shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait for tomorrow, when someone posts "My bi-focal eyeglasses sound much cooler as 'Multi-spectrum Photon Focusing Ocular Enhancers".  /s

(Enough with the stupid Photon word-play posts. We get it, Photon is a neat word for light.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's unethical..to you.  Because you are using YOUR ethical framework.  Please take a step back and realize that Programmers would (almost definitely) not share the ethics that you have.  

When you leave your ant farm on the windowsill and they all die from overheating, you throw it away and don't think about it again.  To another ant colony, you committed Genocide.  

Ethics are relative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are putting the cart before the horse, and ascribing the consciousness and feelings, etc, that we perceive...to be relevant to a Programmer at all.  

It's quite possible that reality is FAR different than what we know, if we are simulated.  Our Programmers quite possibly are gelatinous blobs that we have no way to relate to at all.

Ever played Spore?  Created a six legged creature that was peaceful and benevolent?  If that simulation was more advanced, and those creatures came to the realization that they are simulated...wouldn't those simulated creatures also assume that we were also six legged creatures with their same morals, goals, and motivations?  When, the reality is, that we're just passing time playing a game while we wait for our hot pocket to be done in the microwave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/Showerthoughts/comments/61a2rv/the_division_symbol_is_just_two_dots_over_a/) is where it was in /r/Showerthoughts a month ago.
It as also been here prior to that as well, more than a couple times.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strange, that you would have not noticed it last week when someone posted the same thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...
Yes, son, that's what we called it when we had computers.

What's computers?

Those are machines that run on electricity.

What's electricity?

I'll tell you tomorrow, son, now help me finish defending camp our camp against these roving bands of marauders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhh, there are some real winners in there!  Nice, and thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need advice - Taco Bell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I will have to eat Taco Bell tonight for dinner.  Not eating anything isn't an option, as it is a group thing.  I can order whatever I want though, and no one will notice.  

I've already had 10g of carbs today, so what can I order from Taco Bell that's 10g of carbs or less for dinner? 

Thanks so much, oh experienced Taco Bell keto'ers. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is..seriously...like the 20th, or 25th time, that I've seen this posted.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've looked for etc everywhere, but they have no content! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until they don't.

#macabre </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free rollerskates!  I hope they're my size. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
