<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject322</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 13 only has too choices. Shield, or the one that reduces small damage if you're fighting people like Tracer.

The other one is a trap, in my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first link is actually a recap of the last episode and I don't want it spoiled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The "Does _____ End in a cliff hanger" thread, so people can find out, does this show they want to watch get cancelled on a Cliff Hanger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured, it might be handy to have something like this.

You see, if I had of known Jericho, and AMAZING show, ended on a cliff hanger, I'd probably not have watched it. Because I've been left wanting so much more! 

So the idea of this thread is, if you know a cancelled T.V series write 

"Does *SHOW* end in a cliff hanger"
Then add yes or no. Only finished or cancelled series please.

So that way, if someone googles that phrase, they can find it. You can also ask this question in this thread and hopefully someone will be able to answer you in this format. 

For me, I am curious. "Does Sleepy Hollow end in a cliff hanger?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi guys, I cannot find a spoiler free question to the awnser, "Does Sleepy Hollow end in a cliff hanger" I know it's only four seasons, but will I be left wanting more if I want to watch it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fine, anyone who is getting persnickety about this needs to stop and think. 

They aren't making it sex neutral, the baby will still be male or female, they're just making it easier, for the person as an adult to decide their gender. Man or Woman, or perhaps something else.

I'm personally not educated enough on the matter to know if there is a something else, but I honestly don't see why there couldn't be. 

And again, this isn't about the bodies physical "sex" it's about gender which is all in our heads and our society. And if you think I'm attacking traditional values, I'm not saying gender is bad. I'm saying options are good and people shouldn't be beholden to Societies pearl clutching when it comes to a personal choice that affects no one but yourself.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who don't click the article, like me usually

 The Kremlin fired a diplomatic shot across Ottawa's bow Thursday, warning that the adoption of a Canadian version of a U.S. law that imposes financial sanctions and travel bans on high-ranking Russian officials will cause serious damage in relations between the two countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> King of the Hill Se2Ep07 Pepe's first appearance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just said the age of consent was 15. That's not preteen
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/SV1Rpez.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> King of the Hill was one of the greatest adult cartoons ever made. 

Honestly it only started being beaten recently by the likes of Archer and possibly Rick and Morty.

This is obviously just a personal opinion though, as shows like American Dad, Family Guy and Obviously the Simpsons will far out last it's legacy because of their popularity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 17:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not bullshit calling at all. I see exactly where she comes from. As a Bi man, I hate when shows have gay character's who's only characteristic is being gay. Does that mean I can't enjoy sucking a dick now and then? No sir. 

So why couldn't she find it distasteful to receive a pink invite with flowers on it, but still personally like flowers?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 17:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fine with the side quests because most of the boring ones (Collecting stuff) can be done just walking around during the main quests.

And then there are the awesome ones like Dragon hunting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dragon age is wonderful. 

Even when the game play get's stilted like the most recent one, the story is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My PC cannot run Andromeda otherwise it would have been day one. T_T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/patient gamers. What series of games makes you break your scared vow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, Fire Emblem Echos is coming out in three days and that's a day one goddamn purchase I tell you h'what.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah he and Dehaka would be bros, Abathur thinks uncontrolled change is wasteful and dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 14:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who might be the only person at my rank (Gold 2-plat 4) in my region who plays TLV it does bother me when people I've played with or against are able to ban TLV on me. 

BUT I think that's a good thing. It adds to the strategy, to learning the game, and ultimately the community.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 26 [M4R] Toronto - Friendship, romance and adventure. 10 reasons you should be my pal, 5 more why you should date me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 22:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 26 [M4R] Friendship, romance and adventure. 10 reasons you should be my pal, 5 more why you should date me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, reasons you should be my pal.

1. I'm Nova Scotian, I've got a tiny accent and a huge alcohol tolerance.
 
1. I'm 6'3, you'll look like a badass with me in next too you. And I can help you hang things up high.
 
1. I'm a huge nerd. Comic books, video games, Tabletop you name it, I rock at it, and I love including people in my hobbies.
 
1. I'm an Amazing cook, and I love having people over. Just recently I hosted a small dinner with green onion stuffed, honey garlic glazed, Caribbean style pork roast as the center piece. There's a "Before" shot on my instagram, it was eaten too quickly to get an after shot. 
 
1. I'm friendly and outgoing. Do you need a wingman? I've got your back. Do you want to ask the staff a question but you're kinda shy? I'm not! Do you want to compliment someone, I'll be happy to start a conversation so you can.
 
1. I love camping. We should camp some time. It'll be rad. Leave no trace is the only way! 
 
1. Your pets/kids will love me. I'm fantastic at interacting with things smaller than me. If we become buddies, I also don't mind baby or pet sitting once in awhile. 
 
1. I tell it like it is. I'm not one of those "I'm brutally honest" assholes who think honesty is an excuse to not be tactful, but I will speak up if something needs to be said, rather than let it linger.
 
1. I'm funny too. I've even written my own standup routine. I'd like to say I got a standing ovation when I preformed it. I didn't. But I'd like to say I did.
 
1. I'm super good at lists. Like the best.

1. I'm also super good at counting. This concludes the 10 reasons I'd be a bomb friend.

Now, as for romance. You should probably consider those first ten things, because let's face it. You've gotta be able to be friends with the person you're falling in love with eh?

1. I'll go shopping with you and actually help you pick out outfits I think you'd look nice in.
 
1. I'll make you breakfast in bed.
 
1. I'll take you dancing! (I mean, it's probably more for me. But I love dancing.)
 
1. I speak like a cheesy romance movie when I'm crushing on someone. For real, you'll find it as hilarious as you do sweet.
 
1. I'm an optimist. I'm more of a Tigger than an Eeyore, but he's cool too and I've always loved that Winnie and the gang always included him, just because he was down from time to time didn't mean he wasn't a good friend. 
 
1. I'm 6'3. I know I said this before, but sometimes it's worth repeating. I'll make you feel tiny and safe even if you're near 6' feet yourself! If you're over 6', I'm not sure about tiny but I'll do my best to make you feel safe.
 
1. I'm like, super good at counting.

1. My instagram and gorgeous face https://www.instagram.com/keypaw/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 26 [M4R] Friendship, romance and adventure. 10 reasons you should be my pal, 5 more why you should date me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 20:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. TLV are my favourite character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Iamverysmart found in Blizzard's Heroes of the Storm Moba. Becareful you don't cross his paths you subhumans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 23:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's like, a test for a promoted minion? Instead of bigger with a gold aura, it get's fancier?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 21:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds dirty lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you also use the word Dogged which made me think it was a reference to Scooby. Haha

Plus the (1)Definitive dedication to deciphering dilemmas, (2)dispensing dazzling decisions and (3)doling out decisive declarations.

(1) Solving mysteries, (2)make meals in the midst of being chased by monsters, (3)and yelling Zoinks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I... Is this Shaggy? From Scooby doo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 20:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I give this bit of writing a D+. Haha

Well done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] A speech in the style of the V for Vendetta speech, but with a different main letter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 19:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Crimson Flame (Which Upsets him because he is Emerald. In truth, when he became a monster he also became colour blind but didn't realize it.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. :) 

It's always been my favourite alignment, because to play it in a party you need to be clever about it. It's why I made this post, I wanted to hear other folks experience doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well my character didn't have any restraint. He was a junkie addicted to sadness. But he had to fall in love with these people to feel sadness at betraying them. 

Everything he did was just so he could get his next fix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They ressed both the Barb and his daughter. We all were level 20. 

But, it was the only way my character could end that campaign.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. That's why I made this guy, he just wanted to feel sad, and would do anything to feel that way, but he had to go to greater and greater lengths to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Dear DnDers, the most maligned alignment is "Chaotic Evil". How would you make it work as a player? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it was

**Parblick the Chaotic Evil Grey Gnome.**


Parlick was cursed early on in his life, when feeling sadness he'd get the same sensation as joy, when feeling joy he'd just feel numb. So, he ruined all of his personal relationships just to feel sad, but that quickly was not enough. He began murdering his estranged loved ones to feel pangs of loss.


Eventually he was discovered and run out of town, so he began adventuring. Going on small quests, defending towns etc, before murdering his brother's in arms.


Does this so much, it becomes harder and harder to become attached too people. Can no longer muster up love or affection, and thus no sadness upon their passing.


Joins up with adventuring party for epic campaign. After months and months of playing with them, bonding with them. They are able to reach through too him and bond with him. Becoming the truest friend's he's ever had. Decides not to betray them, continues on in the quest. Months of the numbness of joy slowly killing him.


Upon finally slaying the arch lich and saving the world, reuniting the Barbarian with his daughter, and returning too the bard his voice, the numbness is just too much. Parblick cannot breath, everything going dark.


Being unable to stand it, roll to kill little girl. Nat 20.


Other players at the table had no idea I was playing this character this way. Only DM knew. Barbarian beats me at initiative tries to kill me. Misses. Other's too stunned to take turns. Roll to attack Barbarian. Nat 20. The sadness is too exhilarating, never before has Parblick felt this good! Throw's self from tower so he never has to go another day without feeling like this. Thinks of all the loss he has left in his wake. Smiles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww my credit card was declined for the shipping. So many of these are amazing, especially the one in the top right.

Your shop is fantastic, I've got it book marked. I hope to get some posters from it soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> avengers: infinity war trailer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen. 

There's so many turn around mechanics in this game. You just gotta play.

We should make a team together. For Chair league or just for fun. Six or seven guys and gals who just love to play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I took her to dinner first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude. That's amazing.

I'd love to play with you sometime. Just to hangout with someone else who get's it. That it's okay to lose. 

But feels even better to win </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D.Va was such a noob too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I had fun getting stomped by Tempostorm on the PTR: Noobs Vs The Storm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So me and a bunch of randoms, after 500 seconds in que on PTR got pitted against Tempo Storm, I'm mid gold-low plat consistantly as a player. Diamond on QM if you trust hotslog. I'm not at their level.

I was playing D.Va in a mirror match vs TScottie, who out played me. A little. But I killed Titan who was playing Valeera once, which was nice.

At one point Scottie and I (I can call him Scottie, we're bros now.) butted heads once with our D.Va Dashes and it made a bowling ball sound, which was cool.

But yeah, all in all. We were out played and defeated but I wasn't sad. I had so much fun being able to just try against these guys.

http://i.imgur.com/O8h5JXK.png

It was cool seeing how well they played together, and whenever I dodged a skill shot (Looking at you Javandus) I felt like a baller. 

But to be fair I dived into the four of them without my team, a lot. We weren't super organized haha. 

TempoStorm, if you ever want to play a best of 5 some time, I'd love to just get some guys together and have fun. At the end of the game I tossed my spray down, the floating hearts one, and it wasn't out of salt. It was out of affection. I'm sure it wasn't as fun for yo uas it was for us, but I had a ball. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fingers crossed they stay cheap-ish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Genji and D.Va announcers in the PTR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/6HXpw6P.png

Since I cannot link to a direct image and need to add some unnecessary content to my post just to fit the rules I'm typing this out, but it's self explanatory. D.Va announcer woo!

They both cost 400 to forge on PTR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only open a chest if I have more than 20k gold. In case the release more gold only mounts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah. Indeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love stuff like this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Right off of Spadina and Bloor. We might just be neighbors! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, flirting with someone over reddit based on mutual fondness for different heights might be the cutest thing to happen to me online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoy!

If that doesn't work, figure out a way to shrink an object, and wear it like an earring.

Or use one of your wishes to turn it into a tattoo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first time it ryhmed I realized I had to keep going haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So cute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pleasure. I also have a traveling dwarven god of story telling, he shows up and asks people if they want to hear his story, if they say yes the get forced into simple short stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm all about improv as a DM. I come up with stuff like this all'a the time. 

Literally haven't used one creature from the monster manual once lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a bag of holding, the smallest size you can, enchant it to be immune to acid damage. Put lamp in it, swallow bag.

Rinse, literally and figuratively, and repeat each day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everytime she gets to a new town and asks for the book store, ask her what books she looks for. 

Then roll a d6 for each type she asks about. She finds that many of that kind of book for sale, once she finds 10 of one kind of book (Don't tell her btw) she gains a +1 in checks for that knowledge. Like nature, arcane etc. Up to a max of +2.

If she get's a +2 in all the different kinds of knowledge, give her a +1 to her int score.

She's a druid, so none of these things are game breaking, but it's a fun way to let her know she IS growing.

Occasionally, let one of the books be magic and she can maybe learn a new cantrip? Or perhaps she finds two very slim journals that when you write in one you write in the other, up to a max of ten messages.

Oodles of things you could do for her like that.

Perhaps she finds a cursed book that pulls her and the party into the story and they must finish the book to escape, and that can be like a side quest. And if they find any copies of that book in the future, their exploits are now in every copy. 

Like, if a dude was pulled into Lord of the rings with his Drone helicopter and he just like, flew the ring into mount doom. All copies in the world of the fellowship would be like, ten chapters long. 

All kinds of things you can do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey now. Tall women are wonderful too. I said I liked that height because it made me feel like I kept her safe. But if you let me put my arms around you? Tell you it's alright. Hold you close late into the night?

Let me stroke your hair while you lay your head across my legs? Honestly there's only one question that situation begs.

It's "Are you happy with me, are you safe and content?"
That's what will make me happy, and was always my intent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/heroesofthestorm/comments/68nty8/hero_concept_the_zerg_swarm_with_talents_being/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/heroesofthestorm/comments/68nty8/hero_concept_the_zerg_swarm_with_talents_being/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does she think, that you're just going to haul it out and drop it on the bar and wait for the ladies to come too you? Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah clever. I like that.

Is your first name Kat? (I wont ask the full name in a reddit thread haha.)

What part of Toronto are you from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to hear! Haha

It wouldn't happen to be you would it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does she like tall handsome sort hipster nerds?

If so you can totally be the best man at our wedding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's another girl in this thread who said this short girl talk made her feel like an ogre. :( 

You should find her, it was a reply to my first comment there, she'd love to hear this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see "Uptown Funk" actually being a song in the third movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://68.media.tumblr.com/56ed2ec97e11e2d67030203b494e6133/tumblr_o2ymeaGva01s32omxo1_500.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I said to another poster, if you cannot be big of stature, be big of character. The latter matters way more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That comes up more often than you'd think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's adorable haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No? Adults come in all different shapes and sizes my man. It's the mind you gotta respect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to set me up on a blind date if you know any gals in Toronto ahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha I'll keep that LPT in mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super good! Savory and sweet all on the same plate. 

How about you, what're you up too this fine morning? Well, I'm in Toronto and it's fine, I dunno about your area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic! I just had a great breakfast, onions and diced potato for hasbrowns, some sunny side up eggs, french toast and sausage. I love mornings where I can take my time and cook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the ills of the world that I may be able to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean for sure. I can feel like I'm keeping taller girls safe too, like I'm a shield for them. But with shorter ones I feel more like a wall, but the wall of a cozy house. If my metaphor is any good I hope you get what I mean haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's enough love to go around my man, if you cannot be big of stature be large of character. Chicks dig it, I promise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad I could make you smile. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all! You're still tiny too me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah if you've ever met a small dog breed, I'd wager the little dog feels like its protect acting the big dog! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canada, Toronto. You? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad the feeling translates like that. 

One day I'll find my five foot missus. I wish you and your husband all the tip toe kisses the world can offer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a very tall guy who loves dating short women, it makes me feel strong and manly and  like I can keep them safe no matter what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TLV Master skin. It's literally their skin from the sequel where the murder a robot and wear his pieces.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now you know. :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you log into hots type into the chat box

 /join reddit

You'll join a channel of a bunch of reddit hots users who will usually be happy to help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one is kinda awful so I'm okay posting it where I know it will get buried.

"I'm not sure which was more shocking, my wife's reaction when she came in and saw me fucking our daughter, or the fact the abortion clinic let me keep her." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even have the money to buy a TV to hook it up too, but I'm super going to post in the hopes that I'll have a pretty PS4 to look at and dream about one day playing haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: This Rockclimber dropping his glasses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome. I thought I'd hate her, but she's easily one of my favourite characters in this game. It's made me love her in overwatch too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Type "Extended" after an VGM song's name and you'll get at least a half hour long version. Perfect for playing out scenes.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zb2RldomL64 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to clarify, that he's always introduced in a planned way. I don't use him as a Deus Ex Machina. Basically when he shows up, I make "golems" out of the random things around the stage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tHqy0n_VQJc

"The Bard" 

A Masked wander who seeks to make life more dramatic. With no loyalty he joins the side of whomever seems to be loosing, just to give them a fighting chance. His magic's allow him to make inanimate objects "Dance".

Because he want's to tilt the stage just enough in the direction that's most dramatic, the players have never fought him all out and they're always horrified/hopeful when he shows up. He's killed two of them and saved them from three TPKs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Top Ten OP anime characters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Parblick the Chaotic Evil Grey Gnome.

Parlick was cursed early on in his life, when feeling sadness he'd get the same sensation as joy, when feeling joy he'd just feel numb. So, he ruined all of his personal relationships just to feel sad, but that quickly was not enough. He began murdering his estranged loved ones to feel pangs of loss.

Eventually he was discovered and run out of town, so he began adventuring. Going on small quests, defending towns etc, before murdering his brother's in arms.

Does this so much, it becomes harder and harder to become attached too people. Can no longer muster up love or affection, and thus no sadness upon their passing.

Joins up with adventuring party for epic campaign. After months and months of playing with them, bonding with them. They are able to reach through too him and bond with him. Becoming the truest friend's he's ever had. Decides not to betray them, continues on in the quest. Months of the numbness of joy slowly killing him. 

Upon finally slaying the arch lich and saving the world, reuniting the Barbarian with his daughter, and returning too the bard his voice, the numbness is just too much. Parblick cannot breath, everything going dark. 

Being unable to stand it, roll to kill little girl. Nat 20. 

Other players at the table had no idea I was playing this character this way. Only DM knew. Barbarian beats me at initiative tries to kill me. Misses. Other's too stunned to take turns. Roll to attack Barbarian. Nat 20. The sadness is too exhilarating, never before has Parblick felt this good! Throw's self from tower so he never has to go another day without feeling like this. Thinks of all the loss he has left in his wake. Smiles. 

MFW I look at the other players at the table after playing that last bit.

http://i.imgur.com/3sJRoGm.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is TLOP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No? Because the guy was in jail for four years right? Does the woman look like she's 14? 

I'm pretty sure in the video it even says she was 17. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I admire the self outing here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IT'S NOT OLD! YOU'RE OLD SHUT UP! 

Q_Q </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zarya, take the grenade talent that is a quest, where you need to get a bunch of hits to finish it.

Take the grenade talent that makes the middle of the grenade do more damage

Take the Grenade talent at level 20 that gives all grenade stacks back too you.

Everything else, play with as you like.

But I like the shield two allies ability and the one that increases move speed for my melee assassins to chase. I also like the ability that let's you spend energy to make a new shield. After your first shield is gone people think you're defenseless and blow all their skills on you, this way you get to just absorb them.

Mastering the Grenade build, you'll be topping the damage for most of the game, trust me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'll play with you in Quickmatch if you want. I'm pretty decent at the game and can help you out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, HotS loot boxes are way better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow. They don't even include his name in the video description which I assumed they would.

Just her name.

Though google is clever, it might pick up on the connection between her name and his name, the old case and the new one, and present this in results when researching the case. In fact I'm almost positive if the case itself is googled this will turn up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's what everyone is ignoring. She was 17! Scared of an abusive mother and she told what she though, was a lie without harm. But they found the guy, now she's in deep more and more scared.

I'm not saying let her off scott free, but the people who are calling for her to pay millions of dollars (Which she'd never ever be able too do) or to put her away for 25 years have obviously never been in an abusive enough situation that you'd say anything to avoid more abuse. 

(For the record I think this sentencing was too small, as well as the 90 dollar compensation. But I'm no legal professional.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, thanks to reddit that video will be at the top of any search for his name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, it's probably going to catch traction thanks to Reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. That's what people are missing here. She made up a lie that she didn't think would happen to protect herself from an abusive parent. She may have been a young adult at that time, but fear for oneself can drive you to do many things. Who knows what kind of abuse she lived through before this?

Do I think she should be absolved of all guilt? Of course not! She needs to be punished, and I think more harshly than this. This is bullshit, the man lost 4 of his best years to this lie and there's no way to bring that back. 

But just because she made a huge fucking mistake, doesn't mean it wasn't a mistake. She was a scared young person who honestly thought the lie was harmless at first. She deserves a bigger punishment, but not this insane mob of internet "do gooders" who'd see her life ruined while teeming with this seething hatred. 

Hate the justice system for allowing this kind of abuse.


Hate the judge for sentencing that man so harshly with no evidence other than one person's testimony.


Hate this judge for being so lenient in her sentencing. 


But pity her. In her youth and her fear she told a lie and made a mistake that damaged someone's life. But she came forward. She never ever had to do that. She realized what she did was wrong, and maybe she was able to get out of that environment of fear and that's what empowered her to come forward.

I know people are going to pile on and hate on me for the sentiment that she too is a victim, but I will stand by anyone with abusive parents. "Oh but you're just taking her word about this like the judge did before about him assaulting her!" I am not! I'm not just taking her word. I'm taking her actions. **Why** would she come forward like that? She knew it was wrong. Why then would she make up another lie to compound that one during her truths? I feel her action of coming forward lends more weight to her testimony. 

But obviously I could be wrong too. I could be very wrong. So, before you jump down my throat with your pitchforks I just want to say

It's not our job to mete out justice. Don't turn her into some villain when you don't know the whole story. Let the courts do their job, if you find it dissatisfactory, the judge is a public servant. Write letters to people in power and people above her and let it be known that this judge is not serving the public's will.

But if we vilify all criminal's forever, where then is the hope for rehabilitation? As important as justice and punishment is, so too is understanding and forgiveness. 

I disagree with the  sentencing, but I also disagree with burning her at the stake as some posters seem to be *metaphorically* suggesting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, Diablo's ENTIRE GAME is just collecting more loot lol I'm fine with that.

But legendary in OW is less than 2%? Despite having already paid for the game? That's disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. That's awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got banned there because one of their moderators had a username like "AutisticOrangutang" or something, and he commented on a post in a fashion that lived up to his username so I said something like "Way to live up to your username" haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mechanically represent? How do you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cookies and cream for the PS2. Not only is it skill based, but you use only one hand AND you play Co-Op so you'd actively be playing with your father. I beat it with me mum.

Shouldn't be too hard to Emulate it and get two usb controllers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you said you didn't want to be a Caster, but Consider the Summoner Archtype where you wear your Eidlon like armour, then make your Eidolon materialize as your Junk swirling around you, and turn into a giant angry junk golem to fight. That'd be Ballin'.

And like, you can be super angry because you always need to pick up all the junk after the Eidolon dematerializes because he never puts it back.

That'd also be an intersting weakness if you wanted to play it extra hard. You cannot summon your Eidolon without sufficient junk to tempt it into the real world.

So yeah, you still get to play a smashy frontline brawler. Just a different flavour than you were thinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Azmodan. Easiliy. I'm level 55 with him, but once you get good with him you own that lane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they're suggesting you a hero. That's fine. It's good to build a comp that works with what you got. (I play TLV and Zarya a lot and both are dependent on having more specific team comps.)

Them being angry after you and yelling at you if they don't like your pick is bullshit tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to tie her into it actually!

But the only similar thing is summoning banelings (And this is in a different fashion.)

She actually summons roachlings, and Hunter Killers. :)

So for "The Swarm" the hyrda's would be smaller and do less damage than Zag's Hunter Killer's and the Roaches would be bigger and sturdier.

By tie her in, I mean. Make it evident they're the same race and part of a greater swarm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Hero Concept] The Zerg Swarm -With talents being such an important part of Heroes of the Storm's Identity, I've conceptualized a hero defined not by their abilities, but by their talents! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Zerg Swarm.](https://static.giantbomb.com/uploads/original/0/930/941431-ss76_hires_1_.jpg) A terrifying force, known for it's lack of identity and all consuming way of life. Some say the most Iconic faces of the swarm are Kerrigan, Zagara, Abathur, even Dehaka. But no. These are individuals. These are the outliers. The swarm's Trillions of souls are of one mind and one purpose. Consume.

When the game Starts you have control of one Overlord, it cannot mount. Basic Move Speed, can move over terrain like Medivh's raven. It's Z is "Overlord Drop" On a 50 Second cooldown, "The Swarm" all enter's the Overlord. Pressing Z again drops all units over time.

It's abilities are 

* "Baneling drop" drop four banelings beneath the Overlord, then explode.
 
 
*  "Scourge Missle" In an arc (Think Zul'Jin's Double Axe throw) fire two scourge, they explode on impact. 
* Dark swarm. A defiler unburrows and drops a cloud reducing all attack range within too melee range. Has a set duration, or until Defiler 
* R1 - Super Changling - The Swarm Burrows and the Overlord drops a Changling that becomes a copy of target enemy hero within range. Upgrade's similar to Abathur's Ultimate Evolution.
* R2 - OverSeer - The Overlord changes into an Overseer, gaining an Auto attack (Shut up it has one okay) and a trait you can trigger to resurrect, rounding up, half of each unit in your Swarm.
 
* Trait - "The Swarm" Passively spawn Two Zerglings with X respawn timers. Zerglings are worth 1/20th hero xp. Any Zerg units spawned via "The Swarm" are assigned a hot key (1 for the full swarm, 2 for the Overlord, 3 for the zerglings etc etc) All units with "The Swarm" must stay within the Overlord's Radius

Now then, most of the talents you get will add Zerg units to spawn via "The Swarm"

Let's play with level 1.

* "Zerg rush!" Gain four more Zerglings.
* "Roach Approach" Gain Two Roaches
* "Pneumatized Carapace" When using "Overlord Drop" gain movespeed.

As you level up, you'll get more and more options to get Zerglings, or roaches, eventually even things like Lurker's and maybe Pygmlisks.(Tiny Ultralisks) 

This, I think, would really help capture what it feels like to play an RTS, while still playing a MoBA. Of course I like the idea of getting more upgrades that upgrade the Overlord and the Defiler. Like, maybe when casting Dark swarm after picking up the Plague upgrade, it also deals damage, or perhaps INSTEAD deals damage.

The idea of this character is also NOT that the Overlord is the hero, no. He's just part of the greater swarm. (Though I think having a talent on each level that does not produce a unit would be a good thing, so you could theoretically play him as a hero unit.)

This would take a lot of balancing of course but I think it could be super fun and well done.

Enemy has lots of AOE? Take upgrades that make you a better hero and five you bulky units for your swarm. Enemy has lots of ranged AA? Punish them by upgrading your Defiler. (Ooh maybe a talent that reduces all ability cast ranges too melee as well? For anti spell caster?)

Destroying the Overlord will cause "The Swarm" to all die as well. Kind of like a Misha Rexxar thing.

A talent that will upgrade one of your roaches too a ravager? 
A talent to upgrade a Hydra into a Lurker?

Level 20 talent ideas

* ZERG RUSH! "All Zerglings become swarmlings. For every two zerglings, gain an extra Zergling" (Earlier upgrades could include ingame zergling upgrades.)
 
* For the Swarm "The swarm now share's it's HP pool across all units. All damage taken is done too this single HP pool, upon 0 the Overlord dies."
* Ultimate changling - Gain access too your opponent's chosen Ultimate.
* Cerebrate - The Overseer gains more AA power, it's leash range is now Global and it's Z changes to a Falstadd like flight. (Gaining the effects of Pneumatized Carapace on landing if you chose it.)


[Bonus - In game depiction of "The Swarm" vs "The Swarm" Mirror match](http://vignette3.wikia.nocookie.net/carbotanimations/images/0/08/Scouting_overlords.gif/revision/latest?cb=20151210025755) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pft not when you're facing a pro like me. I micro the shit outta them. No auto attacks anymore for you. (It's when Genji dives into the middle of me and my team and triggers it while I'm fighitng someone else that f's me up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who plays Zarya, and TLV. Fuck Genji. lol

His parry wrecks havoc with my guys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never buy boxes with Gems. They're common boxes and Heroes are legendary on release. Buying a hero is much better value wise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't about Politicans though. In the context of "Quit your bullshit" it's a huge news corporation being called out by a dude for sharing bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I did a post on it awhile back and we determined the value is actually 1/10th what with the amount of rerolls 1000 gold gives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All this Hanamura hate, where's the love? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hanamura might be my new favourite map! I play the TLV and those guys are mind bending on it, but even if you're not playing them, the map is so dynamic and you're always moving from point a to point b. It's the most engaging map in the game! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, he and Pam are best friends.

As for Kreiger, he was Jewish, so he faked is death and signed up with the Nazi army so he could waste millions of their dollars on his projects so they couldn't buy more bombs and guns.

He joined the Nazi's so they would have less money to spend on the war, despite being someone they would murder immediately if they found out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Straight up, if that was said in ye olden times that'd be a hell'uva way to flirt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SGA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reporting does do something. If you report them, they get the skins removed. They did this last time too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Report too support </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes him think he's aimbotting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will you ever be coming to Toronto, and if so can I buy you all a pint? 

Also, have you ever considered doing an animated show? 

I watched your MTV cribs episode just the other day and I would love a series based on all of you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey dude, I'll help you learn support if you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the best one would be to give her an Immortal skin, since its basically the exact same setup as her mech minus one set of legs, and make her a tiny protoss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Sort of spoilers for the most recent episode, but not really.) Archer's Opinion on Kreiger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a lot of discussion about how since this is Archer's dream and it's all happening because of Archer's Subconcious, the characters are not quite themselves but more how Archer percvives them. 

That would mean, despite all the jokes and shit they all make about Krieger being a weird scary Nazi, Archer consider's him one of the most clever and noble people he knows. because holy shit dream land Krieger is amazing. 

While also still being weird and scary. But a fucking hero for sure. Pardon my German. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Iamverysmart and tits! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't but I've seen him around a bunch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah as much as I.... *Like* Tingle. I don't think I'll have him tattooed on me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm collecting a series of "Mascot Characters" from my favourite games to turn into a tattoo. Any suggestions? Even if it's not a suggestion, who are some of your favourite characters? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 07:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are we looking at here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Support will refund one purchase during the life time of your account, as far as I was told when I refunded my TLV Pajama party skin (Because the next day it went on sale.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's sort of ridiculous. The only way to realistically shard into Legenrady items is to first get duplicates of legendarily.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I'm at 600 and some odd levels, and I've got a green boarder with a gem 1/3 the size of the one pictured in your first picture. And that's it.


Also it's the same colour as yours. Does not look very neat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That does make me feel better because I am sad and bitter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why the wildly different release dates from region to region? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's like, two weeks between when Guardians get's it's first public release and may 5th, being the final release. What's the logic for that kind of thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Hand Clap, fitz and the tantrums](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y2V6yjjPbX0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amulet of gobeldy gook - while wearing you may only speak and understand goblin. Only a goblin may remove it for you.

Pocket shower - a square that when you place it on the ground extends into a shower, has a 1/20 chance of summoning an angry water elemental from the tap.

Circlet of potato speech - talk to plants as the spell, but only to potato's. They have strong opinions on how you should prepare them.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for going to the trouble of posting that link. That was handy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talandar is his own character! 

How could tgeybjustify calling him fenix? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But there is **almost** no instance where taking boss is better than taking a fort

This is one of those "Almost" instances I mentioned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops my bad replied to the wrong comment.

Yeah. IT's hard to convince a team of it eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh for sure. I got a chuckle out of it myself. It's great art, and the thing that makes me sad is the fan artist gave the characters more character than the show lol

Any newer anime you'd recommend I watch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, this panel is from "The Gutters" webcomic by Blind ferret.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was browsing through some of my submitted posts and I saw this one and it made me laugh again. I hope it makes you all laugh again too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
