<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1875</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first known currency and determination of exchange value? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 08:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the first known named currency? I.e kroner,pound,taler,lire

How did they determine exchange value between currencies in those days? " oh a litre of beer costs 6 of your money? It costs 4 of ours back home"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First currency - what was the first named currency? Taler/dinar/pound/kroner and where did the name come from? How was the exchange value decided? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 08:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 04:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ASP/Bonowi? Yea it is, thats why recomended areas of application are the large muscles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Head spinning like a pedofile at Chucky-Cheese
Going up and down like a hookers panties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 04:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O'l Bill gave up more, and that was cause of someone elses mouth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 04:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no! No you wont! You made your bed, and promtly shat in too! You ride this thing out and take notes !

The second you settle in somewhere else you will start whining about orange cheese like substanses, too little ice and the parhetic soda cups we offer in our fast food places, and why you have to pay for everybody else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 04:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Body of a classicaly trained pornstar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 04:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess ill throw my hat in this lottery aswell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 01:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ofcourse, i don't know every legislation in the western countries. So i dont know are we the anomality or US but isnt this what theese post are about? You learn new things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Koreas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 14:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
