<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2519</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do it and a lot of the history podcast (history of England and history of China) are just one person - it's hard work. Hardest part for me is trying to talk like there is someone in the room with me-just have to hype yourself up abit haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah okay well, me personally it just got under my skin abit that she was over all the time so that's what your flat mate could be feeling. It's really irrational but I think it's just wanting to be comfortable in your own space and not worrying about making conversation with someone you barely know  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He sounds extremely boring if he can spend all that time on Facebook- like video games are fun and can be very mentally stimulating but just being on Facebook!? Wtf! - are you sure there isn't a brain slug attached to his head!? Sounds like a zombie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last year my flat mates girlfriend was always staying over or just generally at our house. Something about someone being in your personal space all the time can be seriously annoying because me (and your friend) doesn't really know that person and it can make things awkward like showering/cooking/using the bathroom.

However if he isn't actually around that much, and you guys keeps to yourself I don't see the problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How...? Because I pointed out that a bandthat swears in nearly all of their songs doesn't get played on the radio a tonne... that's why that song is mainstream 

Edit: okay maybe I seemed like I knew everything I simply meant a lot of their songs would never be played on mainstream radio because of the content-maybe on XFM after 9pm. They have a song called Balaclava which is all about whether it's better to use a condom or not despite the girl you wanting to have sex with telling you you shouldn't... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only one that seems really odd and manipulative is the one about him threatening to kill himself-the others while annoying just seem like a standard problem  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not unfamiliar with dog being used as a term in other countries like England, but it's seems to exist more today in China and yeah I guess you're right with the feral part  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I guess that's true I just found it weird that it seems more mainstream in China - wouldn't really get anyone calling each other dog as insult in England or something  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know but you don't get many people today using the term is why I thought there may be a link with China's use  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where does the disdain for dogs come from in Chinese culture? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So obviously we all know that the can be eaten in China but after listen to the history of China podcast and reading some Mao Tse-Sung writings/speeches I found it weird how 'dog' is used as an insult a lot more than other cultures. Is there a reason for this? Is there some sort of Chinese myth where a dog has done bad things?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most Arctic monkeys songs were never on the radio too much swearing etc  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had done three divine beasts! Trust me it's worth getting it and playing portably is great  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 14:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure no one knows the most mainstream Eagles and Arctic Monkeys songs... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 05:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh if one of my friends started being a dick and ignoring messages maybe I wouldn't care if he stopped coming. People all have their own lives to worry about stop attention seeking and have some fun wth friends  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 03:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like you have 'Don Draper' syndrome  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This relationship, from start to finish, seemed completely toxic. Most healthy relationships don't involve breaking up at any sign of trouble and you guys definitely rushed things with the proposal. You guys both seem quite immature I'd say it's best if you stay separated. First break ups really suck but you'll come out of it a better person  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 00:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preach he is a scumbag - right in Activision's pocket  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 00:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I would say is first time is always a little awkward, But I at least try it abit more. It is a lot better than any of the other stuff you can do sexually  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought it on switch but had completed most of the game on Wii U... because of the nature of the game it's actually fun to do the same stuff again even shrines and towers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you haven't tried it... so maybe give it a go before you decide it's not for you? Unless you physically couldn't perform you might as well try it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh one kit Kat seems fine and it's mostly just biscuit anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game is impossibly complicated  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Workplace doesn't hire liberals because they can't read! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 01:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 00:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a blog... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I am typing and it doesn't always pick up on grammar mistakes - do you always read over your texts and comments before you post them? And ah yes that makes sense ruins all legitimacy... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this is a gaming article and on I have picked up quotes from this sub you virgin  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And many use it to say what they really think because they are anonymous-the people I quoted had threads of defending their view point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point is these men from different countries fought for their respective countries should be recognised in a game which only attempts to reflect the conflict it's in rather than copy it exactly. So when everything else is realistic in some respect (the MP-18 existed) distorting it for a game is fine, but why can't that also be apart of the racial make up of the factions? These wars aren't only fought by white people so if we aren't beholden to total historical accuracy then who cares if their are more blacks running round the battlefield online then there should be ? It's not being inaccurate by including them in the first place (like the MP-18) but the way it used them is - but the game pretty much does that with everything so I don't see the harm  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so putting stuff that didn't even exist in World War One is fine but making the faction diverse is too much? Seriously!? So you just want everyone to be white in the game? Colonial war fought across the world in the Middle East and Africa not everyone was white... your the type of alt-righter who gets pissed at stuff like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I address this in the article maybe you should read it before commenting... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you even read it...? 

Also there are two white classes in the British faction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote this article for TNS basically debunking the outraged over the depictions of non-white soldiers in Battlefield 1 and linked it to the new outraged at Call of Duty WW2 showing the US Army as institutionally racist. Would love some feedback and opinions on what they think. Used some of your lovely comments and not so lovely :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote this article for TNS basically debunking the outraged over the depictions of non-white soldiers in Battlefield 1 and linked it to the new outraged at Call of Duty WW2 showing the US Army as institutionally racist. Would love some feedback and opinions on what they think. Used some of your lovely comments and not so lovely :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 06:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe focus on making friends first?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol liked 'the kid' love that even though you probably less than a year older! Haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is definitely a smoker or his neighbours come over and he smokes with them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 04:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going bars and drinking is fun. When me and my friends go we rarely talk to anyone we don't know. This seems more like you don't trust him rather than anyone going to a bar is automatically looking to hook up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Joe Kennedy III going to run for President in 2020? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 19:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 19:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The voice I guess kinda...? But still nothing really like Spacey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 05:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay you're 17 not 14... most people in my college wouldn't ever make funny if someone for being well spoken but you probably do it excessively without knowing it. Slang is fun and can be a joke, you might just be perceived as a prude because you are. I find it really hard to believe no one likes you because you throw in the odd intellectual word here and there. I am extremely well spoken and have a good vocabulary-I normally save this for the classroom and let lose with some slang and swear words with my friends - maybe you could try fitting in a little more? You don't have to change he you speak but maybe just join in a little more? There are so many funny phrases and sayings people said in high school that caught on with everyone-can just be part of the experience  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 04:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree so many girls when I was a teen glamourised depression and suicidal thought on social media    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 04:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck no maybe you need to get your mental health checked too  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (HoS) Fighting Iris as a wraith... This is harder when I remember... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 00:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean she isn't hurting me but I just can't kill her! She keeps teleporting back into the painting before I can finish the job and I am using Yrden (is that how you spell it? I never use it). I am playing on broken bones and I don't remember it being hard before! Any tips?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 00:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol so rivalry is dead? We should all be happy Chelsea won...! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 23:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub is so lame why are you all kissing Chelsea arse!? 

Edit-look at all the down votes: embarrassing when Liverpool fans are saying 'can't wait to see what you'll do next season', shut the fuck up. Fans like you are ruin the competitiveness of the league, the days of Roy Keane and Viera are well and truly over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 19:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'What's this Assassin Christmas?' (Or something similar from Jacob)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 18:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insides feel great. If you don't run you don't realise how clogged up they feel  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 05:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must not really be paying attention if you think that these two represent the Clintons. The only way they are linked in this regard is because of their relationship which is actually way closer to FDR and Eleanor than Bill and Hill. And Frank is obviously inspired by LBJ above all-Democrat from the south, WhipVPPres, a bullly-splash in some Nixon and you have Frank. 

And House of Cards 'liberal narrative'..? Do you not pay attention during the show? What would you call showing the struggle of LGBT rights in Russia as..? And including Pussy Riot in the show... seems quite liberal to me already but dont worry this season is about war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 15:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah okay a country that literally attempt to take over others like Ukraine, that doesn't allow under 18's to know about LGTB, that helps Assad used chemical weapons is our ally? No we are not gunna investigate every Russian but when the President doesn't disclose his taxes (first President to do this) and has several ties to the Russian government then you investigate. What is wrong the investigation? If Trump had nothing to hide he is insanely stupid for firing Comey in the way he did which leads you to the conclusion Comey was on to something.

And the only Press which is the tool of the state is Breitbart, Fox and Drudge, all tools of Trump's White House, anyone outside America can see this. All you right wingers are delusional glad I am not American  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 07:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 07:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm my own words Nixon fired everyone who was investigating watergate , Trump is firing everyone who is investigating his ties to Russia. Simple as that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just watched the episode about Admiral television-check out these magazines (and LIFE) in google books for free-full of 'Mad Men' style adds! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 05:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 05:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all its demented not dimented, and when there are several investigations into it, I kinda of believe it. Michael Flynn is very likely to face jail time for working as a foreign agent but Trump hired him anyway, after Obama warned him not to because apparently Trump thought Obama was joking. Shit excuse. The FBI investigation of Trump isn't even about the hacks its about his business ties and dealings with the Russian, and since he has fired everyone who got close to the truth, (Yates and Comey) I'd be suspicious.

But sure go ahead worship and overweight man child as some sort of God. Especially when his health care bill tries to make being raped a pre-existing healthcare condition-wonderful man! And you are a snowflake for being outraged that the guy who creates a show with the themes of Mr Robot, largely about the abuse of power from the elite, is obviously concerned about what is happening in America. Trump fanatics are some of the most ignorant people on the earth, people who still support him after all this shit he has done just so you can stick it to the liberals... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 05:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Comey had up the investigation in to Trump and Russias collusion getting daily briefings instead of weekly. He also asked for more money to pursue these investigations-Trump is doing exactly what Nixon did-fired the people investigating him. It's pretty obvious and even reputable outlets like the BBC are reporting headlines that ask if he did this as part of a cover up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 05:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I said in an earlier comment: I don't think this is really a problem. Are there legitimate reasons for wanting Comey to stand down for what he did? Yeah. Did Trump care about these reasons? Absolutely not. Trump praised Comey multiple times for what he did in and out of office-Trump even blew him a kiss when he was Pres!! It's so obvious why he fired him and I think that's why people are making a big deal not because they have suddenly had a change of heart and think Comey is a great guy

Also seriously!? 'Political bias' in Mr Robot? Gee I wonder what the writer of a show, that is about bringing down the elite and corporations, political leaning is? If that isn't obvious to you in the show you're just a moron. He wants to make it political so he does and just because right wing snowflakes like you can't handle it doesn't mean he should change anything  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 05:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think this is really a problem. Are there legitimate reasons for wanting Comey to stand down for what he did? Yeah. Did Trump care about these reasons? Absolutely not. Trump praised Comey multiple times for what he did in and out of office-Trump even blew him a kiss when he was Pres!! It's so obvious why he fired him and I think that's why people are making a big deal not because they have suddenly had a change of heart and think Comey is a great guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 05:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man this brings back memories. I have been in decent shape for most of my life playing football from a young age. After I finished school in the summer I decided to go for a run-1km. Well I did about 0.5 and I was absolutely dying-how could I be this unfit when I play sport I thought? It was hell. But I kept at it got better and more consistent. In my second year of uni I switched to a treadmill (way better in my opinion) and it's helped a ton. Being able to dictate the speed from the machine makes it so much better and means you don't go to fats and wear yourself out.

I think that's the key don't go to fast, even though you said you were jogging you still ate have been overdoing it. So now I run 10km fast three times a week - and my stamina and insides feel fine! I like to do it everyday if I could but my legs wouldn't let me-so don't worry that pain does go away-for me it felt like I had to clean out my insides before they could function normally for running. It won't be easy but keep at it and you should feel way better! 

Also one thing I'd say is set yourself a target and no matter how many times you stop for a break make sure you reach it, don't get disheartened and stop if you can't make the whole distance in one go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 04:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are way tooo many civilians casualties and if they kill a terrorist they normally classify any killed in the strike as a EKIA anyway  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 19:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you did go home to rethink your life! Congratulations on getting off the death sticks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 19:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit sorry wasn't aware of what the flair exactly meant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 19:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So tired and lying in bed at 18:12pm. Have to get up and do weights before heading off the gym to run 10km and cycle fml  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not about the videos it's about the pedophiles who make them into playlists  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but thought it is something they could cover, and they normally start their bigger stories from smaller youtubers getting the ball rolling  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If YouTube hasn't taken them down why would it be irresponsible? He hasn't down anything illegal and the video proves why he went on the vids in the first place  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess but it's not like the video starts immediately, nor does it have explicitly visual pedophilia, so it's not gunna catch anyone out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video that exposes pedophile communities operating openly on YouTube </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably more if we consider the US a terror organisation in some respect-especially it's drone program  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like him but I wouldn't really describe him as polite... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is the swamp  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still conflicted about the graphics. I know it's stupid but the PS4 version looks so nice and the Switch version looks pretty ugly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah like maybe don't change how you eat or what you like-probably should change if you fucking filthy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eight stream - I run 10km four times a week, and heavy weights weights four times and a 40km cycle once a week. I eat okay, probably pretty well compared to most people, but I work hard at the gym for a good body or I'd just have a dad bod probably. Skinny but with fat around the stomach -And my metabolism isn't as good anymore was great when I was a teen! I'm not just trying to be like 'I'm 22 and skinny blah blah'. I got pretty big when I was 18 quite suddenly so had to work at it. You're are right though healthy eating is a better place to start then working out, depends what you'd rather do I guess for me exercise is a better alternative then eating completely clean  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 'gym barely does anything for weight loss'. Newsflash it does if you do it properly. Not just jumping on the bike for 5mins and walking in the treadmill-yes you're right it's not the whole picture but it sure is a lot. For me gym keeps me healthy so I don't have to eat great (although I don't eat bad). Have you considered suggesting she gets meal prep? As she works I assume she can afford it - you get three healthy meals a day for about 60+ a week-if she's serious might be worth a go!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way - not washing for that amount of time is not healthy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 21 and both my parents are 55... I don't really see the problem? Your probably gunna have at least another 20 years with them maybe even longer - my grandma is 87 and my other two grandparents are 85. They were born in the 1930's and my parents still have their parents around - you could still have several decades left where hopefully your mature and realise nearly everyone goes through the same experience of their parents dying, a lot of people don't even get them for long-so cherish it and hopefully accept the inevitably of yours and their mortality. We have one life and then nothing so make the most of it don't ruin it with worrying about things you can't control </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And as Admiral Thrawn in Star Wars Rebels!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh when they say muslims they really mean Arabs and Africans rather than followers of Islam but yeah would rather live with anyone who isn't a cunt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No racism on r/The_Donald only if it's against 'Muslim filth' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a weird thing to compliment haha but fair play  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're in Ireland sometimes Gaelic haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For running I normally stick on Arctic Monkeys first two albums or Kings of Leon first two, really good and drown out the sound some get you pretty pumped-might be different for weights but worth a listen-I know people say it's 'Alt' rock but it's still pretty loud. Biffy Clyro if you want a little more screaming  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sweat quite a lot at the gym but nothing could prepare me for this week. No air conditioning at all on a jam packed Wednesday night. Still determine to run my normal 10km but shit was like running in the desert. Every breathe I took was boiling air and I sweated in places I never knew I could sweat-was completely drenched after but felt good as a one off. Thought they'd fix the ac by Friday where I returned to do the same workout but I was wrong... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You kinda sound like a Christian/Islamic conservative. Swearing is fine, fast food is fine, rap music is fine, social media is fine.

Granted eating too much fast food is bad and I get being annoyed about social media (if she is doing it rather than spending time with u I get it) but at the same time I think you need to grow up. Everyone swears, that's just the world, it's just meaningless words in a lot of cases so who cares? And rap music is art in many way, so why try and limit her intake of it? You just seem annoying above anything, you guys are 18 just have fun and don't try and ruin each others lives by telling the other they shouldn't be doing something that's perfectly normal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moral of the story is women are stupid and corrupt so men must have power over them for entirety  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Islamism is about to take over the world' apart from you know most of Asia, which contains most of the people in the world as a continent, (India and China both have a billion each with only 10's of millions being Muslim combined), nearly all of Europe, all of North America, all of Central America, all of South America, most of sub-Saharan Africa but keep telling yourself 'Islamism' is taking over the world.

Your comment isn't even about atheism, it's using atheism to be covertly racist, and yes I say race because I doubt you'd care about Bosnian white Muslims 'taking over the world' with their Islamism or white Christians spreading their faith </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbf I did sit by the fire properly until morning so there is that haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She loved my Hylian wood  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dyed grey I think but yeah!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game is fine you noob played 100 hours and have had no problems - you're probably just shit at the game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Piranha Plant power up can eat an ink squid! (Sorry if you know already :P) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just found this out today a nice surprise!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Had a cool moment-saved an NPC from Monsters, went back to her tent, I made a fire and then she was gone when I woke up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone has the old Wii U game pad stand-it's a great one for the Switch has a better slant on it! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only weird thing is that you did it with company. Like if I had someone over and someone wanted to go to bed then both people went into the bedroom for an extended period of time I'd find it weird  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me racing in 1st place when I see someone holding onto a blue shell for more than 2 seconds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was such an amazing map when I was a kid because I loved Sunshine!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Season 2 episode 12, 'The Mountain King', foreshadow the end of the series? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first episode we met Anna in the present time that the show is set in. While in her apartment Don picks up a book from her shelf called 'Meditation in a Crisis'. He asks if she has read it then sits down. He looks towards the window and says 'I can smell the ocean', to which Anna does not respond. Anyone think this is foreshadowing the last scene of the show or am I overthinking it?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best build for the sport bikes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a Horizon and Witcher crossover could work... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So CD Projekt and Guerrilla have been happily retweeting pictures of Aloy and Geralt together which got me thinking into how both games could crossover now I've completed both.

So Ciri (Geralts 'Daughter') has the power to travel through dimensions. In the Witcher world humans entered it through an event that transported them from another dimension-maybe Earth could exist as another dimension? So some event could happen and Aloy could be transported to the Witcher world where she teams up with Ciri and Geralt is transported to Earth where maybe he teams up with one if the cast.

Since the games have similar mechanics (especially the tracking one) you could have Aloy and Ciri team up for a Witcher contract, and Geralt could hunt down one of Horizon's bigger beasts. The could just phrase this whole event like Red Dead Redemptions 'Undead Nightmare'. 

I know it couldn't happen but the thought of seeing Ciri and Aloy interact and Geralt commenting on the world of Horizon just makes me excited. What do you guys think?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Racism is underrepresented in the media in general, but particularly World War 2-you never get the sense the army is a racist institution in any American war movie in the Second World War-Saving Private Ryan, the Thin Red Line, or series like Band of Brothers and the Pacific. It has largely been ignored. You're not one of those people who got pissed the Harlem Hell fighters were included in BF1 right? Actually you probably are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that even the point ? They are choosing to show the struggle of African Americans in service - because most games never have, what's the problem history ain't white enough for you already?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well some soldiers certainly would have had confederate flags either painted on their helmets/tanks or maybe even a patch-they certainly did in Vietnam. It's also doing battle of the bulge where black and white units often mixed in the chaos of the conflict there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we should just pretend House of Cards, a show about US politics and the President, which exists, in part, in our own reality (Bill Clinton, Reagan etc all exist) and covers topics that are relevant to today's world (Pussy Riot, ICO) , just exists in a vacuum? How is that supposed to work?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Trump cuts healthcare the way he wants to he essentially has knowingly killed people as millions would be thrown of their coverage and hundreds at least would probably die as a result  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 09:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in tournaments - go into them and look at Ines with no items - the best one I used to play on Wii U was 200cc no items  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha nice ! Just remember Wither did some
of the stuff first ! I am glad it had an influence on Horizon for the best tbh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait no Swastika...? What is this shit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and my friend were discussing it today Bailly must be a nightmare to play against. He's quick, strong and absolutely uncompromising in tracking players and steaming into tackles   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people just forget man. I only know maybe 5 of my friends bdays exactly and a mostly know the rest by the months-need a reminder sometimes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'You have a great laugh. I dont think I have anything to worry about'... she was found dead later that day... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best game ive played since the Witcher 3, and nearly as good! I think Witcher's cast of characters makes it better overall but both great ! 11/10! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already got half way through Zelda on Wii U so not ruining the experience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cyclone with a 98 round mag is the best !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because little boys speak like that 'okay that's sounds right. You're right'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they died the most they only contributed to defending their own country then taking over others-why did the Cold War happen? Oh right because the Soviets installed governments throughout the world to back them. The died the most because they had shit tactics and weapons - the British and Americans fought across the globe Russians basically only did in Europe and and tiny bit in Asia in 1945. Why are you even defending a brutal dictatorship? A lot of soldiers may have been grave but a lot were raping murderers - did the French go and start taping every German 'returning the favour' (you sick bastard) . Russians also raped Mongolians what did they do to Russian women again? Oh right nothing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'You walk like a jaguar'...? What the fuck... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I'm sooo butt hurt the raping army of a brutal dictatorship aren't in the game ! What part do you want to play? When he Soviets signed a pact with the Nazi's? Or when they invaded Poland and killed 20,000 of their officers? How about invading Finland? The heroic soviets!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Treyarch is the only one who does gore and still does have it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red Army also invaded Poland on agreement with the Nazi's and slaughtered 20,000 polish officers. They also carried out mass rapes whenever they took over territory... the Soviets dishonoured themselves. And what played into them having the most casualties that their tactics were shit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soviets fought for themselves remember they made a pact with the Nazis to invade Poland - they had way higher casualties because they were ill equipped and their tactics sucked - lucky for them Russian winter is the worst  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are so entitled in what way did they screw you personally? If you waited for more than a day after launch the review would have told you what the game was and then you wouldn't have to buy the game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 07:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sounds at times you have had a shitty life but just know you're relationship with him is far from the norm. It's a bad bad one. Sexual chemistry and occasional romance doesn't make up for him physically assaulting you, ignoring you and ghosting you. Maybe he is also part of your mental health problems?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both for noobs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
