<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3240</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 02:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooooh, I'm jealous! I didn't have the funds for that, but I'll still be having a huge bar hopping party  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, yeah, you're behind me a day then. I'm the 13th. But hey, same year, so we'll still both be gettin turnt next month HEY-OOOOOOOO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So close and yet so far //single tear// </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you my long lost skeleton war brother/sister/skeleton person?????? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try again, a little less than twice that age. I'm about to get mega turnt next month if that helps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 00:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a pretty strong stomach so I didn't puke, but I did gag. Which, for me, is pretty intense. I read the Jolly Rancher story and ate dinner 2 minutes later lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 00:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how using extra question marks in a casual online setting for emphasis makes me a cretin. Can you at least come up with anything other than criticizing something that literally doesn't matter at all? And look, I used just one that time since apparently using more than one is a crime against humanity.

But I'm done replying to this so say whatever you want, you win, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 00:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, I'm sorry, question marks and I are going to start marriage counseling first thing tomorrow and I'm going to get help for my drinking problem. My abusive behaviors are tearing our family apart, thanks for your help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 23:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't realize putting * around things made it italicize which is why the first sentence reads funny, I'm still sorta newish to reddit. Its supposed to be two different actions, not one sentence. Your "contrary opinion" came across very rude, which is why I read is as anger, and I was disagreeing with you saying it was "vindictive" or about random Internet people when I thought it was pretty clear that this person was their friend. I can agree it was a bit harsh, but you didn't say harsh, you said vindictive, two very different things. 

Also, nice low blow insulting my grammar. If you can have a different opinion, than so can I. Also sorry if my reply is inconsistent in organization??? Didn't realize I needed to write a college paper to disagree with someone on reddit. I just write as I think it and my thoughts aren't always organized \_()_/   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 23:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *comes to a sub about revenge* *gets mad about revenge* ?????? I think the issue is that they thought this person was their friend, not just a "obscure corner of the internet", who spoke poorly about them behind their back. Sure, maybe possible jail time is harsh, but they didn't get any and just had a big, annoying, and embarrassing inconvience placed upon them. I've seen and read way worse revenge stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 22:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That story is both great and terrible, but I also read it last night haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
