<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2423</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Structurally, it's decent movie. Characters have arcs, they generally behave realistically, everyone has clearly defined goals. 

I could go on, but you're not going to understand... you've got your fanboy goggles on, not your thinking cap.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Negan just plain sucked. Dude is way too stupid to be alive.

He's tried to turn Dwight, Daryl, Rick, Sasha, and Eugene to his side, and he outright failed 3 of those times, had a temporary success with Dwight, and the jury is still out on Eugene, but I think it's safe to say he's failure 5. 

Then he has the genius idea to monologue before he tries to kill someone, and they escape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> then i'd have to say they know nothing about movies either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All perfume commercials are terrible, because you can't smell the perfume, so they try to sell you an experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, you know nothing about movies if you think that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, MOS and BvS are truly bad movies. Marvel hasn't made anything that bad yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the heads up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SHF Anakin Skywalker Released! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SHF Anakin Skywalker Released! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like he's gonna need a hot shower when I get mine. 

It's pretty stupid of the designer to not have made sure that the butterfly joint pegged into the top and bottom of the inner torso. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If DC really wanted to be different from Marvel this is what they should have done. I would have loved it if the DC cinematic universe was modeled after Darwyn Cooke's New Frontier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and it could still be a total stinker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not if r/crackiswack can help it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can voice that, but we also have to accept people will voice their dislike of our lack of satisfaction with the stuff Gimple's been pumping out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> literally right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gimple also wrote Ghost Rider Spirit of Vengeance, a film where he thought we needed to see Ghost Rider piss fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't just drop, they sank like a rock in one season. Ignoring the inflated season premiere, they lost about half of their audience. That is not "minor erosion," that's "we fucking broke something, and we need to fix it fast." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're supposed to decorate those? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were sunglasses one time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanna see Ass Dan host. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope it pops up at tru.com soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That explains it. That box seriously looks as deep as a regular 1/6 figure box is tall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see it lasting more than the initial 13 episodes they typically order. I have a feeling this is gonna lead to another Mulaney situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He says the show's ratings suffered "minor erosion." 

I didn't know losing about half your audience was considered minor, by any standards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMC Networks CEO Dismisses Ratings Concerns About 'Walking Dead' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 22:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was watching Parks and Rec the other day, and the stuff in it seemed so tame compared to Trump's Perpetual Cycle of Scandals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 22:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, that box is deep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feels like it kinda would fit in between The Resistance and The 2nd Law, because it lyrically has similar themes The Resistance, and the wub wubs of The 2nd Law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice.

#NOICE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "business man" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 05:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strangely enough, I can't seem to find that sitcom in his wikipedia page. Maybe I imagined it, or confused it.

EDIT: Found it, it was Guys with Kids. And it starred Anthony Anderson, not Kenan. I'm a racist now. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 05:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was on a sitcom a few years ago that got cancelled. He stayed with SNL the whole time too. Keenan is a machine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 04:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> clunky segue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 04:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll be easy to find because it'll be the gilded tombstone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 03:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its gonna get cancelled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 03:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP Ass Dan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been hanging for 5 months and counting! You're probably right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's worth something today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 00:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump Administration is about to get fucked by the long arm of the law! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 00:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOLY FUCK.

And here I was thinking today was a little bit tamer than yesterday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 00:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have Kevin Reilly in charge of TBS and TNT. He's the guy that picked up a slew of great shows across broadcast and cable. He was behind The Shield, The Office, Brooklyn Nine-Nine, Fringe, 30 Rock, The Sopranos, Last Man on Earth, and more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what terrifies me now that I've graduated from college. There *has* to be more to life than this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can sell the covers songs the contestants sing, and CBS would see none of that money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuck i clicked reply instead of edit


basically they'd only be making money off of the ad space they'd be selling. No money from merchandise, syndication, or any other little thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reruns and shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 17:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god, is it finally happening?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 02:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tiya Sircar seems awfully young for him.

EDIT: And then you Google her, and it turns out she's 35. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 02:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One day, my children will be getting lectured about this in class, and I'll tell them, I lived under the Trump catastrophe. Then they'll tell me to get into the hover car cuz I'm embarrassing them or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 23:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was always going to graduate with a D, cuz I'm a man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 04:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your post is all fine and dandy, but the problem is the soft minded people you describe *are* watching this show. Just take a look over at the garbage spouted by the_donald. They memed themselves into voting for an idiot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Junior high? Kids in middle school are getting pregnant on this show? Damn, the life lessons sound crazy hardcore, especially compared to the shit kidcoms have been pumping out lately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can fuck off with their "Both sides are equally bad" garbage they've been peddling. I'm sure that kind of apathy influenced a lot of people, and led to the shitshow of a Presidency we've got now.

They've lost this viewer for good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 22:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this isn't gonna go over well, but I've gotta say it anyway, but I'm a sick of seeing images of swaps on here, because it's always replaced by a shittier figure. 

If someone one day swaps in a rare figure, like a Rhino Ghost Rider, or Hobgoblin Daredevil, then maybe I'll be more interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope that if it does return, and this isn't some sort of stealth cancellation, they write more action into the series. This season was drastically lacking in that area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they're not gonna give the show a good budget, they might as well just cancel it.

I liked Carter just fine, but this season was hampered by the drastically under budgeted feel it had. There were barely any major action set pieces this season. When there were any action scenes, they usually happened right at the end of the hour. The only good action scenes was Carter's brother versus the terrorists, and Carter versus Tony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they talk about how they helped normalize Trump by having him on the show, and then according to Baldwin, attempt to get him to do a cameo this past February? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could, but I'd take these renderings with a grain of salt. The only thing they've physically got a sample of is the John Lennon head, and the way that's been made, doesn't line up with this skeleton, unless they plan on popping off the head and neck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 17:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just a rendering so far, not an actual figure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 17:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think DC movies have been very kid friendly lately, besides Lego Batman, to take the risk on Lego DC Super Heroes. I honestly wonder how well kids are reacting to stuff like BvS and Suicide Squad. I have no doubt that dark and brooding teenagers love them though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 06:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't be surprised if Netflix raised it's subscription fee, in fact, I expect it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 02:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else having trouble logging into thefwoosh forums? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 01:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You gotta be jacked if you wanna live long and prosper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 00:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously, they wouldn't happen all the time. They've got all sorts of logistical issues they'd need to work out, and I don't believe that they'd happen frequently either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 23:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't watched the show, because I don't want to spend 30 more  minutes on Trump than I already have to, but based on the commercials that play during the morning blocks of 70s and Sunny, I think that they are giving Trump to much credit by making it seem like he is in on the joke. 

Personally, I think that Baldwins impression is better, because Baldwin plays him as the stupid dumb fuck that Trump really is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 22:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's some weird looking art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My denim jeans keep tearing at the crotch. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 21:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been trying to lose weight since March I think. I've started at 238 lbs at 6 ft tall, and I've been jogging/walking about  3 miles every other day. I weigh myself about once or twice a week, and one time I weighed 231 lbs, then I stepped on again, and I was at 236 lbs, and again at 235 lbs. I keep doing this and now I don't know if I've even lost any weight at all since March. Now I've discovered a tear at the crotch of my pants, and I'm just so fucking bummed, man. I've been wearing a pair of pants for a week because all my other pants don't fit. The 3 that do fit, one had a tear in the crotch, which inspired this weight loss crusade, and now another does too. I'm down to one pair of pants that I can comfortably wear that doesn't have a tear in it. This fucking sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 19:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh yeah, that's a real hilarious joke/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 19:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *of Tony Montana* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 19:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He came with PIZZA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 18:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The better hip mobility goes a long way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 17:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's from 2009 according the SNL Vintage rerun last night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 07:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is potentially going to be Melissa Villaseor's swan song on the show that never gave her any lines, because she wasn't a part of the interchangeable Alex Moffat/Mikey Day duo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 07:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /#canceljost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 06:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on the immense lack of screen time, I don't think that Resident SNL Cutie Melissa Villasenor will be return to SNL.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 06:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All season! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 06:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, they're giving Melissa a starring roll in a sketch! It's like her second one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we need to get rid of Ike Perlmutter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just hoping for some good bass face screen time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILERS] 'You're the Worst' Boss and Star Assess Jimmy and Gretchen's Fate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 04:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 04:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The two feuding brothers from Oasis, and Keith Richards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much singing will we get tonight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 04:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both coast to coast live episodes so far featured a lot of singing sketches, ranging from 70% of the episode to 95%. How much singing will the cast, McCarthy, and Haim have to do tonight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering she was 14 to Rex's 10 actual years, I think she was definitely right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just waiting to see what the deal is with New Girl and 24 Legacy at this point. Pretty much everything I watch has been renewed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just keep watching; you'll see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only ever heard of one breakage problem with Figuarts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt he'd ever give an AMA to the website that helped give rise to Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 19:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope SHF gives this Luke another try, because I just don't see Mark Hamill in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 17:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! The Blackish spin-off killed this thing, man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 16:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I've seen, which is not much, it looks like they made donny boy way too self aware.

Also, I just don't care too watch a show about him, when there's already so much of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 16:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely Community season 6. Being on Yahoo made it *way* too self indulgent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 05:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe they had a song in this too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 05:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make their mother cry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 04:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, I figured, I just couldn't resist making the Harry Potter reference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 03:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Nearly Domeless Artoo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long does it take BBTS to get Sh figuarts orders filled? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I PO'd the exclusive Anakin with them, and I hear that it's being released this upcoming week. I was wondering if anybody has had any experience with them.

I'm graduating at the end of the month, and I'm hoping that the figure isn't scheduled to arrive the same day as my ceremony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 22:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it was cancelled we'd all be going 

Nein Nein! frowny face emoji </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 22:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's when he realizes that there's nothing to swing from out here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 20:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 20:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does CNN know WTF doesn't stand for Why The Face? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 18:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was that supposed to be funny? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a dress code for the graduation ceremony, besides the cap and gown? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wondering if I need to wear something like dress clothes or god forbid, a fucking suit underneath the gown.

EDIT: Thanks for the input, folks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I notice you have Casual Vacancy, but none of the Cormoran Strike novels JKR wrote as Robert Galbraith. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 06:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda on the same page. The Killers have been taking their sweet, sweet time teasing out this album, while Muse just dropped a date for their next single (Dig Down, 5/18) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 04:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they sing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 01:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are all the cool jacked dudes Republicans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I've seen of his Trump impression, he plays it like he's in on the joke, and I think that's giving the real Trump too much credit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 22:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man of the people, everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 22:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't be happening to a nicer guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 22:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know he's guilty of going on more twitter tirades right now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 22:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The news today must be getting to the_donald. I've noticed a higher than usual amount of anti-left articles in the new queue today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 22:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL, their ON HOLD function was so good, they applied it to the entire franchise! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 22:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "But I thought build a figure was supposed to prevent this?!"

-Hasbro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 20:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking love the prequels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 18:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's probably gonna rain."


BUT WHEN?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 18:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're banking on Steve Sansweet buying that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 18:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd really appreciate it if you didn't tell me how to live my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 06:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can go anywhere on reddit if you wanna circle jerk Rick and Morty. Just talk about Mulan sauce or something, and *burp* you'll find annoying *burp* Rick and *burp* Morty fans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 04:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BOTCHED RELAUNCH! BOTCHED RELAUNCH! 

READ ALL ABOUT IT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is he about to jerk off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 02:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still doing well for ABC. I was hoping that rising production costs would prevent something like this 2 season renewal, but that we'd still wind up with a final season to send off the Dunphy-Prichetts to the rest of their lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 02:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think they were working toward anything, but seeing as how the show runners are in the middle of a Feud (Ryan Murphy should adapt this) they don't work on episodes together which is why we get so many scattershot storylines that never seem to amount to being more than a temporary thing.  That's what I mean by wasted potential. 

After this season wraps up, I'm sure this will be the last we ever hear of the parking lot Jay and Phil are working on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 01:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 more years until that happens...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 01:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuck


2 more years until we get that unsatisfying ending the show will most likely get considering the show runners blew it's potential. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 01:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were a lot of anachronistic things in that show. For instance, Eric sure seemed to know a lot about Star Wars despite there only being one film out at the time of the show, and a Holiday special I guess. A lot of the Star Wars stuff was modern at the time as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 23:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The D will be fine. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 23:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LA is greater than Vegas. Glad we've got that cleared up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
