<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject350</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So incredibly sad! It's stories and incidents like this that make America's easy access to ammunition a bit of a no brainer to be reconsidered. As someone not from the USA (Australian here) makes Little sense to continue having guns being sold so easily. 
May the old man rest in peace and I hope the perp gets punished to the full extent of the law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She had her regular check not long ago and was all fine. Will be seeing the vet tomorrow morning though anyway    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a shocking story. I think I'll go see the vet tomorrow anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 11:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your kind words! We love Coco she's been with us for 6 years and is truly our first child. We've taken her with us and back everywhere even when we moved continents and hemispheres! 

She's starting to behave normally just now and the trip to the park was much more enjoyable. Hopefully this keeps up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 11:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be! She's turned a corner now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 11:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Appreciate your concern and will do if she wasn't running around and being all normal now. Updated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point re reward and positive association. Got any tips? She loves to go to the pub with me every other week. Might take her again tonight and she can see her fav bar staff and get a treat from them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes she did go from being semi normal after the baby to being hurt supposedly from the towel drying. Definitely not normal. I am keeping a close eye on her and she is walking normally and running / pacing around in the park. It's the tail between the legs and the lack of excitement for normal exciting activities that's bothering me. Will keep you posted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reassurance. I felt that a week or so into it maybe it's got too much for her. We're waking up at odd hours and running around carrying this new pack member (maybe looks like a new leader to her). And Coco is feeling confused and obvs a little ignored. Time for some more doggie love and encouragement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. There is lots of encouragement this afternoon here. Sit next to the baby if she wants to. Or just be on her bed. Hopefully Coco improves and can see we love her just as much as we did before the baby arrived.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] new baby and a scared dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time post here - looking for tips and help 


We've had Coco for the last 6 years from when she was a pup. Coco is a sensational dog - warm, loving, cuddly and like most dogs of this breed very social. Coco is a Cavalier King Charles Spaniel. A Very loving and affectionate dog. 

Last week we had our first child and was brought home on Sunday. Before the baby was brought home I would bring its clothes and swaddles every day for the 5 days.
On Sunday when the baby arrived home we presented it to coco. Coco sniffed and licked its head. Then over the course of the next few days she started to quietly come and sniff the baby when she could. Things were normal. Albeit a bit different for Coco as I can imagine. 

Yesterday though as I was drying coco (we'd walked in the rain) she let out the biggest shriek. I must have pinched her on her leg I thought. Hiwever since then she also started to get scared of me. And my wife. Normally she starts the night by sleeping on our bed. She did this even when the baby was here the last few days but last night she jumped on and as soon as I went to talk to coco she turned her face the other way and started to tremble. I tried talking to her and say things that usually make her happy. She just wouldn't look at me and walk around the house, close to the walls, scared. 

So I let her be since I was clearly making her uncomfortable. With my wife she felt slightly more comfortable. I took her for a walk, which we sometimes do after my dinner. She was not her normal excited self. Usually the lead makes her very happy and jumpy. She also didn't have her dinner. 

This morning again she wasn't her usual self staying aloof and quiet. No excitement at the lead and Walky time. At the park she didn't fetch the ball and appeared to have her tail between her legs. And looking at the exit all the time. This has broken our hearts. We're sad. 

Coco is our first child and have had a great 6 years together. Such a social loving dog having her world turned upside down in a moment of days. I can't begin to imagine how she might be feeling. I'd hate for her lifestyle to get changed because of the child or the fact that I accidentally pinched her maybe last night. 

My gut feel is that the shriek last night was the straw that broke the camels back. 

TLDR - new baby arrived last week and dog is acting strange after a few days. Need help and tips please. 

Edit - thanks for your responses and the concern re a physical injury. I should've mentioned that after the shriek happened. Coco showed no signs of limping or physical pain. As a responsible dog parent I know when she would be in pain. And obviously will consult a doctor if I see this is needed. Here she is jumping on bed and walking normally. Just scared :/

Edit 2 - Gilded! Thank you! I'm just doing what I think every responsible dog parent would. 

I have some good news.. Coco is starting to behave normally and has enjoyed a good walk and a play in the park with everyone. She is back to being bright and bubbly. Earlier this evening after spending time and really letting her take her time to come to me. She has turned a corner and is now walking with ease around the house. She also seems much much more comfortable with me. A signature call we have is I sit down and tap the ground and ask her to come to me. No matter how far she is if she sees me do this she will come running. Yesterday she was not showing any interest in this either to my sadness. Today she has responded. She ran straight to my arms. 
Thanks for all your help here guys. Good news in the end! 

Edit 3 - taking coco to the vet tomorrow morning anyway just to be sure :) no harm there. 

Update - Back from the vet and all is ok. Coco is back to normal and she's finding her place in the pack. Excitement for the lead and the walls to the park and the tennis ball have come back completely. Much to our joy! A regular evening walk with the family and lots of encouragement will continue. Looks like she's enjoying being the older sister now :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help - New baby and a scared dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 11:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just went to the Sydney gurudrwara today. Here!  http://i.imgur.com/nhsTeYx.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 22:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nurses do - I've heard this before. I wonder how unshapely my interiors are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what's the weirdest compliment you've ever received? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what's the weirdest compliment you've ever received? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 02:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 12:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it is in Waterloo (Sydney AUS) so could really be anything :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's fern growing from behind the wall where a door used to be. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 12:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 04:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought I typed ferns - not sure how I got fauna. But yes. Flora /ferns. Not fauna :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
