<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2129</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Above the Contrails (Christ. Remix) by Imploded View </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a really sweet gesture, I'm guessing the guy who rescued the Baboon knows a thing or two about feeling excluded being that he seems to be confined to a wheelchair.

The little things in life we take for granted offer those who don't a wonderful compassionate insight into life struggles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 12:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real victims are the people who buy diamonds...once you buy them and leave the store they are practically worthless.

I'm betting the robber will get a fraction of it's retail value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A plan to put more Americans in prison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 01:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moth Radio Hour: Explorers, Organizers, Interrogations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 23:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 14:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The blue one is a makeup cream from the 1930's, the other smaller ones i'm not too sure of especially the crown top skinny thing.

BUCKLEY'S BROWN GLASS Bottle is an  Apothecary Bottle of Buckley's Mixture Cough Syrup - Circa 1930's Canada </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 13:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Former PARKS employee here, Though those houses are very nice and the idea behind them very kind hearted ...They pose a fire hazard , vandalism , maintenance issues, pests, and encourage people to drill,nail and or hang things to the trees that are not good for the future of a trees health but also for the patrons of the PARKS Eg~ Tripping hazards,snags etc.

Unfortunately we live in a world where people love too sue..so any modifications done to PARKS grounds must be approved.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 12:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder why women don't carry a little bottle of acid to squirt on an attackers genitals ..I think that would thwart any attackers advance, especially when his dong is turning into a smoking glob of jelly.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 12:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Until the republicans lose the house impeachment is a fantasy

Indeed true,sadly true..To think the republicans can sit idly by and watch this clown ruin our country is more than deplorable. It's criminal.

This has all the earmarks of a dictatorship...ALL OF THEM..and disparagingly so few republicans have the nutsack to do anything about it.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 13:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea not bad,dude has substance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 12:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He accomplished his dream, time now to turn the page.

If he enjoys singing on the streets so be it,however, if he doesn't then it's on him too find something else.

I enjoy making music...but i'm not going to quite my day job....this guy can get a job and make music at home just like millions of other talented musicians.

If he thinks he is going to reemerge as a 50 something pop star this dude is grasping at straws.

Best of luck to him.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 12:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Korgoth

From what I heard Korgoth of Barbaria was just too expensive to produce, Because It was so brilliantly animated, the cost of each episode was too high so the network dropped the show. 

Sad because i think it could have taken off.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 02:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also find her on Tinder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moth Radio Hour: Mother's Day Special 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gagged within the first 30 seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 11:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very common, cool find though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying, here is some stuff I've done and some collaborations with folks on reddit https://soundcloud.com/user-345283577

Note: Some of those tracks are just for fun experiments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tim Heidecker Recounts Being Stabbed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your very talented my friend, I play analog synths myself,however, I play very slow because i suck.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet her pussy smells like a preschool dumpster in mid July </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incredible!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most likely water from years of condensation, I have dug up so many bottles with water in them that are corked/capped it's a very common occurrence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rebarb by Sald Voi and The Fade Beta aka (Gradient sky) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rebarb by Sald Voi and The Fade Beta aka (Gradient sky) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moth Radio Hour: More Women In The World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any suggestions of books i can buy to help me with the Arborist exam? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been working for a tree company for a little bit and i really love my job, It has been a goal of mine for the last few years to become an Arborist.

What are some good books i can buy to help me study.

I should say not just to pass the test i really want to read as much as i can.

My ultimate goal is to be a disease and pest specialist.
 
I'm in CT 

Thanks in advance :  )  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will write something up soon for the sub to get you started. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is in CT, he wants to go dig the Yonkers dump if your up for it perhaps i can bring you....i have many dumps in New York. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Aquachigger seems like a nice guy and he is a dog lover, i'd definitely like to dig with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recently went digging with this guy,he has an excellent website and is a great resource for information. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I haven't met a digger yet that uses them.

Probes are useful,however, i usually dig the entire site anyway so i have no use for them.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Project Grizzly - Guy makes and tests ridiculous bear armor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 03:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look how tiny this house is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its an olive bottle probably from 1920's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice job on placement!....I'm a (budding) arborist,not a climber,however, I am getting good at disease/pest treatment.

One day soon i will be a certified arborist....always in awe of climbers and the craft.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 14:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Jrg's videos are in no form encouraging violent behaviour nor do they teach anyone how to commit crimes.

So true the guy is basically a big kid, he has a good spirit and in no way does he promote violence.

Dude embodies happiness and a genuine love for his hobby, how anyone can make him out to be (even remotely) someone who supports violence needs there head checked.

I can't think of a more jolly guy on YouTube.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Repealing Obamacare was why she voted for Trump. Now shes bitterly disappointed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  many Republicans are seeing the ugly side of the GOP shining under the spotlight.

I hope so, I really hope the republicans are humbled by this election and begin a more center right ideology, this far right lunacy has got to go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow Trump really looks deflated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moth Radio Hour: Sword Fight, Hip Hop, Amnesia, Berlin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moth Radio Hour: Facing The Dark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys think Trumps greatest accomplishments are so far? and what are you looking forward too the most. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 13:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious to hear what you think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cities Of Earth - Things They Left Behind (Edit) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 00:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All you need is a basic sound to start, any junk synth you can find at a tag sale will work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good on you for trying, consider this your first prototype.

I think you did a great job, I did something similar when i was your age, my mom bought me this broken organ at a tag sale and i took the output wires from the speakers and spliced them onto a "learn to connect circuit  board" as seen here ---http://s395.photobucket.com/user/SeeMikesPics/media/200_1_Electronic04.jpg.html


You might adopt a similar method as it worked well for me.

Anyway just trying to give you ideas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the presidents spending plans reveal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this could have been so much better, the black guy had very few if any good arguments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blood farts are the worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @Greedeater some story, I hope things get better though it sounds you've got yourself figured out...have you ever considered getting a dog?

My dogs give me strength when i find it hard to have any, They always love me and I refuse to let them down.

Basically they get me out of the house (exercise) and give me strength when it's hard to find.

Adopt a lost soul at your local shelter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I don't like the sounds from VST's for my main synth lines, to me they lack depth and a special something.

My suggestion to OP is to get an analog keyboard and learn how to make sounds, If you love those detuned BoC synth sounds then learn about LFO wave changes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The terrifying reality of being an American without health insurance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cities Of Earth - Tuesday Night Fever (7 -- 4) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to put on and take off the Shed Defender </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No toilet can gobble his log, The pipe clogger. 

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having epic dumps like this is a disability.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How impeachment works </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> clocolan, I love your music keep it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel bad because i posted his stuff on my sub, now I will have to take it all down.

I'm sad because the point of my sub was to be an avenue so people could find new artists they haven't heard before, finding this out really pisses me off.....

Not only is he not paying them but taking credit? that's fucked!

 Eyesix records suddenly started following me a few days ago then stopped a day later ....now i wonder if this guy stole from me?..if he did dude is surely scraping the bottom of the barrel lol. 




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice cut, I have never seen anybody actually execute such a cut, very cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This time the ladder was on the ground </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great track guys, I love that slow LFO.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's good for bass lines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redpoint - Hoechst Skyline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 13:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 03:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda a weird response   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that I have gone back and listened to Tycho's dive album that came out the previous year in 2012 and Volscp in 2013 there is a striking similarly in the sound of the bass from Volscp and Dive.

They share the same basic structure and tone, I'd put my money on this being tycho's creation.

Dive - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z6ih1aKeETk t

Fun fact: The youtube handle (three15two) that uploaded Volscp when matched with the corresponding letter to the alphabet spells out Cob obviously Boc backwards.

I wonder if there is some sort of riddle here?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I have read this tracks creation points to Tycho.

Rumor has it that it's purpose was a promotion for Tycho's Awake album that followed shortly after the release of this track.

Nobody has officially claimed this track, It could be just somebody having fun with the BoC vibe, Me personally, i'd say Tycho, the use of a real bass sample. that may provide a clue as Tycho is an accomplished bass player.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moth Radio Hour: People, Problems, Places </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scooby Don't - 49,7 mph Drive (Artist of the week from r/SoundsLikeBoC) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lens-Echo Synth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 12:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a small world i guess, I search high and low looking for new content for this sub.

I love your song :  )
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ORKID - Orbital Test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scooby Don't - 49,7 mph Drive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alexander Aultman - View From The Hilltop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shammen Delly-Gone With The Fairies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 key arguments Democrats will use to attack Trumpcare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorry, Mr. President, but Obama couldn't simply order the FBI to tap your phones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps revised travel ban may not satisfy the courts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That helps..thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Closes" ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you, this is really good.

I run a very small sub called /r/SoundsLikeBoc so i'm always searching for similar music.

I was hoping to find the original artist who made this track,however, i'm  guessing we will never know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do most Americans seem sure that the president is keeping his promises </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Focus On The Spiral by Transmisiones Rodox (whats the story to this?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the stickies....I'm still working on the sub so no problem  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4T Thieves - Vignette by </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CIALYN - Opal Coast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr Trump has a very paranoid world view that mimics the very real skepticism people have of his campaign.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea they used all the tried methods nothing at all original.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bottles embossing reads W.E Henebry Danbury, Conn

History https://danburybottle.wordpress.com/2002/07/29/w-e-henebry-danury-conn/

More about the man:

Land records and city directories paint an incomplete picture of W.E. Henebreys life in Danbury. But we know this much: at his height W. E. had land and money but by the early 1920s William and his wife, Annie, couldnt pay a 93 dollar debit and a lien was brought against their house. Though incomplete, we know this much about W. E.s life: W. E. kept saloons at 13 White St in 1885 and 21 White St in 1888. In 1890 he ran saloons at 290 and 292 Main St. In addition to moving businesses often in those early days, W. E.s home addresses varied. From 1885 to 1901 William Henebry moved at least five times. However, by 1902 William had set down roots. He leased a saloon at 194 Main St (the business was open at that address for years) and bought a house on McDermott St in Danbury. Business was good at the turn of the century for W. E. He owned several properties in Danbury at least two on White St. One property, number 19 White St, he leased to the Foley Bros, William and John, two well know Danbury bottlers. In 1912 a fire broke out in the Foley Bros saloon and W. E.s property was severely damaged luckily he was insured. However by 1917 the tide had turned against William Henebry and one of his White St properties was foreclosed on. Then in 1918 came the onset of prohibition. By 1920 the country was dry. It appears Henebry and others tried to make a go of business turning their saloons into juice bars but by 1920 they had all gone out of business. Times must have been tough for Henebry. As was stated earlier an injunction was brought against W. E. Henebry. James S. Higgins of Columbia Market Inc an insurance and real estate firm won a court case against William for 93 dollars William couldnt pay and a lien was put on his McDermott St property. In 1924 the paper trail ends. It appears William and Annie simple disappeared. All thats left of W. E. Henebrys existence in Danbury are the bottles we find 100 plus years later. Pictured: three William E. Henebry whiskey flasks ca 1900.

I think i'm the only one with a Henebry that is embossed in script and that looks more like a medicine than a whiskey flask.
Perhaps Mr. Henebry was doing more than whiskey? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bottles embossing reads W.E Henebry Danbury, Conn

History https://danburybottle.wordpress.com/2002/07/29/w-e-henebry-danury-conn/


More about the man:

Land records and city directories paint an incomplete picture of W.E. Henebreys life in Danbury. But we know this much: at his height W. E. had land and money but by the early 1920s  William and his wife, Annie, couldnt pay a 93 dollar debit and a lien was brought against their house. Though incomplete, we  know this much about W. E.s life: W. E. kept  saloons at 13 White St in 1885 and 21 White St in 1888.  In 1890 he ran saloons at 290 and 292 Main St.  In addition to moving businesses often in those early days, W. E.s home addresses varied. From 1885 to 1901 William Henebry moved at least five times.  However, by 1902 William had set down roots.  He leased a saloon at 194 Main St (the business was open at that address for years) and bought a house on McDermott St in Danbury.  Business was good at the turn of the century for W. E.  He owned several properties in Danbury at least two on White St. One property, number 19 White St, he leased to the Foley Bros, William and John, two well know Danbury bottlers. In 1912 a fire broke out in the Foley Bros saloon and W. E.s property was severely damaged   luckily he was insured. However by 1917 the tide had turned against William Henebry and one of his White St properties was foreclosed on. Then in 1918 came the onset of prohibition. By 1920 the country was dry. It appears Henebry and others tried to make a go of business turning their saloons into juice bars but by 1920 they had all gone out of business. Times must have been tough for Henebry. As was stated earlier an injunction was brought against W. E. Henebry. James S. Higgins of  Columbia Market Inc an insurance and real estate firm won a court case against William for 93 dollars William couldnt pay and a lien was put on his McDermott St property. In 1924 the paper trail ends. It appears William and Annie simple disappeared. All thats left of  W. E. Henebrys existence in Danbury are the bottles we find 100 plus years later. Pictured: three William E. Henebry whiskey flasks ca 1900.


I think i'm the only one with a Henebry that is embossed in script and that looks more like a medicine than a whiskey flask.

Perhaps Mr. Henebry was doing more than whiskey? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found a huge dig site, if your local to Connecticut come dig with me and unearth our local history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please use our bottle identification thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Buchla Music Easel

This synth is so far out there, you guys see that slot in the upper left corner?...

That slot is for a pin board that acts like a musical generator and it's fully customizable just by changing the resistor placement or just run your fingers on the back of the circuit board to make new connections ......it's a crazy far out idea and i love it.

Here is a link https://youtu.be/5JI0LzjvjjI?t=5m30s

Here are some links to some really pretty pads  

https://youtu.be/FlzbComjbJw?t=1m5s

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bMSDfkeZVrQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very clean production, this was blended extremely well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this guy is genuine and I think he is, the best response will be no public response from both parties....if you catch my drift.

If Ethan agrees out in the open he will be inundated with requests.

   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Guarino - 1216 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> writhe - Black Velvet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 21:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This poor lady snapped https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r26vYCwKOXQ.

Here is sorta a time line of everything she lost http://ink361.com/app/users/ig-577001325/twistedelegance80/photos.

She most likely has a mental illness that has got progressively worse over time.

  





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was this pic taken from a video? If so perhaps we can see it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump sounds more presidential, yet stays a populist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 13:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea that is amazing, before the gofundme he was seen trying to sell an old boat...now he wants to give his money to h3h3.

If I were Hugh Mungus I'd be paying off all my bills etc.  This guy wants to give it all back.....Wow.

I'm betting he has always been like this. It might be an interesting story to go to the town were he lives and interview the locals and see what they say about him.

Dude must have had a hard life to be able to have that much empathy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Faex Optim-Bias Noise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reflections #1 - Klangriket (United Audio Emirates Remix) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  14-month old

For fucks sake!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The dude is surfing

On a tsunami of Bullshit! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree this is an awesome tune /u/SanctifiedExcrement keep up the good work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   they have always excelled at pulling together and acting in unison when they need to.

It's going to be hard, not only has Trump re branded the right he has also soured there credibility.

The stain left by Trump is going to take a long time for both parties wash away.

Politics as usual has left us with the tail wagging the dog.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both parties are in crisis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Perez is elected leader of a party in crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 12:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you, I do believe Bill is very passionate about spreading the truth and i think it plays into his frustrations when dealing with these climate denier's.

Without aggressive skeptics Bill's message is very clear,however,faced with aggressive skepticism he seems to rattled to convey his point/fact.

I can't fault him really, I'd be frustrated too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 12:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or a Vlog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 22:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one uses 4 bikes welded together  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9VbX_cLEumQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is another tour https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P5lQ9DCXIbs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a microkorg for the synth parts.

Everything that I do is incredibly simple, I just play in real time using my MicroKorg over beats that are made for me, sampled from jazz tunes, or none at all.

This little jam I did a lot of knob twisting to get that LFO warble effect, My fingers actually hurt after recording this one.

Audacisy is my DAW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World Record Progression: Super Metroid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 13:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baltimore Horror Story : Abandoned Dog Fighting Crack House  amp; Scary Westside Brewery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dangerous Abandoned Baltimore : Hidden Trap House Mansion + Decaying Monroe Street YMCA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reporter Gets Marijuana Prescription And Pot In Minutes Without Leaving His Couch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is remodelling the right </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It reminds me of marble madness http://i.imgur.com/gKePk0e.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Killdozer Helicopter News Footage

https://youtu.be/PZbG9i1oGPA
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Destroyed In Seconds - Marvin John Heemeyer's Killdozer -- https://youtu.be/5zRsmcIaB1Q
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
_________________________________________________________________________________
In June 2004, Marvin Heeymeyer destroyed several businesses in Granby Colorado by driving a bullddozer through the town destroying several businesses and government offices. He was upset due to his considered mistreatment by city officials. 

This documentary was created from broadcasted news services. Close by towns include Winter Park and Grand Lake.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yJcB1_EogXc


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice job OP's  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea it was going to happen anyway, after he took that last sip of the liquor his body noped the fuck out...dude got rekt.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really cool idea....It just happens to sound awful.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/employable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! 

I'm near Danbury shoot me a pm, perhaps we can meet up and start working on something.

I'm new to CT so I'm looking to start this spring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd like to start teaching those who are interested in bottle digging how to do it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would really like to start a mentor program to teach those who are interested, how to dig.

I'm reaching out to both fellow diggers and newbies alike to help me set up a program to match those looking to learn the craft with those that have experience and knowledge.

To get the ball rolling i will volunteer my time to mentor (those who are seriously interested) for the lower part of NY and most parts of CT.

If you are a experienced digger and would like to join our mentor program message the the mods so we can assign you a flair so that others can contact you. 

What i'd like too see /r/BottleDigging become is a place of education where the main body of this sub will share everything you need to know about bottle digging, shared stories, dig sites,videos, and everything else related to the craft.

So what do you think guys and gals? 

Iv'e been thinking about this idea for a while and i'd love to hear your feedback. 

I have not thought everything through as of yet so consider this a feeler to see if there is any interest in such an ambitious program. 

Leave your comments below 
 



  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moth Radio Hour: Live From the World Science Festival </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The behind the scenes was pretty interesting.

https://youtu.be/9cbKpCsd2pk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This song is "terribly" accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bottle Identification Thread, Post your bottle inquiries and questions here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This will now be the place to ask about bottle identification and any other questions you may have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Rusty Machine by The Fade Beta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 15:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Matthew Yglesias from Vox said..

"When Blatantly false information is given from the White House it's  basically propaganda"

Lets call this "rally" it for what it is (PROPAGANDA!)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 14:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The media shouldn't televise the rally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 13:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the end of the day he writes for a low brow tabloid, the sad part is there are people who take it seriously.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My biggest poop was over a foot and three inches long, I was actually proud of my accomplishment so I left it in the bowl to shock my wife. Waiting in anticipation to see her jaw agape as she stumbled on my massive log.

The time came when it was her turn too use the bathroom, I stood outside the door like a giddy school boy waiting to hear a scream yet nothing happened.

Perplexed i ask "you didn't see it honey?" she replied "see what that you shat on the toilet seat?"

It was right then my dog came over to lick me, her breath reeking of shit "my shit!...That's when i realized my dog had stolen my glory and filled her belly with my enormous tube steak. 

Sad day indeed : ( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 13:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The fact that Fox news is reporting on this really speaks to the severity of the situation.

I hope Fox news keeps it up they owe it to the American people, especially the ones who get there sources from these outlets.

The majority people who voted for him use our social welfare systems and really latched onto a President that seemingly had there interests at heart.

The truth is Trump wants to gut welfare, gut the affordable health care act etc.

He has no thought out plan for anything other then to bring in his agenda.

Trump can sign travel bans and gut social programs,however, I doubt he will do anything that will be really thought out and that will benefit the people who voted for him.

This is why he decided that those issues (health care, welfare) are to be addressed last and most likely never.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
"They don't because they don't have the resources to do anything until some poor little kid gets run over" --can you elaborate?

Just curious.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let us not forget the time line back when Mr Trump was president elect and i quote "They have sanctions on Russia  lets see if we can make some good deals with Russia," the Republican president-elect was quoted as saying by The Times.
How unusual that one of the first things he wanted to do was release sanctions on Russia, I thought it waa bizarre then, how do you feel now knowing the connection Michael Flynn had with Russian officials? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think this sucks, my only advice is to let your track breath a little EG~ let the beat weave in and out over the main melody line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like Moe's Tavern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the most logical comment, I had bad friends growing up just to have fiends and they did things i didn't have the balls to do ...so i would not be surprised if blue shirt didn't do anything but hang out with Mohawk.

We can tell Mohawk doesn't come from the most stellar of families Eg~ Letting your kid look like a punk/ actually letting him, given his prior offences it would be fitting to curtail that image/ideology. 

Mohawk i think gets abused and is neglected by parents that are ill equipped to promote healthier outlets for their child.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last Week Tonight with John Oliver </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An old fun tune using the Poly 61 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cohesion - Farcaster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 13:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 people got mauled by this owner sending her dog to attack, it was 100% premeditated, In the video she clearly warns the animal control lady "leave now or your going to get bit" 

That bitch sentenced her dog to death and caused bodily harm, two adults and a child 6 months is a fucking joke.

What pisses me off even more is her denial of her wrongs "the door was open the dog just ran out" Bitch just a minute ago you said your dog was going to bite.

This cunt should never have a dog again and she should have got 12 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry I meant to say Watermelon...Scratch that. I meant Fried Chicken....Fuck!...You know what i'm sorry do you wanna smoke a blunt?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help]I am trying to find more information about dog treats that have been killing dogs(source in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to know if anybody has had any issues with dog treats Eg~ are you or anybody you know lost a dog to these treats coming out of China?

Link 1 - http://www.petfoodindustry.com/articles/5822-fda-update-jerky-treats-sickened-6200-dogs-killed-1140

Link 2 - http://www.poisonedpets.com/alert-vets-warn-about-new-treats-from-china-poisoning-dogs/

Help me out on my research anything you can add will be greatly appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tree Fails and Idiots with Chainsaws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From source:

This educational video taken with a dash cam 29 December 2014 at approximately 2.15pm shows the results of a strip wind storm on a small country highway in central Victoria. The windstorm weaved its way up the Watt's River valley before creating havoc at the Watt's River bridge.
This is a great educational video showing the dangers of traveling in the bush during periods of high wind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds logical </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What your going to find on the surface is just the newest stuff ...the oldest stuff is going to be at the bottom of the dump site.

What you will want to do is dig down till all your getting is pure sod.

A good bit of advice was given to me by an old digger "dig down till you no longer find any remnants of human civilization"  

Once you have dug down sufficiently  move outward in concentric circles this i find is the best method because you cover more area in a shorter amount of time and you will have more freedom to move around.


* Things you will need and techniques 

1- Obviously a shovel (Tip) never use a square shovel always use a spade preferably one with a short handle, a long handled shovel will get in your way in tight spaces.

2- Get your self an Aluminum Hand Cultivator http://imgur.com/a/ZnjeS  (Tip) make sure it's aluminum as steel will scratch the glass. This will be used to  excavate small sections of dirt around the bottles when you find them, this gets the bottle loose so you can pull it out.

3- A 2 foot section of a broom handle or something like it, Some of the smaller bottles are very fragile so when you find these scrape the dirt around it with the stick so you don't scratch it or break it.

4- A bucket and news paper, when you have setteled on what you want to take home your going to want to wrap the good ones in news paper so they wont shatter when traveling home.

5- GLOVES very important after all your digging in broken glass.

Other things to follow, [listen to your shovel] when your digging keep your ears open for a squeak sound... as soon as you hear that stop and use your stick or Hand Cultivator to gently remove the dirt around it.

Always throw your dirt and debris down hill away from you the last thing you want is to re-shovel or have a collapse.

Hope this helps 


Edit- One more thing keep what you like as in don't go on monetary value a lot of what your going to unearth are part of your local history and whilst they might not sell for much you now have something historic ....that's what bottle digging is all about.

It's the story of the bottle that is valuable not the worth in dollar and cents.

Hope this helps  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 13:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are good jokes, thanks OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the arpeggiator (which is excellent)

Hell yea it is, I didn't know it at the time being that was my first analog synth but that arp is amazing and the bender is fucking great too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good sounding board....my only problem with it is using those god damn buttons to do everything.

That said the poly 61 makes beautiful sounds and the arpeggiator is one of the best i have ever used.... as a matter of fact that arpeggiator is worth having even if you use it for nothing else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 00:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O my how the republican party has changed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunset Eclipse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd actually want too see this more than the film it's promoting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you make your misic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is awesome...you should have your own sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A track I made this morning called "You Never Get It Back Do You" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This Boards of Canada "Dayvan Cowboy" COVER - BEHIND THE SCENES is excellent and very informative.

https://youtu.be/YSf8Rtx-Nfc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would lessen the delay on the kalimba, it over shadows the entire track.

Good job though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An old bullet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This will dull your chain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post this to /r/McDonaldland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 22:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will redo the bass line and do everything else you said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bass line sucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made something this morning that i think sounds pretty cool. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 16:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Henry Rollins goes full douche mode on a kid trying to interview him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 14:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 12:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The key to the escape pod because i'm a damn coward.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A kind of Bochum Welt sounding sketch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fake cop gets arrested on the south side of Yonkers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 13:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 12:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can  go for up to 3 1/2 years without any food intake whatsoever. During this time period it behaves much like an estivating fish in that it buries itself in the mud and does not move until more favorable conditions occur.

Wow up to 3 1/2 years without any food that's impressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Moth Radio Hour: Leaving, Loving   Coming Home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Casino Versus Japan ~ It's Very Sunny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> paramnesic - Sometimes I Feel by </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked the vid, dude was teetering on a huge fail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Milieu RemixSarin Sunday Mix. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 15:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, that entire album is really good.

Ten   Tracer is very underrated, his album "an hour brighter" is one of the best tributes to BoC I've ever heard. 


  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bochum Welt -- Laurel Canyon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ten and Tracer - Cine Fil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Milieu - Autumn Fog Lifts [Yearbook Version] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 02:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 03:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so powerful,I'm at a loss for words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 18:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You preform them completely live?"

Basically yea, I set a metronome and just play,however my 2 latest tracks are a colab with myself and producer WLFWRK.

All my other works are just played/recorded in real time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me spend a day there enjoying your creation : ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are kinda stale but here ya go https://soundcloud.com/user-345283577 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea i see you got downvoted not sure why, i love different creative works such as this.

My style is very different so perhaps that's why i can appreciate it.

nice delicate track and all your other stuff too loving the guitar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is great, keep it up OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss my psr280 what a great little board that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup learning how to play with others will make anybody a better player...it takes you out of your comfort zone and you learn techniques you hadn't thought about before.

I remember when i got my first decent synth i thought "wow this is the best stuff i have ever made" now i laugh.

That's the good part through because you can see your getting better, never give up and practice every day and you will be surprised at how good you'll get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting there myself,however, i'm always finding new tricks with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Highland Park 12 used to be a awesome decently priced scotch.

It's still good just saying too bad you weren't drinking scotch 20+ years ago the shit was the bee's knees.

     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This track i made could be good for an adventure video game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has a BoC vibe, I absolutely love this you should post this on my sub /r/SoundsLikeBoC  I think fans of the genre will really love it.

I'd really like those layers, awesome track! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> User name checks out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> History doesn't repeat itself but it often rhymes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 13:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude that sucks, I'd be heart broken, Having your instruments stolen is worse than anything.. especially if you don't have the money to replace them.

I wish i had something i could donate or lend you but i recently got ripped off myself....anyway if your near the east coast pm me maybe i can help. 
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Won't it over cook the veggies?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thing is that will over cook the gravy...so i guess i will simmer them in beef broth and then add to the gravy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
