<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3605</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have some sort of cut or injury or something somewhere near my coccyx. Does anyone know what it could be? I'll do the best I can do to describe it bellow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 08:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, take the fact that I believe my injury is near the coccyx with a grain of salt because that's only a very rough guess. So, this will sound crude but I think it might be the best way to describe it. This cut or injury is closer to the top of my butt crack. Imagine it as somewhere between my back and my butt but it's inside of me. Not inside inside, it's outside of the errrrr...hole but closer to the top. 
It bleeds, but never hurts. It might itch if I say put toilet paper to try and staunch the bleeding but no pain. It's actually been going on for a while (1 Year to a maximum of two) but the normal doctors I go to don't really have any good idea what it is aside from a cut. I have been prescribed steroid cream and that seemed to work but due to me forgetting at times to put it in regularly it hasn't been effective (my fault). 
Recently, I've felt that it feels that this "cut" has turned into some sort of groove, and there's this little bump along it that feels sort of like a sack that I believe could be filled with pus. Again, just a theory. Any idea what this is? And I know it sounds gross, but I'am a clean person but money is tight and going to the doctors every time does get expensive but I'm getting worried it could turn into something more serious. 
Age: 17 
Sex: Male 
Hispanic 
USA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 16:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for all of your response, this has been informative and has scratched that annoying itch in my brain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 05:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! This was actually a real eye opener and a well thought out response. Thank you, good sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How successful was denazification towards Hitler Youths? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 23:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always had a fascination with it but despite all the research I could do online it's pretty vague and doesn't go so much into how successful Allied psychologist and denazification was towards the, essentially radicalized youths. 
I did read somewhere that they even had their own groups which attacked and harassed the occupied forces. I want to know how successful it was towards them, if it even worked, and what happened to this that simply refused to retract their beliefs. 
Some were shown the war crimes committed in the hope that it would shock them out of it but was anything else done? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How successful was denazification towards Hitler Youths? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best DMR and DMR loadout in Battlefield 4? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 07:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just think there are so many but I don't know which one is the best, right now I like the RFB but perhaps there are better ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 17:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! This is it! Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know the song used in this trailer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 16:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know the song used in Ready or Not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 16:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=Gd139Nin33M 
I just need to know the song! Please! It's so beautiful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 08:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I scrolled far too far to find this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try asking r/books they might be able to help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cab I, in theory, surrender my country to an opposing country? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say I surrender England to Germany. 
Follow-up: If that's possible can I surrender my units to them?
*can </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was! Thank you so much! It was driving me mad!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need help in finding a recent Reddit post... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was this post about Macron and Le Pen where Macron was an actually macaron and Le Pen was, well, a pen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] "He waited and waited, for one year, ten years, a hundred years. He begged and pleaded for a decision. Finally he couldnt bear the waiting any longer. Then they said to him: What do you think youre waiting for? Youve been in Hell for a long time already." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
