<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1989</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are 2 keys to success </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never tell them everything you know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://uk.news.yahoo.com/congressman-call-impeachment-donald-trump-afternoon-133517195.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting and inspiring but just for the sake of spirited debate, [here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nzj7Wg4DAbs t=22s) is a Ted Talk that speaks to why people shouldn't aim to be ants.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do relatives call relatives in-law? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 17:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Linked is the CGP grey video that wonderfully explains family trees and cousins but doesn't explain something about in-laws that I have always wondered. He mentions that if I marry someone, I am sort of a pseudo family member who is equal to the spouse on the family tree only everyone on their tree gets the in law suffix from my perspective. My question is, then, what in the world do people on my family tree call the people on the spouse's family tree? What are my parents to their parents? What are my cousins to my spouse's cousins? What are my grandparent to their third cousins twice removed? Is there a name for that relationship that can shortcut through having to say 'my ____'s ______ in law' or '____ through marriage'??

 https://youtu.be/PM79Epw_cp8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do smokers get cottonmouth from smoking? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 10:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 06:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My shitty computer lied and told me this was in r/gifs for some reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you call the show that would be you and your friend's witty banter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But like, what else do we even think we know? Not even just about Yoda (or Yaddle) biography, but of how that all plays into the story at large?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/birdswitharms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 01:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that was my understanding of it all except Yaddle is new to me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Star Wars] What kinds of theories are out there concerning Yoda? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 00:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that his origin story is shrouded in mystery but I also haven't heard as many fan theories as you'd expect such a prolific character as Yoda to (not) have in his gravity. What's the deal? What do I not know?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 23:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does vanity have a name? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors that switch from android to iphone or the other way around, what has your experience been, for better or worse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 18:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 10:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. Example well landed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 10:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well okay. So one friend may or may not drink a lot but birthday boy's tab is on me. I know what we're getting because he explicitly divulged all of his favorite whiskeys to me  (but unbeknownst to him is this trip itself so ssshhh) and I think I'll call MWL tomorrow to see what's on his list that is also on their menu.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 09:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So cheap, being a relative term clearly, is $30. That's what I was looking for. hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much can I expect to spend at the Multnomah Whiskey Library? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 09:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a friend with a birthday right around the corner and I want to take him to the MWL. Maybe buy some Hall passes to avoid the line but once inside, how much can I expect to splurge on 2 or 3 people?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If i were to retroactively start collecting a single particular thing that all the organizations I've been affiliated with have put their logo on, what would be my best bet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 08:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pins? Pens? Shirts? Key chains? laptop stickers? Mugs? Lanyards? Drink Cozies? Stress balls?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do androgynous people know or care about how androgynous they appear? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 08:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the apologies in the world if this comes off as insensitive or ignorant or bad in anyway. It's just honest curiosity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 07:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like your flair.   

#YouAreNowBlinkingAndSwallowingMantuallyToo   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 07:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I respect going for the strike-through edit over deleting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are neurotransmitters liquid at room temperature? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 05:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: Or body temperature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 05:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well let's start with exocrine glands. (credit to u/uncutRVAguy1985 for putting a word on it for me)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are the diseases that have been trapped under ice in something that's been dead for thousands of years not dead themselves? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 05:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [source](http://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/deadly-diseases-hidden-ice-sparks-10361230) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help with some light forensic analysis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 05:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firstly, this isn't for any legal issue. I say forensic analysis because I don't know what else to call it but the tutorials I've found online all go into federal law and what is admissible in court. This is an academic exercise and I am looking for a starting point(s), not a full blown legal defense.   


I don't have local logs of work done through an online content provider but I need either that or the next best thing that can irrefutably demonstrate the work completed. What kinds of things should I be looking up besides internet search history?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And so in recognition of the president whose hands will go down in history as the largest of any president's before him, we are pleased to announce that this library's encyclopedias are not split into volumes, but rather bound together - one spine for the entire anthology."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I set up tags in a way that I can filter posts by those tags? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good example of this would be the flair categories on the sidebar in r/explainlikeimfive  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Whats with all the different kinds of bodily fluid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is intentionally as vague as I think I can get away with. I've always been curious about how/why our body can produce so many things. Urine, sweat, tears, blood, mucus to name a few - and that's not even going into the endocrine system or the neurotransmitters (which I only assume are liquids). I understand that each one has a purpose that is well served, but I just find it intriguing and I want to learn about it. Not to the extent of going to medical school, but just something to satisfy my curiosity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> strange signs that the end is nigh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I will be living in a fraternity next year. Any suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 23:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never done communal living before. I moved from my parent's place to a 3 bedroom mouse with two roommates. I never lived in a dorm because I took care of enough credits at community college to blow past freshman status and the requirement to live on campus my first year. I'm looking for advice from my fellow Greek life redditors. What should I definitely have on my packing list or shopping list?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: If DNA is the genetic code in all cells, then how are different types of cells able to form? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 23:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A webpage that lets you customize what list of search bars you want all in one consolidated page. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 22:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I.e. - Google, Reddit, Amazon, or anything else for that matter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rejected titles for popular Disney movies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 21:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you want to put on Reddit but haven't yet because you haven't been given the opportunity to hide it in the comments of an unrelated post yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do hot foods and beverages seem to cool down past room temperature and are cold to the touch but cold foods and beverages appear warmer than ambient temperature after a given amount of time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad times for deja vu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before posting here, be sure you've read the submission guidelines and FAQ. We require that all sarcastic comments start with "[TOMT]". Please review the guidelines and if you feel your post is appropriate, resubmit with "[TOMT]" at the start of your title. Thanks.

I am a bot, and this action was performed automatically. Please contact the moderators of this subreddit if you have any questions or concerns.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] What's it called when soemone, right or wrong, is.very opinionated about a lot of things and liked to stick to their guns? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. His hobby is clearly knives and he clearly sustains it by offing the other big expense item in his life. Sorry doggo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Safety First] Besides the obvious, how do I guard myself against disease? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Besides the obvious, how do I guard myself from disease? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Besides the obvious, how do I guard myself from disease? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sexy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for being vague with the info I'm giving you to help me with but  It's a juggling act between school, work, extracurricular activites, and a personal life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you hear 'Don't try this at home' and call their bluff. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that helps on the mental fortitude front but not with time management. I'm not one to back out of obligations so prioritization is definitely a long term game. But how do I manage my TIME and ENERGY the same way I'm trying to manage my schedule?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's definitely swimming in tasks. So many that putting it all on paper (either a planner or calrndar) takes so much rearranging and planning that it's a full task in and of itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are so many things going on in my life that the biggest wastes of time are now simply organizing and transporting myself. How do I change that? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which of the following are the best text editor for what I need? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 09:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of the following list of programs available to me, I'm looking for the best text editor-esque features that can work with screenshoted material and preserve font, size, color, etc. I want to basically copy/paste and edit text. (I have access to photoshop but it would be difficult so if there is another way to do it from the app suite on my local machine, that would be preferable. )

Adobe Acrobat     
GIMP   
Cannon Picture Style Editor     
Microsoft Office 2010     
MS Paint    
    
Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats the big deal with Mason jars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sauce? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Kids being made to make their own pizza is kinda taking it too far, doncha think?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE have clothes in their closet that they, after all these years, you are still waiting to grow into? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] The name of the 19th (or maybe 20th) century science fiction writer that ended up being very prophetic and predictive in his description of technological advances. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TOMT: The name of the sci fi witer from the 19th century that ended up being as/more than prophetic than Nostrodamous. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pearson Education </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If we were better at keeping track of all the little things our bodies do that we just pass off as quirks, we would at a minimum be a little healthier and more self aware, but at a maximum, potentially revolutionize medicine's understanding of the human body. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I talked to the head of the actuarial sciences department at my university about a career in the field. The material is basically statistics but the job description is basically economics with a fine-toothed comb. If you don't plan on working in the insurance industry, don't worry about a degree in actuarial sciences. According to the prof. I talked to, even a minor can send the signal to an employer that you only wanted to go into it and didn't so 'settled' for something else.  

Edit: And if you do wanna work in this field, being in the East coast helps because that's where all the inurance companies are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is also a good interviewer. Lol. I've got a new favorite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/ELI5 and flair it a biology question. Duh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a part time job but I live in a college town and all the documentation [bills, pay stubs, bank statements] lives with my parents. I have control insofar as the choices I make but the only documents I have to help me start budgeting are shoe boxes full of receipt paper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any good reading material you can recommend and link?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After every flight, FedEx pilots fill out a form known as a gripe sheet to tell mechanics about problems with the aircraft. The mechanics fix the problems (P) and document the solutions (S). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too real. In my retelling of the story of the night that went all night, I always leave out the snack and bathroom breaks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen that infographic before but it even assumes that you are in control of your own finances, which I am not. I'm asking about what to do above that starting point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What steps do I need to start taking to begin to understand and manage my own financial situation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> File this under the NoStupidQuestions category. I thought of taking this question to that sub first but would ultimately end up here anyway. 

So, without further ado. I'm a college student, dependent on my parents, and work part time. I want to start saving, budgeting, investing, and simply knowing the numbers I need to know but am lost as to the first steps I should be taking. I've never checked my credit score before but know that I can/should something like twice a year, I have expenses that I should be tracking, etc. What should I be doing and what kinds of things should I be asking my parents about?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What version(s), if any, of a fit bit also double as a bluetooth notification dongle for your phone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the stickers that I've seen were there in the off season too. Lol. May be but i guess i will go ahead and ask the local Hillel chapter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But then the minors on the internet that totally pay attention to age restrictions won't be able to see gore and porn at the same time, removing the incentive for them to stay away from it, and normalizing the sex. Bad internet! Tsk tsk tsk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could work if you just opened up a background popup with the website you want to appear in the history, yeah, that would work. 

I'm sorry but ELI5 please? How would I go about opening a background popup?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Repost from the Archive] Can anyone speak to or expand upon the top two comments? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That guitar is really sexy and the both of them together - goddamn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A movie where the (main?) antagonist has an office with his net worth accumulating in real time on a board behind his desk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a live action movie but I can't remember much else. Someone's daughter might have been involved with the plot somehow. And by board, I mean the electric kind with block lettering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have the opposite problem from the person in the link where I am trying to generate a search history. How do I populate and backdate search history? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NoStupidQuestions: What's the meaning of the rainbow star of David? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen one on Monroe and another stuck inside the elevator doors in Valley and I've always wondered what they were about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do governments care so much about certain industries? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not asking this with any sort of political bias (or at least none that I can see), but sheer curiosity. For example, the agricultural economy in the United States is heavily subsidized, the transportation industry is heavily regulated (especially air travel), and companies that work with the department of defense almost do so exclusively, leaving no room for say, per example, Lockheed Martin to manufacture consumer grade products. What is so special about these and other industries that governments keep them so close to their chests? Is there any general macroeconomic principle that applies broadly to all of these examples or did we just come to the status quo on a case-by-case basis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do governments care so much about certain industries? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If smell is a chemical reaction betweenyou and the particles that something gives off, then how can something continue to smell for a really long time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would think that either said thing would run out of smelly molecules or that you would get permanently 'nose blindness' to it from overexposure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your least favorite thing about your favorite thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When do you pronounce 'the' as "thee' instead of 'thu'? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 09:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read 'Paris Hilton effect' and immediately thought. "Huh. I know that Paris is a cultural hub but what does a hotel chain in France have to do with - oooh. Nevermind." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts on a movie character </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nightcrawler: its a movie starring Jake Gyllenhaal that came out in 2014. He plays a crazy person who is carving a place out for himself in the news world. Every time he was monologue-ing or dialogue-ing, I couldn't help but think "Man, this guy is crazy but what he's saying doesn't actually seem too far off base." Has anyone else seen the movie? Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is an unusual thing you have expertise in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of these things is not like the other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a niiiiiiice boulder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you'll see that I took a sebatical on the other side of the country. If you'd like tit take a minute and sit alright there, I'll tell you how I became the Prince of a town called Bel--Air. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dating profile bios that are garuanteed to be a good conversation starter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And now, performing her cover of Slayer's best, put your hands together for Ke$haaaaaa!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ladies and gentlemen, I swear, the rest of the rabbit is somewhere." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Jamie! Hold your hand in front of your face! I wanna know if you have cancer or not!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Yeah. I'm all about the Bengamins. Why?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Yes, I'm your 'doctor' and yes, I graduated with a degree in 'medicine'. What seems to be the problem today? ...... Ah, yes. Cold like symptoms. Now if you could just bend over, this won't hurt a bit. "   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the thing I needed to hear. All this talk in the comments about how people think I actally wants to fuck her and am struggling to restrain myself are way off base. My friend and I respect each other and I need to make sure he know he has enough of my respect to set those boundaries. Maybe over a beer or two.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone is giving me the benefit of the doubt here. Lol. Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if the animals that are comfortable hanging out by the road side are only the animals that haven't seen a driver veer off the road and cause an accident yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 03:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder how many people in my life are moderators. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Okay Reddit, what is your favorite predatory animal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How easy/difficult would it be for a professional chef to reverse engineer recipes that they don't have, only given the final product? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A guide that made it on the front page a long time ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It had to do with different hair products and the amount of hold and shine of each one. I have searched all the relevant subs like r/coolguides and such but can't seem to find it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite pen that is also something else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 06:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think laser pointer, USB thumb drive, flashlight, or even the novelty-esque items like whiteout pens. I'm looking for variety.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 10:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ELI5 please? It was jamming with the brass as well. And the steel cases weren't the ones that were seeing the projectile actually buckle into the case.   

[Also, on the vodka comment](https://www.reddit.com/r/guns/comments/62jlc4/troubleshooting_an_ak47/dfn4uto/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 10:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No kit. And no, I don't handle guns under the influence. But I did, however, throw it in the sand, then in the mud, call it a bad boy, establish a safe-word, and then proceeded to kick and otherwise abuse it until I realized I forgot my lube at home. Ya know, all things considered, it might have been camera shy and that's why I couldn't get it to perform.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went shot for shot with the rifle but considering the chronic jamming issues, that actually was a reasonable pace.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metal mags. I went back and forth between brass and steel fmj. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> troubleshooting an AK-47 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My AK is not new but saw it's first range day and we ran into some issues. Not only will it not feed rounds, but after ejecting the jam, the next round after that gets pushed into the case about a full quarter inch. I ended up tossing the stubby bullets but the fact that that was so replicable is really concerning. We lubed and greased it up but that didn't change anything. Any ideas? Is this a home fix or do I need to take it to a shop?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny because I got him mixed up with Kim Il-Sung and was like 'Kim Kim Kim Kim Kim.... I dont get it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The way you pronounce 'tomato', 'Caribbean', and 'caramel', says a lot more about you than how you pronounce 'gyro'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [General] What project names (and the universes they exist in) are worth knowing about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is the last sip of beer always the worst? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And not in a bitter-sweet 'I'm sad that I don't have any more beer' kind of way, but in an 'It actually tastes a little worse than the rest of the beer and I have no idea how or why' kind of way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who, in the entertainment industry (singer, actor, director, etc.) has a collection of work both small enough that it's possible to and good enough that it's worth going through entirely in one day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the copypasta from u/JumboJellybean's response to the version of this same post that only got taken down because of the absent ELI5 at the beginning but I wanna see this post outlive that one and hopefully cast this net wide enough to collect more information. 


Edit: [Here we are](https://www.reddit.com/r/explainlikeimfive/comments/629tsu/how_does_it_work_out_that_blue_and_red_are_both/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jason Padgett, a man with Acquired Savant Syndrome, is able to free-hand these beautiful fractals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How does it work out that blue and red are both primary colors of light and pigment but yellow is the third primary pigment color and green is the third primary color of light? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We should be able to 'follow' other redditors. Exactly how social media platforms are able to segregate friends from prolific figures that a lot of people like to follow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does it work out that blue and red are both primary colors of light and pigment but yellow is the third primary pigment color and green is the third primary color of light? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jason Padgett, a man with Acquired Savant Syndrome, is able to free-hand these beautiful fractals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you choose to handle customer support to get what you want? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My best friend's girlfriend considers me her best friend as well. How do I make SURE he knows I don't plan on making a move on her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 10:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) No two of us have a problem being open with each other.  

2) It's no secret that she is pretty.  

3) I'm single.

Edit: I only ask because it's been brought up before. (Only casually, over some wine, and between the three of us actually.) There is no feels or scheming or anything going on on my end, but my friend is the puppy-with-wolves-claws type. He trusts me and I'm coming at this from the angle of wanting to put my friend's mind at ease, not from the angle of wanting to get away with anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "K. They said 30 minutes or less sooo." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Fresh Prince of Bel-Air theme plays* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When having your twin stand in for you didn't work out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Welcome to the SS Oh Shit." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Sir. Of all the movies in the world, I'd really appreciate it if you could choose to watch something other than Snakes on a Plane" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "K. the orifice is kind of ugly and the inside isn't textured but it's as close as we can get to the real thing down here." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your boss is a reasonable person, then it makes sense to me that they would understand (if you should choose to tell them) that you don't want to be relied upon, and that you only want to disclose the information for information sake. 

 I don't want to be known as the guy with the gun. I also would not want them to depend on me if a situation were to occur. I would not want them to expect me to put myself in harms way to protect money or anything for that matter if I had the option to get to safety. My primary goal is to survive and my gun is my tool to escape danger.  
 Tell your boss something like this... maybe exactly this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dudley Dursley: A Very Harry Potter Movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "There is absolutely nothing wrong with this Bentley. We promise." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I killed Mufasaaaa" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oh my God. There are *actually* 30 Kids Bops. No. I'm serious. Check it out right now!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pirates of the Caribbean: the curse of Jonny Depp's Visa bill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shark tank pitches that didn't make the final cut of the show. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your thoughts on the idea of (or the people who are) treating the dating game like a numbers game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your thoughts on the idea of (or the people who are) treating the dating game like a numbers game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Because every picture can be translated from a string of binary RGB values into ASCII characters, it doesn't actually take much to claim that a picture is worth a thousand words - a thousand real and coherent words though - that's a different story. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "For the love of God Ryan, stop trying to hide behind telephone poles." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Some grammar Nazis told me about a seminar they are going to attend about cause and effect.*


"They're there to affect its effect and it's there for their two affects too." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry hun but we don't serve your kind here. The sign clearly says that if your VIN number starts with either an odd number or a letter in the second half of the alphabet, you are going to have to be served across the street.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your Pearson horror stories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a genuine question for the Fox News loyalists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a genuine question for the Fox News loyalists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2 questions that are both part chemistry and part combinatorics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) Hearkening back to my chemistry classroom, I remember learning about ions and isotopes in isolation of one another. But what about ions that are ALSO isotopes? Is there simply no significance there worth discussing or do we just brush over it in an intro class for simplicity sake? 

2) When it comes to the naming conventions in chemistry that allow you to build names from chemical structures and build structures from names, the possibilities seem nearly endless. Have chemists done the computations yet on ALL the possibilities? I imagine that's what the white coats that big pharma hires do all day. On the other hand, I have to wonder if any chemist since Mendeleev himself actually plotted out an organized chart and said 'This is what should be in this missing spot here.' and then we find it and pat that scientist on the back.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it safe to assume that if Gavrilo Princip never assassinated Franz Ferdinand, then we wouldn't have had either of the world wars or their direct consequences such as the Holocaust, nuclear weapons, the United Nations, the cold war era, space race, Geneva Convention, baby boomers, etc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention the smaller ones like National Biscuit Company shortening their name to Nabisco just to save on ink. This isn't a butterfly effect question. I'm wondering if there were systems, safeguards or circumstances in place that would have guaranteed things to go how they did, just with a different singular first event. What was the backup plan in case Princip failed?

Edit: Bonus for any explanation that encompasses how impactful the assassination actually was vs any other straw that *could have* broken the horse's back.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To consumers, maybe. But I'm giving the business savvy sharks and entrepreneurs the benefit of the doubt on that one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Point taken, loud and clear, but they are rarely (if ever) on the 49%-51% fence. They are usually in the 20% ballpark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My parents are immigrants from a country that doesn't exist anymore. Are genealogical services a waste of my money? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do the sharks in the shark tank groble so much over differences in equity share as small as 1%? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive noticed this a lot. I've also noticed that it doesn't tend to matter where they are sitting at. Someone, most of the time, eventually ends up compromising on 5% after one of the back-and-forth steps of the negotiations, but it's not as if the sharks are asking for controlling interest as often as they are 'enough skin in the game'. Well they are strategic partners either way. What's going on in the heads of the sharks in order to get the equity percentage that they want? I can't imagine that changes how much of their resources the entrepreneur has access to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What skeletons are Spongebob Squarepants characters hiding in their closet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Photosynthesis.   

Photosynthesis. 

Photosynthesis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Requesting a MIDI Snoo on account of the MIDI unicorn floating around out there. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe there is a maximum number of transferable credits - because at the point that you are beyond that maximum, it's as if you aren't really earning your degree from OSU anyway. If you are above that number after having accounted for the credits that don't transfer, I believe the choice is yours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please link as many newsletters and list-serves as you can think of. I'm signing a friend up for all of them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What song tells a good story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Innapropriate things to respond to with 'shoulda coulda woulda' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something that you learned in a professional setting that ought to be common sense? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] The episode of Good Eats where Alton Brown offers his definition of 'Luxury'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the sake of adding as much detail as possible - It was part of one of his skits in the show - on an episode presumably having to do with some luxurious food like caviar or something. (If I could remember what it was specifically, I wouldn't be asking, would I?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spotify Silk Sheets playlist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 12:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone else remember the Android commercial that was a bunch of unlikely pairings of animal friends? Warmed my damn heart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What word do you find exceptionally fun to say? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 07:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strange pairings of famous figures and the things that were named in their honor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 05:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But sugar isn't a contravercial one per say.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Physical activity, shmisical activity. Just put some snacks on the front of the treadmill and crank the speed up." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Grandma... I know I'm heading off to college soon, but I didn't really expect to not need to stock up on condoms myself." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet again, Pascal's triangle pops up when you least expect it. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 22:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) What is the difference between a positive and negative electrical charge? Are they related in any way to magnetic dipoles? 

2) How is that wiggling that generates an electric charge different from alternating current?  

3) If the oscillation of the electromagnetic field *IS* the electromagnetic spectrum, then where do everyday electromagnets register on the electromagnetic spectrum between radio and gamma waves? Is this oscillation the same thing that actually lets light bulbs, radio towers, x-ray machines, and infrared sensors actually do what they do?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 22:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my favorite infographic to casually bring up in conversation when someone tells me that something is bad for me. I totally get, understand, and respect that science needs to do it's own thing at it's own pace, but in the meantime, we are still human beings with lives to live and decisions to make about what (not) to put in our bodies. 

[Also....source.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0Rnq1NpHdmw t=874s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank's for the correction! I wasn't thinking at first about it being additive instead of multiplicative.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] The mathematical name for a mesh-network topology. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have an n-gon, and connect every point to every other point, What is that called? I think the total number of connecting lines ends up being (n-1)! but i'm blanking on what it's called right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What is the relationship between electricity, magnetism, and the electromagnetic spectrum? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 00:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Self-taught programmers of Reddit, how did you do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Email clients should tell you by default that the email address you entered is invalid instead of waiting after you send. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure there is a perfectly good and technical explanation for why this doesn't already exist and I'll actually welcome that explanation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ads everywhere. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm perfectly okay hearing this is the wrong sub if someone has an idea of where to point me but I had to start troubleshooting somewhere.  

K. Now for the problem at hand. I recently started getting pushed adds all the time, and it seems independent of any particular app. YouTube videos, Spotify songs, game play, and texting are all being interrupted by these pop up ads and I don't know where to start diagnosing or fixing this problem. Does anyone else  have this going on?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. Well there's your [my] problem....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know about C, just don't own any C. A micro-B port, like on my Android, looks like it would take a mini-A cable, would it not?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Errors that give away that they are using a translator app. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm more confused now than I was earlier. Micro-B and Mini-A look interchangeable. Which is which?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Story] 6 Anecdotal Lessons in Management </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What were you surprised to find after Googling yourself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 08:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Terry, stop calling it a Devil's Threesome. You have a pair of Jacks and a Queen high, that's it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What breed of dog is doge? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What all do I need to bring my idea to fruition? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 05:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to build a data visualization app for mobile that allows me to collect and present the data that data miners want (think location and the rest), but like, capture the data for myself. What all do I need to do to turn this idea into reality?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crabs must think of fish like we think of birds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *wakes up from being unconscious for 7o years* 

"Oh, I sure can't wait to see my favorite black and white things!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Statements that spark more questions than they answer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 09:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eponym was the word I was looking for! Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A word for company names that are so closely associated with their products that people often don't realize they are separate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 08:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Examples include Lego, Kleenex, Band-Aid and Styrofoam that are all trademarked product names created by individual companies instead of the product, as it should be, more generally refereed to.  (toy building blocks, facial tissue, adhesive gauze, and EPS respectively. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YankeeMarshall turned me onto these on his YouTube channel. He's a bit of a goof but knows what he's talking about when it comes to guns. I think this is his daily carry.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a 3d graphing tool I can use to plot x choose y? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Squirrels are like cigarettes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to not be able to get near them. But putting them in my mouth and lighting them on fire is still where I draw the line.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Non-automotive ways he could be overcompensating. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder how many strangers have stories of me being that random person doing that weird thing that I didn't think anyone saw. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does 100% humidity not mean that we're under water? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I know that it has more to do with how able the moisture in the air is able to condensate or something and rain = 100% humidity but thats just - so dissatisfying of an answer for whatever reason..... I always hear "100% humidity" and think of being completely, totally, 100% submerged under water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unconventional small talk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Of all the benefits there are to staying fit and working out, which one do you personally see as the biggest impact on your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A really comprehensive conspiracy theory that covers world history, geopolitics and socioeconomics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a long YouTube video. Maybe 3 hours or so. Topics include the Rothschilds, Masons, American founding fathers, and several empires.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 07:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That'll do pig. That'll do."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
