<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1772</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 08:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shamelessly stolen from: [here](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/3c/72/c2/3c72c2358e0bcb1b15ad923f3391f222.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Oh, so you like Metal? Name three blacksmiths." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 08:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Will, Jaden, and Willow." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 08:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do I find it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Health-nuts, what's your latest craze you're suggesting to people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 08:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Math formulas were worthwhile memorizing which you found a use for later in life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to think I was indecisive but then I changed my mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /thread :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the punniest pun you've ever punt and how many casualties did it claim before getting toasted by battery acid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too cheesy, needs more cow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What makes America grate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's acceptable elsewhere but not in a bathroom? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most addicting app you put on your phone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 07:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What counterintuitive double-standard is an understatement to irony? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most surprising statistics you've seen from a reliable source? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What high paying job is not worth the effort? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most overrated franchise and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What franchise do you loathe the most and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So SFW is still not safe for work. Gotcha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favorite misheard lyrics which you think are better than the original? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What makes something not safe for work? Isn't all non-work related material not safe for work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's something you purchased which broke too soon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If where there is a will, there is a way... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why didn't Will Smith become a blacksmith? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could rewrite the ten commandments, and the major religions would follow them, what would you change them to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's acceptable in sports but inappropriate elsewhere? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 06:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What video game do you wish they'd make a sequel for which the company gave up on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's the ugliest celebrity you admire, and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, takes a few tries. The crap people upvote and the good stuff people downvote surprises me sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant like to earn the sensation status. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you became an overnight internet sensation, what is something you can see yourself doing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On a typical day, what kind of stuff makes it to the front page? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's something your favorite businesses are missing, and your feedback you wish they'd listen to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your vacation bucket list? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the stupidest piece of advice you heard that wound up useful later? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (aiming more in the relationships territory here) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When was the last time you acted on a misunderstanding, and how did that go? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 07:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like "It's Me, uh Mario. Let's go! Aaaaaahha.... duuuush.... Mamma Mia...." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Mother-in-law jokes aside, what's it really like to see your SO's mother dying? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 09:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Realistically speaking, a well designed large shower with multiple adjustable heads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 08:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picking up the couch to see if there's anything under it I was looking for. Giving me pointers on muscle building. Tag team to pick up the chicks, literally. Sports to kick everyone's ass. Bodyguard. Tow cars that park on my spot. Open that fucking jar that won't open. A movie starting himself. Lumberjack. Blacksmith. Personal Trainer. And helping me move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 08:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most I've used are free to register, but you gotta pay for extra features like chat with a specific person. Might try eHarmony or any dating site with decent reviews: http://www.datingsitesreviews.com/staticpages/index.php?page=11DatingSites </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 08:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gave online dating a shot and started chatting with whoever caught my eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 08:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much anything "sad song for broken hearts" can pull on youtube like: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6QXTV_jPSl4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 07:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant it to be clean. The replies have been dirty so far though in regard to the word "fun"... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 07:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please nobody try this, you'll wind up in the ER, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most fun you can have with a couple of every day household items? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 07:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a must for parties? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 07:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the greatest thing you did in the name of science? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 07:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 07:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm probably alone on this, but: king arthur and the knights of justice.
It was an important show to my childhood as I was a lot into the arthurian legends. Getting cancelled on season two before the plot could finish caused me to continue watching the show thinking I missed the continuation not realizing they cancelled it as it was still airing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 07:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or get promoted if they like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 07:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, meetup.com and search for anything in your area that would be of interest to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some signs a female is secretly crushing on you but doing everything in her power to move on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 07:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the quickest way to get yourself fired? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 06:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's the female equivalent of Nicolas Cage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 06:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're put into a room with the most disciplined of monks that never gets angry. Getting physical not allowed, what's a sure way to get him angry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 06:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What action film had you on the edge of your seat the longest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 06:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your biggest catastrophic blunder? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 06:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's something you know which one can't learn in school? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 06:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst trouble one of your kids caused when you left them unattended for a minute or two? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 06:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What fictional character most resembles your life story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 05:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 05:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Learn something new every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What knockoff is better than the original? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 05:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What mayhem did you set loose today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 05:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the stupidest reason your date left? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 05:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the lamest way you screwed up on a date? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 05:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 04:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever it takes to have conversation material afterwards. Picking tech meetings in your area which you'd be interested in helps put you in a room with folks you'd be interested in talking to.  Meet some people, hand out some business cards, and learn more about the industry. If you don't have business cards, it's very affordable if you have some time to put one together and will make you appear that much professional. About 99% of the people that go to them are already employed. I went there unemployed and met a handful of people with opportunities that would look good for me. Landed my dream job on the second or third tech meeting. After putting together a resume and interviewing with recruiters that found me off linkedin for a while, I learned how to pass the interview process. Finding a job I was interested in though was the difficult part. Found it through tech meetings. Even employed now, I go to tech meetings just to stay sharp in the industry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to tech meetings. That's the secret to getting your name out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omelette du fromage! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joke Writer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> skinny dipping </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About one world turtle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking too many holidays off work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 01:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Business Cards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 08:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My earliest memory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 08:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insults. At some point you just stop caring what other people think because life must go on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 07:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am however I weigh my priorities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 07:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wax on, Wax off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 07:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The paperclip phone holder. I destroyed a handful of paperclips, and even if you can bend it correctly, it just doesn't hold your phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 07:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A personal website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 07:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't think of your tomorrow-self as some super hero that can get shit done. When tomorrow comes, you become a weakling that need breaks too. Rather plan what needs to get done along while being honest with yourself about distractions. There's a saying that comfort-seeking is the root of laziness. Consolidate. One should NOT seek comfort from external things, rather the comfort one seeks is from actually getting the job done. Starting is the most difficult part. One needs to keep a game plan in mind. If you find yourself procrastinating, ask yourself: "How much break time do I actually need?" and while being honest with yourself, plan when you're going to work. Starting is hard, and it's best to start with the easiest thing first. Once you get the easy thing out of the way, the whole task is now less burdensome, you stopped procrastinating. Now work on the next easiest task. Finally you're left with the hardest part. Take a break, you earned it. Come back when you have a gameplan how to approach it, be honest with yourself about when you can actually get it done. Refuel, refresh yourself, and when you're in tip-top shape, tackle the hardest part. Boom, you've now completed the entire task. Now you can go back to your lazy filthy stress-free life since you got shit done, and now there's no discomfort around to ruin your day. You can strike the air, you're a winner. It's one of the best feelings in the world. It's worthwhile to do it just for that feeling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 06:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ending of The Book of Eli. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 06:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part-time web development contracting. Pros: Work from home, when you want, Cons: Trying to explain what went wrong when something takes longer than expected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your funnest "would you rather"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 06:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 07:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If school is about to end, and you'll lose all contact with the girl, what do you have to lose by making a move? She'll be gone from your life soon enough. Try testing the waters to see if you can get her to notice you. if you can get her to laugh, that's a good indication you're in the clear. From there just spill out your feelings and hope for the best. Maybe she'll be like "hey, I like you too, but don't think it would work out" or something like that. Communication is key to any relationship. Get some info flowing so you have more to make a move on rather than play guessing games all day. Could try something like "Hey, you're pretty. Will you be my friend?" or whatever you think would work. If you can't find a way to do it, at least get some contact information from her so you can try further attempts down the road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 06:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you're a senior in high school. Looking back on my life, I regret the crushes I didn't make more of an active move on before things happened like they moved away. Try acting touchy-feely around him, and when questioned act like nothing is happening, and see if you have any luck with that. Guys love that sort of thing. If that gets him more interested in you, reel him in. If not, and it really bothers him, and you think it's related to him already being in a relationship, try settling for the friendzone and keep him as a friend that you can keep a tab in his life, and when opportunity opens up, make your move. Even if you never work out with the dude, at least you'll gain some experience and hopefully a first kiss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 05:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, at least you know he knows that you like him now, and he's ok with that. I'd suggest getting a bit touchy-feely to get him more interested in you. When you think he's more into you, ask him out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 05:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she keeps you as a friend, and probably has already seen signs that you like her, the fact she keeps you around means she must like you to SOME extent. You give her something she needs. But is there enough of it that she desires a relationship with you? What's her dating life like? Why did she break up with her last long-term relationship? If she uses you as some sort of therapist, you have a door into her life to make ends meet. Honestly, any girl that uses you as a therapist has problems they're trying to overcome and are open to advice. If she values your input enough to trust you with a lot of information that would normally not reach others' ears, she probably likes you more than you like her. Maybe get a drink together as friends and see if it starts to feel more like a date.

Then again, I think being too open to the point that they bother you, especially if you told them what bugs you, without being careful not to risk losing you, this could just be them not giving af about her relationship with you, and just exploiting you as an acquaintance.

It's also possible both are true and she's just desperate trying to work out with anyone that comes her way. If that is the case, I think she just needs someone to love her. If you love her, make a move buddy. If your feelings are mixed, and you can't see yourself with them, tell them you need time away from them. If they value you as a person, they'll make a better effort to keep you. If not, they'll only drain your energy and waste your time. Unless you value them as a contact.

I wouldn't suggest anything rash at this point if it's possible the feeling is mutual. But if she's more like an ex, go with your gut feeling and stick with that decision. But, in all honesty, if you're really interested in a serious relationship, don't put up with that kind of crap. Find someone else, and pronto. But if you're just starting to get your feet wet in the dating world and enjoy project women, have fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 04:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant that's what to say as per the quotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you summarize that with a TL;DR? If I find a summary interesting, maybe I'll consider reading that monstrosity of a paragraph. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get her to laugh again and she may regain interest in you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well IF it were the other way around, as a dude, I'm a fan of subtle questions like "Are you available?" in work-related contexts. (women tend to need a day or two in my experience). And just making them laugh in general helps your chances for them to notice and think about you. Then from there, pretty much anything works. I like smooth pick-up lines which make it sound like there's a party and you're inviting them. Anything of this sort should work: "Hey, wanna grab a drink together?" But writing stuff down tends to feel like more of an official attempt, like many of the unique ways to pop the "will you marry me?" question.

BUT as it's a woman asking the guy out, we don't need that day or two to think it over. I think your method would work fine. Whether to put a name on it is another story, and I think it would work best without. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try subtle things like picking up your shirt slightly to reveal your belly button and act like you're getting an itch or something. If you get him used to seeing such things, you can try larger risks. When you have more information regarding his comfortableness around you, you can act more wisely regarding your course of action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell her you need distance. Kind of hard to tell someone you once loved that you don't love them anymore. If you drift apart, awesome. If you start getting back together again, repeat the process. Either you're dating or you're not. Limbo is not dating, so tell her you need distance. It also leaves enough room for your feelings to love her again if that changes for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Are you in a relationship?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But did you finish watching it? I couldn't... lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you talk with a stranger, which topic do you hope most to talk about, and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 01:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rated number one on my "could watch over and over again" list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What film did you have the most expectation for, only to be disappointed by the result, and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out of all the funny films you watched, which had you laughing the longest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What typo impacted your life the worst? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's the smartest person you know and the dumbest person you know? And why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a lifehack you can't believe you never thought of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When's the last time you burst out laughing at something you normally don't find funny? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's something that sucks about the industry you work in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
