<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3288</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have recently become aware of the osprey series, the seems to cover a lot of different and interesting periods, but I am not sure how good they are since I can`t find any review/ previews from the book to get a look at the images and writing style. Might just have to buy a book someday to see for myself.
Edit: Scratch that, just did a quick search on youtube and found a lot fo videos that show the books. Seems like the Osprey books are exactly what I want. Only downside is that the books are so small/short, but still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like the game is dropping kickstarter and steam early access because of massive interest in the game and because the initial backers decided the fund the whole game, all stretch goals and such, and it will apparently release this years. Great success!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can`t find any info about them doing some actuall fighting after ther 11-1200s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I have been reading about them as well, very interesting history and they continued to be a military order untill the 1500s. But as you stated, they ended up fighting christians instead of fighting heathens and muslims, like the Knights of Malta did. Where there any others crusader orders that continued to fight muslim/ottomans in the renaissance like the Maltese did? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 11:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Native Americans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any good books on the later crusades or the knights of malta with lots of illustrations and art? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 11:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the title says, I`m looking for books about the later crusades and/or the knights of Malta that has a lot of illustrations and art. Prefferably a coffe table book. I have been reading a lot about the knights of malta and the later crusades lately, and wanted to know if there were any books similar to what I wanted. Lately I have been rading a few coffe tapple/compendium books about Vikings (Wikings at war by Kim hjardar) and also the general military history of Norway (Norges kriger - Wars of Norway). Along the a few "The world of" books for different fantasy series (The world of kong, the world of the wticher etc) really got me into these types of books, and now I want to find some similar books about crusaders and the knights of malta ( Though any other historical period is also welcome) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did any crusader orders continue the fight besides the Knights of malta? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 11:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did any pother crusader order besides the Knights of malta continue the fight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 11:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been reading a lot about the Knights of Malta (as they came to be known) and what interests me is the fact that even for centuries after the original crusades ended they continued to fight using ships and joing every christian alliance the could. Did any other of the crusader orders continue to fight in the same way as the Knights of Malta did or were they unique?
Side note: Can anyone recoment me some good books about any later crusades and books on the Knights of malta between 1400-1798?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 12:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cold period probably had something to do with it, but I read that the black death was the ultimate reason they left. They were dependent on regular contact with Iceland and Norway, and when the plague hit the population droped massivlet and the ships stopped comming regularly. The fact that a lot of people died in Iceland and Norway (I`ve never heard of the plague hitting Greenland, which is interesing) ment that there were plenty of good farmland raeady for use, and most greenlanders would have prefered the good soil back home. So all the young people went back home to get their piece of land, while the old folk ( as old folks usually do) stayed in greenland, and eventually died out.

Taken form Wikipedia: "After 1408 not many written records mention the settlers. There is correspondence between the Pope and the Biskop Bertold af Garde from the same year.[13] The Danish Cartographer Claudius Clavus seems to have visited Greenland in 1420, according to documents written by Nicolas Germanus and Henricus Martellus who had access to original cartographic notes and a map by Clavus. Two mathematical manuscripts containing the second chart of the Claudius Clavus map from his journey to Greenland, where he himself mapped the area, were found during the late 20th century by the Danish scholar Bjnbo and Petersen.[14]

In a letter dated 1448 from Rome, Pope Nicholas V prescribed the bishops of Sklholt and Hlar (the two Icelandic episcopal sees) to ensure to provide the inhabitants of Greenland with priests and a bishop, the latter of which they hadn't had in the 30 years since the apparent coming of the heathens when most churches were destroyed and the people taken away as prisoners.[15]

It is probable that the Eastern Settlement was defunct by the middle of the 15th century although no exact date has been established." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 12:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven`t read it yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 12:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course if you go back 10 000 years everybody originally came from somewhere else, but it is pretty certain the the original germanic culture and languages developed first in Scandinavia, and the Nordic Bronze age is the earliest attested germanic like culture in Europe.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Germanic_peoples#Origins
(I knwo wikipedia isn`t the best source, but they state my points cleary)
But the germanic origins isn`t the maint topic here. I just wondered if anyone had some info about germanic continuity after they left their homelands. I recenlty watched the Beowulf movie, and what interested me is that fact that it is an anglo-saxon story set in Denmark centuries earlier, indicating that the anglo-saxons remebered/brought with them at least parts of their old germanic culture tol britain, and told the stories for houndreds of years after they left. It could seem like they stayed in touch with their germanic brethern back home, and if that is so how did the vikings and the anglo-saxons see eachother when the raid started? Did they understand each other, since they came from the same region years back?
What also interest me is the fact the the Beowulf story gives an insight into scandinavian history that is otherwise blank, the same goes for the Viking sagas who tell of great migrations a long time ago, which we today know to be true.
Of similar interest is the fact that the lombards (langobards) which also came from scandinavia seems to have broguth with them an early form og rune writing, showing their connection to their ancestral homeland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 12:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I`m putting it on the edge here for sure, but evidence shows that the germanic culture originally evolved from the scandinavians in the nordic bronze age, and the germanic languages evolved there as well. of course some nearby locations like northern germany and such we germanic as well, but a lot of the tribes and peoples the are counted as germanic seems to have had their original homeland in scandinavia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Similarities between the Vikings and the ancient germanic tribes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing that Scandinavia is the homeland for all germanic peoples, and the fact that most of the germanic tribes that eventually defeated the romans and invaded britain came from scandinavia (Goths, angles, cimbri, burgundians, vandals etc), I just wondered if anybody knew about any cultural or military similarities between these different tribes? I for one know that the viking sagas contain stories dating back to the migration period and the movements of the goths, and that norse and germanic mythology have a lot in common. Are there any other similarities between all these peoples? Did the tribes then left scandinavia and settles in Rome and other places retain their language and remebered their old homeland? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cultural and military similarities/continuity between the ancient germanic tribes and vikings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing that Scandinavia is the homeland for all germanic peoples, and the fact that most of the germanic tribes that eventually defeated the romans and invaded britain came from scandinavia (Goths, angles, cimbri, burgundians, vandals etc), I just wondered if anybody knew about any cultural or military similarities between these different tribes?
I for one know that the viking sagas contain stories dating back to the migration period and the movements of the goths, and that norse and germanic mythology have a lot in common. Are there any other similarities between all these peoples? Did the tribes then left scandinavia and settles in Rome and other places retain their language and remebered their old homeland? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 16:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, seems to be a good year for western games, witch RDR2, the rumored far cry western game (that might have a modern day setting) and now this. Fianlly the western gerne is coming back to life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 13:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read ina history magazine that the narrangessett (?) culture did not catch any of the old world deseases because there seems to have occured some form of intermarriage or contact that gave that group immunity to later diseases.
Also, though our best sources on the norse colonication of america are the saga books, in recent years researchers and historians have started to agree that norse activity probably were much larger in scale and laster longer than what has been the norm untill now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course I would. Go all out historical I say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THey should, but doubt they want to have to similar type games competing against each other, and the only real difference being that one clings to the assassins title while the other does not. Imo the fact that the best assassins creed game made was black flag just telles me that whenever they decide the not care about assassins they can get really creative and make epic games, and when they go back to their same old formula of assassins in cities (Unity and syndicate) shit hits the fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://gematsu.com/2017/05/rumor-egypt-set-assassins-creed-origins-features-two-protagonists-naval-combat-due-fall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I for one agree, ubi should just drop the entire "assassins" plot and go full historical. The Assassins plot and modern day parts are REALLY holding the series back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES PLEASE! Was so glad to hear they they reverted their stance on "no naval combat". Naval combat in AC3 and Black flag were the best additions to the series in years.

Can`t wait to explore egypt and the mediterannean.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I`ve read multiple places that it might in fact be a new far cry game. If so, I would still be happy. We need more open world western games, no matter who makes them. Getting both rdr 2 AND a western far cry? Yes please! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If one button push in to hard for you then I don`t know waht to say. battle formations are the staple of total war combat, and IMO one of THE best features, both because it adds realism and also because it just looks badass (also it gives the players waaaay more controll of the army)
I for one want more micro, not less. I love warhammer, but it really is total war for dummies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 12:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonna be epic if they do a rdr live action trailer, better do it in the style of Hell on Wheels! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 08:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only have the first book, as I understand that the 2nd book is more or less a summary of the first 2 games. I want history, politics, magic and fauna, not the background of various individuals.
Never heard of He-Man and Master of the universe, but I loved the master and commander movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it`s "The world of ice and fire" and I already have it. it was the book that got me into these type of lore/compenidum books in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any other World books like "The world of the witcher" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I`m just rereading the "World of the witcher" book, which, for those that don`t know, is a mix of world history, kingdoms, peoples and animals from the witcher universe. I REALLY love these kinds of books, and wonder if you people could add some other video game /fantasy compenduium books of this type. I Already own a few, Like: The world of ice and fire, the world of thedas, Warcraft chornicles and the world of kong. Are there any other of these books for other games or fantasy universes, say lotr or elder scrolls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 10:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. So many features to brought depth to the total war games have been removed over the years, especially in warhammer. Better not do the same to the next historical game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 10:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The warhammer units are by no means more intelligent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 10:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES! The units in warhammer feel so un-lifelike, and I despise the fact that I have less controll of my empire and armies in warhammer than in any other games. Visually it just a downgrade and a bummer too. Actually giving the order and WATCHING your soldiers get into formations is visually pleasing as well as tactically informative. If they implement this "system" in any of the historical games `m gonna be mad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 08:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know, the show arya and sansa are just mad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arya and sansa. Don`t like them anymore, they way they are abviously going mad and are just as crazy as the other "bad" people, but the fans still cheer for them is just stupid. Especially that scene where arya kills walder and sansa kills Ramsay is so obiously just a fan service. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sci-fi game, not fantasy or historical. I just wanna now if there are any upcomming open world fantasy/medieval rpg games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if I wasn`t clear enough, I am aware of all the above mentioned games, but two of them are sci fi (ish) and one is wii game. I am mostly looking for either pc or ps4 games. And what I am looking for are fantasy or medieval games, not sci fi or something similar like horizon is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Open world fantasy rpg droubt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 11:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you people aware of any open world rpg games like the witcher 3, skyrim or dragon age comming any time soon? It seems to me that since the witcher 3 rocked the word there have been no new releases or annuncements of any game like the witcher 3. Right now I can only think about shadow of war, greedfall and bannerlord. Did the epicness of the witcher 3 sacre of all the orher developers? All the new rpgs I can find now are diablo like and top-down games.
EDIT: I just wanna know if there are any upcomming open world fantasy/medieval games comming. Sci-fi games like mass effect and fallout is NOT what I?m looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was hoping for something new </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, you tricked me into work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.facebook.com/TotalWar/?fref=ts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Owners of blood and gore dlc with get it in warhammer 2 as well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CA just announced on the facebook site. Sry to lazy to add link, bet somone will do it for me:)
Anyway, this is good news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I`m happy, this is a beta and the focus shoiuld be on stabilizing the game itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, she`s actually hot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
