<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3535</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If candy companies were drug cartels? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently heard someone mispronounce El Chapo as El Choco. This got me thinking what if candy companies were organized and behaved like drug cartels. Can anyone think of any funny names, scenarios, ect. ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you elaborate on how the comments were irritating? It's a complaint I've never heard before
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 22:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hadn't planned on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, it was. I'm glad it got renewed for a second season, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My only question about the it's all on Steve's head theory is  was that shot of Steve in #2 taking place in his head, or some sort of manifestation?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The younger brother is the smartest and most likable, but I don't like the will they, won't they thing with him and his partner. CBS has run that cliche to the ground with shows like NCIS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can completely get the preachy element. It tries to have a message at the end of most episodes, but it can go off onto after school special territory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree. Stopped watching after season 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just watched 7 seasons of Blue Bloods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my free time, I've managed to explore some shows I've had saved in my list for a while, but never had the time to watch. One of those shows was the CBS cop show Blue Bloods. After watching the six seasons on Netflix and now having saw the 7th season, I've got some pros and cons. 

For those who haven't seen it, Blue Bloods is about the trials and tribulations of a New York family with three generations in Law Enforcement, with Tom Selleck as the Police commissioner and Donnie Wahlberg as the detective as well as a normal beat cop and a district attorney in there as well. 

Some of the pros are: 

1. Its tackles sensitive topics; Most cop shows occasionally tackle some real world topic, but Blue Bloods makes it a regular occurrence where all four of the main characters encounter some kind of moral, ethical, or legal quandary that deals with a real world social or political issue (everything from gang violence, racial stereotyping, domestic violence, sexual harassment in the workplace, police brutality and everything in between) and later debate it with the rest of the family at their traditional Sunday dinner, usually where they try and see it from multiple perspectives, which is welcome change from most other cop shows today.

2. The characters are not all super dark: Another tendency of cop shows, and network TV in general is to have the characters have some kind of dark past, or some kind of lingering trauma or personal issue going on. Blue Bloods doesn't do that. Compared to a lot of its cop drama brethren, the show is pretty bright and the characters are more or less good people who try to do the right thing, which can be quite refreshing. 

3. The characters are also surprisingly deep: A lot of cop dramas tend to have characters that are either wire thin or little more than caricatures. Blue Bloods is slightly different. A lot of the best qualities  of the main characters can also be some of their biggest faults. A big example is that Tom Selleck's character is extremely ethical and rule oriented, however that can make him too rigid when when it comes to situations where most people would have use their influence or bent the rules.

As for the negatives: 

1. Its not for everyone: The show, despite its attempts at debating certain topics, still has a clear opinion on a lot of things and if you don't share those opinions, then its not for you. 

2. Donnie Wahlberg: Don't get me wrong, I like Donnie Wahlberg the actor, but I can't stand his character in this show. Whiny, stupidly written, and the living embodiment of plot armor. 

3. Self-rightiousness: The show tends to go out of its way to make the main characters morally superior to the detriment of everyone else. Got a different idea on what's right and wrong? Too bad, Donnie Wahlberg's right! Caught in a situation that isn't black and white? Shut up, Magnum P.I. knows what to do!

4. Its corny: It tries to be funny, and its not. Its tries to be cool, and its not. It tries to be original, and its probably been done by 10 other shows in the last 5 years, half of them were probably on CBS. 

I realize I might have put too much thought into a Friday night CBS cop drama, but the show kinda surprised me in some aspects.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't put it past them, especially Nick Spencer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could still count. I've heard nothing but good things about it, but is it that cliched? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most cliche filled show you've seen on TV recently? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, its a tie between half the shows running on CBS (anything with NCIS in the title, MacGyver, and especially Blue Bloods)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember a friend of mine saying no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most cliched TV show(s) you've seen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While the Ultimate universe is gone, sure, characters and items have made their way to the 616 verse. Miles, Ultimate Reed Richards, Ultimate Thor's hammer, and a few others. So, its not much of a stretch to think that Ultimate Cap somehow managed to find his way to 616.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Secret Empire spoilers] A question about Cap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Withe the reveal in the latest issue of Secret Empire where spoiler another Steve Rogers appears out of nowhere, some people are theorizing/debating that the new Steve is the Cap from the Ultimate universe. I haven't read anything ultimate in a while, so I'm a little rusty on that universe's Cap. Can someone do a compare/contrast of the two Caps in regards to their personalities, ideals, differences ect. 

Also, feel free to offer your opinions on the reveal and the theory as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the best way to introduced the X-Men/mutants in general is to just introduce them. Maybe say the aftereffects of Infinity War, which is bound to alter the fabric of space and time, causes the manifestation of the X-gene worldwide. 

As for the X-Men, I would want them to go back to the basics, like with Spider-Man, where its the original 5 members, maybe with one or two additional members from the Claremont run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roger Ailes, architect of conservative TV juggernaut Fox, is dead at 77 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 15:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 14:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't be mad at either. Both have the physicality, the charm and the acting chops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 14:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone do a compare/contrast between 616 and ultimate Cap? I haven't read the Ultimate books in a while so I'm kind of rusty when it comes to the differences between the two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The story's nothing unique or revolutionary, sure, but it's the execution of the plot with the acting, the score, the dialogue, etc. that made it enjoyable. Also, I really liked how the overall premise tied into a real event with the Arab Spring. It makes the show seem more grounded than you're typical spy story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just saw The Night Manager and... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 03:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was not expecting something this good. This is probably the best James Bond movie that wasn't actually a James Bond movie that I've seen in a long time. The acting is incredible; If you ever needed a reason for Tom Hiddleston to be the next Bond, this show is it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just found out that Horse Soldiers is getting made  into a movie that's supposed to release in 2018 

http://www.wearethemighty.com/articles/7-upcoming-movies-we-want-to-see-at-the-base-theater </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 01:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CBS is just released the trailer for, and this is the actual title, "SEAL TEAM". If this doesn't look like a poor man's SIX, I don't know what does. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wKMPAOGIA7I

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 00:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comey-Wan Kenobi  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The syllabus has always been my achilles heel. Whenever I receive one, I always read it once, then forget to look at it for the rest of the semester. Maybe I should start having them be the first thing in my notebook folders, or just tape them to my ceiling so I wake up reading my syllabus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any advice about not missing Homework deadlines? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With my semester wrapping up, I'm worried my grades might not be as strong as they could be, not because of my participation in class, but that I tended to miss deadlines for my online homework assignments. This has been an ongoing problem and i don't know how to fix it. I'm thinking about going back to a homework planner like I had in high school, but I'm not sure if that's the best or the most permanent solution. 

Does anyone have any advice?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 05:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the longest time, I thought that was Steve Blume with some extra base in his voice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 23:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that I think about it, there is a series about a bunch of vets who are kind of lovable screwups who work the night shift at a Texas Hospital. It's called the night shift, and it's on Netflix. It's sort of a hybrid of the office, scrubs, and M.A.S.H. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The show was edgy for something Spider-Man centric. I also like how they tried to create new villains for Peter to face, and Electro was probably the most sympathetic version I've seen in a while.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really great suggestions, though in regards to Aquaman, he doesn't have to be a native to either Miami or Hawaii. I also think Atlantis can be either in the Atlantic or in the Pacific, as the DCEU seems to be suggesting given their design of and cast choices for Aquaman. I think a good middle ground would be to say that Atlantis is located in the Pacific a few dozen miles off what is now the Hawaiian islands.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boston's an interesting choice for Superman, why choose it? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone remember the MTV Spider-Man show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to own it on PSP discs as a kid and would watch them on plane rides. I recently caught it on Amazon video a few days ago, and it was surprisingly good despite the early 2000's techno score, the fact the Peter wore purple pants (that always bothered me growing up) and the recycled footage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I both agree with and share that sentiment. Though, the visible part isn't a bad thing to a certain extent. For example, having a flag outside of your home or a small sticker or patch on something isn't a bad thing, but (for me as an American) when you're wearing the stars and stripes as everything from a three piece suit (yes, it happens here) to a bikini and everything in between, then it becomes gaudy and diminishes what the flag stands for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] If the members of the Justice League were in real American cities, where would they be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By this, I'm not asking what DC cities are analogous to real world one, but rather if the members of the JL(for arguments sake, lets use the New 52 league) were based out of real world cites, what cities could you see them being in?

For me, I could see: 

Superman being based out of either New York or Chicago, but more so NYC.

Batman would be either in New York or Chicago, but I tend to lean towards Chicago maybe due to the history of crime we have here.

Wonder Woman would be in or near D.C. or Virginia  

Flash would probably be in the midwest, but I could see him on the west coast also. 

I could see Green Lantern be based out either L.A. or San Diego, given their proximity to military bases. Its also not too far of a stretch to imagine Hal rubbing shoulders with Hollywood. 

Aquaman would be either in Miami or the Hawaiian islands, but I would lean more towards Hawaii 

 Cyborg is already based out of Detroit. 


If you guys have any interesting suggestions for any non JL heroes feel free to suggest them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the likelihood of officers coming OTS becoming STOs or CROs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did some research on it and according to the latest documents, Os that used OTS as their commissioning source are accepted on a "case by case basis", but can someone clarify what the likelihood is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on your definition of patriotism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funnily enough, John Kelly was asked by a GOP congressman as to why he didn't wear a flag pin and he response was "I am an American flag". Just goes to show that true patriotism lies in actions, not accessories.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 07:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only in depth insight we have is from his now wife. I know lot of people point the figure at Army bureaucracy for Gant's dismissal, but despite how effective he was at accomplishing the mission, he was still drinking, taking painkillers and having a civilian live with him. If it wasn't bad then, imagine what would have happened had that stuff went on for a few more months.  

As for your other suggestions, Once an eagle would be great, Ghost Fleet would cool as something on Starz, and I had never heard about Blackhearts until now, and I just read the description on Amazon. It would be hard to watch, and maybe even genuinely disturbing given some of the stuff that happened.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 07:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its getting a movie that's closer to the book. But I absolutely agree that a HBO miniseries with a GOT level budget would be awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [COD] What would be your pitch for the story for Ghosts 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 07:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion, the world of Ghosts is the one with the most potential story wise. I was really disappointed with the story of Ghosts mainly due to the fact that we weren't able to learn about or explore the setting. I also didn't think it had the best characters or the plot. Since the COD franchise is starting to focus more on developing personal or in depth stories, I'd be pretty excited if IW decides to go back to the Ghosts universe. 

With that being said, what would your story pitches be for Ghosts 2?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 06:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good call on American Spartan, but only if a network like HBO does it. I think that the story of Jim Gant needs to be left to interpretation by the audience and in the hands of a lesser studio, I could see them leaning towards one opinion of Gant or another. 

Also, I'm surprised Horse Soldiers hasn't been picked up by a director or a network. I think its one of the most essential American stories of the last couple of decades and should be told, ideally by someone like Peter Berg or Stephan Spielberg.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 06:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I would like to see IW take a shot at Vietnam. I think they've always been the best when it comes to telling cinematic, gritty stories as evident by the MW trilogy and, in my opinion, Infinite Warfare. I would love to see a Vietnam set COD in the vain of something like We Were Soldiers or Platoon, especially with the graphical leap the series has taken like what we've seen in the trailers for WWII. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 06:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they were to go back to the Black Ops universe, I would want them to go back to WWII but focus on the covert operations that took place during the war, maybe with Mason's father (who was in the Pacific theater, but we don't exactly know what he did) as an OSS agent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 04:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like Cops meets The Office? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss The Unit, but you're right, the handling of the wives and the random paranormal stuff from season 3 derailed it for me. Unfortunately, it seems like any show in the vein of The Unit either has a very short shelf life (Last Resort and The Unit both had additional seasons planned, and both happened to be Shawn Ryan shows) or aren't that well made(American Oddessy, The Last Ship, Six, etc.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington Post Accidentally Published Mattis Number, But Its The White Houses Fault </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 01:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 01:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instant emmy winner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 00:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see something like that on the history channel or AHC (formally known as the military channel)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 00:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree. The 442nd would be super compelling, so much to the point that I'm surprised it hasn't been adapted yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 00:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never heard of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 23:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except you have those that really like the New 52 Superman continuity and if they were to completely disregard it, you'd have fans that would be complaining about it. I think that this was the best DC could do to satisfy both groups.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What military event/book would you wanted to see become a miniseries or movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 23:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm about to start rewatching Band of Brothers and The Pacific and I started to wonder why there hasn't been a miniseries in the style of those two since Generation Kill. There's certainly no shortage of stories that can be told, so which ones would you like to see get picked up as either a miniseries or a movie? 

For me, the two biggest ones are the story told in Horse Soldiers by Doug Stanton or a series based on the Harlem Hellfighters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump revealed highly classified information to Russian foreign minister and ambassador </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 23:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me, Superman being a dad kinda fits in with his character. He's been a role model to people for decades, and it only seems fitting that he ends up being a father. I also agree that Lois doesn't have a whole lot to do, but I think it all depends on the story ark.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we'll finally get the learning up of the missing 5 (or was it 10) years to the continuity with Doomsday Clock. With that, I think there's a chance Ma and Pa Kent come back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess is that Connor gets reintroduced in phase 2 of Rebirth similar to Wally West or sooner. If he does, I would love it if they have him move in with Clark, Lois, and Jon and have him be an older brother figure to Jon. Or they could have him end up with Lex if he's still has the armor (which I hope he still does) 

As for Chris, I don't know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the inconsistencies in regards to continuity will be ironed out in the next few months, especially with Doomsday Clock on the horizon. 

I like the conflict between Supes and Lex, as it gives a new dynamic to both, one I which doesn't get wiped away anytime soon. 

I can also see how it cheapens the ending of New 52 Superman but to be honest, I say what we got afterwards was worth it. 

And if you're right about Jurgens wanting a continuity he was more comfortable it, I can't really blame him. Continuity has always been problem for DC, especially with what, 3 or 4 retcons in the last few years. And at least he tried to maintain elements of both and did a fair job of it. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
