<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2728</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you mounted garbage trucks with cameras you could update google maps street view weekly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wheres vincent chase? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 22:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fucking shit. In the name of the father and of the son and the holy spirit. Im speechless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at his pay now he would not be worth it at all. Guy has a max contract...wtf? I guess anybody and everybody is asking for a max these days with mediocre stats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comparing their stats drummond beats JV in pts, rebs, stls, and blocks. The only doownside i see is him being overpaid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JV Trade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone think we shouldve made that JV for Drummond trade earlier in the season?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 23:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LMAO "no! Hes my friend" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf kloe a better playoff grade than debo? Get the fuck out of here... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree with you disagreeing if he cant show up in the playoffs we dont want him and hes definitely not worth a max </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good season, weak ass playoffs. Masai has his work cut out for him this off season, i hope he works his magic. Casey, carroll, ppatt and lowry can all eat my dirty ass i hope they all get traded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea i feel this way too we need to get rid of carroll ppatt cojo and lowry. You know make some trades. However i dont think we should let jv go his game is still developing and he can become pretty doninant if he puts on some mass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It would really suck if your superpower was being able to fly but you're extremely scared of heights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yea i am no stranger to watching breaking bad in a week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In your opinion who do you think we can acquire? Either by trading or signin a free agent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the fastest you have ever binge watched a TV show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like i said hes a free agent, once we get rid of ppatt and demarre and possibly even cojo and lowry we could have enough cap space to sign a few players. We also have the option of a sign and trade. Idk, just gonna watch masai work his magic but hopefully he takes a look at snell, he could be a good young replacement who still has time to develop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tony snell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone think tony snell can be a good replacement for a demarre Carroll or ppatt? Hes a free agent this summer and i feel like he proved to be much more efficient and effective than ppatt or Carroll. He did a pretty good job guarding derozan and hit a number of 3s. Hes also pretty young and could be a good replacement for the guys i mentioned. Does anyone else agree with me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ace venture pet detective </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dazed and confused  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya i just turned it off cant watch anymore.....FUCCKKKKKKKKKKKKKKKKKKKKJ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro why do tese refs deepthroat the cavs cocks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will take your advice and read into things myself, however i dont think that will change my stance. Also 2% is more than you realize. Not to mention the reason ISIS and other groups like it have been doing what they are doing is mostly because of their religious beliefs. Also, i am one of the last people who believes what they are told, i look at it from all sides before deciding what i believe. Im actually a very logical person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All i have to say is after you die, there is an eternity of nothingness, i know its very disappointing, i mean i would love to have a life afer death type of thing happen but thats not how it goes. Im sorry. Im not opposed to believing in religion. However i have never seen anything that proves god is real. I will believe if/when I ever see proof, and if that ever happens, i will eat my words and apologize.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair i know all about these people teachings i was forced to go to catholic school all my life, actually, one of my schools was named after one of those people you mentioned. Its not like im completely clueless about all this. Ive been to mass so many times i cant even count, listened to countless prayers, i just dont believe in it and dont think anyone else should. To me, religion is an outdated concept and to see how far we have come and still believe in religion is sad. Not to mention the amount of unecessary wars religion has started.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, of course its not the first time. Im just tired of seeing so many people brainwashed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Youre telling me i cant be serious? Buddy, im not the one who believes in God... its like believing in fairytales and myths. YOU cant be fucking serious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really...a vegans beliefs are much more logical than any religious person. I dont wanna expand too much of my energy typing, so go watch a documentary on Netflix called Zeitgeist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I dont want to shit on religion too much because people will get extremely sensitive. In short, no, i obviously dont.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 08:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im speachless...so you believe in life after death i assume? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 07:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You actually believe in god, jesus etc....? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 07:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a serious subreddit? I cant believe people believe in this stuff... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was a a pool party this girl went underwater and when she came up her damn titty was out. Her friend noticed about 15 seconds later and somehow no one else saw.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Improvisation in Film </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking an std clinic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the worst place to pick up women/men? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jake and amir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
