<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3944</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> samurai jack scaramouche wallpaper [3440x1440] (xpost) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can we... *sniff* not reference the guardian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scaramouche 21:9 wallpaper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samurai concept, number 10554? [Hopefully with decent reasoning] pls be gentle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 22:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Disclaimer* I am not a balance team member, nor do I consider myself to be good at this game, take everything here with like, a few grains of salt, I mostly made this thread to geek out over the idea of a badass samurai being the rival of Hanzo and Genji
-
The desire: To add a high risk, high reward tanky DPS, much like Roadhog, who can turn the tides of a battle by being a force of assertion upon the enemy team. Left to his own devices, the samurai can dish heavy damage to tanks and squishies alike, or, being a frontline shield punisher, forcing enemies to rethink their strategy. My reasoning behind this kit, is that we have Roadhog, who excels at deleting one low health enemy at a time, can retreat to get back to full health, and does his job from range, with the tools to handle himself upclose, but let's be honest, if you're not using Roadhog's hook, you're not playing him to his full potential, not even close. Then we have Winston, very similar in his role, being an annoyance, dealing chip damage to multiple enemies, then jumping out of the fray when he feels like he needs to retreat. Samurai is almost an amalgamation of these two playstyles, but the one big thing I like about him, is because he's entirely immobile, he has a reason to have the tools required to punish foes who get too close or try to fight him one on one. I know melee is hard to balance around, because it's very easy to make a melee hero either completely broken, or entirely too weak. IE Genji, the long range dash would be ludicrous if he was melee, having too much safety to fall back on, not to mention deflect as added safety. Not to mention Reinhardt's shield and charge, which makes him deceptively mobile and adds a rather fast gap closer, that can be used as an escape if needed.
-
Samurai's style of engagement also reflects the Bushido way of life (if you're into that sort of thing), going into battle being prepared to die. His jump would never be able to be used as an escape, unless he was standing in front of vertical terrain, but does allow him to dodge some damage while dishing it out himself. If you read this far I applaud you, as there's probably COUNTLESS threads made about a samurai hero.
-
I really like the idea of Genji and Hanzo facing a common, terrifying enemy, essentially forcing them to put their demons to rest. I know, cliche, but it's still a slot that's open for the imagination.


-
Truncated origin: Family was killed/troubled by Shimada clan thugs, trained his whole life to exact revenge, Genji and Hanzo are the last members of the Shimada bloodline, whatever generic blah blah, he wants to kill them. (I'm not expecting anyone to read past the title, and just downvote me and move on)
-
Melee tank/DPS, why tanky? Well, Samurais.. wore a lot of armor. Steel plating, layered like scales, over leather.
-
300 health/200 armor
-
LMB- 60 damage, ~33% faster than Reinhardt's swings (Katana), not a cleaving attack al a Genji/Rein
-
LMB- 100 damage, ~10% faster than Reinhardt's swings,
 +50% bonus damage to all shields, (Rein, Zarya, etc) (Kanobo), no overkill damage if the shield breaks. Still not a cleaving attack.
-
E- Stance Change: switches between Katana (fast attack) and Kanobo (slow, powerful, shield busting) [8 second CD]
-
Shift- Dive: Leap into the air (about the height of 3 jumps), then propel downward and very slightly forward (10 degree angle if you're keeping score) to deal damage in a small AOE, equal to the drawn weapon.
-
Q- Naginatajutsu (names pls): Draw a naginata that deals 85 damage per swing, (same speed as the katana) this weapon cleaves with its attacks, has double the reach of other weapons, and any ability key can be activated during this time to use Whirlwind, a fast sweeping ability that knocks all enemies outward from where they're located. Naginatajutsu lasts 9 seconds)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy crap really? why invert it?

edit: ohh, the clear side panel.. ffs. oh well, i think i can work around that. i need to rewatch the reviews and see if the inversion was the only thing i disliked about that case

edit: it's also about 20-40 mm smaller in all dimensions, and 100 mm shorter :/ didn't notice it though, i'll look into it and see if there's a noticeable difference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, watched a review of it, was considering it, but thumbscrews, and if i remember correctly (watching 20 case videos within a few hours of each other can mess with your memory) the SSD chambers were kind of crappy? i think? i'll get back to you

edit: ohh yeah, i remember it was also a mid case. and you're talking about the glass one right? yeah... if i thought i could deal with a mid case, i'd probably go with that one. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i would like a nice amount of SSD chambers, yeah, but also i've seen some PCs that barely fit the old 990fxa gaming mobos in them, and my z170 is waaay larger than those, not to mention the current 390 i have is massive as well, and i think the gtx 1080 is even bigger, no? but that's what i'm going to next, possibly dual 1080s, not to mention room for 2 radiators is a plus for overclocking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [build help] Out of option for the perfect PC case, or am I too picky? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've looked at:

every Corsair case. (That was full tower)
Bitfenix Aurora
Thermaltake Level 10 GT
Coolermaster Cosmos II

I was able to find the above cases with about a day's worth of research. Cannot. Find. A. Case. I. Like.

Here's what's wrong, the corsair 600q, I hate the inverted design. Is that justified or am I being paranoid?

The 760t, the top is sealed off, preventing airflow, actually I won't go into detail for every case.

vvvvv

The case I was the CLOSEST to buying was the Corsair 750D, but... the panels opened with those damn thumbscrews. THE DAMN THUMBSCREWS!!!

I'm looking for a case that's SIMPLE in appearance, (like the 600Q) preferably the doors on hinges, easy to access SSD chambers, like how Corsair has in every case, room for liquid cooling (shouldn't be a problem), adequate ventilation without sacrificing aesthetics, and it has to be full tower.

PLEASE HELP! 

Edit: nice typo in the title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually isn't me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly this is fake news fabricated by liberal cucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> excessive force... an AR-15, i doubt center mass shots would've killed. he must've been pluggin either multiple rounds, or aiming for the head... i would never go straight to lethal areas i don't think.. i don't know, i guess. i sure as hell know i wouldn't put more than 1 bullet into an invader, unless i saw their hands going somewhere else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's me_irl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> idk how many people have done this but-

crushing/opening a pin feather on a bird is seriously the most satisfying thing I've done in my life. ESPECIALLY COCKATOO CREST FEATHERS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] $50 Cracker Barrel GC [W] 80% PayPal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] $50 Darden GC [W] 80% PayPal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not much to really say, $50 Darden Gift Card, looking for 80% worth in PayPal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/subject3944 GCX Rep Profile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Redditor since 2015 
* If you have been linked to this page, please make sure that you're on the real /r/GCXRep, and the user who linked you was indeed me, and not someone with a similar username trying to impersonate me. Note that just because you're reading this doesn't mean a scammer didn't include this note in their fake profile to trick you into a false sense of security. Double check, and don't get tricked or scammed! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what a lovely day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> staging text messages is still worth upvotes i guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who the fuck pays with $19 and not 20 and why the fuck is it upside down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmao yeah zer0 from borderlands definitely didn't do this years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any StarCraft (Tal'Darim) fans? (3440x1440) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh

1. It's bli$$ard. They don't put money into anything that won't make them money. 

2. If you don't know what I mean, look at any of blizzard's content, ever. Then look at pentakill from League. A full length album with well established band members. Totally free (unless you buy on itunes), with a second album coming soon.

Blizzard just doesn't have the drive/will/talent for that, but we know they have the resources.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried checking out the neo nazi subreddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 08:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bullshit. At silver/gold elo, the enemy team would NEVER allow that to happen. Not to mention they ALWAYS have rein/dva which makes projectiles worthless during a zarya ult  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't traffic lights countdown their duration? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 08:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just does not make sense to me in any way. If traffic lights had a dot matrix timer, that counted down from 60 for a green light, 5 for yellow-- whatever- I feel like light-related accidents would decrease to a radically low level. Programming this wouldn't even require much work, especially with the advent of LEDs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Galaxy Cluster - Abell 2666 (3440x1440) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me_irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually.. every time i try to upload it, it stays that resolution.. haha... no idea why..

(proof)

http://i.imgur.com/3gxl89M.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
