<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3788</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I make an omelet every morning and throw 4 eggs, 2 pieces of ham, sprinkle cheese, and toss the peppers in the pan. Stir them all up for scrambled or omelet it out...boom tasty!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking the same thing. We only buy them here in MI, USA when they are $1.00 USD each! 15 for $5 is an awesome deal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much pot did Mr. Rodgers smoke? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 03:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean he has deep pockets and ya got to start somewhere...lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 03:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea. 

I remember there was a State Farm case that developed these guideposts to determine whether punitive damages were excessive, the guideposts themselves were developed in an earlier BMW case: (1) degree of reprehensibility of Dfs conduct; (2) ratio b/n punitive, harm likely to result, harm that actually occurred; (3) civil/criminal penalties that could be imposed for comparable misconduct.

The reprehensibility factor is the most significant. Only the reprehensible conduct that is closely related to the plaintiffs particular harm. 
- the most important factor
- State Farm Considered: (i) whether the harm caused was physical as opposed to economic; (ii) the conduct showed an indifference to or reckless disregard to the health/safety of others; (iii) the target had financial vulnerability; (iv) actions were isolated or repeated; (v) harm resulted from intentional malice, trickery or mere accident.

...those are a snip-it of my notes. We obviously don't have all the facts, but it sounds like this guy does this quite often by the way Fieger responds to some of the questioning. Maybe they are going with the 3rd guidepost by showing that is the value of Mike's license? Shot in the dark...I'm sure there was a lot of weighing the facts to come to a number like that. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. Sorry misread. 

I don't do PI, so all I can say is what I know from Law School. 

From what I remember civil assault and battery you get nominal damages. I would think most of this is going to be punitive damages because of his status.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember in the article it said the Plaintiff was seeking $10 million in damages. 

I'm sure if there is a basis for it, Morse could counter with a defamation suit, maybe, but if they have him on tape trying to coerce this lady...dude is going to want to pay and flee. 

Edit: I don't see how she can justify $10mil when she was grouped and then had the capacity to go back and eat with her friends...then go to the police and file a report...then get wired up and go tape a conversation with him and the restaurant owner. I mean I know their not claiming IIED, but it's a stretch, I'm sure it's based of his status as one of Michigan's most prominent PI attorneys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Logistics aside...but very keen rational. Possibly, there is a mechanism within the time machine and geo-synchronize with the location the pilot desires. They would have the ability to travel through time and space, calculating the exact point in space they desire and in turn the exact time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two HUGE Lawyers at it in Michigan; Jeffery Fieger vs. Mike Morse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 01:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two HUGE lawyers going at it in Michigan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 01:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Jeffery Fieger v. Mike Morse](http://www.freep.com/story/money/2017/05/15/woman-claims-attorney-mike-morse-groped-her-he-denies-accusation/323295001/)

Both names are large in the Metro Detroit area, and from what I've heard, Fieger is known nation wide. Very interesting circumstances.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 00:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here in Michigan you can get treble damages (x3) for Conversion, but this isn't conversion. You could file a suit in small claims court under a breach of contract principle for misrepresentation. Article 2 of the UCC would apply because they are in the business of selling goods, and therefore from purchasing the good you have a reasonable time to inspect and reject the good if it does not satisfy your reason for purchasing it under whats called the [perfect tender rule](https://www.google.com/search?q=perfect+tender+rule rlz=1C1CHZL_enUS687US687 oq=perfect+tender+rule aqs=chrome..69i57j0l5.2905j0j7 sourceid=chrome ie=UTF-8). 

You could be a super dick if they won't accept your return. I would do it out of principle. 

Edit: PM me if you'd like I could help you out if you want to cost them some money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be incredible to see someone stumble across Antartica. 

I'd actually really like to see North America before all the trees were chopped down and shipped over to Europe. A great forest once covered all of the North Eastern up to the Appalachians and they cut down...nearly everything...it is amazing what humans have done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure any castle would be interesting to go and visit. Just to be a fly on the wall and listen to daily life would be interesting. Go to a Blacksmith, have them build you a fricken amazing sword... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 12:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's long, could you trim up a little so I'm not scrolling down so much? Maybe at a few more CTA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 12:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What castle would you specifically go to?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 12:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. 

This was malicious on their part I can guarantee it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 12:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did the description of the item say? Did they market it in any way as an "official Nintendo 64" controller? 

That is called Misrepresentation, that is most certainly a reason for returning it, even if they have a no-return policy. That sticker placement was deliberate my friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 03:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need that baby groot...like now. Haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 02:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 02:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take it back...they deliberately placed the sticker over the one place that could represent a true controller.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 00:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just sit back, watch the Battle of the Delta...NBD! Maybe the Egyptian's history survived the way they wrote it, and they secretly went over and raided villages taking captures/slaves..? Needless to say, it would be something to defiantly document for history...good work! 

"Gbekli Tepe changes everything." Maybe you could set up a time-lapse camera at certain parts of the world, where no ancient people could find, with an unlimited amount of data storage, to just watch these places get built and thrive! Wouldn't that me something to see... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 23:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too would search to see if Atlantis was true. Maybe go and talk to Plato himself and ask him to point me in the right direction. 

I think the Native Americans would be receptive of a time-traveler. You could provide knowledge to them, possibly warn them of the English landing...haha man that would be an interesting plot twist in North American history! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 23:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, in the time machine your totally invincible...

This is your adventure so you can understand anything you want. 

I would like to have a birds eye view of those floods, that actually sounds super interesting, devastating, but super interesting. 

I think to see Yellowstone erupt at it's full super-volcano potential and just blow it's load...to witness that amount of force would be awe-inspiring. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just one day, out of the blue, The Library of Alexandria winds up on its own web page...Reddit top page for sure! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be an epic adventure my friend. I would be completely down for a ride like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I understood what you were saying. Even just in shape, it would still be amazing to maybe sequence it's DNA to see how similar it is to modern humans. Really, to sequence any then living species to compare it's DNA would be amazing; maybe it's sequence was something completely alien to what we have today... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa...you just blew my mind with that comment. Wow. Is there any evidence of such a creature? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or...you could go back and digitize the library... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, that would be interesting to watch. I'd be sitting there with you, ju ju bees in hand, just waiting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be interesting to just walk the halls and poke around before and after the fall. Go check out their libraries, mints, bath houses...really compare it to what we envision today.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the [Cambrian Explosion](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cambrian_explosion) would be awesome to witness as well. It's weird to think that, " Fossilization is a rare event, and most fossils are destroyed by erosion or metamorphism before they can be observed. Hence, the fossil record is very incomplete," to me this blows my mind that there could be thousands of species we will never know existed...almost like aliens once among us...this blows my mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think they could handle that much information at once. The ancient scientists and engineers could, but not the governing bodies. 

It's pretty incredible the amount of information we learn today is far far beyond what they even had the opportunity to know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can understand that, but at the same time you already have by taking yourself out of the "now" and turning up in some other "now," which in turn, even the smallest fart could change the path humanity or even the Earth could go down. 

Taking the Butterfly Effect out of the photo... 

Wouldn't it be fascinating to see what the ancients would do with such information? To see where it takes us? Would it destroy us? It would be interesting to see the effect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's deep man. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 17:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, that would be some of the most interesting things ever. To be able to sit down and interview each prominent figure whom ever lived. Could you imagine picking the brain of someone who wasn't privy to today's culture. 

I've thought about going back in time to the Library of Alexandria or Rome, and just placing a few books down giving them the most current in science, math, technology...just to see the profound influence it would have on today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 17:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the idea. 

I'm in the process of creating a blog as well. Go check out: 

r/lawfirm
r/lawfirmmarketing

On those subs there are a lot of good ideas for law blogs. I have a list of 200+ blog topics that I'm beginning to go through and write. I would suggest writing out a list of topics that you think are important to whom your targeting. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The future is history, just from a different perspective. 

The [Meiji period](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Meiji_period#Economy) would have been a good place to sit and watch their economy take off in their own industrial revolution. It shows that if you want something bad enough, you can always find a way. 

I've often thought about my conscious and memory being stored. I think without context or proper explanation, a lot of what we store and think would be vastly misunderstood. I think that's one of life's gifts, we are able to coherently ponder our own thoughts, without bias, without explaining...you're able to just think. I don't think I would want anyone else to know my thoughts on that level.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to see Rome in it's height. I can only imagine the ingenuity and knowledge it held. 

I would like to see the land where my house is situated as well. I know it was old farm land, but to see who and what it was used for would be wonderful to be able to connect on that level. 

I would like to see how civilized Mesoamerica was as well. At their peak, they were an incredibly thriving civilization. 

...I would LOVE to taste food from these times as well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 15:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be so interesting. I would be so interested to try and catalog every dialect ever voiced or written down in Earths history! 

What part of the world would you go to first?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, just have an employment-engagement letter ready for them to sign in blood too, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time Machine: Where would you go? What would you do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know there are somewhat similar questions in this subs history, but I'd like to have a frank conversation with anyone who would indulge in submitting a response to this post. 

I always told myself, I'd want to see it all, but was naive and shook my head thinking, you'll never have enough *time* to *see it all*. Clearly my mind was closed off to the fact...I have a *time machine* and I would be capable of seeing it all! 

Take out the security issues, landing logistics, and step onto the Ship of Imagination. 

I'm fascinated with animals that are extinct or on the verge of going on extinct. I would start my quest with cataloging EVERY SINGLE, and I mean it, every form of life to have ever been present on this planet. I think that would be one of the most fascinating things. 

Once I completed that journey, I think I would go visit the Grand Canyon, Niagara Falls, and the Great Lakes to watch them form frame by frame. Maybe go to the Yucatan and watch the [Chicxulub Crater](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chicxulub_crater) form. 

That would be just the start of my journey through time and space.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 12:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That really is the best thing to do. 

Cuts down on the time they have to spend writing a response or calling you back. You don't have to wallow in self-pity waiting for all these letters hoping they hit their mark. People are busy, they don't want someone who is going to sit back and trust someone is going to read something, they want a fucking hustler, someone who is going to go out and get shit done. 

I'd suggest finding the firm you would like to work for, doing research on them to determine who the correct person to talk with, and then reaching out to that person for 5min of their time. It becomes easier when you have met this person or you have some type of in-office connection. 

Things will work out, but you have to put yourself in the best position for it to do so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 12:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is an interesting story about people not showing up](http://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/wayne/2017/03/21/no-show-jurors-wayne-county-circuit/99453948/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great question! I'd love to know the answer as well!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 01:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hats awesome! No wonder your eye caught it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 01:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks to me like someone dropped their fruit by the foot; disclaimer, I'm not an expert, just a sarcastic asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 01:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did this yesterday! Lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 23:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know that. I assumed it was more expensive. That is good to know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 13:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some benefits to how quickly the water heats up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 13:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um...I need this in my morning routine. Do you sell these? I will buy...now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 12:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, a combination of possibly uppers and downers; I've seen this before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 12:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not OP, but my water heater is gas :( 

I wonder if OP's water heater is gas or electric?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 12:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just go read a book in your school's library, its free.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 01:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's cool, do you sell these? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 16:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to keep the cost down as much as possible so I'll check out Yoast. Could you explain Yoast to me like I was five (ELI5)? I've watched some videos about it on YouTube, but I swear people make it much more complicated then necessary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 16:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> X5 is Ridgid's new line of brush-less motors. By being brush-less the motors do not burn out or lock up with continual usage like most brush motors do; supposedly, they are more *ridgid* (pun intended).

[Ridgid Website](https://www.ridgid.com/gen5x/)

You could also check out the line on YouTube where people put the tools through strength and battery tests.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 15:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look into your home insurance and energy supplier's website, they could offer you some sort of rebate on purchasing new appliances.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 15:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is good advise. You don't think about it, but some of the bulbs could be really old and energy taxing. Plus, if you have all the bulbs on the same install schedule you should not have to replace them for quite some time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 15:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did this! I purchased the Ridgid line from Home Depot because of the lifetime warranty. I purchased the box set up with the Cordless Drill, Driver, Reciprocal Saw, Circular Saw, Charger, and Radio. It was like $499.00, but the lifetime warranty and the X5 was a huge plus. I think this is essential for being a home owner and these will last you a lifetime with minimal regular home usage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 15:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AutoZone has an oil drum in the back of their shop customers can use to dispose of used oil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 15:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect! I have a list of 236 blog topics I'm getting ready to start going down the list and writing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 14:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started going hard 4 weeks before, but that was even after making my own outline from the start of the class.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. When you say blog consistently, you talking about writing original content for the site, correct?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, that makes sense. Thank you for your input. I guess where I'm trying to focus is on how to broadcast the blog best. I've just seen so many firm websites with shitty, non-original content and it makes me annoyed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the links, I would love to listen to these! I will edit my post when I do so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 13:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Understandable. I would be able to use a separate Linkdin account to share and link the most current blog posts, that's my idea/goal.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So your saying combine the law firms website and their blog into one cohesive website. 

Thank you for your input.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 03:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Partly correct. 

Take out the SJ concept for right now, that is a different subject and you can make the connection later. 

The Plaintiff has the burden to established that the Defendant owed them a duty, the defendant breached that duty owed to the plaintiff, the defendant was the causation (cause in fact/actual cause), and the plaintiff suffered damages resulting from the defendant breach of their duty. 

The evidence part comes with showing the defendant acted negligently, the causation portion of the prima facia negligence analysis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 02:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YEAAAA, I loved that absurd Palsgraf case; reminded me of the Mousetrap game. 

Dude, I would ask the prof. I can almost guarantee that Prima Facia *IS STILL RELEVANT* because I just went over it in my bar prep and had almost my entire torts two class about it back in LS. 

Statute = Negligence Per Se...NOTHING ELSE. 
Prima Facia Negligence will have a person, most likely a professional or someone to whom you've had a case set out some type of duty of care required, and they will usually fail to act or at in a way that is inadequate in reference to their required duty. Ex. would be if you cause someone to be in peril, you have a duty to attempt to rescue them, if you just sit and watch the house burn down after you set it on fire knowing there was sleeping babies in the house...you failed to act and therefore you would be negligent in the event the suffered damages...super absurd example, but you will remember it. There are different standard of care each person owes another given the individuals position; usually its going to be reasonable care, but most professionals are held to a higher standard of care. Standard of care = the duty owed to another.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 01:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, those are it. Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 01:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, thanks again for the response!

I guess I'm having trouble following all these "creative avenues" because there are so many of them. Essentially my goals would be able to talk to someone, who we'd eventually have in-house, who would be out web developer. 

Maybe I need to find someone now on the ground level to let them in on the beginning so they can scale the business with us so we don't have to pay someone max price one we finally start operating. But, my goals, yeah-my goals would be to essentially be able to talk to the client about what we can offer with regard to their law firm. 

The traditional law firm scheme doesn't work in my opinion and because of ethical rules attorneys are bound by in each state it is somewhat difficult to market to your prospective clients. I want to design a best practices of law firms that is almost a guerrilla style marketing scheme to put them in front of as many people I can. 

Also with the SEO, I'm putting off writing it because all these little tricks you can use with the langugage when you write it make a big difference says everything I read on the internet. (Yes, everything is not true, but a lot of it is and I don't know if it's not)

TLDR: In a nutshell I should develop my own law firm strategy and bundle what works into something scale-able to sell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 01:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * (1) Not always a safety statute, but a statute indeed. The most common example you'll see if the violation of some type of moving offense. The key to look out for is the defendant MUST be doing *EXACTLY* what the statue outlaws. I had bar prep and one of the examples was a trick where the statute was that it was illegal to text/use mobile phone while driving. The defendant was on their phone at a red light, they were subsequently pulled over and given a ticket...they were NOT using the mobile phone *while driving,* so it was NOT negligence per se. 

* (2) Id have to see the case. Can you rephrase your question, I don't know what your asking; it may be beyond my negligence expertise. 

* (3) Remember to keep these things COMPLETELY SEPARATE from one another. Res Ispa does not need actual evidence, it means "the thing speaks for itself," There is a rebuttable presumption that the defendant was the one who is negligent because of (insert factors and analysis). If the defendant can provide enough evidence to overturn that presumption, they are going to be found not guilty. Prima Facie Negligence your going to get into a deep delving into actual evidence of proving each facet required. Duty, you must established there is a duty, if there is no duty then there is an irrebutable presumption there could be no prima facia negligence against the plaintiff-motion for summary disposition, boom judge rules in your favor absent plaintiff provides sufficient evidence. In that instance you could even go with a motion to dismiss for failure to state a claim upon relief could be granted because the plaintiff did not satisfy their initial burden of establishing a duty. Best advice I could give you is to learn how these things work individually, and then learn how you can mish mash them a get them to work together...that's lawyering. Just like any other law suit this is going to go through the correct court with property jurisdiction (personal, subject matter, and venue), while utilizing the many tools at an Attorneys' fingertips to attempt to get it tossed out or ruled in their favor. 

* NO QUESTION IS EVER STUPID, seriously, I EMPHASIZE FOR A REASON! If you don't ask questions, then your not learning. Your, assuming you are, paying a lot of money to go to law school...do it right the first time. Ask questions, rephrase, reconsider, re-ask! Don't be shy. 

Um, I had my torts prof. tell us this shit was no big deal...come final time, it was all negligence. On the MBE, something like 20 out of the 27/8 torts questions will be on negligence. You need to know negligence, absolute period.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 00:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Negligence Per Se: Your driving down the street *over the speed limit* and your pulled over and given a ticket. You violated the statute, you were negligent in monitoring your speed, thus you were negligent. Statute must be involved. 

* Prima Facie Negligence: Duty, Breach, Causation (Cause in fact/actual cause), and Damages. There must be an established *DUTY.*

* Res Ipsa Loquitor: Barrel falls out of a barrel warehouse window. No direct evidence that the barrel warehouse was at fault, but there are no other barrel warehouses in the city. There are 3 requirements for this one you have to meet I think, maybe two, I can't remember. (1) Defendant must be in control of the instrumentality...I know that's one. There is no direct evidence linking the Defendant to the damages, but it was them, they were the ones who did it...everyone knows. 

*Sorry at work, otherwise I'd give you a more in depth analysis*

This is an open-source response, someone polish it up. haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Law Firm Website and Blog, together or separate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 23:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious as to the effect it has on a firm's website for SEO purposes whether it's smart to have a website with the blog within, or a separate website devoted to blog both of which would back link to each other? 

New at this game, so be gentle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 18:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, thanks for the comment. 

Backstory a little, I have some past experience with HTML. In High school (10 years ago) I have made a few websites for my school and myself using Dreamweaver and writing the code myself. 

The problem I'm running into is the information overload on how everything has changed over the ten-year span. I downloaded [Learn How to Code in HTML5 and CSS3](http://howtocodeinhtml.com/index.html#toc) and love it; It's written very well and is super straight forward. 

I'm just trying to soak up as much information at once and I think I'm overwhelming myself. I'm in no rush and want to do it "right" the first time; similar to OPs observation with their procrastination, perfecting it in your head before putting gears in motion. I have three service businesses that are in the same/or similar industry which I would be able to operate continuously and independent of each other which linking them for SEO purposes: 

* One of them would be a law firm (in the process with my state to become an Attorney);
* Another would be a registered agent services business for companies within my home state; and 
* Another would be a property management firm. 

Also, I have a friend who is in school right now working on their bachelors in marketing. He has some extensive experience working for Microsoft within their marketing team. We have talked about opening up a marketing firm specifically tailored to law firms in our home state. Where we are from, there are hundreds if not thousands of law firms that do not have any direction with how they market their business. Many of the firms don't have mobile optimized websites, some have broken links all over their websites, some have websites that just dump information because they think its a good "blog topic" and go on and on...etc. He has worked at a law firm, and with me soon to be an Attorney, our thought was to leverage my knowledge of the legal field and his marketing background to form a marketing company geared specifically to law firms. 

I may be taking on too much at once, but that's just how my brain works. My main focus is obtaining the license to practice law, and then I feel everything will fall into place. 

Edit: A set of best practices would be nice, but it doesn't seem that cut and dry anymore. This SEO shit has got me all confused, it's so fluid it's annoying. I've read you should string keywords, then read not to string keywords, just as an example. I guess I'm subconsciously attempting to sift through all this bs to develop a best practice for law firms. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This.

They are in the business of negotiating. Don't be afraid to step up to the table and fuck shit up, they are hoping you take the money and walk on to your next project.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep telling myself this for three business ideas I have. I continue to make excuses for putting off starting. One reason is legitimate, but the others are pure procrastination/fear all rolled up together. I keep telling myself that I should learn how to build websites, from scratch, instead of using something like Wix/WordPress, which would be much faster and get the job done. I just want to be able to do it myself and not front the cost, even though I know I can write the cost off as an expense. 

I'd say the number one thing I struggle with is, by far more than anything, fear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> booze, I think you forgot to mention that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Under the US Constitution Congress is free to regulate commerce under the Commerce Clause. Absent Congressional regulation, States are free to regulate, as long as the State's Regulation *DOES NOT* unduly burden and discriminate against interstate commerce. "Dormant" refers to the absence of Federal Regulation. 

* In the absence of Federal Regulation, State Regulation of commerce is *PRESUMED* valid if: 

* (1) There is *NO* discrimination against out-of-state "interests;"
* (2) The regulation *DOES NOT* unduly burden interstate commerce; AND
* (3) The regulation *DOES NOT* apply to wholly extraterritorial activity. 

You must analysis all three of these elements to outweigh the presumption that the state regulation is constitutional and thus violates the Dormant Commerce Clause. 

* (1) No Discrimination against out-of-state interests (*Most Important Factor*): Applied to both business and personal interest. Discrimination exists if state/local regulation protects local economic interest--*at the expense of out-of-state competition.*
* There are 3 exceptions to this though: (1) State as Market Participant; (2) State Subsidy/Welfare to State only citizens; and (3) Federal Approval/Ratification of the States' regulation. 

* (2) No Undue Burden on Interstate Commerce: You must balance objective/purpose of the State law vs. the burden on interstate commerce; ie. Is there a less restrictive alternative? If the State law benefits are grossly outweighed by the burden on interstate commerce--it's likely the courts will strike down the regulation as unconstitutional. 

* (3) Extraterritorial: States *CANNOT* regulate conduct that occurs wholly *BEYOND* their borders. 

Edit: Stuff. Nobody's perfect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * (1) She will be on Facebook ALL CLASS...guaranteed. 
* (2) Secret Service will answer all her cold calls for her. 
* (3) Insert sarcasm for the above bullet points... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd know some basics of the law you'll be working with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe for other people, but I buy the two dozen every other week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Case name, key facts, and the rule the court developed. 

Just synthesis each case down into a bite size sentence or two and you will remember more than you think.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. 

Also, you can't fix stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea that's the wild part for me. 

Did they really have to foot the cost to design and package two different bottles when they are offering the same damn thing?! 

It's a waste in my eyes, unnecessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, right. 

2.5x the original price...but you get 50% more! 

They play on your psychology so hard. Look at the photo again, I wonder if there is an actual difference between "extra strength" and " super strength?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did this with eggs the other day. 

* 2 dozen "grade a eggs" = $2.69
* 1 dozen  "grade a eggs" = $0.89

So naturally I got 2 one dozen cartons for $1.78, which is $0.91 cheaper...so dumb...but people get burned all the time! 

Edit: This is that math they told us in school we would need for everyday life. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you need a new realtor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've bought a few of these to work out in the yard. They breath nice and hold up well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Listen...](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4bQ1BX3hz7I)

...and then act! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really is going to depend on what type of compliance your getting into. One of those friends works in Medical Industry compliance, loves it and is constantly talking it up in positive light. The other works in Mortgage/Real Estate compliance and has some good days and others not so good. They are similar in temperament, and I would say it's not their personalities that makes it differ; it's really going to depend on your personality, goals, tolerance, aspirations, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had three friends that have done that. The base salary has been significantly higher than our other friends who have gone the traditional law firm route. They have also achieved a better work/life balance as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. There isn't a uniform set of salary scales nationwide.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't agree more, or say it any better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I've heard some really harsh stories from Cali as well. There is such an over-saturation of potential employees, naturally it's going to drive the starting salaries down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure they didn't include the data because it ranges so vastly depending on so many circumstances. I've seen posts in r/lawfirm that have talked about salary and it's always such a vast range.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would think there are a lot of solo practitioners given the condition of the market. I would also think that market to market there would be a wide difference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Listen ABA Journal, I know, how do we fix this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know more than 10 police officers who have professional-side jobs. One of them flips houses regularly, and currently is renting out 10 houses at the tune of $1000/mo per house. Another owns a PI Firm and contracts with local PI/No-Fault law firms and does surveillance and process serving. Another, owns a website-marketing business. Another, does private security on the side. 

The fact is...if you can achieve a $90,000 core salary, you can easily supplement your salary over a extended period of time by building your solo network up as you go. You don't have to take on criminal cases, but you can do transactional work to generate a lot of income. As a police officer your going to have an extensive network. 

I've thought about this exact scenario as well. I have a BA in criminal justice and over five years of private security experience; add the JD in the mix and I'm a shoe in to any department around me. I went to law school to get away from the criminal justice system, so that's my reason to forgo a PO position. Someone has posted on here that you going to have to answer a lot of questions for a while, but that isn't that hard; just site this article [Here](http://www.abajournal.com/news/article/lawyers_salaries_slipping_compared_to_other_professions_data_indicates/?utm_source=maestro utm_medium=email utm_campaign=weekly_email). 

Moral of the story is...this is your story, and everything from this EXACT^exact second is unwritten..write what you want to live! Good luck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10,000% this!

I don't know what his student loan status is, but you could also take advantage of the PSLF program.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your arguing that the legislation infringes upon a fundamental right, your going to use the strict scrutiny analysis. The government has the burden to show that the law is necessary to achieve a compelling government interest. The law must be the least restrictive means to achieve the compelling government interest. "Least restrictive" means that there cannot be a way to achieve the same interest that is less restrictive. The law should be neither over-inclusive nor under-inclusive. "Compelling interest" has no definition, but must be necessary and crucial to national security, health, and/or safety. 

Now, if the same legislation also effects a classification of persons, then EPC will apply as well--but in a stand-alone analysis. 

You should read your facts SUPER^super carefully. Even if it doesn't call for it, don't forget to address Standing, Ripeness, and Mootness. If you have something canned in your head, you should be able to jot it down right quick to show your prof your train of thought; this will almost always give you deference because they will know you know what your talking about. 

Edit: Format. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in a solid routine, I have the ability to work wherever (mostly from home), and I work that spread over 7 days. 

It's really not that bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5am. Biked 3 miles. I wish I could do that, but now my job drains me. 

(haha, sorry...it's literally the same story...I work 65+hours a week now) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha! Thought the same thing! Holy shit, bro! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
