<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2997</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever the local affiliate station wants (usually local news). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   But perhaps they will move Arrow to Tuesday at 10 PM for Crossover week

They can't do that, the CW only has the 8pm to 10pm airspace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Live+3 ratings don't really matter. The CW sells most of its commercials on C3 and C7 ratings, so Arrow is certainly being evaluated based on those, as well as other metrics pertaining to revenue. 

Also if you rank the CW shows by L+SD ratings and them rank them by L+3 ratings the order is pretty much the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 00:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It seemed more like a specifically tailored response to alarm by someone whose job it is to sell the show.

Exactly. It's just like how last year the AoS producers were spinning the move to 10pm as a good thing even though it clearly was not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because the CW shows *are* cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 18-49 demographic ratings. C3 and C7 ratings are the most relevant but also rarely released to the public, so Live + Same Day is the next best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Live+7 total viewers, restricted to ABC comedies. Not a metric that matters to broadcast networks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It was rated number 2

By what metric? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Riverdale has a better chance of standing up to shows like This is Us and the Shonda Rhimes block. 

Can't agree there. TGIT and TIU have a much different viewership demographic than Arrow, whereas Riverdale's is a lot more similar; also as a second-year show that's not pulling huge numbers Riverdale needs more protection than a sixth-year show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 21:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is on the CW. The pilot was originally being developed for Fox but they passed on it and the CW picked it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   now they are gonna compete with Arrow

Gotham airs at 8, Arrow at 9; they're not in direct competition.

  DC should try their properties to not clash with each other. 

DC doesn't control that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After Flash, assuming LoT has another 16-17 episode season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only a few CW shows made it longer than 6-7 seasons; being on the CW is no guarantee of running forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This has already aired correct?

Nope.

 What channel is this mainly on

It'll be on NBC, you can stream it from their site/app after it's aired (or get an antenna and watch it live).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if the episode count has been officially announced, but the filming schedule for Riverdale S2 is reported to run from late June to early April indicating a ~22 episode season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Arrow had the second highest crossover ratings of the 4 shows last year.

And the highest was Flash, not the finale on LoT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  big budget Hollywood won't even show two men kissing

And does the CW? In the DC shows they've shown plenty of kisses between two women but none between two men as far as I've seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trailers for The CW's New Shows: 'Black Lightning', 'Dynasty', 'Valor', Life Sentence' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trailers For New CW Shows Including 'Black Lightning' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today at their upfront presentation. The CW president said "Black Lightning at this point is not part of the Arrowverse". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TGIT and TIU both have very different viewership demographics than Arrow, I doubt they'll hurt Arrow's ratings all that much. Thurday Night Football is probably a bigger concern, although LoT held up well against it last fall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supernatural's ratings this season were only slightly lower than Arrow's, and if you don't include Arrow's crossover episode then Supernatural's were actually slightly higher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CBS sold the international rights to the show (everywhere but US and Canada) to Netflix.

As for having their own streaming service(s), of course the major networks/studios are going to do that rather than just resign themselves to selling everything to Netflix. Giving up on competing with Netflix would be stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Trek reportedly has a budget of $5-7 million an episode, *way* more than the CW could possibly afford. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  why not just wait a week before putting these out.

Because the CW's upfront presentation is today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure she already left the show; she has no writing credits this season and mostly stopped tweeting about the show a few months ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 16:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotham is against Supernatural, not Arrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 08:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arrow was always relationship heavy as well, it had a bigger S1 love triangle than Supergirl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 07:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Usually studios reduce # of eps, not increase them.

Uh what? Ordering additional episodes for a season is common and is pretty much always a sign of confidence in the show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what CBS showed at its upfront presentation so it's more for potential advertisers than viewers.

Now why they didn't make a separate trailer to release to the public I don't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but perhaps I should be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 01:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [following his exit in October as Showrunner of Star Trek Discovery, co-creator Bryan Fuller has now confirmed he has no further ongoing role in the CBS All Access series.](http://deadline.com/2016/12/star-trek-discovery-former-showrunner-bryan-fuller-1201863775/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 01:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because TBBT is massively popular so they want to capitalize on that with a spinoff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 00:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems consistent with adult Sheldon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 00:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  they had a budget of something like a $1 million per episode

Try 5-6 times that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 23:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks good to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 23:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  what about the international audience.

It'll be on Netflix outside of the US and Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just from last year.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 16:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SWAT Thursdays at 10? MWAP left off the fall schedule in favor of Superior Donuts? Not sure what CBS is thinking there. At least they did the right thing in moving Criminal Minds and Madam Secretary to 10.

Overall, not very impressive scheduling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 00:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here:](http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/amp/live-feed/abc-renews-agents-shield-1002925)

 Sources tell The Hollywood Reporter that the show starring Clark Gregg and Ming Na has been working to reduce costs for its fifth season, with ABC looking to lower the drama's budget on the ABC Studios-produced series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 00:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're down from a 0.57 to a 0.51, but okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 23:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Two months ago it was up 150% for live +7 DVR.

TIL an 150% increase is tripling. [A month ago it increased 88% from L+SD to L+7](http://tvbythenumbers.zap2it.com/dvr-ratings/week-31-broadcast-live-7-ratings-april-17-23-2017/), which put it at another 1.5 in L+7. Currently it's doing around a 0.7 in L+SD; 1.5 is not three times 0.7.

 Considering if you aren't a Neilsen family, your live viewing isn't even monitored, and streaming services force commercials on you, I don't think you are fully understanding exactly what C3 and C7 is actually measuring comparably to that of +3 and +7.

Neither Live+3 or C3 includes streaming views, those are measured separately and the numbers are not released to the public. Live+3 measures the number of people who watched the show live, DVRed, or On-Demand within 3 days; C3 measures the number of people who watched the commercials live, DVRed, or On-Demand within 3 days. Not unexpectedly C3 tends to a lot lower than Live+3, since most DVR viewers fast-forward commercials. (This all applies to Live+7 and C7 similarly.)

 The AoS doomsayers have been saying the show was going to get cancelled every single season and it has not. In fact, it's gotten better and more people are watching it than before.

Anyone saying AoS was likely to get cancelled in its first few seasons wasn't doing so based on actual data. AoS ratings (relative to the rest of ABC) were quite good in S1 but have declined every season since then, to the point where they were near the bottom this season which is why people were concerned. And it has been reported that AoS had to cut its budget for S5, a clear sign that it was not performing as well as it used to and was in fact close to cancellation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  AoS triples its ratings at +7 viewing.

You keep repeating this, but it's not correct; AoS is not pulling 2.1s in Live+7.

Additionally networks get paid for C3 and C7 numbers, not Live+3 and Live+7. How many people DVRing AoS do you think actually watch the commercials?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the comics Hank Henshaw built himself a body that was genetically identical to Superman's and pretended to be Superman, so the 'Cyborg Superman' moniker made sense. In the show there's no good reason for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he has won a World Tour race more recently than them, so maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably just got older </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supposedly it makes a ton of money on the back end from streaming and whatnot, so ABC's milking it for every last drop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 20:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Sounds like a PR spin for them being dumped on the Friday night death slot. 

Because that's what it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ABC doesn't see any syndication money from LMS since it's produced by Fox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also they've been updating the article and adding to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who else would they replace him with as their top American at the moment? He's one of only like 4-5 Americans to actually win a World Tour race in the past 5 or so years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LMS suffered from being an expensive show that wasn't owned by the studio of the network it aired on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be amazed if OUAT can hold a 1.0 all next year, it couldn't do that this year and now it's losing most of its main cast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [22 episode order for SHIELD confirmed](http://deadline.com/2017/05/abc-schedule-primetime-fall-2107-2018-once-upon-a-time-greys-anatomy-marvels-inhumans-the-goldbergs-blackish-1202094339/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the comedy scheduling, The Good Doctor on Mondays makes good sense as does keeping Designated Survivor in place, and TGIT is a no-brainer. The rest, eh... (edit: actually Sundays aren't terrible, especially with Idol coming there in the spring).

In particular, sending Inhumans to Fridays behind the corpse of OUAT really makes me think it might be [TVLine's blind item](http://tvline.com/2017/04/27/blind-item-bad-tv-series/) (though Still Star-Crossed would also still make sense for that). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't know that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SHIELD likely to take Inhumans' spot once the latter ends, according to deadline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 09:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He's not a regular...is he?

He is not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 09:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think you might have the wrong sub... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 09:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  based on no information.

No, based on all the information that was available to the public, which is far less than what the network has at its disposal but typically enough to make fairly good predictions. And based on that information things were not looking all that good (though not completely dire).

The fact that [AoS is having to cut its budget for next season](http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/amp/live-feed/abc-renews-agents-shield-1002925) shows that it was indeed not far from the chopping block. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 06:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Garber isn't listed as a main cast member for this so it shouldn't be an issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 05:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly. The CW has yet to announce their schedule, and Supernatural gets moved around a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 04:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So is Cat coming back full time? 

Nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 04:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buzz only has relevance to broadcast shows in that it will hopefully translate to viewership; buzz without viewership is worthless.

 No one watched The Americans

By broadcast standards, but it isn't on broadcast. Its viewership has never been terrible by FX's standards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 04:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LMS got cancelled because it was an expensive show that ABC doesn't own (same reason CBS cancelled 2 Broke Girls); if ABC playing politics was the issue then LMS would never have gotten six seasons in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 03:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Flash

You got any data showing that The Flash has 8 million viewers an episode, let alone way more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quantico Renewed For Season 3 By ABC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a lead on one of the most-watched shows on television makes him a star. Whether or not you personally find the show funny is completely irrelevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being fearless may be a prerequisite to being a food descender but by itself doesn't make you one. Perhaps Quintana has improved but I from what I remember he would often take suboptimal lines through corners (including taking a terrible line into a corner on a descent in the 2014 Vuelta and crashing out as a result). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Physics obviously works against him because of his size, but from what I've seen he's not a particularly skilled descender either (by pro standards, obviously). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks no hillier than the 'flat' ITT in last year's Tour where Dumoulin beat Quintana by 3:08. Granted Dumoulin was training specifically for TTs rather than GC last year, but still.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 22:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotham has already faced TBBT and held up fine.

Orville looks to be targeting a different demographic than TIU so that may not be as big of a problem as it first appears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 22:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $$$ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ratings are more for selling commercials than determining a show's total fanbase. And networks have access to mare data than just linear ratings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Don't you have to already have a cable subscription for the streaming service to be free?

They're free to stream without a cable subscription, but for some shows you can't watch new episodes until a week after they aired unless you have a cable subscription. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotham held up well on Mondays against Monday Night Football, The Voice, and Dancing With The Stars; I don't see the Thursday competition as that much stronger that Gotham would get crushed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotham already competed with Football and two huge reality shows on Mondays.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  this show has a largely male audience and is now up against football.

This show was already up against football. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but their best performing scripted show?

 Their best performing scripted show is Empire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 17:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  24 episodes for such a "dumb" show is just too much.

It had 23 episodes in both seasons combined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 07:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fox and FX may be owned by the same parent company but they're separate entities with different management. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 07:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FX </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 06:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is currently the only X-Men show on Fox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 06:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [MRW people want distance shown in km](http://i.imgur.com/6GEIUBw.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 01:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They had to cut the show's budget to get it renewed for S5, that alone shows that it wasn't that far from cancellation. 

As for its timeslot, it wasn't a megaflop like the last few shows ABC aired in the Tuesday 10pm timelot but it still got crushed by the timeslot competition on NBC and CBS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 01:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Variety says "theres speculation that the show could be a midseason entry next season" so I gues we'll have to wait and see what actually happens. If the syndication deal is still ongoing I could even see Elementary going to Saturdays.

Code Black getting renewed is not that surprising to me. It seems like the perfect schedule spackle: it's ratings last season were weak but really not that terrible, it's not very serialized (as far as I know) so it shouldn't suffer as heavily from an extended hiatus and/or getting moved around, and CBS presumably has some stake in the back-end what with it being a co-production. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 00:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's not an ABC show. It is made by 20th Century Fox and ABC buys it from them. Since ABC doesn't own it, they don't get any syndication money or streaming money.

Yeah this is hugely important. As TV revenue continues to shift from first-run ad sales towards streaming and other back-end sources, networks are favoring in-house productions more than ever; expensive shows from outside studios have to perform very well to survive these days. CBS just cancelled Two Broke Girls for the same reason ABC cancelled LMS: it was from an outside studio and cast contracts were up for renewal meaning an increase in price, so it didn't make financial sense for the network despite the ratings being pretty good in a vacuum (and TGB had better ratings than LMS). Meanwhile at NBC, Blindspot and Timeless only got renewals after the producing studios (WB and Sony respectively) gave up major monetary concessions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 00:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Isn't he contracted to Disney like, forever though? 

LMS was produced by Fox so I highly doubt he's contracted to Disney. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 00:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'The Brave' sounds a lot more generic, but on the other hand I can definitely understand why they didn't want to go with 'For God and Country'. Overall I'd say it's probably an improvement from a business standpoint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 18:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He specifically said thanks to the Flash finale, crossovers will be easier.

He didn't say that; go listen to it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 18:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ['This Is Us' to air after Super Bowl](http://deadline.com/2017/05/this-is-us-to-super-bowl-christmas-episode-thursday-preemptions-1202093177/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 18:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay? "Multiverse shit" is a prerequisite for any Flash-Supergirl crossovers, that says nothing about any merging or anything like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NBC Fall 2017 Schedule </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 18:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 18:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said there would be more crossovers in the future, but didn't go into any more detail than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 18:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't recall reading that the deal was just for 5 seasons and syndication deals are often for the entire run of the show, so it's quite possible that WGN is still obligated to buy more episodes of Elementary if they're produced. Also the articles about Elementary's renewal mention the syndication deal as if it's still ongoing. 

If the syndication deal is finished then it's hard to see why CBS would renew Elementary as spackle before Code Black or Criminal Minds: Beyond Borders. On the other hand if the syndication deal is still ongoing then I agree it's odd that it took so long for the renewal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 17:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I am positive he talked about the Flash finale having big impacts on Supergirl

He didn't; go back and listen to the podcast again. It was slightly ambiguous but in context still pretty clear that he was talking about the *Supergirl* finale affecting Supergirl, not the Flash finale affecting Supergirl. He also mentioned that there would be more crossovers in the future, but said nothing about anything changing on the shows to make that easier.

People on reddit were so set on there being a merging of Earth-1 and Earth-S that they would ignore evidence to the contrary and misinterpret stuff like Kevin Smith's comments to support their opinion. Some were still convinced that it would happen months after the EPs straight-up said that it wasn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 17:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He teased a Crisis event last year for Supergirl and Flash's finale, an event that would make "crossing over the shows way more easier", something huge on Flash that would have big repercussions on Supergirl and its connection to the other shows.

To be fair, he didn't actually say that. He talked about the Supergirl finale having big effects on Supergirl, then people on reddit misinterpreted it because they were convinced there was going to be a Crisis or something similar and were willfully ignoring all evidence to the contrary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 08:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any fan poll you heard about had nothing to do with Timeless's uncancellation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 08:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything is an emotional rollercoaster to Kevin Smith, i wouldn't read too much into this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 07:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that attributing the deaths from the nuke to Felicity's kill count is not accurate. However I think it is fair to attribute the deaths from the Undertaking (503 people) to Malcolm, which should put his kill count well above Oliver's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 07:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *When the sun goes down the tide goes out...* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 06:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colonel Flagg on MASH. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 06:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like a lot of younger people are somehow unaware that broadcast networks are free to watch over the air and instead think that cable/satellite  or streaming are the only ways to watch TV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 06:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nielsen ratings are still the standard metric for pricing the sale of commercials on networks' linear broadcasts. That says nothing about if/how networks are looking at other sources of revenue such as streaming (which they absolutely are doing). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aside from the few EPs that work on multiple shows (and have done so since the inception of the shows) there has been very little transfer of writers between the shows. If you don't believe me go and look up the writing credits for each episode of all the shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 04:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No that's quite high (and has proven a very costly mistake for WGN America). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 04:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Syndication must be KILLING it.

Supposedly the syndication deal plus SVOD and whatnot brings in $3 million an episode, which would explain why CBS is keeping it around even with terrible ratings. 

Now the reruns themselves have tanked in ratings, but that's WGN America's problem and not CBS's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 04:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess WGN America hasn't been able to get out of its syndication deal yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 01:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah Mom was at 9, and would often get higher ratings than TGI despite not having the TBBT lead-in. When they recently replaced TGI with TBBT repeats on Thurdays, the repeats rated better than TGI and Mom's ratings went up as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 01:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its ratings were heavily inflated from airing after The Big Bang Theory. When they moved it to Mondays for 2 or 3 weeks it got worse ratings than all of their other comedies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 00:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If only NBC had done the same for Constantine...

If only WB had agreed to give NBC most of the show's profits the way Sony reportedly did for Timeless... (although Constantine's ratings were arguably worse so it probably wouldn't have mattered).

As for Hannibal, NBC gave it three seasons despite it never having good ratings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 00:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It seems like that's where the bulk of the viewers are.

And you think networks don't know that? Streaming rights are a major factor in network-studio negotiations these days.

The issue isn't just raw total viewership numbers but translating that viewership into revenue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 00:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is there a reason they can't just take online viewing more into consideration?

What makes you think they're not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
