<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1713</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When i was a kid I wouldn't even think about drying myself when I got out of the shower. Now I can't even leave the shower without being bone dry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally my favorite comment on this thread
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and she clicked that for all the cards, they said they are unable to verify her and she was locked out of the account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HELP] My girlfriend went to get an ssa 1099 form and as she found out someone opened up credit cards under her name </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was helping my girl friend file taxes, and we needed to get an ssa 1099 form, so we went to the social security website. She went to create a profile and when she got to the verification page to ensure it was her it asked her which different cards she opened from 2011-2014. She is only 18 so there is no way she did it and her mom said that she did not do anything. What do we do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 07:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a truck, t-bone a smaller car at probably forty mph. The car was totaled, and the driver opened the door and I saw shrapnel in her stomach. She started coughing blood and a nurse or something ran to her and started helping her. I still remember it clearly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 06:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are those the left overs of eating ass or your mustaches?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 05:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it make your boyfriend feel inadequate when he lays his dick across your forhead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 01:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I now repair fire creators. Helping people make fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Showerthoughts are like koans for the modern world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 22:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
