<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2069</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 11:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit opinions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 11:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its an absoloute joke people think this movie is any good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 10:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im glad to see some people can still tell a shit movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 10:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol comparing shaw to newt and hicks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 10:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats what I mean, the whole thing is poorly fucking written. Alien,Aliens alien 3, even resurrection, all had plausible reasons for where they take place and why, not simply ignoring all logic for no real reason. He shouldnt be that stupid, as a captain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 10:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Resurrection shits on this movie. And its not because resurrection is great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 10:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a disconnect because ridley doesnt give a shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 10:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you stupid?  He CLEARLY didnt trust david. He fucking wanted to kill him. How is that trust in any way shape or form? Would you suddenly let someone you wanted dead say "hey lookit this its kewl i swear"? If so you would be a moron </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 10:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Resurrection shit on it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many alien movies did someone put their head near an egg because someone they tried to kill for being shady told them to? Remind me  of that. Its not the act, its why he did it and how. David could have koed him and forced him into the egg, that makes way more sense than trusting a guy your gut tells you is shady. And if youd look because a guy you dont trust tells you too, that makes you one of the dumbest human beings alive


And its a plot hole because its fucking stupid and doesnt make sense,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 05:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really think season 4 got a bad rap. They worked it as best they could and i still appreciate how it all weaved together </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO the only canon movies are alien four movies and avp movies.

Im totally ignoring these in my own in head canon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> David is jar jar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont understand why people like these prometheus characters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 03:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that still doesnt explain it. I mean fifield was nothing like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 02:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh? Bishop says hi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were both crap tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should have been a different script </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah this should be fuckingg common sense to be honest

If someone you dont trust asks you to stick your head into something weird, who the fuck would be stupid enough to do that???

Its like people who accept this stuff have no common sense. Nobody would realistically do that. It would be different if david was his friend or earned his trust but the guy nearly killed david and thought he was shady </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 23:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this gonna be on region one blu ray? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 20:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its kind of a joke you can get arrested for comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol dude im super glad we are leaving the eu. I voted out and am so happy and glad the country might finally go back in the right direction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 19:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank god someone else wants those. I actually brought the original xbox for the first buffy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whens it out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is indeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its common sense dude. A person you know or strongly suspect to be shady asks you to put your face in a thing you dont know what the hell it is. Would you do it?

Like really, now. If you knew someone who was dodgy and they asked you "hey  put your head in this weird thing i made"  would you really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think its hilarious how triggered you are lol :) im happy we are out of the eu shitshow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wanna explain how the EU has that shitty human rights list that makes criminals more important than victims? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it fucks the eu then its good for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont need to get upset. Lions dont worry about sheep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Farage should pocket money from the frauds. Good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UKIP got what they wanted all along though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/worldnews/europe/eu/8837224/Scandal-the-European-parliament-tried-to-keep-secret.html

What now lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its an echo chamber what do you expect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It SHOULD be purely trade and security. Not laws . Its not our fucking buisiness how other countries are run. If you had a brain in your head you would see historically interference makes things worse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/worldnews/europe/eu/8837224/Scandal-the-European-parliament-tried-to-keep-secret.html

Yeah totally non corrupt.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The donald is better than this shit.  At least they are only 90% retard, this sub is like 99.9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what it should be or what it is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah ok. You got them hugo chavez posters too i bet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well thankfully we chose,to leave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im showing you twats the EU are an undemocratic organisation that overstep their boundaries, like when they replaced democratically voted leaders with their puppets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol NO, you are just an echo chamber just the opposite end of the donald. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A plot hole is a plot hole if it doesnt make sense, and none of the things they do in prometheus or covenent make sense. And no, i dont think anyone buut the biggest fucking idiot in the world would not trust someone then put their face in a fucking literally alien egg. Thats dumb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ridley said they arent xenos different creatures </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you can do it again this week then cant you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your arse is grass and I have a lawnmower! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LOL Posts showing the EU in a bad light are deleted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 13:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Show some love for Tucker and Dale vs Evil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/8BwQBjJvN5Y </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any love for Tucker and Dale vs Evil? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One track lover is one of the greatest songs ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The negatives like major logic and plot hole errors?  Whats wrong with wanting narratives to make sense? Isnt that what story telling is kinda based on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where does it imply the goo creates xenomorphs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It still doesnt explain anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Check out Garth Merhengi's dark place </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tucker and Dale parodied typical slasher movies in a far better manner in my opinion. Far warmer and an homage, this felt more like a hollow piss take which would be fine if it didnt try to be a parody of bad slashers by being 90% a bad slasher.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 12:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone a fan of the comics? Hellboy kinda lost steam imo but BPRD is fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 10:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah dead orbit first issue was great! They have really been doing a great job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 10:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah some of the art in life and death wasnt great. But i did enjoy it, seeing marines back in the modern aliens universe. And defiance is 12 issues i believe, nearly finished </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 10:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So explain those plot holes then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 10:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is retarded though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 10:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes because a lot of people are idiots </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 03:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you trolling? I kinda think you are lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 03:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 03:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I mean they had pretty much proven the engineers are completely hostile and kill humans on sight and even went as far as planning genocide. You wouldnt get any reasonable explanation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its been a while since I saw prometheus but im sure she was told or figured it out?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone reading Aliens Defiance or the avp/a/p/prometheus life and death comics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aliens defiance especially is really impressive, half way between alien isolation and aliens in feel with great art.

Life and Death was pretty solid but not as good as fire and stone last year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bug Hunt is very meh imo but has marines 

You should real the original trilogy of novels,  earth hive , nightmare asylum and the female war.  Genocide is good too, marines on a planet overrun with two clashing xeno breeds
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So does anything in covenant make sense?? (Spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.thespread.com.au/sydney/alien-covenant-10-things/

Those are some pretty fucking stupid things in the movie.

Davids motivations seem to make little to no sense. Hes a creator who kills? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 01:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made this thread yesterday :p

alien 3 is up there with aliens for me as the best movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 22:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bro! Its barely second to aliens but its close. Super close. I love it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 22:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant when he put the goo on charlie. Why didnt he do controlled experiments with human tissue instead of risking everyone, including himself? And doesnt he have programmes to not kill, or at very least not kill weyland who he also endangered? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 22:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Days gone and last of us 2, tie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 22:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cant wait. As much as I dislike how sapowski distances himself from the games, the books are actually excellent too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 22:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never gonna happen but Id love remasters of the buffy games and call of cthulhu. Darkwatch too. Blood omen 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 22:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Youre right im being a bit unfair. Its just I cant stand how its been handled so far.  So maybe ill be wrong and eat my words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 22:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gotta admit not yet LOL. Tomorrow. I just fucking hate the idea this android somehow created the aliens. Its terrible. Its also retarded shaw trusted him and went after the engineers in the first place. Its completley contrived and feels like ridley has no real plan and is making it all up. No way are you gonna convince me he planned david creating xenos, he admitted he didnt even want to do more xenos untill after the prometheus audience reactions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 22:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But sociopaths tend to care for himself. How would he know his little experiment wouldnt kill him as well? In fact events he set in motion nearly did. Does he lack foresight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 22:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do they not know with all the recordings ? And are you telling me no scientest is smart enough to figure it out? And what about behavioural moderators? Isnt he supposed to be emotionless and logical? And how did he know his experiments wouldnt kill him?

And what awnser do you expect from a super hostile race who was on their way to wipe you out and attacks on sight? Would you ask ebola why it does what it does, or cancer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But why? Whats the motivation? Are you saying he has no sense of self preservation or just common goddamned sense? LOL but hes supposed to be a super smart emotionless android? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok since youre being cool ill respect your opinion too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since youre dicktucki the plot holes heres two for you out of many :D

Plot contrivance: It made no sense for David to poison Charlie with the goo. He is the most advanced android in existence; spent two years guessing an alien language from snippets of old languages but somehow  skipped all the literature on basic scientific process. If he wanted to test the black goo on humans, he could have tried in a controlled environment in a lab with a sample of human tissue. He did the complete opposite of that. No one knew what the black goo would do. He infected one man with it and let him loose. How could he know Charlie would not transform into a monster in an hour and try to kill him? Or that he would not spray airborne viruses from his lungs and transform everyone in monsters that would have tried to kill him? David  had his own motivations, but he put his existence in jeopardy and the only reason he didn't die was because of circumstantial luck.

Plot contrivance: The effect of the black goo is all over the place and unpredictable like a diva on PMS.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aliens shit on the first Alien. 

And alien 3 was better than alien too. Unless youre one of those pussies that cries how it was depressing lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The stupidity of it.

I dont believe ANYONE would be fucking stupid enough to trust a homicidal robot, davids intentions are cliched and make no real sense,   And plus the whlle idea of shaw going after a murderous race who hate humanity is fucking stupid. The stupidity of prometheus is a basis for covenant. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL

http://www.movieplotholes.com/prometheus.html

There you go, you admit you love plot holes and movies that make no sense logically :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its worse than either.

And its bad because its obvious ridley has no clue about the franchise outside his own silly and stupid ideas. Its obvious he didnt want to carry on making alien movies with xenomorphs so hes had to retroactively change prometheus to force them in and it shows. Sloppy ass shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lets remember Ridleys "brilliant" ideas for alien </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - alien turns people into eggs, which makes little sense if they need hosts to be born. Camerons idea made much more sense logically.

-alien was originally going to mimic ripleys voice after biting her head off.

Thank God they didnt happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well so is Ridley scott! He doesnt have a clue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Youre telling me you read but you think shaw trusting david makes sense? LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By enforcing their rules and laws on a country with its own already. Democracy people!


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably have trouble with the whole reading thing :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. The audience doesnt seem to notice. Or at least the dumb ones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you dont mind shit things :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But didnt you say you liked convenant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colonial marines  covenant. And i fucking thought that story was bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they watching us? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus fan fiction isnt actually licensed :p. So thats not quite right  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how embarassing is it they are better than the films currently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not mad, the comics are actually superior in terms of story. Or some are anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 20:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not fucking surprised. The left dont agree with you, no matter how reasonable, youre racist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how you get downvoted for calling diane abbot racist but nigel farage  who has never said anything about race is by the same peoples token. Wonder why? Hypocrites

Diane abbot said "dont play the whites game." What does that mean you fucking idiots? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And thats just covenent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you not fucking watch prometheus you fucking dummy?

David infects and kills her husband you goddamn dolt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diane Abbott is a racist cunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL no reason? He killed her fiance!  Brutally! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol thats democracy right?  Pressure and Force your rules and laws onto other countries.

Yup, democratic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU pressuring Poland to change its laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She rebuilt him from a head. After he caused everything that went wrong in prometheus, and betrayed the humans multiple times and infected her loved one on purpose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You tapping little girl? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 19:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would take ressurection over an android creating aliens any day

I mean, shaw would have to be the galaxys biggest idiot to trust him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You admitted youre in a couple with a dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 18:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can tell you objectively anyone that prefers alien covenent to any of the other films except prometheus has shit taste.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
