<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1101</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bobby Moynihan Departing Saturday Night Live After 9 Seasons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 03:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bobby Moynihan Departing Saturday Night Live After 9 Seasons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 03:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 01:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Created by a Trumper. Sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 13:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank mr bernke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 00:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love to read these headlines and then immediately see the Republicans' measured reactions like this one: https://twitter.com/rachaelmbade/status/864608676740554752 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, he does have a character actor look about him. I can imagine him playing some meek old man on a TV sitcom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't exactly give him a chance as much as I deluded myself into thinking he was just being crazy to get into office so he turn out to be wouldn't be as bad as I feared. Nah, he really is an insane motherfucker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Montana </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah Pence once wished Garfield a happy birthday on the House floor. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tHnZphCBWTA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 04:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh? That's the whole point of the site. Put a name in there, it works. It's meant as a site to generate random joke articles about celebrities.

I'm not saying this news is true, but mediamass doesn't disprove anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 03:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mediamass is bogus. You can put any celebrity name in the URL and it vomits up those death hoax articles that are all the exact same outside of automatically generated biographical details.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 01:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I hope trump never stops digging and grinding into these people's eye."

Same. It would be just awful for him to motivate the people who hate him to vote against him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 23:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First Dr Ken got the axe and now this, must all be part of The Community Movie comin to fruition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 20:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the rate and coverage of them being disowned it's more than likely a strong case against Ben.

 it's probably true because it spread across the internet really fast

Que?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 00:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This Is Why Trump Won

How? What will Trump do to specifically combat this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 21:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC didn't the remaining Lostprophets members just form another band with a new vocalist? I dunno if that's really crumbling. 

I'm no expert but it doesn't look like the other PWR BTTM member will be able to come back from this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 18:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, he's right. The kind of people that like Al Franken aren't Republicans, and Republicans typically like Reagan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 18:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, if that guy was talking about Eastwood politically, he's right. His only experience is that he was the nonpartisan mayor of Carmel-by-the-Sea for less than two years. While from what I understand it's a beautiful place it's also not very populated or well known, so it's easy to see why his empty chair debate is probably what would come to mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 18:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not old enough until 2024 :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 18:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I really doubt he gets away with visiting Trump.

The Rock though? If he had experience, he would be a shoo-in for POTUS. He's poised and professional, level-headed, and nobody really dislikes him. I'd say his biggest issue is that he is barely involved politically. Normally when a celebrity is able to glide into office they've still been active politically for a while (Franken with his many books and radio talk shows, Reagan rooting out communism in the SAG, Ventura as a small-town mayor and third party champion). The Rock all I know about him politically is that he was registered Republican for a little bit and he disapproved of Trump's travel ban. That's not a whole lot to work with especially if he wants to run soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 18:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ted Nugent

Don't you mean FUTURE SENATOR KID ROCK?

(Anything come of that?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 18:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you on The Rock, not Kanye though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schilling I seriously doubt walks the walk. He would get destroyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 17:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends. I wouldn't be so sure Trump has opened the floodgates. If some celebrity runs for the presidency with no experience, I wouldn't vote for them. For house/governor? That's been happening for quite a while, and is worth consideration if they prove themselves politically viable. It's also worth noting that some people just aren't electable. For example Antonio Sabato Jr, a minor celebrity and vocal Trump supporter, says he wants to run in his CA district for Congress. You could think "oh no celebrity!" but it is so blue that he stands no chance. (I forget the exact district at the moment, but IIRC it's the one with Westlake Village in it.) Also, there's the fact that most celebrities are left-leaning and therefore hate ol' Donnie. Don't think they're rushing to follow in his footsteps.

I don't particularly care about people rambling about 2020 until it actually happens. For example all the rumbling about Zuckerberg doesn't concern me because he is basically the definition of unelectable; he has no charisma, is a horrendous public speaker, has loads of baggage, and no Democrat will accept some experienceless businessman after Trump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 06:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care about a huge racist screaming at Muslims crying in a mugshot. He is just going to vote Trump again in 2020. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 04:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Renewed](http://ew.com/tv/2017/05/11/agents-shield-season-5-renewal/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't Imaginary Mary like three episodes in? They really eviscerated that one...

It's aired seven of its eight episodes so far, but it was one of those shows where the network chopped the amount of episodes it got even before it hit the air, so it's clear they didn't have any faith in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ABC cancels comedies "Dr. Ken", "Imaginary Mary", and "The Real O'Neals" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 01:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 20:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to go against the grain here and say I thought Making History was pretty bad. It was an interesting concept but I didn't care about any of the characters. John Hancock and Sam Adams were quite annoying and I've hated the last few episodes that centered on them, and Leighton Meester's character's whole thing is that she's unassuming and from the past. Yawn. Yassir Lester and Adam Pally had decent chemistry together, but the show itself just wasn't all that entertaining.

Son of Zorn felt like it could've become good if it had another season to iron out the kinks. The problem with it was that Tim Meadows and Jason Sudeikis were far far funnier than anyone else in the cast and it was just annoying when they would focus on stupid relationship stuff with the kid who was a terrible actor. Also it's pretty funny that they ended the season with an insane cliffhanger which will now never be resolved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 05:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty shaky and last season was admittedly full of filler but it did get quite good near the end I thought. Plus regardless of what you think of the show it shouldn't end on a cliffhanger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 21:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is just angry that Blumenthal is older than him yet doesn't look like a walking dumpster fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God damn. Trump is such a fucking idiot. He has hours and hours of bad press because of this Comey thing, and then breaks his silence by lamely insulting Chuck Schumer and addressing nothing else. Time for another round of "I can't believe people fucking voted for this guy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad Wolves Lower is doin well. Definitely my favorite Chronic Town song </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LOL, looks like Trump's got a new banner on Twitter. He totally doesn't care about this investigation though!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I hope they come back, but I honestly feel it works fairly well as a series finale

How come? If it gets canceled sure, this is probably better than last season's. But I would be pretty sad if this was the end, there's a lot of buildup they have yet to get to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not well. Their new submissions feed is a goldmine of salt atm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *puts Le Cap on Le Pen* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally Not A Cult </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not right now! Go 6'4" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember some dude a few days ago smugly going "ChapoTrapHouse has more subs than this sub, truly you are all irrelevant!" 

Wonder where he is these days... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the camera work in this new season is definitely poor. It is the same flat shot for both the mads and the SOL. It's a definite step down from the previous seasons, and the fact that it's in widescreen makes all the dead space that much more notable.

Also, am I the only one who thinks movie sign is a bit too stationary this time around? The camera pretty much just wiggles a bit and that's it. Feels spectacularly lame each time. Are they afraid they'll show the edges of the set, or is the camera just stuck in that one spot?

For the most part I think the new show did a decent job at capturing the charm of the old show despite having a huge Hollywood cast and crew, but there are elements like these where you can tell they might've gone a bit too sterile and glossy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to the gulag with you also you write so sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no! Mar-a-Lago is closing for the season? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, without any proof of when it was cut I have a hard time caring. Lots of shows are blindly trimmed down for re-release with scenes chopped indiscriminately. For all we know this could've been edited out in like, 1997 with no motive behind it at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lolin hard at "current president (my president)". What a dweeb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It is not clear whether the 1996 segment was cut when it was first uploaded, or whether the edit was in reaction to recent controversies over Bill Nye's stance on gender identity."

This part is pretty important imo. It could've just been a syndication cut that Netflix has always had. I personally doubt they'd go back and remove something like that, given that Netflix has a lot of "offensive" content that isn't edited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank Sen. Joe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, shirtless Trump sounds like anything but hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just feel bad for the people who voted Trump not because they're alt-right but because they actually believed he'd bring back jobs that are long dead. Then again they will probably vote to re-elect him so maybe I should save my pity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one thing that makes me feel slightly better about all this is just how damn mad you know this dude was under Obama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's ok, but it's not even close to second best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not exactly family, but the second host segment in The Brute Man is him and the bots calling his girlfriend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, Mike is by far the best host of the show. I know a ton of people disagree but I like that his era gradually snuffed out the all-ages lightheartedness of the Joel years. I mean, just look at that dark SOL!

also, his "three guys carrying on" dynamic with the bots is far superior to Joel's "loving but wacky family" one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see the problem. Of course it was rigged against Bernard the underdog. Everyone agrees with him on everything, so how can you explain his loss. Checkmate. Now to make it up to him we must allow Bernard to become king of and radically transform the party that did not vote for him. Neocon hacks like Jon Ossoff will eat dirt but True Progressives like Heath Mello will finally get their time to shine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was on /r/bikinibottomtwitter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, there were 21 KTMA episodes, so Joel would have 86 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant in terms of the majority. I would be fine with a progressive person taking Heitkamp's seat, and am definitely not a big fan of hers. I just want to go to bat for her as a reasonably useful tool from taking the GOP out of senate majority </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, I'm not a huge fan of Heitkamp or people like Manchin, and I wouldn't cry if the seat went to a different Democrat. But, jeez, comments like this:
 A red state Democrat is a Republican in any moderate/liberal state. The idea that we should support her just because she calls herself a Democrat is laughable.

I mean, come on, you don't have to be going YEAH HEITKAMP and begging people to vote for her, but can't you at least acknowledge the fact that she's useful in getting the Senate to a 51 majority? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Govtrack.us' placement is from bill sponsorship. More than a tad misleading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, this doesn't accomplish that. If this guy defeats Heitkamp and wins election, nothing happens. If that happens and this guy loses, the Republicans get another seat. What this guy really should be doing is waiting a few years and trying to defeat Hoeven </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Ossoff even an "extreme liberal"? He seems pretty benign to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd watch an Obama-hosted MST though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hi hows it goin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: he's also in Stranded in Space from season 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It still doesn't fit the sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno I have a hard time saying that it's some impossible task because we have 10 whole seasons of the old show that mostly got it right. The old show mostly realized that 5 seconds of dead air =/= 5 seconds of riffs. It's not really a criticism of "this isn't funny!!", it's "this is poor presentation." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's definitely more apparent in the riffs in this season. It's blatantly obvious they aren't actually watching anything and the riffs are pasted in. For example the most recent episode I watched was Time Travelers and their riffs on the credits start the exact frame the credits fade in. (The joke on the Directed by Ib Melchior credit is halfway out before the name is even legible.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely he has to be joking. The last time a Democrat really cleaned the EC was in 1964. The Republicans are by far the party of the Electoral College Landslide, and this goober thinks his 304 electoral votes entitles him to a seat at the "against all odds" table? Jeez. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the way the SOL is staged, how huge he is doesn't really register in the host segments, but his silhouette definitely looks towering. Had to look it up to find out the dude is 6'5". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please calm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, this was a huge improvement over Reptilicus. The movie is just so mindbogglingly stupid but never really dull, hard to believe they never tackled it in the original series. Every character is nuts, the dubbing is ridiculous, and there's pretty much no plot, just consistently random scenes (Paul getting caught in the net is one of those hilarious moments in an MST3K movie where no riffing is even needed).

I agree with everyone who said the bubble transitions were pretty weird. Kinda distracted from an otherwise decent invention exchange.

The riffing is quite good in this episode. There are definitely a few moments with the rapid-fire joke strangling but I think this movie is much better suited to riffing than Reptilicus, something stupid is pretty much constantly happening so they don't really have a lot of dead air to fill.

The lack of any transition between the segment with Pearl/Bobo/Observer and the theater was kinda jarring. Surely a quick fade wouldn't have been hard to do and woulda looked much nicer. I agree that Bobo didn't look too good, but Bill barely missed a step.

Favorite riff: "No longer will a hipster read the liner notes of a Tame Impala album." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't contribute because I didn't think it was gonna be any good. I feel like a bit of an idiot now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm with you. I think Joel-era MST3k, while good, pales in comparison to most Mike MST3k, and I've been really liking the new season. The only parts that seem especially Joel-like to me are the invention exchange (which tbh I'm not that big on) and the fact that goofing with the silhouettes is a bit more pronounced. Jonah himself definitely seems to be taking from both hosts in his performance, and the riffing reminds me a lot of, say, season 6 - Joel's sensibilities are there, but it's definitely its own thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laughed so hard when the gun was pointed at Paul and then "roll credits!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Captive Worms

:V </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overall very good. Mostly solid riffing and decent host segments.

Praise:

- Jonah is a great host. He feels like a good mixture of Mike and Joel and he has solid chemistry with the bots, who are also reasonably funny themselves. I was very pleased with how natural they seemed even in this one episode.

- Felicia and Patton are a pretty solid duo. I was laughing really hard at Patton failing to come up with any actors outside of Dirch Passer.

- I really dig the Moon 13 house band. The way they play old songs is a great way to throw the old show a bone.

- The song in the first segment was amazing. Classic MST3K right there.

Criticisms:

- I don't really like the new opening sequence. It's too theatrical and showy and doesn't really mesh with the rest of the show. I saw a bit of episode 2 and it's pretty stupid they do the "huh what the???" bit both times. The fact that the Robot Roll Call is in silhouette with no identification is also pretty lousy.

- Tom flying and Gypsy dropping into the theater are both pretty useless additions. Definitely feels like adding stuff for the sake of it. Tom flying is probably the worst offender, though. It wasn't used for any good jokes and was just distracting. I get they want to play around with the silhouette but it's kinda hard given that the HD makes it a lot smaller.

- The puppetry isn't great. I'd give it a pass for being the first episode but I expected more from the fact that each robot has 3 credited puppeteers. But it definitely doesn't seem like these are professionals operating them. Crow's mouth hangs open when he talks and Gypsy's barely syncs up with her dialogue. They don't feel very animated.

- The riff paces needs work, yeah. For the most part I didn't think it was as bad as most people were saying but there were times where they definitely needed to slow up. Strangled a few good jokes simply because they were tossing out riff after riff.

- The show looks nice but it's not shot very interestingly. Just straight ahead flat. The old show at least had angles!

Best riff: "It's just a sign that says Made You Look."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 06:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't heard it yet but don't the whole band have writing credits on it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't Netflix originals available on every Netflix? For instance Netflix lost the rights to the FOX seasons of Arrested Development, but they're still able to stream the season that was made for Netflix.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Vimeo vhx site connected to the Kickstarter where backers can stream the episodes, obviously non-backers can't stream the videos buf the thumbnails (which are the film title cards) and the host segment summaries are viewable to all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also not a real article. Mediamass is meant to be a joke news generator. You put in a celebrity name and it generates several articles, one of which is "victim of death hoax". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mediamass is bogus. You can put any celebrity name in the URL and it vomits up those death hoax articles that are all the exact same outside of automatically generated biographical details. Don't trust it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think he would get the nomination if he pledged that. You get a huge bonus at re-election just for being incumbent. Would the Democratic Party really want to go through primaries again just because their guy is old? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you explain to me how those 4 above aren't to the left of Ronald Reagan. I admit that I'm not an expert on any of them. But that seems hard to believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Non-backer with serious question. What's with being all hush hush about the titles, host segment summaries, and guest stars when they're all public on the Vimeo package anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad, sorry, I guess I got mixed up there. Still though, I have a hard time using these polls to guess how he'd do in a presidential election where all eyes are on him. I get why he'd be popular now, a few months after the election where he's seen as "the one that got away", but come three years when he's older and if he's the leading candidate going against Trump with all his baggage flying out in the open, I don't think it would be quite so glowing.


I think Bernie got out of this election season relatively unscathed; if Trump truly wanted to attack him, there's a lot he could use, and as far as I can tell he mostly avoided him. And there's also the more superficial issues I mentioned like the fact that he isn't really oozing with charisma, and his age (there were rumblings about it this election, could you imagine 2020?).

Of course this is all incredibly difficult to predict but my stance on Bernie being kinda middle-tier in terms of electability is pretty firm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are fighting immeasurable corruption and faux progressivism within the Democratic Party and helping regular America in seeing the light, as evidenced by Bernie being the most popular senator in America. These people likely will no longer vote for corporate Democrats. The Democratic Party is eventually going to wise up and realize the country doesn't want stupid efforts to prop up liberals no one wants. I am excited for another term of Trump, not because I support him but because America will finally realize Bernie was right all along and begin to make actual progress.

edit: yes this is a joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. He would turn 80 months into his first term. And he looks really old already. If he got two terms he would leave office at 88. When Reagan left office, he was just over a decade younger than that. 

I feel like, regardless of VP, people don't really want to vote for such an old man. It also won't go well against Trump, who would be up for re-election at 74. Surely it would look incredibly lame to put up someone who's way older. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I dunno, I think I'm kinda crazy at times because I seem like the only person who seems this way, but I don't really get why Bernie is seen as really electable. I myself don't have pressing issues with him and would vote for him if he was the nominee, but I just don't get it. He's not really all that charismatic, he's really old, he doesn't have a good minority base, he isn't popular among moderates, and I definitely believe his positions would rev up the Republican Party like we've never seen.

I also definitely get your point that he's sort of untested. We never really saw the Republican Party go after Sanders, and Clinton had to get his supporters to vote for her so obviously she couldn't really either. He has skeletons, though, and I think they would play really well for the GOP. You think the Trump camp wouldn't love the "man goes home" essay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He's not much older than Trump

Eh, he's a full presidential term older, which imo is important. Like if Sanders got elected in 2020, he would turn 80 less than a year into his first term, whereas Trump would only be 78 at the end of a second term. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, this is a crippling loss. Because, you see, a Republican was elected in a super conservative district, but this time it was a close race for the first time in like 20 years. This dooms the Democratic Party.

The super negative reaction from folks makes me sad. To them this is yet another direct affront on Bernie Sanders' politics from the big bad DNC, and not the fact that this district is so conservative is hurts. Like, is this really that unexpected? Thompson is very liberal and he did really well in super conservative Kansas! Don't you think this bodes well for like Pennsylvania or Michigan or any other state Trump won in an extremely slim margin? But nope. Just growling. You'd think a Republican was elected Governor of Vermont or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nooooo, that's my birthday. Donnie better not try anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly not old enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Martin Sheen is far too old. We'll have to put up Charlie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 06:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Souter retired years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? How old are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 03:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has like a billion tweets about Syria that have decidedly aged poorly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 13:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump Sr got demolished in New York, why does this guy think he has a shot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ivanka tweeted about ending the wage gap the other day. I found it incredibly baffling. The majority of MAGAers aren't the type of people who put much stock in the concept of the wage gap, and it's a pretty liberal thing to tweet about while your father is Donald Trump (and you work for him!). Tldr Ivanka is confusing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man Seeking Woman Canceled by FXX </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man Seeking Woman Canceled by FXX </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great article. From what it sounds like, they totally nailed it.

Except for the fact that it reminded me the bots aren't being^operated^by^their^voices^yes^im^still^salty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbf Gener has a few stinkers under his belt too. Rivers could've gotten him if he wanted to!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to see I'm not the only one who doesn't really dig this one. Michael's voice is pretty annoying and the melody isn't that interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bumper sticker, window   side decals... fuck, this is some next level economic anxiety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Sauce](http://metro.co.uk/2016/04/22/exclusive-john-lydon-talks-pil-punk-and-donald-trump-5795582/)

Also worth noting in this new interview where he praises Trump he also simultaneously praises Brexit. While in that above interview he says "To leave [the European Union] would be insane and suicidal." Gee, sounds like a true centipede... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
