<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3065</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 18:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm happy for the kid, at least he has an opportunity to do something if he wants to.  He's already a black belt which is an accomplishment in its own.  Past accomplishments are a good predictor of future performance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He seems to be well on his way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 17:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd make him bark like a chihuahua if I were bubba (kinda like squeal like a pig if you know what I mean wink wink). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 04:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea they played videos all the time, I would record my favorite ones on the VCR and watch them again later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 03:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I still don't get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-18 02:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw it on MTV when the video came out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 22:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry man, good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 22:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to their chart they should work together, maybe you got a bad shifter.  I am assuming you read the manuals and set it up per instructions vs winging it.  You should probably contact their tech support or customer service. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a bike mechanic but I was looking at the SRAM compatibility chart and everything is compatible...What size chainrings are you using?  The chart specifies 44/33/22. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 21:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 02:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems the consensus so far is the "winners" don't get punished, only the losing side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 02:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reading material!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 02:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info!  I didn't even consider when the UCMJ came along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 02:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you heard of IMBA? https://www.imba.com  They have a forum area and this is where you will find the answers you are looking for.  I have no personal experience on getting land access, good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 23:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome reply, thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've just been seeing people argue about war crimes that were committed in the past when, at the time, they were not really considered crimes.  It's easy for us now, long removed from the situation, to criticize what was normal behavior during times of war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thanks I'll check them out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the Lieber Code allowed reprisal against recently captured POWs by musketry.  Can't do that anymore.  Do you know of any instances where a Union soldier broke the rules of the Lieber Code and were punished or was this more of a guideline? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See what you get from talking to the anus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 21:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's right, the officers were from the aristocratic class back in the day and they had to maintain political ties back home for the most part I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out Time Z pedals.  They are clip less and have a platform, it's what I run on my xc bike.  I've had them for a long time and they never gave me a problem like my old SPD system.  I started out using toe clips and eventually switched to clipless and never looked back.  I like to be firmly attached to my bike and not bouncing all over the pedals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like the first step is to secure permission for building trails before you start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 19:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why you need to wear a helmet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, so the trials were conducted at the end of the war.  I'll look into those to see if they knew they were willfully violating any prior agreement.  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I'll do some reading on the Hague Convention.  Thanks for the reply! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> History of the concept of War Crimes question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 17:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How well established was the concept of today's version of "war crimes" during the American Civil War?  I saw some discussion about war crimes on another post during the civil war and I am wondering if they are applying today's concept of war crimes onto the actions of the armies of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a rare piece of history, make sure it stays in your family.  I like the picture of the big storks nest on top of the old house!  Thank you for sharing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like this was the last time the Whitehead torpedo's were used in battle anywhere.  https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Whitehead_torpedo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 16:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very interesting, thank you for posting!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 05:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, gotta strengthen the core for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 05:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got four! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 04:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I remember reading about different suspension designs and how they react to terrain differently.  My bike has the Faux Bar design and when I stand up to power up a steep hill the torque tries to lift the back wheel off the ground which makes it spin out easier vs old hardtail.  Or maybe I'm hallucinating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 02:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $5,000 you say...I'll definitely check more into it.  He's only 8 and he said he doesn't do it that much but watches videos or other kids scripting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 17:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I rode a hard tail for years but now I ride FS.  The main trade off I noticed is the FS lack of climbing ability compared to hardtail.  I had bar ends on my hardtail and I could stand up and pedal, you cannot believe how much traction those things have until you try one.  I miss technical uphill climbs, sorta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 06:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My daughter had made them today while my wife was at work...We ate all of them before she got home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are these separate spank sessions?  If so I would recommend cutting the number down a little, maybe 3 max. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's Japanese porno cartoons.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your service! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last cookie on mother's day...I'm not the mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I yelled at you earlier, I'm bipolar and have multiple personalities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Punching the clown, petting the pickle, shukin' the Tater, jerkin' the gerkin, jackin' the lumber </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bomb dot com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put hotels on Board Walk and Park Place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty calm, almost sleeping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like fake nice people.  I can see right through it so don't even try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 05:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only a movie, chill out man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 22:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, I have mental problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 16:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure about the down votes...the man asked a question, I replied with my experience of not performing any maintenance and the longevity of the components with said lack of maintenance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 16:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean 50 minutes right?  I usually eat a power gel every 45 minutes to keep me going on rides over an hour.  Anything less than an hour ride for me and I'm fine with only water.  If I go longer than an hour without eating anything I start having mood issues and start having a bad time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 06:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm talking about!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 06:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 06:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried only water on a 35 mile ride, I didn't make it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 06:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My last FS bike I had for 8 years and serviced the rear shock once towards the end before it was stolen, never touched the front shocks.  My current bike I've had since 2011 and so far no service and no problems...If it ain't broke don't fix it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 05:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of war material the US was able to muster was three times that of all the other countries combined!  If the US had remained neutral throughout the war and not provided any materials whatsoever the outcome in Europe would have been much different.  Here are some very interesting stats:  https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Military_production_during_World_War_II </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 03:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out the IMBA epic map...https://www.imba.com/model-trails/epics/all-rides </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 06:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said earlier that the guy who raped his 12 year old daughter should literally have a new asshole torn by bubba...With a broken broom stick.  Fuck that guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 06:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should've could've would've...Should of could of would of, once I saw should've of </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 06:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A large angry man wearing camouflage threw a trash can down the bay and woke us all up after getting 3 hours of sleep.  I was wide awake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 05:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here, I really don't remember when I learned how to use a clutch.  Maybe I was born with it like you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 05:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hero with Jet Li.  The sound is awesome on a surround sound system, the story line is great, the action is on point, it was done in Chinese which adds to the whole martial arts theme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 05:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My kid loves playing Roblox.  He would always talk about whatever he was doing on there and for a while I didn't want to hear it.  Then I realized this is something he is passionate about so now I let him tell me all about it and I ask him questions to keep him going.  He likes building things and scripting (still not sure what that's all about).  I watched a part of one of your videos yesterday and that's cool you two make videos together.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in a similar situation as you but I HAD to run because I was in the military.  I was in the Air Force for about 10 years and we never had to run but then they came up with fitness standards so I had to start running.  At this point I have been biking quite a bit so I had my cardio base built up like you.  The problem I found was I could go out and hammer out a couple hours on the bike but barely run 1.5 miles.  This was before internet so I was on my own.  I have learned that being good on a bike does NOT transfer over to being a good runner.  Different muscles are used and it takes lots of training to get them strong enough to be worth a crap.  Another problem I developed was plantar fasciitis, which may be what you experienced with the heel spur issue (I'm not a doctor).  That's because I would go out and run long runs without the proper build up to strengthen my ligaments and tendons, basically I was doing too much too fast, apparently you need to build up mileage slowly over time.  So "becoming a runner" is going to take a long time and you need to ease into it or you will get injured, unlike biking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 19:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sick fuck gets what he deserves.  I hope they put him in the same cell with big bubba and he tears him a new asshole, literally...With a broom stick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 18:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wanted to live in Salt Lake City.  It looks like they have everything I like to do close by.  Plus they have four seasons unlike Texas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 18:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bam!  https://www.amazon.co.uk/d/9jt/BICYCLE-DISNEY-GOOFY-HANDLEBAR-MOUNTED-SQUEEZE-HOOTER/B005FVXMT0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 16:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A real man isn't swayed by marketing hype. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 14:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I can explain.  When I'm out on the trails I'm out there to have fun and relax.  I want to be alone in the wilderness and not be comparing myself to other people or even myself while railing some sweet single-track.  I have used it trail running a few times though just to track how far I went.  Running is different for me, I'm there to torture myself so I'll be better at MTB'ing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 05:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something something violent pose...TURN THAT SHIT DOWN!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 04:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Air Force mechanic...A yard of flightline, bolt stretcher, K9P, fallopian tube, prop wash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dirt.  I vaguely remember eating dirt as a child.  Once I ate some that had oil in it from my mom's car in the driveway, I think that's when I stopped eating it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't.  My parents were anti sports so I never got into it.  I did ride my dirt bike, 4 wheeler and snow mobiles a lot and I enjoy watching a good motocross race even if I don't know the names of the guys racing.  That is something I can relate to, I know how much skill and conditioning it takes for a person to go that fast on a motorcycle.  I'm guessing it is similar for people who played football or baseball as a kid, they know what it takes to be able to perform at the professional level and probably wanted to do it at some point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Statistically speaking, you have a better chance of being struck by lightning (1in 960,000) than die in a plane crash (1 in 1 million).  However, you really should be scared every time you get in a car because your chances of dying in a car crash are 1 in 4,433 if you live in Montana.  Your fear is irrational compared to the other every day things that have a higher probability of killing you so relax and live like there's no tomorrow!  (Because you might die choking on your dinner 1 in 4,404) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping for at least 85, possibly 90. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A hand crafted turkey sandwich made from HEB's finest brand name wheat bread, stuffed with Kroger's mesquite smoked turkey and a slice of Kroger brand pepper jack cheese topped with a slathering of spicy mustard.  Chased with a 12oz can of Mountain Dew and a few chunks of freshly cut pineapple.  Mmmmmm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen many smart people make stupid decisions and I have also seen stupid people make good decisions.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have Viagra for that now...Be careful what you wish for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had the same problem as you.  You want to recreate the scene and the feelings you had while you were taking the pics.  I have come to realize that it's not really possible and I try to disconnect my feelings and memory of what I saw while taking the pic and focusing more on what I can make it look like afterwards because I rarely get a photo to come out like I "wanted" it to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my pics, I do what I want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in the military and was stationed in Alaska and was transfered to Louisiana, I'm from Michigan and we stopped by to visit family.  I didn't want to leave AK but I had to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea we thought about walking around devils tower but we used our imagination lol!  We did actually pay to go check out Custer's last stand, that was worth a stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For lubrication it's not what you want to use but I like the way old stuff looks after coated
With WD...to each their own I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it were mine I'd rub it down with WD40 and let it look old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got out and looked, left the car running, snapped a pic and hauled ass.  I was driving from Alaska to Michigan and had to lay down some miles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 42... I went full suspension because I had moved and the trails were a lot rougher and my hard tail was slowing me down.  It's up to you if if you feel the need to go FS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is one on this site but doesn't say who made it:  http://www.oldengine.org/members/gamtra/images/WoodShop/Thumbnails.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was eating at a diner and the KKK walked in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turn that shit off and go do something fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are 3.8 liters per gallon...It's always on the urinal flush handle valve deal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion you are not evil but you are an idiot.  Sure, you've found a way to cheat the system and not get caught...so far.  But like you said, you're constantly stoned and it's just a matter of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot BY GOD between West and Virginia lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there little buddy, you are getting red necks and white trash mixed up here, they're two different things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're so poor you have internet access!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That dirty damned scruff always fucks shit up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually it's redneck for "bad ass car truck" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our cars for shooting up were in the back yard, ya'll are real rednecks lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My buddy had an El Camino we did this with.  We lived close to tourist town so we went down town and made a scene, splashed water at hot chicks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did the dog notify authorities? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm willing to bet not everyone would be ableor willing to get this guy's pic, congrats for pulling it off! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After being on r/photocritique I have found myself looking at pics on other subs such as this one and thinking of some constructive criticism.  I stop myself every time because this sub is not asking for a critique so it would be rude to give one unsolicited.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it cold out or was he slingin'?  Maybe both? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first MTB was also a GT!  It didn't last very long, I am mean to bikes and it didn't hold up very well but this was back in '97.  Now I have a Merida 120 and it takes a beating and keeps going.  Welcome to mountain biking, if you keep at it you will reap the benefits when you get older.  Most people my age I know or work with have all kinds of health problems but I'm doing pretty good relative to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fired up a bong?  I can see at the bus stop but during the ride, inconsiderate!  There was this one guy that would get off the bus and beg for a cigarette at every stop and if nobody gave him one he would dig through the ash tray and collect all the butts and smoke them.  Another time I had to sit next to this huge fat guy and he fell asleep and was snoring like crazy.  Every time we hit a bump it was like a snoring bowl of jello.  Sat next to a nice Canadian girl my age one time, that was nice for a change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha my bad!  I've been thinking about developing my own film so I just assumed, oops.  Welcome to the club! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tuck your shoe laces into your shoes so they don't get wound around your pedals and you crash.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
