<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3183</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> grinding and mmo's kind of go together though. it's tough to make long lasting content that doesn't involve something that's slightly grindy. 
   
hell, climbing ladder in hearthstone or even heroes can feel grindy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the real answer is yes and no. the cross-genre incentives are there. and it could be a way to work destiny into it as part of promotion. more likely though, being that it's not blizz's IP or directly a blizz game it won't be. 
   
I'm not saying it's a lore thing but in many ways, it wouldn't feel right. I also imagine as an fps thingy you wouldn't have nearly the flexibility you do with other characters that don't already overlap with current characters or overwatch ones.   
  
And as a lore thing, it just wouldn't feel right either in some ways. I really, really, doubt it'll happen. It could. But def isn't likely. If they did anything it could be like a play this and this and get rewards for both games without introducing a character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i doubt that. blizz has as much leverage and say in this as activision does. hearthstone makes like 20 million a month? a month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to a degree, depending on how the company is structured and how much of an emphasis is placed on upselling, depending on the exact field it very much can be people who are brought into a poorly defined and executed job. 
   
if that makes sense. not saying you should do away with your common sense. partly i don't believe everyone is born an asshole but being trained by one makes it much easier to fill the shoes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 04:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, you gotta forgive us for fucking our Unions up. Then forgive us for thinking about me, first, on an individual level. Then you have to teach us all about NAFTA and the TPP which wasn't nearly as bad as people made it out to be and got scapegoated in the election. Then, maybe, throw in a class about international economics.  
   
Then send some of the jobs back!!lol...lol...  ]
   
Sigh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 22:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but this is what's throwing me for a loop. 
   
if the plastic of the bed of the pickup doesn't ground the can, doesn't the plastic of the can not ground the can? aren't you the ground in both cases?   
   
additionally, i think the spark, either way, very well causes ignition traveling through the fumes of the gasolin rather than the gasoline itself, inside the can.  
   
edit: either way kind of interesting to think about. maybe an /r/askscience or some youtuber could figure out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 09:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> isn't it grounded in the bed of the pickup though? and wouldn't a spark go to the gasoline over the plastic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 08:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm listening to them argue and stuff and don't get me wrong, Shermer was citing, once or twice to be fair, one of Jared Diamond's works. Or possibly two of them. I do believe it was only *Collapse* though. I'm not sure if there are similar criticisms on that work as others. 
   
I really started to lose it when they were really pressing hard for the Sphinx and the signs of water erosion on the wall that may indicate that it was much older than we thouht.  
  
I google the professor who wrote hte paper, and some peopel do agree with him. On, one all (is my understanding) of the one sphinx there's evidence of what appears to be water erosion on one wall that would mean it was much older, 12,000 years. That professor also believes in telepathy though. And that really just put me off. The strongest argument, that we can't find any other evidence of a society, no pottery or other ruins of people living or using anything there. And it seems hard pressed to say they just disappeared.   
  
Forgive me fore typos or anything, it's late here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 00:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How hyped are you guys for the James Webb telescope?  
   
this is some cool shit man. Grats guys n gals! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the currently accepted theory for structures like Gobekli Tepe and these older large structures? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 00:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I'm curious, as an added question, the risk of proposing alternative theories on speculation for things that we don't have evidence for yet? Additionally other examples of 'alternative theories' would be interesting.   
  
I'm not going to bullshit I was listening to Joe Rogan's podcast in the background today while cleaning and he had on Graham Hancock (author), Randall Carlson(architect), and Michael Shermer (editor of skeptic). Some of the conversation they had were interesting regarding advancement of theories and the growth of those theories vs mainstream scientific thinking.  
   
Seems to be somewhat big in archaeology/history? To a degree? Or does it taper off the closer we get historically because of better record keeping?  
   
Just seemed like this interesting aspect of studying and in the process of discovery. Is it important to challenge mainstream ideas? Or is it dangerous to do so on light amounts of evidence? Is there value there?  
   
I guess my mind is kind of blown, and I write too, fiction. I make shit up writing fiction. A lot of times I base what I write on some factual stuff. But it really seems like it's a dangerous place to go. Or a profitable one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 22:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
if a baby has a cosmetically shitty cleft lip. not one that medically sucks because they can't eat just cosmetics, do we wait till it's 13 to make that choice on its own? Because that kid's going to feel pretty pressured and ostracized to do that. 
   
Shameless did a bit about a teenager getting the circumcision done. And the doctor tells him to try not to get an erection while it heals, few days. When a young man, or person, is going to feel them most pressure to do it and uncomfortable with their own body, 13-24, they're also going to be their most hormone boner popping selves. So it sort of feels like we haven't even thought through the results of what we're wishing for here. That it might be worst.
   
It's not necessarily 'right' how we got here, but we're here. don't be ridiculous. and then there's the whole when you compare those discrepancies in how the law applies, and how we got to those differences...i don't man. it's jsut such a stretch and a me, me, what about me! mentality we all need to lose.  
   
i appreciate you sharing ab it about though and there is a point there. i think the circumcision vs fgm one is poor one to stand on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 23:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol why? does it matter either way? seems like a mean thing to say!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 23:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my bad dude!  
  
yeah and i was jsut talking about the rag sucking. once u push her off the core kill teh catas, heal and you're good. rest of team cores. lol 
   
my bad tho! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 23:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did I say they were missing any? Thought I made it clear that I felt 'modern' feminism really has a poor focus. And that many of the issues are ones that can benefit everyone.
  
I think right now a big focus on maternity leave that isn't punishing the worker, along with paternity leave is a big one. Better handling of sexual assault is another one, for both sexes.  
   
In modern society I think we've really checked most boxes for women. Minus maternity leave. We've done a pretty good job. Ofc like anything similar to this we're not done but getting there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 23:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think you're playing semantic with the circumcision. is forced male circumcision a thing?   
  
personally, I'd much rather have my circumcision done as a baby. I don't need to worry about considering the choice later in life nor go through the pain and discomfort.  
   
And not because it's healthier or more hygienic as neither of those things seems to really be an issue with if you shower and can take care of yourself. But like not having the option...really just doesn't effect me at all and really feels like we're making an issue out of nothing. 
   
Are their cultures that are a bit backward when it comes to this? Absolutely. Just like there are cultures who have it backwards with FGM. But that's a stark difference there right? We call one genital mutilation and one by its medical/cultural name. 
   
So even if doctors were wrong but did it with the right intentions. That it doesnt actually effect health and the hygiene issue is a nonissue, culturally it's now a differentiating thing that definitely leaves some people making a really difficult choice later in life.  
  
I don't know, I'm sure it's an issue with some people. Just a small one and really seems to be grasping. I've read up on a bit about it but it generally just doesn't seem to be this widespread thing that's really hurting us socially as a group. Not as men but as a society. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 22:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a guy I get a bit confused about men's rights. Are there thing like abortion decisions, custody, sexual assault and stuff that are sorely overlooked? Of course. 
   
But I'm not sure what 'rights' I'm missing out on, outside of those which don't apply to me, that I should be concerned with. 
   
If I felt there were I would have sought out help or delved into it more. Never once did I think, man, that's some bullshit! Cause I'm a *dude*!  
   
I don't know I have a hard time taking them seriously. Most feminists too for that matter. Nowadays feminism exemplifies that militant natured shit from the 60's   70's and that's no good either. 
   
Treat people...like people. My god, what a fucking revolutionary idea. That shit irks me that it's like oh me, me , me! My group, my group, my group! 
   
The more you look at shit, the more you realize what's good for one or a part, very often is good for most if not all. Not always. Sometimes things are awarded to people who shouldn't have it or abuse it in some way. But generally, when it comes to rights of people, awarding those, besides on a human level as something that should be taken seriously, I don't think anyone ever said! God Damn! We let them have x! Now look at life! Unless you come from a place of misaligned unreasonable hatred, that isn't based on fact.  
  
just looked up the definition of egalitarian...do  i delete this? lol.  
   
just been trying to move away from labels i guess.   
   
edit: i understood it's meaning in context was curious what it's definitive definition was </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 22:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I liked the show a lot, most of it. I'm not hating on it either. DOn't take it from that perspective.  
   
The language I used certainly implied that but it isn't quite that really. I just think it's gonna be in palce of a trauma but not that it neglects a whole otherworldly thing going on. I just think we haven't even begun to touch on it really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 21:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah so what he's suggesting isn't a good play. Because outside of pro play not only is that difficult to execute (and in pro play) there's still no guarantee it works. If the really did small wall and just focus the keep then core, imo, it still might have been close. they only kinda get to the gate when she's with catas getting to their core. 
   
not saying a keep doesnt fall fast, it does, but red's keep fell a lot faster. 
   
imo what the did was fine, and in that situation, absolutely right that would have won the game. just hots shit. dude was bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 21:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, if I was going to bet on it I wouldn't. And partly it was a visceral reaction to an overwrought, ridiculous ending. And I don't get to be too cynical anymore. 
   
That said, the director and the people who worked on the show, their comments are what absolutely pushed me over the edge. If you say something like 
  
and I'm apraphrasing but, 'Well, whether every detail is true or not doesn't matter when it comes to the message' or 'If it stands as metaphor or story...' 
   
That kind of shit just is a big red flag from a source you can trust. 
   
And the fact that it's an unpopular opinion absolutely adds a bit of strength to it. But it's not going to be a flat out lie. You can't alienate your viewers that much but it'll be in place of some trauma or something. 
   
I think the way they threw it in there at the end is just not that well done or it should have been done on its own without the shooting part. The way it was 'thrown' in there felt like a red herring but you don't just throw something like that out there.  
  
And I absolutely take a big leap with the whole, If 7/10ths are made up then all of it must be, particularly in regard to the being blind part. But it almost, because of that, makes me think it's the one thing you won't believe is coming because it just isn't anticipated.  
   
edit: and the fact life of pi's been in the pop culture in the last 5 years, bound to be something influenced by this. this just has similar markers.  
   
and you're telling me that a girl, missing, for 7 years pops up and the FBI didn't have a massive manhunt for the other 4 captives? That don't have google searches when other people besides her look for them? I guess I missed a bit in the beginning episodes here or there but still. 4 Other people are captive, somewhere a x hour *drive* from where he dumped you, he shot a sheriff, and noooooo one found this guy or this place? Where he's experimenting on people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 21:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> everything. like literally everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me and my gf just finished this and we really enjoy it...almost all of it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 02:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's going to be spoilers here in case you still care, figured I'd give a heads up.  
   
 
   
That ending though was either overwrought or just plain not needed. That's really frustrating because hinting that the whole thing was a lie was cool. And really added a solid dimension to the show. But then the next part was just like, really? Come on. 
   
As far as what I think, regarding all the theories, is that she very well was lying. Even, possibly, about being blind. Probably developed as a response as a kid to her trauma. I absolutely think she was lying about a large chunk of what 'happened'. 
   
As to why she was lying I think it was probably something akin to Life of Pi. Where the trauma was so bad or the experience so horrid that she needed, in order to cope, to come up with an alternative version of it.  
   
Especially when you consider what the creators said about details not having to be true or whether it was a metaphor. It all points to her tale being made up.  To what end? I don't know. But probably not from her being crazy, or not just that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 03:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i fuckin love you guys. because you do this because you love it and do it in a way you love. which isn't only admirable, but badass. 
   
was just missing it, dopey me.~~that said, wish there was a more accessible class tier list or maybe i'm just missing it.~~ 
   
also what's really good with the ADWCTA led NYC (queens what up) fireside/grinning goat meet up? lol. had to throw it out there man. and throw in some nyc slang as much as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> was bout to comment here. saw how old it was and thought...ill just give em a poke and say hello! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 23:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> me and my girlfriend say...
   
he's a slipper seal. 
   
really. we do that. weird level *100^^^emoji* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 22:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wasnt tryen to be anything just silly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 21:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah? got a source? who made you all high and mighty to decide that?  
  
kids these days. just hop on wikipedia on their phones and babble out whatever they see first! surprised it's not just a picture with an arrow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 22:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks like the LIE a lil bit. doubtful but really reminds me of it for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 19:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jerseys so ehhh. Just not really contributing but just there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could also be confirmation bias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the whole thing just pushes people to suicide. There's no right answer, you laid in a coffin and mentally accept that death. Now you realize you don't need to pay anyone 20k to die. And off yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, at least proof of the bankruptcy and shit like that is a first step. Because it very well could have been a nut stashed away for the shoe dropped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not exactly. Because scripted by whom. The implication is the government. Clearly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vegetarian, didn't see that coming.

Not that it matters or has any bearing on it but, for a moment, I thought there was some genuine passion for steak in there. Lol, must of been the history.

Actually been thinking of going vegetarian. As is my red meat consumption is super minimal and my chicken etc. Isn't that high either. Was considering giving it the final boot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it could very well be hung up around a college campus for a bar near by...and that situation if pushing it by a long shot even. And if The Friars are the band then this is almost just non sense.   
   
So here's to hoping it's for that one scenario where it counts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure how it's so low.

It's still not a bad thing. Nor do I think it's even staged. It's probably a mix of genuine good guy pilot and company sayen, hey, let's show how we treat our passengers. And didn't even get a camera crew for it and they had to ask her to hit the call button didn't know who she was.

Point being it's not manipulation of reality. And the point also being that if you don't know it's a manipulation there's no harm done. Hell I don't remember what airline it was. You don't even see a logo in the video. It's so not planned or if it had any involvement by pr it's was to share what's a genuinely nice thing in light of some shittiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean what's the difference? 

One of you gets no joy out of this, the other a ton. In this world it's hard to keep naivety but if I could choose I'd pick it everytime. Sure as hell try to at least.

Like most things this very well probably fell in the middle of both. He had the idea, checked with the company who said, sure have your stewardess film it. Or he loves the company enough he saw the value in it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Priest isn't bad either because of the heal friendly character spells and dmg enemy spells rather than the more ambigous  3 damage to a minion. At least in my experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends though. I think the care was covered but these may be procedures he wanted, like he describes in his second AMA rather than needed. Additionally I'm not sure why he didn't go back to his original doctors for it. And if he didn't want to and choose to go to another doctor for the surgery I don't know why anyone would expect him to not have to pay for it.

Plus, in all fairness, it was an accident. But then he choose to pull someone off live lines. Am I missing something here? Here's a hair short of a Darwin award. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy was in a car accident. Lines went down and another person in the accident exited the car and got electrocuted. He pulled them off the lines and got electrocuted.

They paid for the surgery and after car. I think a lot of his other surgeries were plastic surgery touch ups so it's as nice as he wants it to be. 

I'm not entirely sure why he didn't go back to the originals MDs for the work, cause then it'd be covered or if it was deemed not necessary why he wouldn't think he would t be on the hook for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen the show Black Flag? The depict Nassau, and I dont mean to ask if Nassau was somewhat lawless, but that an island or area would take pirate goods for sale to other ports.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wondering if there's a bit of context we're missing. Also, for hanging on the outside of a bar or something like that it would be kind of clever. That's the kind of place people loiter around smoking or waiting on line. 
   
It would probably work in that context. Where people who are seeing it already know the bar and venue, and go to it, and now they're just getting the upcoming band nights.  
   
edit: my intial reaction was disparaging because the font is a bit small, it takes a lot of reading to get to the information that matters and i think i took it slightly out of context but after i realized it was probably being hung in a place where people already knew htat information it made a bit more sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's fear as much as its plain economic logistics. If this pops off it's going to happen because SK is done putting up with their shit. They're the ones that receive random rockets and shit like that. But what do you gain? Besides a few million refugees. The natural resources won't pay for the war for a couple years. It'll be a money sink shit show, that risk paralyzing or destroying your own economy when it happens and possible destroying much more from nuclear attack.   
  
So what's there to gain? Wait this fucker out, let them revolt or something eventually, and then keep em fenced in and sending aid. Imo that's the business way to do it. 
   
The human in me says we have an obligation to get the fuck in there and do something. People raise dogs for meat. They're starving and dying and the price of human life has become too cheap with the toll too high. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think to a degree one of the largest things against that possible argument, because in some ways it's unfalsifiable, is that he didn't figure out how this works. It's been what North Korea has been doing for a long time. Beats their chest, gets a bit of aid. The system was in place long before he got in power, he's just using what works. He also hasn't figured out a better way to do it. Which would really be the direction he should have went in. To a more traditional dictatorship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't think Trump knows how NK works. In the sense of gifts and shit to maintain power. Gifts or violence. It's not genius. It's criminal. And while not a terrible system in the sense of it's effectiveness, it wasn't a system this Kim created. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking of Easter I really wanted to go to the mass this year. They hold it on Shinnecock Inlet at sunrise and it was super warm.   
  
https://goo.gl/maps/yZbTPpgX4YE2  
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's nothing wrong with participating in the ritual. Both the institutions and your family's. I had trouble with  this because when I first stopped believing in god I really felt religion wass the opiate of the masses. And was more Sarin than opium (having done the latter...lol I'd be at church every week if they were similar!).    
  
I felt it was an infectious poison and nothing reflected that more than my parents insistence on church as a habit but not as something permeated into our daily lives. So that shit got me pissed, confused, and naturally  I wanted to push back. Oh to be young, read too much philosophy, and have testosterone. Read: to be a bit of a dick. 
   
I've really come to respect the institution. It was this class called Misotheism (the idea of hating god or faulting god an holding him accountable). Religion brings the best and the worst out in people. I don't want to get too far off topic but generally it probably tips the scales a touch more into the positive. Either way, as something, to the people I know, they feel betters themselves and consequently the world through their actions, no matter how occassionally, it's something I don't need to abstain from because locally it's not corrosive. 
   
Plus just as a respect thing. I can respect the ritual, my family's beliefs, and their own ritual for holidays, participate, and litmus test if God does exist every now then for good measure (if I combust when I enter the church or touch the holy water, so far, so good).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I get it. It def could take a second to say hey wait! Once a year? But I get it. I also agree with Christians/Catholics going 1-3 times a year.

What's interesting in this chart though is less those numbers and more the many times a year/month/week because it's of Americans who don't believe in God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girl dated a....damn can't remember it's a Spanish word that's super similar to it's English counterpart like invigorated maybe or...shit.

Anyway crazy long services and intense speaking in tongues stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I get it an made the post to someone else except I said, you don't go to Christmas Mass but you do go for a funeral.

Lol... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I might not go for Xmas but I'll go for a funeral. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honestly part of me wants to say that an area being traversed by humans probably can't have anything sprayed that's too harmful. Chemicals like that tend to be bad just being in the area, especially sprayed, and don't need you consuming it to make you sick. The other consideration that is usually abided by is the wildlife in the area can't just eat a thing of grass and croak either. Not that I'd eat them really. Just saying probably not nearly as bad or dangerous...aaaaand I could be completely wrong, but one time prolly ain't gonna kill ya.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same with never and less than once a year. makes sense though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hooked up with this chick during the day, the evening  with the girl I was almost dating and the night with some other chick.

And that time I met the husband the next morning with a mix of surprise and shame. 

Shrug, you only get to do that kinda shit once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was laying in bed listening to it. Thinking, lotta thunder...wonder if anyone is out there getting shots.

Glad to see so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 10:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so i read this comment and am like...i come across what looks like a decent jerk chicken and there's no recipe :( wtf!...next comment down...thanks! looks great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 10:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i know right? wtf guys. 30? *Fucking* thirty. That's some verifiable bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any time someone 'leaves to form their own thing' it's usually that much more radical/extreme/bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh nice man. Glad to hear you make use and enjoy it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I picture the party all happening under a table as legs converse. Or conversely a party where everyone lays on their back and swings their legs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. You really get surprised by the camera a lot on difficult shots. It seems like it'll be impossible and it might be hard but you'll get it eventually. Good shit man. Might have get me to the range a bit more.

Ever have issues, if you have, bringing your camera in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tips, all appreciate seeing someone share what they know. I absolutely get the direction for the settings to get the shot. This just seems like an incredibly difficult shot to get. Was really curious what he was shooting. And if he was a pro. I'm skeptical you'd get anything like this without being in the 5d range.

Really, I get the low aperture but focusing. Focus on the front of the gun and shoot through the shot?

My cameras old, I have a few lenses one is a prime with f1.8 (85mm). Nor do I shoot all that often(guns). Was just impressed that if he weren't a pro that he got such a great and difficult shot.

In case you missed it he said it was a still from a slowmo video. Makes a bit more sense. Regardless of the range you're shooting at, the environmental settings like that can all obviously be accounted for I feel like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro...

Bro you gotta tell me how you made the ring of fire to shoot through it? Makes such a cool photo and a textured sense of where the bullet is going.

I'm joking ofc. What camera are you use though? And what are your aperture/shutter speeds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I thought you meant. Then I thought maybe he rigged it anonymously and won." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder what happened? OP deleted text to their post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God damnit, this is Reddit and it's pitchfork time. Maybe your comment is relevant. And maybe it contributes to a similar conversation but not the conversation.

Don't throw the witch Hunt off! 


Lol jp, that's super interesting. The anonymous part is confusing me though. He scammed to win jt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless, even if his photos were the best and say he deserved to win.  
  
The ethical issues here are absurdly wrong. Period.  
  
Apparently he was taking money from people to enter too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> burned! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was no stop to it. Blink and you missed it. 
   
Gone in a flash. 
   
Generally contests shouldn't include $ to enter, at least in my experience with writing contests. Occasionally there's a small reading fee. Obviously judges can't enter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  i do know it's some variation of a standard askH mod post sticky. super curious how it translates though.
  
the amount of people having a god damn discussion about latin grammar is a lil astonishing. 
   
really smart or a bit crazy? or a mix of both... 
 
i mean that with the utmost sincere love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pffff.

Pepsi's ad team had an idea like this too probably. But Pepsi also has someone who really wanted to us a celeb spokesman too. And ultimately they have poor judgment and taste. Let alone atrocious execution.

Don't give em a drop more credit demand better ads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either way, to a degree, you got to introduce yourself. Like I open a letter hey, this is m from blah blah. 

Don't think it's like that bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> would a no kill kind of run be like way out of realistic kind of aspect to that scenario? 
  
It is clearly a video game, so realism isn't waht you strive for, to a degree. But if you create a world, you try to stick to the rules of that world. And making the no kill run, incredibly difficult with some killing by proxy seems as good as you'd get in a post apocalyptic world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> made my comment like 'ill do it, pm me' 
  
scroll down and saw another 2-3 people with the same sentiment. lol. 
   
i also think, at stern, there's a good chance people are just hirin someone to do work that they need done but aren't expected to do themselves. Unless it's writing a business plan for them. It's an MBA program. like get a grip dude we're all adults here. Don't be a tattle tale on some shit like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> without details to the project i'm not sure how you don't know it isn't kids who had an idea for something, as part of a class project/school of business, who are expected to hire someone to design their shit?  
   
Stern actually starts companies or whatever. I doubt anyone who be expected to 'learn' design while studying for their MBA. 
    
If you won't do it, explain to them why and PM me. I'll take the work. 
  
Design/Web Design i'm good for. Development I'm not as strong with but can do that basic ish.  
    
Props on you for asking the question. But really, is this an issue? Like come on. Plus I think you might be projecting more into a situation than its reality actually is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i suppose it really is an all or nothing proposition though.  
  
Saving it, who knows the next time he'll really be able to sit down and enjoy a drink? I say, fuck it. Enjoy that shit before you have 2 kids and even less time.  
  
Don't take this out of context it's fulfilling and all that, kids are demanding, especially newborns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> writer checking in here. googled it (er maaay have a few physics tabs open...fucking youtube physics videos) it's pretty much straight off of the wikipedia page. 
  
 and what's interesting about that is it gives several variation, with that being described as explicitly regarded to change. Which is kind of...implied? I feel like when you mention time   distance in the other equations.  
  
That said, for the writerly part. He thinks he's being clever and really he's poorly communicating.~~And part of me wants to smack that smug look off his face.~~  
  
Writing Knowledge is Power (Or [Insert Equation]) would actually be funny. And, I wouldn't need to Google shit. I'd even go so far to say I might be more intrigued to Google it out of a positive sense of curiosity rather than a pestered one. 
   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think everyone here is simplifying something through their anecdotal experiences. 
   
sometimes psychologist do just cut through everything else and physically force someone to bear what it is that's prohibiting them mentally with real world results. and sometimes it works. 
  
you don't know that this wasn't the first time the guy did it or if it was happening out of depression or apathy. and maybe they did do a favor.   
  
not that i agree with it, making a decision on someone else's behalf with such an arrogant take on it but i also don't think judging the action as actually good or bad on a topic that none of us are experts on is just pretentious bullshit.  
   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is like whale ambergris. It forms in the digestive track comes out looking like poop and is worth 1k-10k a pound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for sure man. keep on...ehh i hate that saying. keep crushing it! 
   
lol. and the reality is even if someone is doing it, if you can do it faster or better then you win anyway.  
  
ha, speaking of ems. i wonder if that would apply to something like that. you input all the 911 calls and then tell it 1. how the call was ranked (as in critical vs non critical 2. what the call actually was (critical vs non critical) 3. the critical nature (heart attack vs breathing problems. 
   
and then, especially with repeat callers, depending on what they say if it's a critical call or not despite what they tell the opreator. 
  
they do have some hard factors they use to disqualify things, or rather, qualify them and it's easy criteria (breathing/heart problems) but a more specific evaluation of that might better utilize resources.  
  
i'm going to see i pretty much had moved on from it because i'm not sure I could beat that response time improvement, and with such a practical take on it too! but there's lotta possibilities with that kind stuff now that i'm thinking about it.   
   
edit: particularly to streamers themselves. they do 0 marketing. no email lsits no merch ( or lil) like the email list thing drives me nuts. licensing this to them might be tough but it might not be as tough to try and get smaller streamers trying to grow to use it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuck it, leaven it. mighta been on mobile. 
   
mighta just been a whole lotta don't give a fuck it's reddit. 
   
meh.h </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hooooly shit. 
  
man you know, especially when you play, there's certain ways to hit guys. and out of all those you know a few choice ones that are likely to take em out. 
   
sometimes for a fewm inutes, sometimes the period, sometimes the game, and sometimes for a while. but you're trying to win. so that's hat you do. 
   
of course no one wants to really hurt the other guy for good. but tryen to win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my thought exactly. 
  
it's also exactly how you fuck someone's knee or leg muscles up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i also own the same lamp. can't tell you where it's from though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> had to check what sub i was in for a second. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have that lamp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So son, we actually conceived trying to do this experiment and we'll yeah, that's that.

Was I...An accident?

No, no not at all. We just didn't consider that outcome. Just an anomaly. In hindsight by all means you were not just random chance considering the poor controls.

There's a joke there somewhere I don't know the right words to use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er 4500?
I got a stupid place for like 250. On or some range time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it'd def be a bit of a brain fuck (surreal) to eat right? like oh this is dessert. it's dessert. it's dessert just eat it, okay? okay. oh it's spaghetti...i mean dessert!  
   
damn this shit is good. is this real life?  
    
edit: especially if it loops at all like spaghetti. things that look like other things but if you have to 'cut' it into a piece or fork it in your brain says okay that's not what it looks like. but if this had any visual stringyness to it it'd be like dayum yo!  
   
then again, i'm not sure what's real life anyway. most of the time. and i'm pretty sure this is just a simulation. with it running so well i need to balance it out and buck the trend.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and honestly a touch of oil at a 3:1 ratio to vinegar isn't that bad for vinaigrette either. especially if it has some healthier fats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm really running through possibilities. And it sounds awesome man, good work.

Before people tell you shit you might be able to sell it anyway. Either to Google for people subbing to YT live shit they watch. Or applied to comments sections of shows maybe after some modifications.

Or to Amazon so that, whether they have it or not yet, no one else gets it to market to their users (like an MCM) who very probably doesn't have anything like this.

That said, it's possible that they may not have even gone that far and something simple as visiting a stream twice within a month with one email follow up turns it into a sub or follow or some shit.

I was trying to figured out if you could do predictive EMS (for 911) based on age, race, sex, etc. And even within some health systems people who have the medical history as part of a hospital system responsible for their transportation (or even nursing homes). 

Anyway, it's a baby idea that I'm doing research on with the goal of reducing response time by one minute, 9min to 8, roughly. Thinking that would be enough impact.

Then they start a program of fly cars, where paramedics respond in a truck and the ambulance comes after. The truck/flycar response reduced response times a minute on its own.

So while very cool, and don't want to discourage you, sometimes the world is wacky is all. But figure it out and I'm sure you could sell it somewhere. Super curious about it too.

You could consider licensing it to streamers themselves who then, if they started running email lists (they should but don't, thus MCMs) could target any crossover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also think to an extent people that are there, talking to chat are obviously already followers. How many of those are resubscribers?

Sounds super cool though too. Def have a couple things to consider though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're the balls! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I gotta be honest here /u/slickwillyballs. I love you too. And your slick balls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i'll agree with that. 
  
yeah and ultimately the argument gets put to a stop when you try to see if you can apply it anywhere else. 
   
When you look at comparing other professional tools to amateur or lesser counterparts it's not much of a conversation. (Gimp/Photoshop, Ai suite to...most other shit)   
   
That said, when you look at your average picture quality, even phone picture quality, outside of low light, long distance kind of shit, you don't need to go too far up the scale to get decent quality. 
   
Like you don't need to jump to the end of it and buy a 5d when a 70d will probably suffice for a large chunk of what you're trying to do.  And before making that jump a higher end point and shoot or rebel will do just fine. 
   
This is all coming from someone shooting on an old ass camera looking to upgrade to a higherish end one. 
   
That said, I very strongly believe, especially in terms of art, that you can make shit happen anyway. Even look at the number of youtubers shooting on 70d's. Making hours and hours of content seen by millions of people. 
   
So, I guess it's a bit of both and people do put way too much into it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By golly /u/karmisson it was a willy of a match though! And by-golly, I swore you had me snookered there!  
  
Next time, You'll take it for sure! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mine's still 'flaired' at 2 days so i dunno. and i called him a liar for it. so i hope it's his flair lol. 
  
i'm also kidding but you know, the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 days* redditor for 2 days. 
  
It also looks like /u/slickwillyballs is a liar. So, take from that what you will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the most interestin things I read/heard is that runner, I believe life long runners, tend to have average MI rates to the rest of the population. Implicating that stressing your heart through exercise, in that way, might not be that great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's kind of what is important. Giving them that time to properly say goodbye if they haven't or were doubting wether it was actually happening, you're ROSC does do something. 
  
Really no one has the right to judge anyone else's decision in that regard. And shame on anyone for thinking otherwise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But part of me wants to say that it is an issue. You can't have one with addressing g the horrifically absurd notion that the opinion is wrong.

Not misstated or uninformed. Just flat out wrong. It's dangerous to assume everyone who reads him will say oh he's nuts on the climate stuff.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno man...

Isn't light exactly what you're learning how to shoot with? In like so many ways?

I'm not sure how you're not considering or learning to consider it after it happened several or during shooting and you're wondering that's not the picture I wanted to take? Is it still good?  

And then you absolutely learn to account for it. Sure do I come home and find out a couple photos look blown out? Ofc. Not unusably bad but the lighting was shit and I didn't have a flash so got stock with certain things being g stuck directly under lights and the event ran for a couple hours. But the whole shot wasn't irreparably blown out. Only when I had the light source directly over a subject. There was this table against the wall with two people sitting at it that needed to have a picture of it and the light just sucked. It took a shot from some creative angles but it worked out. Where I didn't get stuck with a blown out picture.

I was shooting this St. Patty's day parade and there was this kid sitting on the curb, somewhat bored eating cotton candy or some shit. Might have been two kids. Middle of the day. Cute af. Thought it was great shot but there's no easy way to shoot the kid, from across the street and I didn't really have time, because a parade ain't gonna stop for me and need to shoot certain groups marching.

I didn't even realize, at the time, the shot looked that blown out. My editor did. And after that I absolutely accounted for it  everywhere I possibly could. Certainly, unless it was appropriate, never included or submitted, with limited exception where it played into the picture, a blown out shot again.

I guess what I was speaking as a student that seems to be exactly the type of thing you are trying to learn to shoot around. And that guy absolutely made a choice either to shoot something at the wrong g time or possibly just picked a bad subject/place. And that speaks to my first point. That's exactly what often comes across as a forced photo, blown out or not. Just someone who needs to shoot till they develop their eye and understanding of wtf is going on when they click the button. 

So sure. A parade middle of the day with 2 3_5 second gaps to shoot that kid? And like 2 opportunities before I have to move? There's probably little I could have done bout that. But it also probably wasn't a picture I should I decided on using. Or maybe I was, because I learned something from it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 10:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure. I personally think it's a cool effect sometimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one has any excuse for blown out photos unless it's the first 6 months of shooting, either amateur, professional or hobby.

I mean to be frank if his photos do the feel natural he probably lacks a creative eye. Further, I'd wager they're not natural.

I'm not putting myself on a pedestal or even want to say I'm good at the things I do. On the contrary, I doubt I'm any good at much. But that's because creativity is hard af to utilize. Recognizing it,l and, equally, executing it from idea to final product, whether it's a print ad, video, photograph is not easy. Doing it well is that much more difficult.

I 100% agree though that gear has limitations or advantages. Particularly better cameras do better in lower or not ideal light situations. That's what I'm looking toward, and video. Be naive not to include video looking ahead. 

I think putting a 5D anything or a 6d in most students hands isn't going to change shit until they learn to exercise their creativity.

All that said, in 2017 and all the post we have, no one's photos should be blown out.

Edit: I mean a rebel t1i. I've waited 8? 9? Years to upgrade. That's through some professional photo coverage of stuff and lots of pictures that I've shot fine. 1,000's really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great video. really love the whole 
   
"the art isn't in your gear. It's in your *mind*." 
  
As a creative type who is a hobbyist photographer shooting on Rebel T1i (yes you read that right) I couldn't agree more. 
   
That said, I'm desperate to up my game and am hoping sometime in the next year to put ~750 (+-50) for a 70/80d, 5D Mark II, or 6D. Atm I'm very much in a trying to get my cousin to give me his 5d mark ii kind of place, lol. He doesn't use it nut neither am I expecting his hand out, just kind of realistic to my situation.   
  
Great video though and now I might have a new thing to buy...the puts off my bigger purchase for longer. Dammit. How does this work?
   
For anyone who reads this and is curious I do have a 50-250, 85mm prime,   18-50mm (which i really appreciate as the kit lens). I do take my shooting seriously. 
   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that rock he walks by, after he steps off the coral, he takes like 2-3 steps and almost steps on a rock that looks a helluva lot like a stationary stone fish.  
   
Still, prolly not as dangerous as people make it out to be but also, very clearly, not our environment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol my bad yeah kent, on the river basically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im not 100% sure but  believe they do have a building south of metropolitan now on like so3/4th maybe? And the river (basically forgot the name of the most western Street (begins with a k? Iirc).

Been a while since I used to hang out down there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it's technically the old vice building but it feels weird calling it old in any sense. Then again the neighborhoods been popular for 15 years now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warlock or priest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah for sure. i been taking it lightly on heroes myself. hearthstone and all that.    
   
yeah not sure where it as from, def awesomely impressionable though. haha 
   
lata. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, with 1beat/sec you could probably learn the timing without too much variation.  
   
especially with the 'space' between a beat maybe helping you time it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her make up is on point!  
  
haha glad i'm not the only one who thought so! 
   
And also absolutely love this list showing Li Ming's total Diva. 
   
Awesome.   
  
Also your username is equally awesome.  
  
Did we play TL together recently? or HL maybe...I'm not sure the username feels like i'm remembering it. Oh, I think it was just in game chat, maybe reddit channel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard the 8 didn't have the same issues or to the degree the iPhone did at least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> samsung 8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mah bad! i did browse the side bar didn't catch my eye and i did search but did so poorly. so sorry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that 6d low light -_-...Give me all the cameras now...

Also ur username is the shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well some vlogging is kind of partly why I'm leaning hard on the video thing. Combined with it just being so media relevant in the ~10 min video format I'd hate to overlook it then handicap my capabilities. Also why the 70d/80d are so appealing.

As for the A7 I've heard a lot of good things. As for vlogging and stuff Neistat did a good breakdown on it from a practical approach. He touches on a few other cameras and it seeing those flip out screens and being able to see the shot I'm taking when the camera is facing me seems just too good and soooo convenient.

Otherwise you either guarantee more than one take or marking the ground and height measures, to a degree.

And people very much don't look at video as needing too be staged or done perfectly. Ki d of just need to get the shot that moves your story and be able to give your reaction/feedback to it. So I guess for today's type of video that's so popular seeing my framing seems really practical.

Then again I'd hate for it to make me lazy too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah 5d3 def not in the ballpark. IMO the reality of video is very much defined by when you shoot it.

I think I'm with you there regarding the crop sensors. Drives me nuts actually since currently my viewfinder will include shit that isn't in the shot at really not so short focal length.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure. But I try to approach stuff practically and with an eye toward the future. Video is super relevant and going to be that much more moving ahead. 

But yeah I think I just been noticing the lagging in iso performance, blurring with movement. I used this camera, the one I got, during journo internship 3_4 years ago, grabbed lotta different t shots. And it did well.

I guess today I'm just looking for a bit more. And a part of that is video. I do think that anything I get will perform well enough for my needs. The 6d's low light seems really tempting. Truthfully I'd be happy with either, 6d or 70/80d. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Appreciate the heads up. That's interesting. I feel like video is too relevant today to kind of neglect it in a camera purchase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I agree. I occasionally do use my camera professionally in my design and mock up work. Sometimes it's just easier to import q photo into photo shop.

Like me and my girl are thinking of pushing her town for a dog run, to mock it up I'll photograph the location and turn it into the dog run I'm Photoshop. Or when showing we stuff off I'll photograph it myself.

I'm a creative type or whatever the fuck you want to call it. Either way I'm not sure there's another lens of buy at this point and a camera upgrade is needed. You're right though it's very much irrelevant just making a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Care to expand I've heard a couple things about video issues but no direct experiences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH I'm pretty creative as is. I absolutely see the value in seeing the shot rather than taking 3 or 4 trys/shots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did consider an option like this. I think, today, the option for video is too important. 

Then again my gf's phone shoots 4k. Just need a tripod/holder for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but from a design perspective, even our early rocket planes had cockpits. The shuttle had one too. You really end up with a "bridge" type of solution I guess. 

Then again it's fiction and a TV show, best not to squeeze too much science from or into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
