<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2337</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 14:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Collector value. From what I understand there was quite a bit of looting during WW2 that makes the '45 very, very scarce.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 06:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's be real, what would an authentic empty '45 go for...? I'd bet over 30k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude. Super props are in order. You hung in there. The buddy falling ruined what could've been an epic level prank, the spaghetti would've just been bonus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 19:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no issue. Using the noprovisioning build.prop edit. Just ran a speedtest with a different device on my 6p hotspot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 18:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this no Big Red bologna for the 6P? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did notice, wasn't turned on when I looked. I'm on Verizon. Never realized that was a thing- Maybe something Project Fi related? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 20:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that mean we 6p users could charge our phones faster with this charger? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 07:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read that as "Hair burns can now diminish a surprisingly large amount of hair" Not the fiery red strands I expected. Your hair is lovely though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers S2E07] Music throughout season 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 07:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else been disappointed in the lack of captivating music like we heard throughout S1? I get small hints of snippets from certain themes every now and then, but nothing as amazing as the first season offered. Honestly I thought the music added to the allure of the show and seems to have dimmed the luster a bit for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 04:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That opening had more captivation, through the commercials, than anything I've seen in quite a while </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
