<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3504</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also interesting to see them eat tacos at all. I legitimately had no idea they loved tacos like us. Damn, I loves tacos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interesting... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 17:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 10:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Greeks are gonna get weird </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 10:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lil Mama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the computer hacker stopping the threat counts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 20:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were talking to you Michael Bay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 02:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R/funnyandsad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 00:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aaron Taylor-Johnsons wife is way older than him. Strapped him fully with kids too. He was 21 so nothing illegal. But love is love I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-14 00:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The medium salsa "Woooooo there buddy!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 08:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bones ft. Snoop Dogg and Candy Man. NOPE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 08:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone ringing the doorbell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 07:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I remembered to ask what the micron size. I never do and Now I feel like I fucked myself lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 07:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I remembered to ask what the micron size. I never do and Now I feel like I fucked myself lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 07:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey try the coin, just not with bud inside. I
Step 1. Grind weed regularly, then remove.
Step 2. Add coin into now empty chamber.
Step 3. Freeze for a bit then shake to death.
Step 4. Reap rewards then place weed back in chamber.
Step 5. [1000} </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 02:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously why is he not in jail!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 02:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But holy crap, did he do well. When I saw it before I legitimately thought the actor was actually skilled in doing this. Like he said he guys I have a random skill type of thing. Now I wonder how long this took to learn lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True! But for #1. I never have bud in the chamber for that exact reason. I ended up with powder bud that partially got into the kief. So that sucked, and never did that again lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-13 01:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually combine the two. I put my grinder in the freezer for 15 mins then I knock it around with the coin inside!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 10:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pain they've caused will always be there. The "forgive   forget" mentality never works. It's toxic. I haven't spoken to my birth mother in 6 years. She wants to talk to me, but I won't give her the benefit of the doubt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 09:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. I feel so bad for celebrities for that reason. It obviously got so bad he had to tell people to give him personal space at his own personal space. Oh well. I wouldn't apologize either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 08:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's weirdly personal to me. When I was a kid I tried to ask my gma how much she made and said it was rude to ask such a question and that that was personal. So now when people talk about their money, I feel like they are releasing sensitive info.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 08:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I'm not. There was a post on r/relationships that talked about a guys gf learning he had cash and started dropping hints like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 08:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This explains what I'm trying to say much better! I think finances should stay in the home. You never know who wants to try and make a gain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 08:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love that movie. Love their confused ass reaction lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 08:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thai tea, water and a creamer. It is traditionally served with creamer like half and half. On it's own it's very sweet (probably where the cream comes in). I like to add a bit of my own creamer if any. It's so good on it's on with extra ice. Go to a thai market they'll hook you up.

Edit: [Here is the Tea](http://imgur.com/HQ7x2nK)
[Inside the bag](http://imgur.com/zflG1BB)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE think sharing personal finances is taboo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 08:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My roommate is getting a small inheritance and is telling everyone. Even the day it will arrive in the mail!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 07:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im a vegetarian, too! My so went to a party in Ohio and they were serving that. She noped to that but her friend ate it mistaking it for beef lol I'm Californian so that was strange hearing that. Interesting to hear this is so common, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 07:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were they rude every time you went? I was "in France" In Epcot, Disney world when I had one of my rude interactions. I said Au Revoir to two workers who then proceeded to mock and laugh at me. I would never go to another country and be rude. I don't get it. We just keep running into the assholes, dude. What was the most friendly country?What is a typical New Zealander demeanor?

"HELLO SIR! WOULD YOU LIKE TO TALK ABOUT OUR LORD AND SAVIOR THE ALL BLACKS!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 07:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude what is up with deer chili? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 06:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 06:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eating popsicles in the shower. So hot. So cold.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 06:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What state do you hail from?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 06:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from the west coast. That probably explains why I cane never heard of this growing up. Hmm. I've never eaten sweet potato fries sweet. I have eaten them savory with regular French fry dips.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 05:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This so damn good  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 05:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure exactly. It seems some people are answering here. The sweet potato marshmallows thing is new to me. It sounds really awful haha now sweet Potato fries are my jam! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 05:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We absolutely hate them, too. I just try to hang a jacket or bag to cover myself. I can't be the only American that gets excited over stalls that have full blown doors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My thai tea sans creamer! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 05:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 04:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just apart of regular terminology. I was watching a British show and for the life of me couldn't figure out what a frock or a fringe. Like bathroom here, loo there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 04:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just the word we grew up with. When asking someone where one is, we actually call it a bathroom. Restroom sounds more formal in my head. Some countries just plain call it the toilet. That is totally weird to say here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 04:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I WAS A FREAKING LION ANIMORPH. ME AND AND MY WHOLE CREW WALKING AROUND TOWN AS ANIMALS HELL YEAH. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 04:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very true! This ideal is skewed depending on your region as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 04:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes we can be very overly patriotic or nationalistic. Only a small number of people are like this, though. "AMERICA THE GREAT!" Type ideal. It's pretty bizarre to a lot of us too. Any examples? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 04:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We also like crackers with chili! We like to dip the cracker. Very delicious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope I get a lot of honest questions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a Hot German post up just like this, word for word! Check it out! I was inspired by the super interesting questions there and wanted to do this post!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Non-American Redditors, what are some things about our culture that you would like to be explained to you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 03:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard from non-French Europeans that the French were rude. I've had pretty negative interactions with The French as well. I don't believe all french are like that but damn I am running into a lot of assholes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 02:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that, actually. A YouTuber I follow loves it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sounds like she developed FOMO and is wondering why you never coughed it up before? "why don't we do this (since you've had money)?" "Why haven't we gone here (since you've had money)?" If you like to stay frugal, tell her so. Also, make sure the people you have told aren't telling anyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They cancelled because the creative people went to make regular show. (Secretly never watched the show for that reason), petty I know.  Of course I'm probably wrong though lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 00:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's such a nice guy. Who would even say anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 01:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I call it kief Lasagna  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 00:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always thought this idea was looked down upon. I think fake meats should be weaning foods for people who switch from omnivore to vegetarian. But living off if them? Too processed for me. I eat it once in a blue moon but thats it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 00:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SAVE THE TEXT MESSAGES  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's okay I am used to it. People don't phase me as much anymore. If you don't love them. Fuck them. Kiss that plane ticket for us! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk why people think a vegan diet is fatal. Like bitch it's food? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to hear this. My family is Muslim and they accept me. (They are from America) I'm sorry you can't practice. A'Salamu A'Laikum anyways. Seriously. One thing I took to HEART is that family will always love you even of you have to cut them off or they cut you off. (To live openly you might have to. Super sorry again.) I always tell myself that if a family member decided to never speak to me again, I KNOW they'll love me for life. Your own happiness is all you have, Honey. So I was out and was like any questions? I am of a minority race and people give my folks shit all the time. I can't me being gay even be a problem on top. I am out. I am a gayby. It's probably hard now and maybe years away. But I swear when you have YOU back, your heart will be so damn light. Damn. I wish you had the means right now. Yes. I understand appeasing family. Just remember NO MATTER WHAT YOU DO OR WHO YOU DO IT WITH THEY CAN TAKE BACK LOVE SUCKAZ THEY'LL JUST BE SALTY AND YOUR LIFE WILL BE SWEET, BB
A'SALMAU A'LAIKUM.

Edit: Take that degree move to a gay friendly area. Support yourself and make awesome gay friends. Having a lesbian click is amazing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pay a guy to do that in front of your dad. Tell him thats what de does before he kills him. This is such an extra thing to do but it's more raw. He'll feel the raw awkwardness of it all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think she might take pics when you see her though? I think the "how much was it?" question is offensive too. I heard my so's pal once told a guy to ONLY get her a Tiffany. She ended being a bitch and it took him years to pay off. If I got a ring pop I'd be excited. When people ask that, I think they miss the entire meaning of the ring. Lowkey putas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take your time. It's YOUR EDUCATION. I know PLENTY of people who took a bit of time. It's okay. There is nothing weird with being educated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lito suddenly sobbing after bartending had me crying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone turned into creeps s1 orgy! Lol Yasssd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love a good showerbeer post without the surprise genitals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohio is a strange state. Someone I know went to a party there and they served deer chili. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like having your parents be the best chefs in town, but everyone is discussing Gordon Ramsey at the dinner table.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taylor Swift  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> African-American Vernacular English. I answered fully in the top comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> African-American Vernacular English or simply Ebonics. I lowkey hurts because I know the majority of black folk can speak SAE or Standard American English. They fucking teach us in school. I learned when I took Linguistic Anthropology.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Count Olelf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A ton of colleges have rugby teams! It's pretty cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes! I don't know why I didn't mention the German Bundesliga! I like Schalke 04, M.Gladbach, Bayern (arturo vidal keeps me going) and Dortmund. I know! And tbh we are low ranked in Football (not our women's side though! We're currently ranked 2nd) Dude, watch an MLS game and you'll see a few empty seats. May only be a few, but in a Football county every seat is filled and even lap sitting! I honestly want to visit Mexico to go see a game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% agree. If we had time we could be greater! I think they should have AF players trickled in to promote. Like having the first game hosted by Peyton Manning. (Retired, Star Quarterback) Or players attending training sessions or something. It just needs attention! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey my name is Choco-Latte.

Bihh..what..

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder what a strippers name would be? Sexy candy chocolate? Delicious donuts?

YES DIS IS DOG lmao girl you crack me up. You're really pretty btw. Lady to lady not creep lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Football, too! MLS, La Liga, Liga MX, and EPL are my main favorites. I'm trying to get into another league! Any suggestions? American sports are irrelevant outside of the U.S unfortunately. I love how international Football and Rugby are. Everyone knows who Pogba is, but ask anyone outside the US who Richard Sherman is and their utterly lost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. I was thinking the same thing. They need to watch Owen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. We go NUTS over Football. LIKE LETS CHANNEL THIS ENERGY INTO RUGBY. We'd be damn good at it too. We can run. We can tackle. And we can sure as hell pitch/throw. We have a special dude just for kicking like we're set! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish we had more serious Rugby here. We can producers great players. No one cares enough to fund it though. We had one pro season  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am honestly so surprised that Rugby has not taken off in the states. It is so damn action-packed. I honestly get off watching rugby sevens. Perry Baker gives me life!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg high in church! Lmao I wouldn't be able to concentrate at all!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That first time feeling feels so fancy/isthisreal lol congrats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hangover feeling is shit. Next day after smoking feels so damn good! I'm refreshed sista, refreshed.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone like Florida? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I appreciated Rugby so much more after finding out that my first love, American Football, stemmed from it. Damn, I love this sport! (Also, when I typed Rugby this ball came up. Holy crap, there is a rugby emoji) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any other American Football crossovers?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had to google iirc. Jeez lol but cow tipping? To scared to do that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dreadlocs? YOU DON'T WASH YOUR HAIR.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was asked this A LOT as an English major. Sheesh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
