<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3428</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hacking has proven medical benefits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Poetry] Anonymous Delivers Ultamatum. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-19 01:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 10:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how long have you been eating spaghetti? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 07:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and meatballs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 07:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here](https://np.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/6bmwdw/captain_comedy_speaks_out_against_metacritic/) you go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captain Comedy speaks out against Metacritic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-17 07:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 23:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for clearing that up, I don't know why people were so confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 18:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's get vaping boys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Poetry] Vaping has a New Hero. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 17:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 17:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love your videos so now I am shilling you out on reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guy makes some extremely high quality comedy videos. [344 views] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 13:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vaping has a new hero. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-16 12:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 21:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thing with arrow, "lets make Batman relevent". Jobbing is one of the key powers of speedsters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 19:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they just wanted to make Oliver look cool, like "Oh ya Oliver could totally take down Flash's villain if he wanted to", and I am just like,"No". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barry cought a bullet when his back was turned.  Using this theory then anyone should have been able to shoot Reverse Flash with a gun. And they could have just shot him in the legs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not just say that Ray sent Barry the nanites, and then not include Oliver at all.  Ray doesn't ever seem to reference these nanites that can stop speedsters for multiple minutes. It just seems that they wanted Oliver to look cool while make everyone else look stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "NANITES COURTESY OF RAY PALMER. THEY'RE EMITTING A HIGH FREQUENCY PULSE THAT'S DISABLING YOUR SPEED. YOU WON'T BE RUNNING AROUND FOR QUITE A WHILE." If only Reverse Flash could move faster than an arrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-15 18:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the only reason Oliver could help was because A. Reverse Flash was Jobbing,and B. They invented a device to stop speedsters that has never been used again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-12 10:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have actually seen really good videos doing sins of his video before.  Here is a [link](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qnTZbZw1JPQ ab_channel=bobvids). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't remember exactly who it was, I just know that Huber didn't like handeheld gaming before the Switch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it was Huber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why you have to trust the user reviews instead of those paid shills? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I am ok with that.   It's just that some people believe that if it wasn't a remake of New Hope it wouldn't have made money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prove to moviegoers that they knew what star wars was all about, and that they could handle it well.

This is something many people have said as an excuse as to why FA had to be a remake of a New Hope.  

Tell a cohesive plot that succeeded in drawing in the audience

This is not something that can only be done by remaking a New Hope.  Even though the Prequels were panned, they were all box office successes.  All Force Awakens had to do was tell a good story and it would have made a ton at the box office. Just look at the success of Star Wars Battlefront, even though it was not reviewed well, it was still one of the best selling games of the year.  Star Wars Battlefront released before Force Awekens, which means that Disney didn't have to prove anything, and people would still eat it up because it was called "Star Wars". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Being a Saitama jerker is now considered a pre existing condition. #wanpunch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Podracers are my favorite sound in star wars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 08:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you prove that Saitama's power is to kill everyone in "wanpawnch"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you missed the "/s". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're mocking me, aren't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shall take the bait. How does he win in one punch? That is if you are actually serious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet people complain about the over saturation of comic book movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently saw this video.  I agree with some of his points, but he seems to be making a ton of stuff up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is basically just a repost of [this post](https://np.reddit.com/r/gaming/comments/67uq9t/how_to_tell_when_it_isnt_actual_ingame_footage/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the r/movies poll it was number 3 for underated movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya I do prefer Titanfall 2 to Call of Duty, but the way jetpacks worked in Advanced Warfare is still my favorite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Infinite Warfare had the weakest gunplay, but I ear the story is good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cultural impact and quotability don't even make a movie good. Otherwise rediit is going to have to acknowledge that the prequels are some of the best movise of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /uj If avatar bombed like people thought, reddit would call in an underated gem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /uj I am actually sure that some of it was gameplay just with the HUD removed.

/rj SLEDGEHAMMER LIED!!!ii!!iI1! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every Call of Duty is dumb stuped action that only normies like, DAE TURN OFF THIER BRAIN FOR F8 OF THE FURIOUS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is not very popular with reddit, but I felt that the jet packs and wall running were a natural progression for Call of Duty.  I had always played it for fast paced smooth combat and wall running added to that.

/rj Stop making the same game every year and go back to making the same games you used to make every year.....but all CODs are the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
