<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3220</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 11:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes You are right. I realized that, when My son, after few minutes said, that this is so boring, and I had to end the work alone ;-)
It was to be fun, and it was... ath the beginning, but then work was tedious.

Now I know, why craftmans lost battle against mechanisation. So many work for just 5 bucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 09:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is useless in nowadays, but it could be way to kill boredom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to make carpet from old t-shirts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 07:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 21:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very pretty tvideo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If You are a little bit expirienced computer user, You could try deflickering script. There are many of them, just google deflickering script.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be gratefull for any suggestions/comments. This is my second serious time lapse video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OC] I've made autumnal Time lapse music video and I'm proud of it :) From sunrise till sunset somewhere in Poland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What ? Who is raheelkhan2007@hotmail.com ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iceland: Iceberg breaking and rotating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 10:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as for the bed frame - it's ok, nothing unusuall, but if You consider, that it is without no screws or bolts.. I'm amazed! Awesome and hard work.
Great perfection in making junctions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 20:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice thing made from scrape of wood
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 23:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great looking and well done.
I know how hard is to make 45 degrees junctions in the coners. You've made it perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 23:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember such furniture in Poland when there was communism in our country and the people are very poor and they have small houses.
Why to make such things now, when there is no need ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Useless home made mini rockets - tutorial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 23:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 08:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank You for the link and comprehensive answer.

I'm from Poland, but Your's IKEA is in my country too, so I will try to order such 'Ordning' from Your link.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 20:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This form You are writing about. You've made it or bought it ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 20:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This home made dough can be later put in oven and becomes hard as rock. Usefull for creating durable works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 07:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really nice creatures You've made :)
But.. where are You working, so You have a time for such activity ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 07:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice work, but isn't the roof too short ?
In rain it will be all wet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 07:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First I think-what is so cool in this gokart, but then.. i noticed the cooler:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 07:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How You achieved such nice shape? I'm making cheese too, but I didn't manage yet to create something with so nice shape as Yours ;-)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've also made a catapult but not magnetic.
Great work, interesting thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, this is awesome. Why it has only 4 points ? I don't get this whole reddit sometimes.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is that ? it's a hammer or some kind of knife ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do You tried retro style bulbs ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, what is the purpose of such deck ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is really good looking pen. I'm definitely interested on, how You do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crazy humour and really good music in free, retro style, point and click indie game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends what do You want ;-)
I recommend something which allow You to listen podcast from the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what do You think ? It is my first post on 'somethingimade', so I'm curious of the others opinions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 08:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. I don't know where You from, but You can buy such doors in shops (on the internet), but it could be expensive way.
You can built them by yourself (there are tutorials on youtube), or, as I do, You can find 'guy which knows how to deal with metal' show him the project, and he will do it. 
Doors are easy to make. Just plate, frame and additional decorations.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 08:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

Whole projects it's quite easy. You have to remember few things:
- construction is heavy, so it needs to be on reinforced foundations
- pizza/bread oven has to be built from special materials that accumulate the heat. I use fireclay bricks.
- smokehouse hearth and walls shouldn't accumulate heat, so I use normal, cheapest red bricks
- on the back of the construction there is a second heart for smokehouse. It has longer vent/chimney canal to get the colder smoke from fire. I use it to smoke with the smoke with temperature less than 24 degrees (celsius)
- it is important to have good air/smoke flow in smokehouse, so the minium diameter of the chimneys should be 10 cm. 

If You want to build something like this, You have to remember to fire it first without the meat inside and with opened doors. It is because, the walls should be drained from the water (water is in plaster and mortar). If You don't do that, the first somoked will not be so good, and You will have ugly, black stains below the metal doors (it is where the steams will condense - on the metal walls) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 22:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.
My son.. eh, yes, he was in his baby-swimming pool. It was very hot day then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to show smokehouse I've just built (the whole building process). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 21:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 20:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've made something like this by myself. Great effect, especiallyin dark room.
Try to move this device around - it still works and gives 3d effect but in a little different way.
You can try this type of holograms with normal PC screen. It gives You larger holograms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice one
very raw, I believe that it will be finished soon, yes ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 10:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, someone asked me what is the range of this cannon - it depends :)
If glider is perfectly made, it could fly more than 60 meters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 09:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toghether with my son, We've made powerfull toy which gives us a lot of fun and it's easy to make.
So, this is presentation of the balista and video from the building process. 
Easy, fast good project for father   son activity. 

Enjoy ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Medieval cannon (balista, crossbow) for paper gliders - powerfull toy with a lot of fun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 09:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 20:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, maybe someone has a question ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 09:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great timelapse, but it will be much better if You add some music. Now it is very raw material. Yes, nice, but.. I do not managed to last itill the end.
Keep making such timelapses:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
