<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3901</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wenn Menschen sich fr Parteien entscheiden, machen sie sich meist entweder ber materielle Dinge (zum Beispiel zu wenig Lohn) oder bestimmte Werte (wie ein schlecht funktionierendes Schulsystem) Gedanken. Fr mich spielen Werte, die eine Gesellschaft prgen, die ausschlaggebendere Rolle.

Die Einkommens- und Wohlstandsverteilung ist also nicht gesellschaftlich prgend? So so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Berlin  das assoziiert man mittlerweile nicht mehr nur mit hipper Grostadt und einzigartiger Geschichte, mit Nachtleben und Multikulti. Sondern vermehrt auch mit organisierter Kriminalitt, auslndischen Grofamilien und Clans, maroden Schulen, kaputtgesparter Polizei, Hausbesetzungen, misslungener Integration, Huserblocks, in die sich Post und Polizei nicht mehr trauen  ich knnte noch lange fortfahren. 

Bitte was?

Mein Grovater in seinem 700-Personen-Dorf hat vielleicht solche Assoziationen, aber ich kenne niemand in meiner Altersklasse (bin 29 und lebe seit 8 Jahren in Berlin - vorher in Bayern), der so ber Berlin denkt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Als Frhaufsteher in Berlin kann ich das nur besttigen.

Bin ursprnglicher Bayer und allgemein sehr viel glcklicher in Berlin als in Bayern, aber in den Bereichen Pnktlichkeit und Frhaufstehen bin ich definitiv auch nach acht Jahren hier noch eher bayerisch geprgt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schn und gut - ich bin voll und ganz fr Space Exploration und Kolonien - aber ich pldiere dafr, dass wir unseren Konsum dieser Realitt anpassen **wenn wir soweit sind**!

Stattdessen sehen wir berall diese religise Technikglubigkeit, die so tut als mssten wir nichts an unserem Verhalten ndern weil der techniche Fortschritt ja schon alles legitimieren wird. Und fr jeden Prozentpunkt an gesteigerter Effizienz dank Forschung erhhen wir whrenddessen unseren Konsum um 5%.

Wir leben im Grunde alle mit einer massiv berzogenen Kreditkarte und gehen einfach davon aus, dass wir bald genug verdienen werden, um das alles problemlos abbezahlen zu knnen.

So geht das aber nicht! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'edgy'

Nehme an, OP machte sich Sorgen, dass er auf https://www.reddit.com/r/2edgy4me/ verwiesen wird.

Halte ich fr unntig - seine Kritik und Verzweiflung finde ich sehr nachvollziehbar und angemessen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolut. Es gibt drei Anstze, unser Dasein auf der Erde nachhaltig zu machen:

1. Unseren Konsum pro Kopf massiv senken.
2. Unsere Effizienz massiv steigern.
3. Die Geburtenrate massiv senken und damit die Weltbevlkerung reduzieren.

Das idiotische ist, dass in dieser Diskussion immer wieder so getan wird, als sei das eine *entweder/oder*-Frage. Realistisch betrachtet(!!) mssen wir **alle drei** tun! Selbst im absoluten best case scenario (in realistischen Mastben) ist keiner dieser drei Anstze *im Alleingang* ausreichend, um unsere Nachhaltigkeitsprobleme zu lsen!

* Wir mssen unseren Konsum in den entwickelten Lndern senken! [#postwachstumskonomie](http://www.postwachstumsoekonomie.de/material/grundzuege/)
* Wir mssen forschen und entwickeln, wie wir effizienter in den Bereichen werden knnen, in denen wir nicht auf Konsum verzichten knnen/wollen.
* Wir mssen die Geburtenrate senken! Und dabei global denken! Deutschland und Japan sind hierbei schon ganz vorne mit dabei - das ist gut so.

Ich selbst lebe vegan, bin kinderfrei (und werde es dank Vasektomie auch bleiben) und lebe materiell auch sehr gengsam (kein Auto, nahezu keine Flugreisen, lebe in einer 2-Personen-WG, sehr geringe Ausgaben). Hoffe so zumindest meinen Teil beizutragen. Vielleicht geht alles vor die Hunde. Kann gut sein. Halte ich sogar fr wahrscheinlich. Aber ich will sagen knnen, dass ich es zumindest versucht habe.

"You can resolve to live your life with integrity. Let your credo be this: Let the lie come into the world, let it even triumph. But not through me."

 Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mir zeigt das eigentlich, dass die meisten Nachrichten eher als Unterhaltung sehen.

Absolut. Die Kommerzialisierung des gesamten Lebens und die Gehirnwsche zur durchgehenden Konsumgesellschaft haben auch die Auseinandersetzung mit gesellschaftlichen Themen selbst zur *Konsumhandlung* gemacht - mit der entsprechenden Einstellung, Erwartungshaltung und Aufmerksamkeitsspanne.

Nachrichten sind bloe Unterhaltung geworden. Und was nicht unterhaltsam ist, wird nicht beachtet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Die Menschheit ist eklatant kaputt im Kopf.

Ich fhle mit Dir - und verzweifle stndig daran. Aber Verzweiflung bringt nichts. Zorn und Wut und Hass bringen nichts.

Tatsache ist, dass der Groteil der Menschheit sehr, sehr simpel denkt. Das war schon immer so, und wird vermutlich auch immer so bleiben.

Wirklicher Fortschritt wurde schon immer, und wird auch in Zukunft, nur von einer kleinen aber engagierten und kompetenten Minderheit gegen den Widerstand der trgen aber vergleichsweise passiven Masse durchgesetzt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greenpeace - Plane Stupid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 11:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Es geht nicht mal um die Font, sondern um den Witz. Kreativitt ist nicht nur, wenn etwas 'hbsch' ist.

Und wenn wir ber *ntig oder unntig* diskutieren, dann mssten wir noch **[deutlich weiter gehen](http://strikemag.org/bullshit-jobs/)** (auf das 'here' klicken, um das Essay zu lesen). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 11:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like problem is with obsession more than with minimalism per se. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Der Witz hier funktioniert aber nicht, wenn er auf eine *erlaubte* und offiziell und brokratisch lizensierte Wand gesprayt wird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DELL XPS 15 9560 fans randomly flare up while doing super low-effort tasks like web browsing. It only started doing that since a couple of days ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any idea what's wrong here? I've had it for a few weeks now and it was virtually silent for most of that time whenever I was doing just lightweight tasks. Since a couple of days or so, the fans are going off unreasonably loudly during just normal web browsing tasks - with nothing more computationally expensive running that I know of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TLDR: Die Wirtschaft diktiert Gesetze und Kultur - nicht andersherum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mll am Boden kann ich auch nicht leiden - da bin ich ganz bei Dir.

Da hebe ich auch Abfall von der Strae und v.a. in Parks auf und entsorge ihn im nchstgelegenen Mlleimer.

Aber wenn's um Graffiti, Street Art und andere Formen von kreativem 'Vandalismus' ohne *echte* Schden geht, finde ich das *mit* besser als *ohne*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Aber fr mich bedeutet Gerechtigkeit, dass auch andere (zb reiche) nicht unfair belastet werden sollen.

Und fr mich bedeutet Gerechtigkeit, dass es nicht 'unfair' ist, wenn Reiche strker belastet werden als Arme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich halte sehr viel von persnlicher Freiheit - und bin berzeugt davon, dass in Deutschland die Zahl der Leute, deren persnliche Freiheit durch prekre Verhltnisse ernsthaft beeintrchtigt ist die Zahl jener deutlich bersteigt, deren persnliche Freiheit durch solidarische Verpflichtungen ernsthaft beeintrchtigt ist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Uhm...](https://i.imgur.com/VMhMhwG.jpg)**

Menschen ohne Kapital sollen also 'aus Prinzip' eine Partei whlen, nach deren Philosophie Ertrge aus Kapital rentabler sein sollten als Ertrge aus Arbeit? Welches 'Prinzip' soll das sein? Prinzip Dummheit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich glaube, Du nimmst den Scherz etwas zu ernst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich finde das viel unterhaltsamer und sympathischer als sterile industrielle 'Sauberkeit'.

Vielleicht ist das der Grund warum ich mich (als gebrtiger Bayer) in Berlin viel wohler fhle als in Mnchen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By all means, delete Twitter for a whole host of reasons.

But if you'll retreat from any platform where you encounter grossly misinformed people and nonsensical arguments, you'll spend your life on the run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course not.

But UBI would give *a lot* more people the time and security to even dedicate energy towards societal/political upheaval. Most people are so caught in the rat race that they don't even have any time or capacity to think anymore. And without that, no change will occur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit is Being Manipulated by Professional Shills Every Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 16:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is *Flammenwerfer* surprisingly specific when English has the exact same compound word *flamethrower*, which *throws flames*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Neuromancer and Snow Crash both are *the* top mentions on virtually every **[top cyberpunk novels](http://bestsciencefictionbooks.com/best-cyberpunk-books.php)** list ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schlieen diese Vergleiche gleichwertige *Umfragen* ein, oder geht's hier nur um den Vergleich einer Umfrage mit tatschlichen Wahlergebnissen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Snow Crash by Neal Stephenson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The problem with Trump (as it relates to comedy) is everyone is cashing in, the comedians are thrilled. This is exactly what they wanted. To act like you're the victim and cash in at the same time. This is exactly what the system called for."

 **[Bo Burnham](https://youtu.be/s97kW93VWLk?t=1m31s)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 15:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend did the booking - I don't think she left a review at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 12:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Journey** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 12:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That reminds me when my girlfriend and I went on holiday in Italy, and the airbnb guy we rented a place from in Rome told us not to mention his profession (he's a police officer) in the review we would write, for privacy reasons. I said sure, no problem... a bit later in the conversation I asked him what exactly his work as a police officer is about.

Turned out he was a **tax officer** and he didn't want us to mention his profession because he was renting out the house on the down-low and wasn't paying taxes on it.

You can't make this shit up! A **tax officer** evading taxes! He wasn't even particularly embarrassed about it.

As a German, I just couldn't get my mind around that. :D Truly different cultures there I guess... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 12:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patriotismus intensiviert sich!!1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian PM Justin Trudeau laying a wreath at the memorial for murdered Jews in Berlin this morning  r/Frisson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 12:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 09:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[Buy it for only $125.00](http://www.condenaststore.com/-sp/Yes-the-planet-got-destroyed-But-for-a-beautiful-moment-in-time-we-created-a-lot-of-value-for-sh-Prints_i9318014_.htm)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 09:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real existing capitalism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian PM Justin Trudeau laying a wreath at the memorial for murdered Jews in Berlin this morning  r/Frisson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 08:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turning hardware acceleration off in Chrome fixed it for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 13:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And German. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 11:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Layman's question: Is the fact that Whisper Systems is based in the US a security risk, or does its design/encryption make this irrelevant?

As a European, would it be safer for me to use a Europe-based alternative? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Masculinity Is an Anxiety Disorder: Breaking Down the Nerd Box </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 11:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 11:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what to do with myself as most of the things I did for fun in Boston are impossible here.

What were those things, and why are they impossible in Pittsburgh? I'm European, so familiar with neither Boston nor Pittsburgh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 11:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reprsentiere!

Kein Fan von Mett oder anderem Getier hier.

Bei der Ablehnung Deutschland-Schwachsinn verbreitender Angelsachsen bin ich aber ganz beim /r/de Konsens dabei.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The rise of Trump has led to an unexpected twist in Germanys election: A resurgent left  r/europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 11:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dutch House of Representatives passes dragnet surveillance bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 10:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately they're really terrible in terms of messaging, presentation and just general **politics**.

Just watch https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Bgo8Ow5DZtk and see how many voters this would attract. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Khan Academy   Pixar: Introduction to Storytelling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 11:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Talk of tech innovation is bullsh*t. Shut up and get the work done  says Linus Torvalds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 10:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 07:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mouse stops, everything stops (i.e. keyboard input also isn't registered - sometimes mid-typing). After a few seconds, the machine catches back up and letters typed in the meantime appear.

No accessories used at all, only the 9560 itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 07:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried only the EXE (assumed the ZIP would be identical in content) and still couldn't install it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried that but I got **[this error](https://i.imgur.com/fTpb6Ug.jpg)**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you maybe have a look at https://www.reddit.com/r/Dell/comments/5u9q6h/trying_to_install_ubuntu_dual_boot_with_win10_on/ and chime in if you have any tips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to install Ubuntu (dual boot with Win10) on my XPS 15 9560, running into issues. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all when trying to shrink my Windows partition, **[I get this error message.](https://gfycat.com/PalatableZealousDotterel)**

Then I read that Windows' disk management can be unreliable and that I should use GParted instead. So I started up a Live Ubuntu session from a USB stick, but neither GParted nor anything else in Ubuntu can see my disk. The SSD doesn't show up anywhere there.

Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How/Where else do you get the newest Intel HD Graphics drivers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DELL Update says I'm all up to date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> XPS 15 9560 randomly freezes for a few seconds every couple of minutes since a few days ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay now this is getting really annoying. Has anyone else experienced this? The machine worked just fine for the last two weeks but since a couple of days it keeps freezing for a few seconds all the time. Any idea what's up here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any idea what's up with what? I *need* the GPU support for work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My XPS 15 9560 is not seeing my NVIDIA GPU after the latest NVIDIA driver update! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw his special **[MAKE HAPPY](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iE5WwlwJeDQ)** the other day and was pleasantly surprised by some of the points he makes. Especially towards the end of the special he deconstructs the absurdity of celebrity and entertainment, as well as noting his frustrations with it.

"You can tell them *anything* if you just make it funny, make it rhyme." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bo Burnham:"It got completely commodified and corporatized and now the most-viewed videos on YouTube are clips of Jimmy Fallon lip-syncing with celebrities. There was something that could've been of the people and it's completely corporatized." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bo Burnham on Work and Millennials </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw **[MAKE HAPPY](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iE5WwlwJeDQ)** the other day and found it not just really *clever*, but surprisingly *wise*.

I've been thinking to refrain from Last Week Tonight, Colbert, The Daily Show and Bill Maher since the US election last year, and becoming aware of the echo chambers people are in - and that these shows are the left's echo chambers.

His comedy special may have convinced me to give it a go and quit these shows. Which is tricky because watching them has become quite the habit for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bo Burnham: "The problem with Trump (as it relates to comedy) is everyone is cashing in, the comedians are thrilled. This is exactly what they wanted. To act like you're the victim and cash in at the same time. This is exactly what the system called for." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 12:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Monkey:** You are my quest, he whispered. I had seen the wonders of the universe, but the warmth of his gaze as I looked into his eyes. Thatthat I had never known. It was his humanity I saw, and it was more powerful than anything in my cold realm. In recognizing his compassion, I recognized my own. I spared his life. He gave me mine.

**Kubo:** Why does Grandfather hate me?

**Monkey:* Oh, Kubo, he doesnt hate you. He wants to make you just like him. Blind to humanity, as I once was.

----

**Moon King:** You want to be human? Then share their weakness. Suffer their humiliation. Feel their pain!

**Kubo:** I know why you want my eye. Because without it, I can't look into another and see their soul. Their love...

**Moon King: (as the Moon Beast):** Everything you loved is GONE! Everything you knew has been TAKEN from you!

**Kubo:** No... it's in the memories. The most powerful kind of magic there is.

[he strums the strings again and summons the spirits from the lanterns, much to the Moon Beast's anger]

**Kubo:** It makes us stronger than you'll ever be. These are the memories of those we've have loved and lost. And if we hold their stories, deep in our hearts... then you will never take them away from us.

----

I think Kubo and the Two Strings has a lot more substance than people give it credit for. I loved the film.

The grandfather is an old an cynical, bitter man who says there's nothing great about living on Earth, with humans. He has forgotten how to see the beauty in the world.

And Kubo in the end breaks through his cynicism and bitterness, and helps to connect him with the world again.

Zootopia is another fantastic animated film and one of my favourites in recent years but I'm really happy that Kubo is getting some of the recognition I think it deserves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not just you having watched the original film a long time ago.

It *is* way more complex and rich than this trailers suggests the Hollywood remake to be. This here looks like all style, no substance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they really making this **[little side character scene's 'twist'](https://sites.google.com/site/lis404gits/_/rsrc/1256172679533/themes-and-terms/00024.png)** into the main story for the main protagonist?

This trope and similar/related ones have been **[done a million times](https://youtu.be/Nl0BGD-SxS0?t=28s)** now.

I'd hate it if they reduced the full philosophical and political wealth of the original anime movie into a cheap 'twist' and tweetable motivational slogan 'message'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I genuinely appreciate that. I wish more designers - and people in general - had a sense of integrity and responsibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **LPT:** If you use Reddit, delete your account and create a new one in regular intervals to avoid *identifying* with it and the 'karma' score on it. High scores are a powerful manipulation tool.

I've personally found myself less than consciously caring about down votes and karma points to some degree or another even though rationally I completely rejected the notion that this should be of any importance to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
