<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3727</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> who is your most favorite beloved person whom you never met? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 14:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 14:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is (Abdul Sattar Edhi )(https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Abdul_Sattar_Edhi) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is your favorite social worker? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 14:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 14:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 12:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is my late grandfather.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is most wonderful memory of your childhood? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 12:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> you love a movie and a character is going to be substituted with you. what movie and character will you prefer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 11:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 11:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have also our twitter political players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You can close one social networking site. What will be your choice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 10:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 05:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2008 after my blindness I felt first time bitterness of life. I doing intermediate with Math computer and Physics. Because I am in a third world country where educational awareness is almost none for common people you can imagine what suffering will have to face disable people. After the interval of 3 years I again started my study. Now I have done my graduation with History and Political Science.
My marriage broke down because of my disease. My every perspective of life changed. I want to make a social welfare organization specially for disable people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 05:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Pakistan being a muslim Muhammad is very common other names are Ali, Umar, Usman, Akbar, Asghar, Bilal, Kamran, Waqas, younas, ahmad, shoket, Farooq, Jameel, Luqman, Ilyas for males
Fatimma, Nasreen, Kosar, Misbah, Khalida, Bushra, Lubna, Ayisha, Asiya, Nighat, Naheed, Nazia, Shzia for females </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 01:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am going to tell you mine. It was my wedding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-11 01:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> + beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> you love a movie and a character is going to be substitute with you. what movie and character will you prefer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> very good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is going to happen some day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also love chicken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so cool  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice thoughts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will ask to God for forgiveness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your life is going to end and you can do one thing before it. What will you do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Night Before Christmas 1905 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frankenstein 1910 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jack and the Beanstalk 1902 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> video editing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am almost a blind person. I want to know can a blind person edit videos? if, yes than how? 
I am trying to edit videos but, cannot understand timeline function of "windows live movie maker" and "camtasia studio". So, Help me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look at the eyes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> international conspiracy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, Everyone. I love thrill novels specially that involve international conspiracy . So, Please tell me about some books which have both elements. Not spy novels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Mistake  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have You Read </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this world most of the people follows religions different ways. religion takes a very definite part in our life sometime. All religions have their holy books like "bible" and "Quran" etc. Have you read any other religion's holy book? If yes than what is your Thoughts about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JFR King of Terrors by D. M. Mitchell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a thriller about a international conspiracy expanding on more than 400 years, started between devastating plague in England. In summer 1929 chief detective of yard found a murdered rotted body in a barn with a curious black symbol painted on wall. but, he never solved it.he gave this case's unofficial research papers to his grand son who found very strange facts later and began a group with his friends.
More than eighty years later in 2011, guilt-ridden Gareth Davies who wanted to seek a quite and peaceful life but one day a lady struck by his car who claimed to be his twin sister and warned him that his life is in danger. She disappeared quite suddenly in hospital. Davie tried to find his sister and than nightmare began. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big Brother is watching you, I read "1984" and Fell in love with this book. If you are science fiction lover this is it for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
