<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3232</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you like your steak drama? Eaten off a model's back? /r/oldschoolcool has an argument over proper preparation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 23:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This drama has a nice balance of malt and hops, but can you really call it craft drama? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 21:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, in retrospect, I realize my bridal shower last year was basically Beetlejuice's wedding scene... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 00:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coconut cream pie I just finished making </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 00:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coconut Cream Pie recipe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 20:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my husband asked me to make coconut cream pie. I've made it before, and it was good, but it's not as good as my mom's. And that recipe is the one recipe she won't share with me, for whatever reason. All I know is that I've seen her preparing to make it before and she uses cream of coconut instead of coconut extract (coco lopez brand) and flaked coconut both in the pastry cream and on top I went on their website, no coconut pie recipe. Does anyone have a really good recipe for this? I have the ingredients (and I got both coconut milk and coconut cream just in case). 

EDIT: so I just decided to try something, as I have to grade a lot of papers today and I know this will take time to cool. Here's what I've done so far: I made a pastry cream by heating 1 can of cream of coconut, 1 cup milk, and 1/3 cup sweetened condensed milk until it simmered. I whisked 5 egg yolks with 1/3 cup sugar and 1/4 cup cornstarch, then I tempered the eggs and cooked the whole mess in a bowl over a pot of hot water a la double boiler till it passed the spoon test and then I beat in 2 tbs of butter until smooth! I blind baked the crust already and cooled it, so now I'm waiting for the pastry cream to set up. I haven't made a pastry cream quite like this before, so I'll update with a picture when it sets (let's hope it sets!). I'm doing a meringue top, so I'll be using those 5 egg whites I separated from the yolks. 

EDIT 2: [Finished pie!](http://imgur.com/FB61wie) When it chills fully I will try to get a cross-section picture after I cut it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama in AdviceAnimals about age and seniority in the workplace. Epithets are exchanged, reading comprehension is questioned. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 14:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Short but buttery drama about psych majors in /r/funny. "Maybe you couldn't get a job because you're a douchebag lol." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 21:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's been a while since we had bullfighting drama... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 07:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extra crispy drama when OP disagrees about how much char should be on a pizza </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 00:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How far can you stretch drama about vaginas? In this /r/funny thread, it's pretty far. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 09:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alice Cooper and Salvador Dali, 1973 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 07:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Josephine Baker, circa 1925. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 07:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salad with olive oil poached tuna, campari tomatoes, kale, spinach, purple cabbage, and lemon-mustard vinaigrette. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 01:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Balls to the wall drama in WTF about a dog's testicular cancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 11:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of the commenters can't figure out if they're more pissed about neutering pets or about [the OP's appearance](http://np.reddit.com/r/WTF/comments/33tp5j/this_is_testicular_cancer_not_a_heart_spayneuter/cqoef9c?context=3)

[Debate about whether or not neutering is necessary.](http://np.reddit.com/r/WTF/comments/33tp5j/this_is_testicular_cancer_not_a_heart_spayneuter/cqob4ua?context=3)

[Fuck you, keep your dog intact](http://np.reddit.com/r/WTF/comments/33tp5j/this_is_testicular_cancer_not_a_heart_spayneuter/cqobzxk?context=3)


[Yet more criticism of OP's appearance](http://np.reddit.com/r/WTF/comments/33tp5j/this_is_testicular_cancer_not_a_heart_spayneuter/cqocb10?context=3)

Someone calls OP a [ham](http://np.reddit.com/r/WTF/comments/33tp5j/this_is_testicular_cancer_not_a_heart_spayneuter/cqok6xk?context=3)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in the Northern hemisphere, less than two percent of tornadoes rotate clockwise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 02:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama in /r/gaming about modification packages for Steam games. "...we have shills amongst us." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 05:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP in /r/relationships says she's being stalked by a neighbor she had sex with, commenter thinks people are jumping on the bandwagon to call the guy crazy--bandwagon of downvotes ensues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 03:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reheating/Keeping warm Mac and Cheese? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 14:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to a potluck tomorrow and I was assigned macaroni and cheese and fruit salad. No biggy, except I'm not sure how to handle the heating issue. My office doesn't have an oven or stove, just microwaves. I have to be in a meeting that lasts from 10-noon, then the lunch is from noon to one. I know mac and cheese can get mushy when you reheat it. I have a crock pot that I can use to keep it warm or reheat it, but I have no idea A) if you can let mac and cheese sit on the "warm" or the "low" setting for 2 hours without destroying it or B) use it to reheat mac   cheese if I choose to make it tonight instead of early tomorrow morning. I don't care if I make it tonight or in the morning, I'd just like it to be really good. Any advice would be much appreciated!

UPDATE: So It went well! Thanks for all the great advice in this thread! I ended up using Alton Brown's stove top recipe mentioned in the thread, but tweaked it a little by adding a couple of ounces of buttermilk and some different seasoning (nutmeg, smoked paprika, ground tellicherry peppercorns). I cooked it, put it in the crock pot, transported it, and let it sit on low/warm for the two hours until the lunch (added just a little half and half to keep it from drying out). While it turned out a little thicker than I personally prefer, I will say it was absolutely delicious, and everyone loved it (I made a *lot* and there was about one serving left by the end of lunch). So thanks to everyone who helped me with advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Infographic: Similarities between comic book shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 05:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Short but savory drama in /r/foodporn about pasta and sauce. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 17:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tons of children spawned in an /r/news post about vaccine exemptions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 16:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ["What a load of horse shit. My body isn't a part of your fucking body"](https://np.reddit.com/r/news/comments/3331wu/australia_ends_religious_exemptions_to/cqhcdn9?context=3). 

[More debate about government overreach](https://np.reddit.com/r/news/comments/3331wu/australia_ends_religious_exemptions_to/cqh6rhy?context=3)

[The topic of informed consent comes up](https://np.reddit.com/r/news/comments/3331wu/australia_ends_religious_exemptions_to/cqh8ej3?context=3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gun drama takes a very personal turn in TIL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 23:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama about Gwyneth Paltrow's food stamp challenge in /r/nottheonion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 23:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Experiment drama in /r/TIL! "You are an enemy to science." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 07:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commenter in /r/nottheonion says teaching is boring, and a not so boring argument ensues. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saucy drama /r/foodporn about what makes pizza pizza as one commenter keeps calling it bread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 14:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make way for drama in /r/aww about eating cute animals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 16:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/Tinder discusses love and "shit tests" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 04:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that there was a "vampire panic" in 19th century New England. Numerous bodies of people who died of tuberculosis were exhumed and their organs removed to prevent them from "feeding" on others. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 02:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corn starts popping in an /r/AdviceAnimals post about trigger warnings. 83 children. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 03:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Argument in /r/WTF about whether or not it's "low class" to put your feet on the dashboard of a car. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 18:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cooked some sand bass and a crappie last night (resubmitted to fix title) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 17:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are selfies narcissistic? One commenter thinks so and asks, "What is your legacy?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 17:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OKCupid post about date rape awareness--surely this will go well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 23:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have Endo, just went off my pills because we want a baby... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 06:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So was diagnosed with Endo almost four years ago through surgery to remove an endometrioma. She started me on continuous, high dose estradiol pills and it worked. I haven't had a period in over three years. Then Saturday I stopped taking them because we want to try for a pregnancy while the odds are still in my favor. The pain and bleeding started about ten hours later (my doctor told me this is normal). She also told me it wasn't the same bleeding as a period, so I have no idea how long it's going to last. More importantly, I don't know how long this PAIN is going to last. The past four days I've been hanging out at around 4 or 5, but it's constant pain that doesn't seem to blink at Aleve. Has anyone who has gone through this had this experience? Any advice?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Things take a personal turn in /r/videos when someone calls Justin Bieber "irresponsible." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 20:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some good old-fashioned game console drama in /r/AskReddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 17:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GTM] Amen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 22:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bride leaves groom on wedding day after he fails a math problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 22:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that U.S. Submarine crews have an 18 hour day instead of a 24 hour day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 18:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama in /r/movies about the Freddie Mercury biopic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 21:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL actor Eddie Albert was a spy during WWII. His cover was that he was trapeze artist in a Mexican circus. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 00:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP admits he let his dog run around unattended, and people lost their shit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 13:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Argument about age differences and dating in /r/relationships. "Sounds disgusting and sad." "You sound disgusting and sad." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 02:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Semantic + relationship arguments in /r/gaming. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 18:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Debate about age and rounding numbers in /r/facepalm. The term "illogical" is thrown around and people are upset. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 18:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama in /r/AdviceAnimals about cancer and the medicinal properties of cannabis oil. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 01:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commenter in TIL identifies as Irish and Native American, drama follows. "I'm not trolling, you obviously have had little real contact with American Culture." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 23:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post about poutine leads to long argument about Quebec and whether or not it's part of Canada </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 18:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ridiculously long drama in WTF about what the word "most" means. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 07:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commenter in /r/whatcouldgowrong really, really hates the concept of a "passing lane," replies to everyone who disagrees. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 02:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seared tuna, cut from some of the tuna my SO brought back from his fishing trip yesterday. Any other ideas for things I can do with all this fish? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 16:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which historical figures changed the human species? One commenter in /r/historyporn has a short list. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 19:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "You are a textbook prude." Drama surrounding body modification in /r/WTF </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 00:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cleanse your drama palate and get ready for four simple words: popcorn chicken fried steak. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 21:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bizarre dream sequence from Lair of the White Worm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 07:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know this sub might be fed up of the fat drama, but this thread was too good to pass up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 06:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alaska Republican's solution for homelessness: Wolves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 17:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AdviceAnimals arguing about parenting skills again! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 15:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL circus strongwoman Katie Sandwina once beat strongman Eugene Sandow in a weightlifting contest by lifting 300 pounds over her head. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 23:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A complex, sophisticated little drama, with just a hint of butter: wine bickering in TIL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 03:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone posts about their sobriety in /r/pics--one Redditor says "you shouldn't have done drugs in the first place" and corn starts popping. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 23:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leonard Nimoy: Amazing actor, photographer, director, but also amazing feminist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 00:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simple. Classic. Steak drama. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 23:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what are we going to do now? Please post your thoughts for actions, qualifiers, categories, hopes, dreams, secret lingering urges, etc. And let's see what sticks to the wall. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 07:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP in /r/relationships finds out his girlfriend framed his sister who lives with them. Is everyone overreacting? "Don't be a moron. No I'm not OPs girlfriend..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 18:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reporter's fake eyelash detaches on TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 20:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poutine drama reaches a new level when tater tots enter the picture in /r/foodporn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 07:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Street Magician + Knife Throwing Act Gone Wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 02:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Street Magician + Knife Act Gone Wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 23:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do these two video game characters look alike? "'Prosopagnosia'... What you have is called 'Prosopagnosia'." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 14:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Love is in the air as the topic of dating is debated in /r/dataisbeautiful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-15 17:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 50 shades of drama in /r/AdviceAnimals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 02:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama in /r/delusionalartists when someone comes to the defense of a linked artist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 03:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL President George Washington loved ice cream, and spent $200 on it in the summer of 1790. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 16:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What horror films do you want to show your future children? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 07:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a lot of horror films, and I watched a lot of horror films as a kid because my parents wanted to share what *they* loved as kids. This involved a lot of the Universal Monster movies, as they were born in the late 30s, but they were also game for later stuff (my mom first showed me "The Collector" and "Straight Jacket" and "The Omen" my dad showed me "Kingdom of The Spiders" and "Motel Hell" and, if you can believe it, "Killdozer.") My oldest sister showed me "Return of the Living Dead" when I was 9 and I thought it was the funniest thing I'd ever seen at the time. Now that I've started a family, I'm thinking of what I want to share with future kids--and I have no idea. I wonder if they'll be bored with the classics (like Dracula, or The Exorcist, or Invasion of the Body Snatchers, or Freaks, or any other number of movies that I think are amazing), or even bored with anything that doesn't involve CGI. What would you show your future kids?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone posted a picture of Anita Ekberg on /r/oldschoolcool. She's old--drama about the effects of aging follows. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 08:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When worlds collide: Somehow, cheese sandwich drama developed in a thread about sushi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 22:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are you afraid to go to sleep? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 10:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those crossfit weights are oversized aren't they? AREN'T THEY?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 02:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Film pedantry is the best pedantry! The butter here is real, not CGI </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 19:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Babe Didrikson Zaharias--U.S. Track, golf, and basketball star of the 1930s [800  686] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 08:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hot sex on a platter: /r/AskReddit discusses some "dating lifehacks" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 06:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What I've learned from some considerable time on Reddit... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 06:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama about showing porn to teens in /r/funny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 03:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A big thank you... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 19:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted several times in this sub under a throwaway looking for advice, and you were all so helpful. And I just found out that The Knot magazine wants to include our wedding (it was 5 month back)! How cool is that? I don't think it would have gone so smoothly without the advice I got here, so thank you all! This sub is pretty awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Painfully awkward interview with the band Hippo Campus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 23:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Very petty argument in /r/funny about what "the early 2000s" means </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 20:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MLK discussion /r/conspiracy style </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 20:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is OP "pandering to potheads?" One commenter thinks so, and doesn't take it well when others downvote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 01:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cultural appropriation drama in /r/malefashionadvice. Is a hat just a hat? Is it though? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 21:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL debates contemporary race relations. Blocks of text and name-calling ensue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 20:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP gets pummeled with downvotes when he comments on his own post. "We don't need you to point our your own stupidity... We can see it all by ourselves." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 19:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please help me identify this video/song </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 05:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, this is a weird question, but I was recently in Cuba and the room I stayed in had access to numerous channels--I saw a music video but there was no artist or title information provided, I think it might have been a Mexican channel based on the accents of the interviews in between songs but I could be mistaken. Anyway, the video featured people in a mansion fighting in a makeshift ring, and a maid busts in and starts fighting and another woman clashes plates like musical cymbals around her head, and there's a bit of a lucha libre feel to the whole thing, and the song sounded a hell of a lot like Belle and Sebastian in terms of style--I only saw the end half of it and I thought it was awesome, but I still have no idea who performed it--if anyone has a clue, please let me know, as I'd love to buy it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amber Galloway Gallego interpreting Rap God in ASL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 22:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ice cream from Coppelia in Havana, Cuba. It's one of the biggest ice cream parlors in the world, serving up to 35,000 customers a day. We waited an 1 hour and 45 minutes for ice cream, and it was delicious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 06:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Debate over baby fat in a post about Heather Locklear. "I'm really curious about your level of attractiveness and your BMI..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 19:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally made it to Havana for our Honeymoon! Here are some of the many things we saw... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 01:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stewed chicken, swordfish, black beans, rice, squash, and salad I had a few days ago in Jaimanitas, Cuba [5184  3456] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 00:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is Islamophobia, really? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 07:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bettie Page, Kathleen Stanley, and Bunny Yeager, 1954, photographed with timer by Yeager while she was on assignment shooting petticoats for a catalog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 02:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slick Rick - Children's Story[Hip Hop] 1989 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 23:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Armchair psychiatrists are in full swing in /r/videos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 18:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone in /r/movies says Avatar hasn't held up well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 17:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The True Story of Traditional New Year's Lucky Foods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 09:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Founder of Credit Karma does an AMA. One Redditor really, really dislikes the credit system. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 21:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where's the beef? Apparently, it's in /r/food when someone decides to share their opinion on the potential danger of carbs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 17:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smoked duck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 23:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/7wQVI

Marinated the duck in 4 cups pineapple juice and 1 cup soy sauce pureed with 1 clove of black garlic. Stuffed it with wedges of onion and orange. Patted dry and rubbed with:

1/2 tsp white pepper

1/2 tsp ground cardamom

1/2 tsp ground coriander

1/4 tsp ground star anise

1 tbs. kosher salt

1/4 tsp ground ginger

Smoked it at 260 degrees F for about 3 hours (to about 160 degrees at the thickest part, though that's lower than what the USDA recommends, so be warned. I just can't stand overcooked duck). 

Let rest 15 minutes wrapped in foil, then enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smoked a duck and a chicken last night for a small dinner party (with roast potatoes and salad) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 22:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it weird to ask for an open relationship? Is putting hot sauce in someone's fleshlight assault? Things get heated in /r/AdviceAnimals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 21:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone drops a "bah humbug" in an /r/AdviceAnimals thread about a single mother and Christmas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 04:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Christmas Botox voucher leads to drama in /r/skincareaddiction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 05:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This thread about a child-free wedding in /r/relationships is definitely not drama free... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 02:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone proclaims the intelligence of their dog in /r/aww and drama ensues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 22:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it weird to write "SO" vs. "BF" or "GF?" Unusual semantic argument in /r/food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 17:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the term "yellow journalism" originally referred to the first comic strip, "The Yellow Kid," and the papers that ran it were referred to as "Yellow Kid Papers." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 15:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Husband cheats on his wife with her twin sister, and /r/JusticePorn debates who is more at fault in this situation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 21:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama in /r/cooking over the merits of American cheese. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 19:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Profound theological debate in /r/AdviceAnimals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 23:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for best sushi in DFW area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 05:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm taking my husband our for his birthday next week, and he wants sushi. We've been to Keiichi,  Tei Tei Robata,  Little Katana, all of which I thought were good, but I was hoping for some expert tips from people in the know. I head Fujiyama is good and I like the look of their menu, but I'd like to do more research before I book anything. Any tips?

EDIT: Thanks everyone for all of the wonderful suggestions! It was hard to pick one, but in the end I chose Sushi Robata after seeing some pretty interesting things on their menu (and taking location into account). But honestly, there seem to be so many good options, and I'm looking forward to trying all of your suggestions in the future! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obesity and race spawn drama in TIL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 01:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some people in /r/videos don't care for OP's title, drama ensues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 19:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Simpsons joke generates predictable drama in /r/funny. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 19:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Debate about how well-known Amy Adams is in /r/movies, with a fun smattering of SJW discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 19:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Religious drama in /r/Texas. "He's quoting the same bible your faith derives. Do you not have faith in the bible?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 01:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Logical, respectful argument in r/PuzzleAndDragons about the term "Waifu" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 19:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Semantic bickering in /r/WTF--do we go to college or go to university? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 19:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/gaming debates whether or not GTA exploits women </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 19:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's nothing like Japanese cuisine to raise hackles in /r/food. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 05:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is OP a lying cheater? An alcoholic? An alcoholic lying cheater? /r/relationships hashes it out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 22:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a lot going on here--more than just one thread, so I linked the big ones:

[Debate about the details, accusations of lying](http://np.reddit.com/r/relationships/comments/2okhab/my_22f_boyfriend_28m_of_3_years_doesnt_believe_i/cmo0hjb?context=3)

[Alcohol abuse is brought up](http://np.reddit.com/r/relationships/comments/2okhab/my_22f_boyfriend_28m_of_3_years_doesnt_believe_i/cmnz08w?context=3). 

[discussion of previous cheating emerges, OP is heavily downvoted](http://np.reddit.com/r/relationships/comments/2okhab/my_22f_boyfriend_28m_of_3_years_doesnt_believe_i/cmnzb8q?context=3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have a seat on the couch and check out the psychiatry drama in TIL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 02:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heavy drama in /r/funny when Redditors chew the fat about BMI. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 03:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheater drama is fully popped in /r/AdviceAnimals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 10:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP in /r/relationships is mad at the woman her son got pregnant, and the sub is mad at OP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 16:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First time hosting Thanksgiving in our new house. I cooked for a solid day, and I was happy with the results. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 19:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man feeds the homeless, but is he just a shill for Olive Garden? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 17:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP in /r/pics gets into a scuffle about how civilized Iran is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 16:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two teen female bombers kill more than 40 in Nigeria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 22:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Lena Dunham drama in /r/rage. Lots of emphatic comments using ALL CAPS. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 14:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nonconformist in /r/books explains how the present world is like 1984--others disagree. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 23:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone asks "what do you think of my BBQ?" Which, of course, leads to bickering over what BBQ means. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 16:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP in /r/relationships used a mobility scooter at the store, leading to drama about health, weight, and fat-acceptance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 00:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama in /r/videos about stopping on crosswalks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 15:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OKCupid expands options for gender and sexual orientation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 04:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disabled puppy drama! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 01:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salvador Dali on "What's My Line" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 22:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby name drama in /r/funny. "get off your 'pretend-like-you-care' soapbox." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 14:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Awkward Interview in which reporter asks (formerly anorexic) Jamie-Lynn Sigler if she would date fat men like her BF on Entourage, finds out that is her real boyfriend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 07:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Working through the first deer of hunting season, made some venison chili! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 23:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fine dining drama in /r/funny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 20:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone quotes George Carlin in an /r/politics thread about legalizing prostitution. Someone objects, and things get buttery. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 19:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now THIS is how you toss pizza dough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 22:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Soon they'll be claiming that their paedophilia is a right..." Yep, it pretty much gets buttery from there. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 00:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paging Nurse Drama to /r/WTF.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 07:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fishing for drama... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 03:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone made a TIL post about PETA, so this was probably inevitable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 15:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama in /r/rage about whether or not a father should have stood up for his son </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 02:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Candy is dandy but honey is drama in /r/food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 22:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/sex has a petty argument about the importance of accurate anatomical terminology. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 21:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marriage...marriage is what brings us some drama...today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 21:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Things get heated in /r/whatcouldgowrong about the proper procedure for treating an exploding glowstick to the face </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 03:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a common phrase that drives you nuts when people say it wrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 20:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama in TIL about how a lotto winner chose to use her winnings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 20:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My department is having a dinner tonight, so I made a flourless chocolate cake (ganache is still warm in this pic)! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 21:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My department is having a dinner tonight, so I made a flourless chocolate cake (ganache is still warm in this pic)! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 21:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GTM] Average Neighborhood... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 03:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paprika and pork butt brings spicy, savory drama in /r/food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 22:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Freemium debate comes up in /r/videos post about South Park. Rugged battles are fought, and it sees a Pyrrhic victory is at hand... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 10:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patriotic "goose/duck" is a steal at $200. Put it anywhere and share your zeal! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 07:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This creepy chef can be yours for only $50! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 07:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strange GamerGate brouhaha in /r/conspiratard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 06:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gregory on Cutthroat Kitchen?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 00:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been working my way through Cutthroat kitchen and just saw that Gregory is in the last episode of the 2nd season. Did anyone notice that? The more cooking competition shows I watch, the more competitors I see on multiple shows--there's this weird, incestuous thing going on with cooking competition shows (on different networks, no less).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Childcare drama in /r/relationships </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 22:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you have to be creative to be a musician? Drama about muscle memory and musical artistry in /r/videos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 21:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Person in /r/music says they've never heard a Taylor Swift song. The great pop music debate rages on... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 01:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GTM] Investigating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 21:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A passionate Miley vs. Madonna discussion in /r/OldSchoolCool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 21:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Energy drink drama in /r/worldnews. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 20:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GTM] It's only a dream... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 02:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GTM] Heading home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 00:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GTM] We interrupt this broadcast... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 19:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drama in /r/OKCupid when one Redditor speculates that OP must have omitted part of a posted conversation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 17:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tonight's Word: Drama. Huge argument about the merits of Stephen Colbert's satire in /r/television </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 23:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A liberal dose of Liberal drama in /r/facepalm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 02:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monsanto is brought up in an /r/AskReddit thread--then someone cites a high school paper and everyone argues about what makes a source "reputable." Fun times! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 07:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Piss Test Etiquette Drama in /r/AdviceAnimals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 06:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/Relationships talks about feelings! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 21:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Draw My Hell--Mary Doodles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 03:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Easy-to-assemble drama in TIL about the food at Ikea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 18:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My spouse landed a doe yesterday (clean lung shot with an arrow) and he brought me back the liver...here's what I did </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 02:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My spouse brought me a fresh deer liver, so I did my best to make some venison pt! Possibly NSFW due to blood... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 01:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did some test makeup last night--looking for tips! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 18:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/U9vzw

So I haven't done any horror makeup in probably 10 years or so, but I saw liquid latex on sale and thought hey, why not? This wound was done with the latex, some wet tissue for texture, and my blood recipe. I had difficulty with the skin tone and was wondering what type of makeup works best? Also, any tips on making really nice bruising? I used a little eye pencil, but I'd like to get some advice on what works best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need a horror recommendation for someone who doesn't typically like horror movies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 03:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, my spouse doesn't like horror movies, although we've watched films like The Shining, and Cabin in The Woods, and The Silence of The Lambs, and 28 Days Later together. He just doesn't like the whole slasher/gore thing very much. I, however, love horror movies and have seen hundreds, and I told him I would love it if we could watch just one scary movie together this Halloween because it's my favorite time of year and he agreed. Can you give me some recommendations for not-so-gory and high quality horror films? I would love to go deep and show something slow building like Don't Look Now , Alice Sweet Alice, The Changeling, or the Orphanage but I'm not sure he would have the patience for that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bacon-wrapped pork tenderloin with roasted squash and a slaw of kale, cabbage, carrots and Brussels sprouts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 02:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antipasto, followed by a primo of drama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 18:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Section 8 housing leads to drama about section 8 in the military in /r/facepalm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 16:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A commenter in /r/Chicago says yes to ketchup on hot dogs. Responses vary... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 22:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that only one member of Congress voted against the Authorization for Use of Military Force Against Terrorists after 9/11, stating that they should be "careful not to embark on an open-ended war with neither an exit strategy nor a focused target." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 03:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Infidelity + HIV = drama in /r/relationships </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 17:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
