<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject331</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gotham - 2x04 "Strike Force" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 01:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 2 Episode 4:** [Strike Force](http://i.imgur.com/W30bbpu.jpg)

**Aired:** October 12, 2015

***

Captain Barnes is called to duty to create a law-abiding task force, with the help of Gordon. Meanwhile, Penguin gets caught up in a favor for Galavan, and Nygma asks Kringle out on a date.

*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Affair - 2x02 "Episode 2" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 02:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 2 Episode 2**: [Episode 2](http://i.imgur.com/VrN5iPA.jpg)

**Aired**: October 11th, 2015

***

Alison's summer with Noah is interrupted by an unwelcome guest. Meanwhile, Cole's self-destructive lifestyle causes everyone to become concerned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Leftovers - 2x02 "A Matter of Geography" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 02:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 2 Episode 2**: [A Matter of Geography](http://i.imgur.com/YrH4RlW.jpg)

**Aired**: October 11th, 2015

***

Kevin, Nora and Jill try to pick up the pieces in the aftermath of the Mapleton riots, but problems from the past keep resurfacing. The new Garvey clan finds a fresh start in the safety of Miracle. Nora makes an impulsive choice, while Kevin gets entangled in the Murphy familys problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homeland - 5x02 "The Tradition of Hospitality" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 02:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 5 Episode 2**: [The Tradition of Hospitality](http://i.imgur.com/MKrU4h0.jpg)

**Aired**: October 11th, 2015

***

Carrie and Dring visit a refugee camp. Saul and Allison are at odds. Quinn stays on mission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Dusk Till Dawn - 2x07 "Bring Me the Head of Santanico Pandemonium" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 20:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 2 Episode 7**: Bring Me the Head of Santanico Pandemonium

**Aired**: October 6, 2015

***

With Uncle Eddies help, Richie and Seth hatch a plan to complete Santanicos revenge and walk away with the score of a lifetime. Meanwhile, Freddie and Kate find themselves facing an unexpected foe after Malvados attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gotham - 2x03 "The Last Laugh" - Post-Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 03:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gotham - 2x03 "The Last Laugh" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 01:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 2 Episode 3:** [The Last Laugh](http://i.imgur.com/mlllNml.png)

**Aired:** October 5, 2015

***

Gordon and Bullock track down a nemesis from the past, leading to a standoff between Jerome and Gordon. Meanwhile, a magic show at the Gotham Children's Hospital gala turns into a hostage situation.

*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First trailer for Vinyl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 08:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fear The Walking Dead - 1x06 "The Good Man" - Post-Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 04:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Affair - 2x01 "Episode 1" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 03:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 2 Episode 1**: [Episode 1](http://i.imgur.com/F4E7JCA.jpg)

**Aired**: October 4th, 2015

***

Noah and Helen try for amicable divorce proceedings, but complications indicate inescapable conflict. Surprising developments in Helens life reveal unexpected emotions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fear The Walking Dead - 1x06 "The Good Man" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 02:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 1 Episode 6**: [The Good Man](http://i.imgur.com/UGK6tbx.jpg)

**Aired**: October 4th, 2015

**Directed by**: Stefan Schwartz

**Written by**: Robert Kirkman   Dave Erickson

***

As civil unrest grows, and the dead take over, Travis and Madison try to devise ways to protect their families.

*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homeland - 5x01 "Separation Anxiety" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 02:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 5 Episode 1**: [Separation Anxiety](http://i.imgur.com/c1Rz2CI.jpg)

**Aired**: October 4th, 2015

***

Almost two years after the Embassy attack in Islamabad, Carrie is building a new life in Berlin. But her peace is threatened when a request from her boss forces her towards the dangerous world she left behind.

*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Leftovers - 2x01 "Axis Mundi" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 02:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 2 Episode 1**: [Axis Mundi](http://i.imgur.com/fLVd0F0.jpg)

**Aired**: October 4th, 2015

***

Jarden, Texas was renamed Miracle after it was discovered that no one had departed. The town has since become a magnet for tourists and people who are convinced it is special and can keep them safe. Among the local families is the Murphys: the father, John, the mother, Erika, and their twins, Evie and Michael. While trying to protect his town from frauds and charlatans, John gets an ominous warning from a man who claims to have psychic powers. Soon afterwards, Kevin Garvey, Nora Durst and Jill Garvey show up in Miracle. This newly formed family left Mapleton to start over, but Kevin cannot seem to escape his past. The Murphy family and Kevin subsequently experience a mysterious event that will that change their lives forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parasyte - Series Premiere Discussion Thread [SPOILERS] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 06:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Premise:** They arrived in silence and darkness, descending from the skies with a hunger for human flesh. Parasytes - alien creatures who must invade and take control of a human host to survive - have come to Earth. No one knows the secret except high school student, Shinichi Izumi, who's right hand has been invaded by a Parasyte. Shinichi and Migi, the Parasyte, begrudgingly form a friendship in the middle of a silent war between humanity and the Parasytes.

**Subreddit:** | **Network:** | **Premiere date:** | **Airing:** | **MyAnimeList:**
:--:|:--:|:--:|:--:|:--:
**/r/Toonami** | [Toonami](http://www.adultswim.com/toonami/) | October 4th, 2015 @ 1:00 AM | Sunday| [8.65/10](http://myanimelist.net/anime/22535/Kiseijuu:_Sei_no_Kakuritsu)

**Links:** 

* [IMDb](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt3358020/)

* [Wikipedia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Parasyte)

* [Official trailer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kW7Gb9mKUeQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The rule requiring spoiler tags in titles has been removed in /r/TheLeftovers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 21:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have removed the requirement to have tags in your title, such as [Season 1] or [No Spoilers]. We primarily instituted tags in season 1 so as to separate spoilers from the book, but now that season 1 basically covered the book, the rule no longer feels necessary.

Many users encountered troubles with the tagging system, and we feel the frustration the system caused submitters outweighed the benefit some users gained from being able to browse with specific spoiler scopes.

All we ask now is that you abstain from putting spoilers in the title. You should now expect spoilers up to the latest aired episode in any links or comments posted here, unless the title specifically says otherwise (such as a user with a season 1 question, or an official episode discussion).

Also keep in mind that episode previews and information from IMDB (such as the number of episodes a character appears in) is considered to be a spoiler and should be tagged appropriately.

If you have any feedback, or even requests for the sub in general, feel free to comment.

Remember - season 2 airs this Sunday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Dusk Till Dawn - 2x06 "Bizarre Tales" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 05:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 2 Episode 6**: Bizarre Tales

**Aired**: September 29, 2015

***

Following the trail of the mass grave, Freddie and Kate uncover epic secrets and confront Oculto, a reclusive and dangerous Lord. Seth and Richie take the girls on a double date, and Carlos lets go of the past.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gotham - 2x02 "Knock, Knock" - Post-Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 03:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fear The Walking Dead - 1x05 "Cobalt" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 03:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 1 Episode 5**: [Cobalt](http://i.imgur.com/8WdISdw.jpg)

**Aired**: September 27th, 2015

**Directed by**: Kari Skogland

**Written by**: David Wiener

***

The National Guard's plan for the neighborhood is revealed. Meanwhile, Travis and Madison make a difficult decision.

*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Masters of Sex - 3x12 "Full Ten Count" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 12**: Full Ten Court

**Aired**: September 27th, 2015
***
Masters and Johnson find their life's work in jeopardy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ray Donovan - 3x12 "Exsuscito" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 12**: Exsuscito

**Aired**: September 27th, 2015

***

Abby and Terry finally tell Ray the truth about Bridget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Look at Series Premiere of 'Billions' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 06:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Dusk Till Dawn - 2x05 "Bondage" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 00:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 2 Episode 5**: [Bondage](http://i.imgur.com/htDahW2.jpg)

**Aired**: September 22, 2015

***

The Gecko brothers finally call a truce and work together to find Malvado's headquarters; Carlos, unhinged from the Labyrinth, abducts Santanico and claims her for himself. And Kate enlists Freddies help as she attempts to save her brother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Masters of Sex - 3x11 "Party of Four" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 03:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 11**: Party of Four

**Aired**: September 20th, 2015
***
Agendas collide as Masters, Johnson, Logan and his wife meet for a dinner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ray Donovan - 3x11 "Poker" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 02:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 11**: Poker

**Aired**: September 20th, 2015

***

Mickey pushes his luck by throwing himself a goodbye party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fear The Walking Dead - 1x04 "Not Fade Away" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 02:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 1 Episode 4**: [Not Fade Away](http://i.imgur.com/jn4YVWP.jpg)

**Aired**: September 20th, 2015

**Directed by**: Kari Skogland

**Written by**: Meaghan Oppenheimer

***

Madison and Travis see different sides of the National Guard's occupation in their neighborhood; the family tries to adapt to the new world.

*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Official 2015 Emmys Discussion Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 02:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ***

Welcome to the /r/television discussion thread for the 67th Primetime Emmy Awards. Please post all discussion regarding this years event in this thread.

***

**Time:** 8 PM ET/5 PM PT

**Location:** Microsoft Theater, Los Angeles, California

**Host:** Andy Samberg

**Network:** Fox

***

### Nominees

**Outstanding Comedy Series**

* Louie (FX)
* Modern Family (ABC)
* Parks and Recreation (NBC)
* Silicon Valley (HBO)
* Transparent (Amazon)
* Unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt (Netflix)
* [](/emmy) Veep (HBO)

**Outstanding Drama Series**

* Better Call Saul (AMC)
* Downton Abbey (PBS)
* [](/emmy) Game of Thrones (HBO)
* Homeland (Showtime)
* House of Cards (Netflix)
* Mad Men (AMC)
* Orange Is the New Black (Netflix)

**Outstanding Variety Series**

* The Colbert Report (Comedy Central)
* [](/emmy) The Daily Show with Jon Stewart (Comedy Central)
* Jimmy Kimmel Live! (ABC)
* Last Week Tonight with John Oliver (HBO)
* Late Show with David Letterman (CBS)
* The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon (NBC)


**Outstanding Miniseries**

* American Crime (ABC)
* American Horror Story: Freak Show (FX)
* The Honorable Woman (SundanceTV)
* [](/emmy) Olive Kitteridge (HBO)
* Wolf Hall (PBS)

***

**Outstanding Lead Actor in a Comedy Series**

* Anthony Anderson as Andre Dre Johnson, Sr. on Black-ish (ABC)
* Don Cheadle as Marty Kaan on House of Lies (Showtime)
* Louis C.K. as Louie on Louie (FX)
* Will Forte as Phil Tandy Miller on The Last Man on Earth (Fox)
* Matt LeBlanc as Himself on Episodes (Showtime)
* William H. Macy as Frank Gallagher on Shameless (Showtime)
* [](/emmy) Jeffrey Tambor as Morton Maura Pfefferman on Transparent  (Amazon)

**Outstanding Lead Actress in a Comedy Series**

* Edie Falco as Jackie Peyton on Nurse Jackie (Showtime)
* Lisa Kudrow as Valerie Cherish on The Comeback (HBO)
* [](/emmy) Julia Louis-Dreyfus as President Selina Meyer on Veep (HBO)
* Amy Poehler as Leslie Knope on Parks and Recreation (NBC)
* Amy Schumer as Amy / Various Characters on Inside Amy Schumer (Comedy Central)
* Lily Tomlin as Frankie Bergstein on Grace and Frankie  (Netflix)

**Outstanding Lead Actor in a Drama Series**

* Kyle Chandler as John Rayburn on Bloodline (Netflix)
* Jeff Daniels as Will McAvoy on The Newsroom (HBO)
* [](/emmy) Jon Hamm as Don Draper on Mad Men (AMC)
* Bob Odenkirk as Jimmy McGill on Better Call Saul (AMC)
* Liev Schreiber as Ray Donovan on Ray Donovan (Showtime)
* Kevin Spacey as President Frank Underwood on House of Cards (Netflix)

**Outstanding Lead Actress in a Drama Series**

* Claire Danes as Carrie Mathison on Homeland (Showtime)
* [](/emmy) Viola Davis as Professor Annalise Keating on How to Get Away with Murder (ABC)
* Taraji P. Henson as Cookie Lyon on Empire (Fox)
* Tatiana Maslany as Various Characters on Orphan Black (BBC America)
* Elisabeth Moss as Peggy Olson on Mad Men (AMC)
* Robin Wright as First Lady Claire Underwood on House of Cards (Netflix)

***

**Outstanding Supporting Actor in a Comedy Series**

* Andre Braugher as Captain Ray Holt on Brooklyn Nine-Nine (Fox)
* Tituss Burgess as Titus Andromedon on Unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt (Netflix)
* Ty Burrell as Phil Dunphy on Modern Family (ABC)
* Adam Driver as Adam Sackler on Girls (HBO)
* [](/emmy) Tony Hale as Gary Walsh on Veep (HBO)
* Keegan-Michael Key as Various Characters on Key   Peele (Comedy Central)

**Outstanding Supporting Actress in a Comedy Series**

* Mayim Bialik as Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler on The Big Bang Theory (CBS)
* Julie Bowen as Claire Dunphy on Modern Family (ABC)
* Anna Chlumsky as Amy Brookheimer on Veep (HBO)
* Gaby Hoffmann as Alexandria Ali Pfefferman on Transparent (Amazon)
* [](/emmy) Allison Janney as Bonnie Plunkett on Mom (CBS)
* Jane Krakowski as Jacqueline Voorhees on Unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt (Netflix)
* Kate McKinnon as Various Characters on Saturday Night Live (NBC)
* Niecy Nash as Denise DiDi Ortley on Getting On (HBO)

**Outstanding Supporting Actor in a Drama Series**

* Jonathan Banks as Mike Ehrmantraut on Better Call Saul (AMC)
* Jim Carter as Charles Carson on Downton Abbey (PBS)
* Alan Cumming as Eli Gold on The Good Wife (CBS)
* [](/emmy) Peter Dinklage as Tyrion Lannister on Game of Thrones (HBO)
* Michael Kelly as Doug Stamper on House of Cards (Netflix)
* Ben Mendelsohn as Danny Rayburn on Bloodline (Netflix)

**Outstanding Supporting Actress in a Drama Series**

* [](/emmy) Uzo Aduba as Suzanne Crazy Eyes Warren on Orange Is the New Black (Netflix)
* Christine Baranski as Diane Lockhart on The Good Wife (CBS)
* Emilia Clarke as Daenerys Targaryen on Game of Thrones (HBO)
* Joanne Froggatt as Anna Bates on Downton Abbey (PBS)
* Lena Headey as Cersei Lannister on Game of Thrones (HBO)
* Christina Hendricks as Joan Harris on Mad Men  (AMC)

***

For a full-list of categories and nominees please visit the [official site](http://www.emmys.com/awards/nominees-winners) or [Wikipedia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/67th_Primetime_Emmy_Awards). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Westworld Adds Tessa Thompson To Cast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 20:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Bastard Executioner - Series Premiere Discussion Thread [SPOILERS] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 00:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Premise:** The Bastard Executioner is a blood-soaked, medieval epic that tells the story of Wilkin Brattle, a 14th century warrior, whose life is forever changed when a divine messenger beseeches him to lay down his sword and lead the life of another man: a journeyman executioner. Set in northern Wales during a time rife with rebellion and political upheaval, Wilkin must walk a tight rope between protecting his true identity while also serving a mysterious destiny.

**Subreddit:** | **Network:** | **Premiere date:** | **Airing:** | **Metacritic:**
:--:|:--:|:--:|:--:|:--:
**/r/TBX** | [FX](http://www.fxnetworks.com/shows/the-bastard-executioner/about) | September 15th, 2015 | Tuesday| [55/100](http://www.metacritic.com/tv/the-bastard-executioner)

**Cast:**

* Lee Jones as Wilkin Brattle

* Stephen Moyer as Milus Corbett

* Bran F. OByrne as Baron Ventris

*F lora Spencer-Longhurst as Baroness Lowry "Love" Aberffraw Ventris

* Kurt Sutter as The Dark Mute

* Kyle Rees as Calo Caine

* Sam Spruell as Toran Prichard

* Katey Sagal as Annora of the Alders

* Darren Evans as Ash y Goedwig

* Danny Sapani as Berber the Moor

* Timothy V. Murphy as Father Ruskin

* Sarah White as Isabel Kiffin

* Sarah Sweeny as Jessamy Maddox

* Ethan Griffiths as Luca Maddox

* Ross O'Hennessy as Locke

* Alec Newman as Leon Tell

* Tim McDonnell as Huxley

* James Rousseau as Denley

**Links:** 

* [IMDb](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt4218618/)

* [Wikipedia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Bastard_Executioner)

* [Official trailer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pCUoDZI9CpY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Dusk Till Dawn - 2x04 "The Best Little Horror House In Texas" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 23:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 2 Episode 4**: [The Best Little Horror House In Texas](http://i.imgur.com/INfp5wm.jpg)

**Aired**: September 15, 2015

***

Kate hunts down Scott in Bethel before he can exact revenge. In Houston, Richie and Santanico find themselves deep in the flesh trade, while Seth tries to get back in Uncle Eddies good graces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gotham - 2x01 "Rise of the Villains: Damned If You Do..." - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 05:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 2 Episode 1:** [Rise of the Villains: Damned If You Do...](http://i.imgur.com/Nt7LJNT.png)

**Aired Online:** September 14th, 2015

***

Penguin is King of Gotham and after a shakeup at the GCPD, Detective James Gordon's moral compass wavers, as he seeks help from Penguin. Meanwhile, Bruce Wayne continues to explore the secrets from his father's office, and Gotham newcomers Theo Galavan and his sister, Tabitha, make friends with some unlikely allies - a group of dangerous inmates from Arkham.

***

Another episode discussion will be made for when the episode airs on broadcast television. For context, those who have a PlayStation Plus subscription were able to watch it on Monday as a digital exclusive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fear The Walking Dead - 1x03 "The Dog" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 02:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 1 Episode 3**: [The Dog](http://i.imgur.com/mcS26mR.jpg)

**Aired**: September 13th, 2015

**Directed by**: Adam Davidson

**Written by**: Jack LoGiudice

***

After they escape a riot, Travis, Liza and Chris seek refuge with the Salazars; Madison defends her home.

*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Masters of Sex - 3x10 "Through a Glass, Darkly" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 03:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 10**: Through a Glass, Darkly

**Aired**: September 13th, 2015
***
Johnson objects to Masters' program following missteps in the protocol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ray Donovan - 3x10 "One Night In Yerevan" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 02:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 10**: One Night In Yerevan

**Aired**: September 13th, 2015

***

Ray comes up with a fix to help Mickey. Bridget gets into a fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Longmire - 4x01 "Down by the River" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 09:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 4 Episode 1**: Down by the River

**Aired**: September 10, 2015

***

The team struggles with the fallout from Branch's confrontation with Barlow, and Walt's Crusade to bring Nighthorse to justice spins out of control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Longmire - 4x10 "What Happens On The Rez..." - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 09:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 4 Episode 10**: What Happens On The Rez...

**Aired**: September 10, 2015

***

The line between justice and law gets even blurrier for Henry and Walt as their hunt for a killer intensifies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Longmire - 4x09 "Shotgun" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 09:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 4 Episode 9**: Shotgun

**Aired**: September 10, 2015

***

Henry's attempt at justice backfires, resulting in new problems for him and a new investigation for Walt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Longmire - 4x08 "Hector Lives" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 09:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 4 Episode 8**: Hector Lives

**Aired**: September 10, 2015

***

When a former suspect in a rape case ends up dead in another county, Walt and Vic aren't convinced the death was an accident. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Longmire - 4x07 "Highway Robbery" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 09:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 4 Episode 7**: Highway Robbery

**Aired**: September 10, 2015

***

A highway robbery sets off an investigation into a strange relationship, while Walt struggles to let go of the past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Longmire - 4x06 "The Calling Back" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 09:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 4 Episode 6**: The Calling Back

**Aired**: September 10, 2015

***

A young Native American girl is raped on the reservation, which sparks new, volatile tensions between local oil rig workers and the Cheyenne people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Longmire - 4x05 "Help Wanted" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 09:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 4 Episode 5**: Help Wanted

**Aired**: September 10, 2015

***

When the husband of a former soldier is assaulted during an apparent robbery, Walt is drawn into an emotionally charged investigation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Longmire - 4x04 "Four Arrows" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 09:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 4 Episode 4**: Four Arrows

**Aired**: September 10, 2015

***

A body found in the luggage of a tour bus further complciates Walt's troubles with Nighthorse. Henry makes a bold move to help a mother and son. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Longmire - 4x03 "High Noon" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 09:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 4 Episode 3**: High Noon

**Aired**: September 10, 2015

***

The investigation of Nighthorse heats up, but not in the way that Walt was hoping for. Cady makes a shocking discovery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Longmire - 4x02 "War Eagle" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 09:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 4 Episode 2**: War Eagle

**Aired**: September 10, 2015

***

Walt is forced to split his focus between new evidence in a personal case, and the murder of a caretaker at a former Japanese internment camp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Dusk Till Dawn - 2x03 "Attack of the 50 ft. Sex Machine" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 23:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 2 Episode 3**: [Attack of the 50 ft. Sex Machine](http://i.imgur.com/jEIIzg7.jpg)

**Aired**: September 8, 2015

***

Richie and Santanico pose as sex traffickers to infiltrate Malvados food supply, while Sonja forces Seth to kick his drug habit. Meanwhile, Freddie faces off with Sex Machine, who attacks his family to retrieve the codex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Masters of Sex - 3x09 "High Anxiety" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 00:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 9**: High Anxiety

**Aired**: September 6th, 2015
***
Masters continues his surrogacy program, now under Johnson's critical eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ray Donovan - 3x09 "The Octopus" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 00:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 9**: The Octopus

**Aired**: September 6th, 2015

***
An attempt to draw Mickey out of hiding jeopardizes Bunchy's wedding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jim Carreys Showtime show casts Me And Earl And The Dying Girls RJ Cyler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 07:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Dusk Till Dawn - 2x02 "In a Dark Time" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 20:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 2 Episode 2**: [In a Dark Time](http://i.imgur.com/9EIwdWh.jpg)

**Aired**: September 1, 2015

***

Seth and Kate stage a heist, while Gonzalez endures frightening visions that lead to a grisly discovery, and back at the Twister, Malvado's plans are set into motion by Carlo's emergence from the labyrinth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fear The Walking Dead - 1x02 "So Close, Yet So Far" - Post-Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 04:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Masters of Sex - 3x08 "Surrogates" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 03:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 8**: Surrogates

**Aired**: August 30th, 2015
***
Johnson jets away with Dan Logan. Masters begins his surrogacy program. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ray Donovan - 3x08 "Tulip" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 02:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 8**: Tulip

**Aired**: August 30th, 2015
***
Romero appears at the Fite Club, challenging Ray to repent for his sins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Show Me A Hero - Parts 5   6 - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 02:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Parts 5 and 6 of 6**

**Aired**: August 30th, 2015

***

Armed with a growing recognition that he had fought on the side of angels in the battle over the housing, Wasicsko plans his political comeback, while the residents for the new townhouses are screened and chosen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Narcos - Series Premiere Discussion Thread [SPOILERS] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 09:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Premise:** The true story of Colombia's infamously violent and powerful drug cartels fuels this gritty new gangster drama series.

**Subreddit:** | **Network:** | **Premiere date:** | **Airing:** | **Metacritic:**
:--:|:--:|:--:|:--:|:--:
**/r/Narcos** | [Netflix](http://www.netflix.com/title/80025172) | August 28th, 2015 | Friday| [74/100](http://www.metacritic.com/tv/narcos)

**Cast:**

* Wagner Moura as Pablo Escobar

* Pedro Pascal as Javier Pena

* Manolo Cardona as Eduardo Mendoza

* Boyd Holbrook as Steve Murphy

* Mauricio Compte

* Ana de la Reguera as Elisa

* Stephanie Sigman as Valeria Velez

* Joanna Christie as Connie Murphy

**Links:** 

* [IMDb](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt2707408/)

* [Wikipedia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Narcos)

* [Official trailer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U7elNhHwgBU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Dusk Till Dawn - 2x01 "Opening Night" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 00:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 2 Episode 1**: [Opening Night](http://i.imgur.com/uCkUuBk.jpg)

**Aired**: August 25, 2015

***

Santanico and Richie are outside Houston, living like Bonnie and Clyde; Seth and Kate are scraping by South of the Border; and Freddie Gonzalez is protecting his wife and young daughter in a Houston suburb. And Carlos Madrigal and Scott Fuller emerge from the Titty Twister, changed men. They will all come together once again - this time facing off against an even bigger threat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Brink - 1x10 "There Will Be Consequences" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 02:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 1 Episode 10**: There Will Be Consequences

**Aired**: August 23rd, 2015
***
There is a looming global crisis, which Walter tries to avert with other heads of state via videoconferencing. Zeke and Glenn end up in a compromised state. Alex attempts to make a personal connection with Zaman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ballers - 1x10 "Flamingos" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 02:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 1 Episode 10**: Flamingos

**Aired**: August 23rd, 2015
***
Spencer faces a tough decision when Joe has an idea for a new venture; Ricky is confronted by his dad; Charles gets another chance; and Jason and Spencer try to get through to Vernon once and for all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Masters of Sex - 3x07 "Monkey Business" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 01:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 7**: Monkey Business

**Aired**: August 23rd, 2015
***
Masters and Johnson are interviewed as they take on an exotic new patient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ray Donovan - 3x07 "All Must Be Loved" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 01:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 7**: All Must Be Loved

**Aired**: August 23rd, 2015
***
Ray is contacted by Romero. Bunchy joins Mickey against the Minassians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Show Me A Hero - Parts 3   4 - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 01:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Parts 3 and 4 of 6**

**Aired**: August 23rd, 2015

***

Mayor Wasicsko finally achieves some consensus and rams through a housing plan with a tough vote, and housing officials finally begin to plan to build the new townhomes. But even as they do, the political costs to Wasicsko become apparent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fear The Walking Dead - Series Premiere Discussion Thread [SPOILERS] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 01:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Premise:** Set in Los Angeles, California, the series follows a divorced male teacher, a female guidance counselor, and her two childrena son and a daughterin the opening stages of the zombie apocalypse as they come to terms with the impending collapse of civilization.

**Subreddit:** | **Network:** | **Premiere date:** | **Airing:** | **Metacritic:**
:--:|:--:|:--:|:--:|:--:
**/r/FearTheWalkingDead** | [AMC](http://www.amc.com/shows/fear-the-walking-dead) | August 23rd, 2015 | Sunday| [65/100](http://www.metacritic.com/tv/fear-the-walking-dead)

**Cast:**

* Kim Dickens as Madison Clark, a high school guidance counselor, fiance of Travis', and single mother of Alicia and Nick.

* Cliff Curtis as Travis Manawa, a high school English teacher, Madison's fianc, and a divorc who shares custody of his son, Chris, with his ex-wife Liza.

* Frank Dillane as Nick Clark, Madison's son who has flunked out of college and is battling a drug problem.

* Alycia Debnam-Carey as Alicia Clark, Madison's high-achieving and ambitious daughter who is in a relationship with her jock boyfriend Matt. She is able to read situations well and often finds herself at odds with Nick, due to his unmotivated nature.

* Lorenzo James Henrie as Chris Manawa, Travis and Liza's son, who resents his father for their divorce.

* Elizabeth Rodriguez as Liza Ortiz, Travis' ex-wife and mother of their son Chris. A free-spirited bohemian type, she is attempting to rebound from her disastrous marriage and is in nursing school.

* Rubn Blades as Daniel Salazar, Ofelia's father. He is a barber who moved his family to LA from a different culture decades ago to start fresh.

* Mercedes Mason as Ofelia Salazar, born and raised in the U.S. and protective of her immigrant parents.

* Patricia Reyes Spndola as Griselda Salazar, Daniel's wife and Ofelia's mother, Catholic and unwilling to justify the supernatural phenomena with science. She attributes the ills of the world to the sins committed by mankind.

**Links:** 

* [IMDb](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt3743822/)

* [Wikipedia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fear_the_Walking_Dead)

* [Official trailer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WDxew5SguVw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Brink - 1x09 "Just a Little Crazy Talk" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 03:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 1 Episode 9**: Just a Little Crazy Talk

**Aired**: August 16th, 2015
***
Walter seeks to make a deal with Zaman's highest-ranking general; a grounded Zeke and Glenn find a way to pass the time; Rafiq's translation helps Alex determine how to go about implementing Walter's "Plan B." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ballers - 1x09 "Head-On" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 03:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 1 Episode 9**: Head-On

**Aired**: August 16th, 2015
***
Joe feels slighted when his efforts at work go unnoticed; Spencer tries to make amends; Bella challenges Ricky to act like an adult; Vernon is nowhere to be found after discovering what Reggie's been up to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Masters of Sex - 3x06 "Two Scents" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 02:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 6**: Two Scents

**Aired**: August 16th, 2015
***
Masters and Johnson take on a famous couple hoping to renew their sex life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ray Donovan - 3x06 "Swing Vote" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 02:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 6**: Swing Vote

**Aired**: August 16th, 2015
***
Ray must ensure Verona's Election Day victory to protect his NFL interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Show Me A Hero - Series Premiere Discussion Thread [SPOILERS] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 00:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Premise:** Based on Lisa Belkin's nonfiction book of the same name, in the 1980s, a federal court order forces Yonkers mayor Nick Wasicsko (Oscar Isaac) to make a decision to build low-income housing in white neighborhoods that could ruin his political career and further divide the city.

**Subreddit:** | **Network:** | **Premiere date:** | **Airing:** | **Metacritic:**
:--:|:--:|:--:|:--:|:--:
**/r/ShowMeAHero** | [HBO](http://www.hbo.com/show-me-a-hero) | August 16th, 2015 | Sunday| [83/100](http://www.metacritic.com/tv/show-me-a-hero)

**Cast:**

* Oscar Isaac as Nick Wasicsko, former police officer then Yonkers City Council member running for election to be mayor of Yonkers, eventually the youngest big-city mayor in the nation

* Carla Quevedo as Nay Noe Wasicsko, City Hall staffer, Mayor Wasicsko's wife

* Jim Belushi as Angelo R. Martinelli, a six-term Mayor of Yonkers who is Wasicsko's opponent in the election to be mayor of Yonkers

* Alfred Molina as Henry J. Spallone, Yonkers City Council member who was passionately anti-housing

* Winona Ryder as Vinni Restiano, Yonkers City Council president who advocated for integration

* Jim Bracchitta as Nicholas Long, Yonkers City Council member who was outspoken in his criticism of the federal ruling

* Terry Kinney as Peter Smith, the Yonkers Housing Authority director

* Jon Bernthal as Michael H. Sussman, civil rights attorney and former federal prosecutor; represents the local NAACP chapter

* Michael Stahl-David as James Surdoval, Wasicsko's political consultant

* Clarke Peters as Robert Mayhawk, neighborhood consultant

* Catherine Keener as Mary Dorman, an East Yonkers homeowner

* LaTanya Richardson-Jackson as Norma ONeal, a home health aid who lives in the projects, and is struggling with losing her sight

**Links:** 

* [IMDb](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt2492296/)

* [Wikipedia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Show_Me_a_Hero)

* [Official trailer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t8VpChKfkd8)

***

Please note that given that I've seen HBO "spoil" the show in their promotional materials, discussion of all the real world events pertaining to the show do not require spoiler tags. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Show Me A Hero - Parts 1   2 - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 23:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Parts 1 and 2 of 6**

**Aired**: August 16th, 2015

***

Nick Wasicsko becomes the youngest big-city mayor in America, but at what cost? Even before he is inaugurated, the obligation to build public housing in the white neighborhoods of Yonkers looms over his new administration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Simons Show Me A Hero turns public housing into essential TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 09:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Season two of The Affair will include betrayed spouses perspectives </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 21:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Billions | Official Trailer | Paul Giamatti   Damian Lewis Showtime Series </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 21:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creator David Simon interview: 'Violence and sex are the only two currencies that work on television time and again' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 02:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lessons of Yonkers From David Simons Show Me a Hero </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 02:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> True Detective - Season 2 Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 22:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread will be set to sort by new comments by default. The discussion for Omega Station is [here](http://redd.it/3ger7h) and the post-episode discussion is [here](http://redd.it/3gf3k7). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S2E8] Post your quick questions here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 22:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread is set to sort so that new questions will automatically appear at the top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Olivia Wilde as Devon Finestra </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 07:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bobby Cannavale as Richie Finestra </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 07:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> True Detective - 2x08 "Omega Station" - Post-Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 04:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We get the world we deserve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ballers - 1x08 "Gaslighting" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 02:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 1 Episode 8**: Gaslighting

**Aired**: August 9th, 2015
***
Spencer tries to save Vernon by confronting his past; Ricky tries to reconcile with Bella; Charles finds that his football skills come in handy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> True Detective - 2x08 "Omega Station" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 03:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 2 Episode 8**: [Omega Station](http://i.imgur.com/yH8omUn.jpg)

**Aired**: August 9th, 2015

***

Frank, Ray and Ani weigh their options as Caspere's killer and the scope of corruption is revealed.

***

This thread will temporarily be set to sort by new comments, and the creation of the post-episode discussion thread **will not occur immediately** after the episode ends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Brink - 1x08 "Who's Grover Cleveland?" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 02:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 1 Episode 8**: Who's Grover Cleveland?

**Aired**: August 9th, 2015
***
Alex makes amends; Zeke is forced to face the women in his life; Walter urges caution in the Situation Room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Masters of Sex - 3x05 "Matters of Gravity" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 02:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 5**: Matters of Gravity

**Aired**: August 9th, 2015
***
Johnson's parents arrive unannounced. Masters takes on a promising patient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ray Donovan - 3x05 "Handshake Deal" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 02:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 5**: Handshake Deal

**Aired**: August 9th, 2015
***
Ray's new mission drives a wedge between Finney and Paige. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> True Detective - 2x08 "Omega Station" - Pre-Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 20:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Synopsis: [](#s "Frank, Ray and Ani weigh their options as Caspere's killer and the scope of corruption is revealed.")
***
The preview and synopsis for this episode can be discussed here without spoiler tags, as well as any other promotional materials for this episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Daily Show with Jon Stewart - Final Episode Discussion Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 04:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread will sort by new comments by default. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> August 6th, 2015 Republican Presidential Candidates Debate - Discussion Thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 22:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread will sort by new comments by default. The following info is copied from the /r/politics [thread](http://redd.it/3g1md4):

***

[**Click here for the /r/politics Reddit Live thread**](https://www.reddit.com/live/vcum7xwwd9rz)

##How to Watch

A cable subscription is required in order to watch the televised debate live:

* Fox News Channel on TV
* Livestream on [FOXNEWS.com](http://www.foxnews.com/live-coverage/fox-news-republican-presidential-primary-debate)

Options for readers without a cable subscription:

* [/r/politics live feed](https://www.reddit.com/live/vcum7xwwd9rz)
* Fox News 2016 Election HQ app live feed: [Apple iOS](https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/fox-news-election-hq-2016/id1020952535?) | [Google Android](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.foxnews.foxnewselection)

Fox's Election app has a "live scorecard" which you can use to compare your own views to the candidates' answers.

##Schedule

All times in Eastern Time. Click any time to convert it to your local time zone.

* [5 PM](http://www.wolframalpha.com/input/?i=Convert+5pm+ET+to+local+time) - First Debate
* [6 PM](http://www.wolframalpha.com/input/?i=Convert+6pm+ET+to+local+time) - Online Pre-Show
* [9 PM](http://www.wolframalpha.com/input/?i=Convert+9pm+ET+to+local+time) - PrimeTime Debate
* [10 PM](http://www.wolframalpha.com/input/?i=Convert+10pm+ET+to+local+time) - Online Post-Debate Show


##Lineup

###5 PM ET - Bottom 7 Candidates

* Rick Perry (Former Gov. - TX)
* Rick Santorum (Former Sen. - PA)
* Bobby Jindal (Gov. - LA)
* Carly Fiorina (Former CEO, Hewlett-Packard)
* Lindsey Graham (Sen. - SC)
* George Pataki (Former Gov. - NY)
* Jim Gilmore (Former Gov. - VA)

###9 PM ET - Top 10 Candidates

* Donald Trump (Real Estate Magnate)
* Jeb Bush (Former Gov. - FL)
* Scott Walker (Gov. - WI)
* Mike Huckabee (Former Gov. - AR)
* Ben Carson (Former Neurosurgeon, John Hopkins Hospital)
* Ted Cruz (Sen. - TX)
* Marco Rubio (Sen. - FL)
* Rand Paul (Sen. - KY)
* Chris Christie (Gov. - NJ)
* John Kasich (Gov. - OH) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teaser for Vinyl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 22:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Promo for Vinyl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 19:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Condola Rashad Joins Showtime Pilot Billions' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 06:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> True Detective - 2x07 "Black Maps and Motel Rooms" - Post-Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 04:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> True Detective - 2x07 "Black Maps and Motel Rooms" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 02:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 2 Episode 7**: [Black Maps and Motel Rooms](http://i.imgur.com/cmClAdz.jpg)

**Aired**: August 2nd, 2015

***

Ray, Ani and Paul take precautionary measures to elude detection and untangle a dark mystery; Frank deals with the fallout of his betrayal.

***

Discussion about the episode preview needs to be spoiler tagged. Copy paste this code to talk about the preview:

\[Preview](#s "Text goes here")

***

This thread will temporarily be set to sort by new comments, and the creation of the post-episode discussion thread will not occur immediately after the episode ends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Brink - 1x07 "Sticky Wicket" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 02:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 1 Episode 7**: Sticky Wicket

**Aired**: August 2nd, 2015
***
Alex plans an escape for some Pakistani schoolgirls; Zeke is challenged to a fight; Walter fakes a medical emergency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ballers - 1x07 "Ends" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 02:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 1 Episode 7**: Ends

**Aired**: August 2nd, 2015
***
Ricky flies off the handle; Spencer and Charles say good-bye to Roddney; Jason meets his mother's new beau. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Masters of Sex - 3x04 "Undue Influence" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 02:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 4**: Undue Influence

**Aired**: August 2nd, 2015
***
Masters seeks unexpected advice. Virginia is distracted by news of Henry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ray Donovan - 3x04 "Breakfast of Champions" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 02:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 4**: Breakfast of Champions

**Aired**: August 2nd, 2015
***
Ray puts out fires as Paige tries to broker a deal. Abby goes to Boston. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> True Detective - 2x07 "Black Maps and Motel Rooms" - Pre-Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 00:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Synopsis: [](#s "Ray, Ani and Paul take precautionary measures to elude detection and untangle a dark mystery; Frank deals with the fallout of his betrayal.")
***
The preview and synopsis for this episode can be discussed here without spoiler tags, as well as any other promotional materials for this episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martin Scorsese and Mick Jagger team up for record label drama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 18:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Fincher HBO Pilot Utopia In Jeopardy Over Budget Issues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 03:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rookie Blue - 6x11 "74 Epiphanies" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 02:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 6 Episode 11**: 74 Epiphanies

**Aired**: July 22nd, 2015 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flairs from Season 2 are now available </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 00:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also if you have any additional flair suggestions or suggestions for the subreddit feel free to leave them here. 

Flair suggestions should preferably come with an image, or at least the general time in a specific episode your character appears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> True Detective - 2x06 "Church in Ruins" - Post-Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 03:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> True Detective - 2x06 "Church in Ruins" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 02:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 2 Episode 6**: [Church in Ruins](http://i.imgur.com/9JRJtFE.jpg)

**Aired**: July 26th, 2015

***

Desperate to locate a missing woman with intel on Caspere, Frank meets with Mexican drug dealers. Ani infiltrates an exclusive inner circle, with Ray and Paul keeping close tabs.

***

Discussion about the episode preview needs to be spoiler tagged. Copy paste this code to talk about the preview:

\[Preview](#s "Text goes here")

***

This thread will temporarily be set to sort by new comments, and the creation of the post-episode discussion thread will not occur immediately after the episode ends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Brink - 1x06 "Tweet Tweet Tweet" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 02:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 1 Episode 6**: Tweet Tweet Tweet

**Aired**: July 26th, 2015

***

Walter runs into Joanne in Tel Aviv and tries to use her new position to his advantage. Meanwhile, Zeke and Glenn, who are being held hostage by Martin and Vanessa, agree to participate in role-playing games in hopes of being released; and Kittredge shares a revolutionary dream with Alex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ballers - 1x06 "Everything Is Everything" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 02:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 1 Episode 6**: Everything Is Everything

**Aired**: July 26th, 2015

***

Charles decides he is going to be selfish. Joe negotiates with Maximo. Ricky's off-field activities end up being revealed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Masters of Sex - 3x03 "The Excitement Of Release" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 02:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 3**: The Excitement Of Release

**Aired**: July 16th, 2015

***

Masters and Johnson look to capitalize on their burgeoning fame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ray Donovan - 3x03 "Come and Knock on Our Door" - Episode Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 02:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Season 3 Episode 3**: Come and Knock on Our Door

**Aired**: July 26th, 2015

***

Ray and Mickey make a desperate attempt to get Terry released from prison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
