<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3269</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 04:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Faber-Castell pen and even though it was kind of expensive ($100), I love writing with it.  The solid metal feel is way different than the other plastic pens.  I love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 07:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sandra Bullock in While You Were Sleeping anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 06:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 06:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok cool.  I have read some about creating functions but I don't really understand it yet. Also can I just use c for this or do I have to use c++?  I would like to implement things such as armor and a combat system of some sort.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 06:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks again.  I will understand exactly what my code does in the future and understand the underlying concepts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 05:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will read the chapters that pertain to what I am doing and try to understand it fully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 05:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also realize that programming, like everything else, is a process.  I know very little about the language and am not trying to get ahead of myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 05:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I realize that     scanf() takes user input.

I generally understand these concepts.  I am in a computer class at the local community college and was just trying this as an additional exercise to try and get a grasp on the concepts.  I have read the chapters on loops and input and output, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-06 05:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thanks.  Yes I will expand further on the no path.  What I'm wondering is how I get it to ask the user for input again if they press "p" for example.  And yes, if I only have one line I do not need the curly braces.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 06:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try C for Dummies.  It's really easy to understand and explains the concepts well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 13:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swim. "Blub blub blub!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 13:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harry Truman was a soldier in World War 1 and fired some of the last shots in the war before the armistice went into effect.  He also fired the last two "shots" in World War 2, with the dropping of atomic bombs on Hiroshima and Nagasaki. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 06:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That if I squeeze my chin with my hand as hard as I can for 30 seconds and then flick it, my face would be relieved of stress.  Turns out it doesn't relieve stress, just leaves a huge hickey for days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 02:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's always how it is.  Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 03:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah boredom and just sitting there not getting anything done are my triggers.  Just get tired of sitting there and give in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 19:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finally feel like I have a plan when I am tempted.  Thanks so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 16:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude great job!  It's so fulfilling when you don't do it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 16:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's be accountability buddies.  This is one of the big steps in conquering this.  I just found reddit today and it seems great.  90 days here we come! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 16:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ill be accountability partners with you guys.  lets do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
