<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1989</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 08:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orion, daylight, M7G677, Phase 2, Weller and Jane have to obviously fall back in love, Sarah and Reede have to fall in love, and I'm not entirely convinced Mayfair is dead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Lets talk about online dating. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 07:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Reading about yourself by putting your name into urban dictionary is like reading a horoscope. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 05:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 05:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My high school physics teacher showed this to my class on the day he gave us the lesson of not assuming that just because you know what you are looking for, you know what is there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 05:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If i am drinking something straight, I prefer something brown like a good bourbon or cognac - neat. I'm a classics man when it comes to mixed drinks. Gin Tonic always hits the spot for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your preferred Reddit app and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 04:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do I see commercials for brick and mortar businesses that don't exist in my area? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 04:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pugs! Yeah! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 02:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 02:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oops
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2r_001PXgdI  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When a girl messages me first and gives me her number right away, I assume it's a bot and either ignore, report, or unmatch her. Am I overly-skeptical? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 00:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something that has to be on a bucket list? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 23:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 21:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dudettes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 18:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Volunteering is free </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some of my favorite shows revolve around FBI agents. CIA must be jealous. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 18:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 17:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SI was established in 1960 by the 11th General Conference on Weights and Measures. With the only historical context to speak of until then being Avogadro and his contemporaries at the end of the previous century, a kilogram was defined as the mass of a cubic decimeter  of water. But the kilogram had to be *commissioned* by the GCWM where an arbitrarily sized hunk of  platinum-iridium was put under a glass cloche to match the mass of the liter of water and be oohed and aaahed at. They already  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 10:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I'm not proposing another change. Im simply trying to understand why a council of scientists, especially chemists and physicist that work with materials on a regular enough basis that it matters, didn't pick a standard mass unit in the first place that would scale the atomic mass unit by a rounder number than 6.02*10^23. It's a moot point, I know, but I'm sure there is a better and historically more interesting reason they came up with than convenience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 09:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Originally, but the council that later redefined all those standards changed the definition of a meter to a specific fraction of the speed of light and the kelvin temperature scale that starts at absolute zero. They had the opportunity and didn't take it is all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Survey] What makes a coach good/bad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 09:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 09:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about conforming to regular sound pollution laws like only being allowed at particular times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 09:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Have you tried turning it off and on again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 09:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coffee and carbs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why not set the SI base unit of mass at something that would turn avogadro's number into a round number? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 09:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 08:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem like the exception though, growing up with the organ eating. Also, if you are suggesting that the pesticide industry is the reason the bug-cooking kitchens are having a traction problem, I wanna see that because I think the pesticide industry is alive and well around the rest of the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All the Coca Cola brands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 07:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are entomophagy and eating organs not common practices in the US? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 07:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems popular and fine in most of the rest of the world. Why are Americans so turned off by it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Draco Malfoy a Werewolf!? Credit to the SuperCarlinBrothers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 06:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A paper airplane guide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 05:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A saber that was invented toward the end of the use of sword in battle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 04:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember watching a documentary on the History channel on swords and they were talking about one sword in particular that is considered to be one of the better designed sabers in military history and never got to see actual battle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 03:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is his Lucky Cricket?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Reddit, what do we think of using karma as an incentive to get people to look things up that would otherwise be reposts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 03:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exercise is REALLY good for you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 01:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 00:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree but what I want to add is that depending on the size of the college, you are going to have a pretty easy time either making the kinds of friends that drink all the time or the kinds that don't so make the choice for yourself first and stick with it. Peer pressure in college doesn't happen the same way because everyone is an adult and that being an adult puts a lot on your shoulders like the incentive to care about your grade more than your professor does or the decisions you make in your personal life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens to the eyelash that gets stuck on my eyeball if I don't pick it out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 00:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 23:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you plan on taking CS 162 in the fall, plan on taking 140U in the summer. It will be a required prerequisite instead of just a recommended one. Found that out on day 1 of the CS 162 class I am taking this term. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 22:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things like loading a web browser and loading a document each take minutes, and booting up is also slower than it should be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for the most cost-effective solution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 21:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am working on a laptop for a friend that is a few years old and slow. It's running windows 7 home pro on an Intel i7 and most of the parts are good but to speed things up, I am looking at putting more RAM in it as well as replacing the disk drive with a solid state. I could either get those parts OR invest in a new, less powerful laptop. Keep in mind we are only talking about a machine that is going to be for a basic user that only needs to do things like check email and pay bills. Which option should I opt for?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What is the difference between meteors, meteorites, comets, and asteroids? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 08:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do I see commercials for brick and mortar businesses that don't exist in my area? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 07:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do sprinklers stutter instead of letting a steady stream of water out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 01:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes for a decent dance move but I wonder what the actual reason is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 01:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 19:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct. Default to thinking in my dominant language but I could almost just as easily not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 11:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Capable but often, the mind picks a dominant language. They say it's the one that you default to counting in. Rings true for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alphabetical order is named for Greek alphabetical order. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 01:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alpha Beta  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 23:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you can't upgrade the screen quality any easier than speakers. But weather it's 4k resolution or YouTube 360, things seem to be changing every day whereas the audiophile can feel confident in saving up for something that won't be yesterday's news tomorrow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How are innovations in video quality able to to happen more frequently and in bigger leaps than audio quality? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 23:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 23:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But  not everyone ( for more or less obvious reason) makes the point of saying that they are spoken for when they are. Give people the benifit of the doubt?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something that doesn't exist anymore, but could stand to be great if it made a comeback? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 21:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only man on Venus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 21:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The loneliest man on Venus. Thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 20:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 20:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's big business now for the industry to get those buildings up to code.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 18:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why Canada prints maple syrup scented Monopoly money.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where is the line between being nice, being flirty, and being interested? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 10:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 08:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did investors not like about the financial element? What changed about the finances when Alphabet acquired Google and it's assets? I understand that Google now has more breath to do other things but is that it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 08:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a few years into college and stay in touch with a few separate clicks of my best high school friends. The single best friend I have go back father than that though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 08:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen this one before but I finally saved it, cropped everything else away, and confirmed for myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why did Larry Page and Sergey Brin set up Alphabet Inc. only for it to acquire Google? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 02:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the projects and companies that are in Alphabet's portfolio look like things that Google was already in charge of. So why give Google a parent company?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 02:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a pretty flat town. Lots of people use bikes. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sure, Aphrodite poses naked in a giant clam shell, she's a goddess. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 00:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But when I do it, I'm ''drunk' and 'no longer welcome at the aquarium'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recommend to me the last song/album/artist you listened to. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 23:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 23:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Specific examples aside, some languages (in English) are named after their country and vice versa while plenty aren't. I was just looking for a pattern that maybe existed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 23:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Specific examples aside, some languages (in English) are named after their country and vice versa while plenty aren't. I was just looking for a pattern that maybe existed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are some languages like German, Russian and Japanese named after their nationality versus languages like Farsi, Mandarin or Hindi? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 21:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 21:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Dark Knight Rises </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 20:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tl;dr... Kidding, but then you have professionals in the auto repair, coffee, fragrance,wine and other industries whose livelihood depends on their ability to communicate with a client to a level that I have never been able to get on. Obviously there is a cultural element there too. I remember walking into a place for a coffee tasting and they showed me their palette wheel and I saw 'tobacco' on there. A month later, I am buying a cigar as a present and pass by one that was described as having coffee notes. The level of discretion that people give themselves seems to be greater when they aren't talking about what something looks like but there is still soooome uniformity to it all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 20:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is a tire level for? And correct me if I'm wrong but it sounds like an either/or decision with a patch kit and spare tube.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 18:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and her number is 867-5309 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yeah I pronounce it pasketti. Why? Is there another way?  Winston Churchill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 17:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.definitelyrealquotes.com/?id=12_9  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 17:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me know how things are going for you with that!. I have my bike but no gear and I won't actually make the lifestyle change until I move out to a college town.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 10:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *consonant* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite word to say out loud? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 09:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How are people able to describe their sensory experiences so effectively? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 08:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I see something, I can communicate to you what it looked like. I can't say the same though for smells, tastes or sounds. It seems to come so naturally to others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a triple threat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 07:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My singing, dancing, and acting are all threateningly terrible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 06:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious how an industry where you know all of your competitors deals with moles and talent poaching differently than where the market only gets saturated after there are too many names and faces to keep track of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 06:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l9CZr10ebLQ  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 02:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're adorable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I am in a subreddit, why is the box that limits my search to that subreddit only checked by default half the time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 22:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Discribe your sex life with a movie title. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 21:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I know it's a repost. I like this game though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 18:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That'll do pig. That'll do" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 18:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.jasondavies.com/wordcloud/ 

You get control over some cool variables </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taking a drug test pass/fail is much more ambiguous than knowing if you show up positive or negative. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 08:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Controversial posts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 06:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I sort my submitted posts by 'controversial', they are ordered by the number of comments, is 'controversial' just a shorthand for must commented on?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Word Cloud of Trump's Speech on Foreign Policy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 06:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Foreign Policy speech 4/27/16 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 06:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 05:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> keyloggers, etc. - Does 'etc.' include the screen-monitoring software that professors use in classrooms?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is an invaluable skill you have that most others don't? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 04:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did the hipster burn his tongue on his coffee? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 03:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because his barista fucking hastes hipsters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 02:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not entirely sold on SIMON's original motive though. Either way, they only traced Liam's steps through the last couple season to fill his timeline up to Grand Central. That wasn't all the plot holes. I think Systemics might be implicated. If not through the Hass family, then by their own accord. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 22:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finale began with a flashback to before his first day at Quantico where he told Miranda he was being forced to take the blame for Chicago. 
The a montage of all the setup. 
They show Liam taking the plans from Simon. I'll re-watch the entire episode later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 22:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, in his confession to Alex and Ryan before they drop him, his original plan was to try to get Alex to drop out of Quantico. The plans came later. I'm not sure but I'm gonna go out on a limb and assume that when he bugged the Nat's rooms, that he found out about the Grand Central plans that Simon had right around the same time that he realized he wasn't going to be able to get Alex out the easy way. It still makes me hate how Liam's character was written because apparently Grand Central was plan B and that was a huge leap in planning without the equal leap in motivation. His beef with the FBI mismatches his obsession with Alex. All shoehorned into an episode and a half. Lets see what happens next season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 22:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what are some of the hardware challenges of quick-sort? Does it demand more processor power or something?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 22:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pivot?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 21:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is my situation. I know how to ride a bike without falling and after that is where I am out of my depth. I'm looking to adopt bicycling as a mode of transportation. How should I prepare for the impact on my physical wellness?How will it impact my time-management? What about protecting my investment with gear, maintenance and accessories?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quicksort seems to beat everything else in every scenario. Can someone explain to me what purpose other sorting algorithms? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 21:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZZuD6iUe3Pc  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain to me the purposes of using anything other than quick sort? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 21:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waiting for it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 21:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Mongols! I really wanna see a montage of all the Mongols references throughout the series all in one video. I think it would be an awesome way to put into context just how many trends they are the exception to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 20:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bicycling as a form of transportation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 20:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is my situation. I learned as a kid and haven't forgotten how to ride. But kids aren't often worried so much about fitness goals, maintaining a busy schedule, or protecting their 2-wheeled investment. So here I am, basically a noob, asking for some basic advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 20:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that if I want to write code, I need an IDE geared toward one particular language or family of, but for the execution of code that is written in Java or Python or CSS, are the compilers really that ubiquitous or what? I can't remember the last time I ran into a page on the web that couldn't show me something because I wasn't on a machine with flash player. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 20:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a traveling expo? I am on the west coast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 19:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm not mistaken, traveling got to a peak 15% at 5-ish P.M. which blew morning rush hour our of the water. One of the coolest things I have seen in a while! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 10:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Slavic and Cyrillic languages to name a few.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 10:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think English has enough gendered words for that to be an issue but for someone whose first language doesn't contain articles, the idea of articles needs to be clearly and concisely communicated. For example; I [as posing as someone who is learning English] can tell that 'a' is to be used if the noun begins with a continent vs using 'an' if it begins with a vowel but when to use 'a(n)' vs 'the' is still confusing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 10:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was visiting family and friends that live in Germany and it was less of a tourist drawing conclusions from observation that seeing for myself what they (the people that live in Germany) had said. I guess some Germans just know better than other Germans... obviously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 10:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all the examples that I'm coming up with in my head blurred the mouth too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I like my doctor and my mechanic but I hope I don't have to see them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 10:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are articles (the, an, a, etc.) so difficult for ESL speakers to pick up on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 09:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I understand that most languages have something quirky about them that native speakers just get and most others just don't but it's maddening to think that in a day and age where we understand so many things so much better than we used to, we can't quite articulate language itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 09:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Israel asked America out and that made everyone that Israels neighbors very angry, especially after how America and Syria have been looking at each other the last couple weeks. Taiwan also wants to ask America out but China is being the jealous friend. Brazil, usually the fun one, thinks prom is overrated and too expensive, especially since she is feeling under the weather, but the Prom committee reeaally wants Brazil to show up anyway. Russia is eying all of her exs. Ukraine was single. Everyone thinks Puerto Rico should be able to go but she isn't officially a student yet, admin is really dragging their feet with the paperwork. Costa Rica wore the prettiest dress. India brought 5 dates and is trying really hard to get rid of a couple. Saudi Arabia and his squad were the ones that showed up in a stretch hummer limo. The Korea twins make a point of showing up separately at different times with different dates in the same dresses. Greece and Spain are getting drunk in the parking lot but it's okay because Germany is their DD and they are totally not gonna puke on the car ride home.
After party at Ireland's place.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 09:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://cdn.meme.am/Instance/Preview?imageID=84688 generatorTypeID= panels= text0=cant%20tell%20if%20slug%20is%20big text1=or%20if%20banana%20is%20small text2= text3= </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'tl;dr' also means that typing out four full words is too long for them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 08:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apparently, a game of mine backed up to my SD card. Where in this Labrynth of folders do I go? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 08:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 07:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That much I understand, it was that leap from hunk of metal to Turing test taker that I was trying to break down into bite-sized pieces.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 07:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Follow up question - higher languages? I know that there are hundreds of languages out there but how are they compartmentalized? Is it a spectrum or a hierarchy or something else?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 06:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To echo what u/dandimae said, casein is dairy enough that someone like myself who would react to any milk product would be allergic to that particular powder versus lactose intolerant customers could handle it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 42 maps of the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 06:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 06:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blurring the mouth is enough of a visual cue enough of the time that you'd think people wouldn't get confused. Redundancy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do computers understand binary? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 06:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, binary is the language of computers, but what is the grammar that helps a computer differentiate between what is supposed to be a character on the screen from the sound or color corresponding to the same binary value?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After a long and tough discussion, my wife and I decided to go with adoption. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 04:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let the little shits be someone else's problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Found a website where you can either get your music to match your mood or get your mood to match the music. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 04:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I go to get an online order wrapped like a present? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 03:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does 'Next of kin' not exclusively refer to your children/grandchildren? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 03:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The selfie stick that will give you a workout. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 02:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Sausage,
Turkish Wax,
Brazilian Bros,
German Kiss,
Cuban House Mafia,
French Eagle,
Dutch Coffee,
Polish Shepard, 
Swedish Cigar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was about to say that it looked familiar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the closest location to me. I'll try to come up with a group.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 01:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was actually. But warranty or not, they should have fixed it. It took LG a while but I think they came out with a public statement about the bug (bootloop) for the models made before early October. They fixed it for free and paid for shipping both ways but I did loose some data.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to recover messages after a factory reset? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 23:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the list of users that I have messaged with before but not any of the content. Even my favorites have been cleared.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The record holder for the largest 'Where's Waldo' hunt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 23:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does it mean that a post is archived and why can't I comment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 22:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10-4 = message received. There are 199 more </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 21:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Index of Important Irrational Constants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 20:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are the Reddit-esque banner adds legitimately Reddit's or paid third-party spam? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 20:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 20:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was in Germany a few years ago, I saw a bunch of decommissioned windmills that were build for the tax breaks and abandoned for the lack of actual energy provided. I'm looking forward to see what is going to be different about this time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 20:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's great acting like athletes are the types of people that only care about how much money, publicity, and fun they can get in before they peak and then seeing stuff like this and realizing that some if not most are actually pretty damn good people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 20:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Food porn.... just as fake as actual porn...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 20:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New York is also over-represented but most people don't care about anything outside of the 5 bureaus  of NYC and maybe Buffalo, Rochester, Syracuse, and Albany.... Lets go with over-estimating how much people know about the state because maybe my experience hasn't been a representative one but it is still fascinating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 09:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do I go? How can I find this? Must do. Bucket list just got longer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SuperCarlinBrothers do a good job of explaining just about everything Disney Pixar. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 09:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 09:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I purchased the phone I have now just weeks before the android 6.0 release date and it ended up being defective for hardware reasons so I sent it to the manufacturer (LG if you were curious) and got it back with MM. I thought they were just doing a factory reset but it turns out they did me the 'favor' of loading up the new software for me too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 08:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, so, it seems like everyone knows all the cities in California. Not just LA, San Diego, Sacramento and the Bay area, but all of it. I get that it is huge in a lot of respects (population, physically, economically, historically) but the only other places that people *seem* too have as good of a handle on is somewhere like Italy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I KNOW if I am getting the best deal or not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 07:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always am [or at least think I am] on the lookout for money saving techniques, deals, sales, how to do the best research, etc. I'm not a penny-pincher but I am getting tired of friends and family telling me how much I could have saved on my latest big purchase if only I had come to them about if first.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are people able to talk about California's geography as if it's all assumed knowledge? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 06:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm becoming familiar with it just by virtue of talking to Californians all the time but that doesn't seem like what everyone else is doing so I'm just curious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt is a mental hospital patient singing about himself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 06:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 06:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been thinking of trying a pizza recipe out! Thank you! What about the dough though?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 05:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how notes like 'sea foam' and 'bursts fully-armed from forehead' have their own mention in they key when they happen once.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 04:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't need as much a sense of security as I need security. I don't use apps i'm not confident in using.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 04:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well now I am slightly more confused, the second part of your explanation where it is smaller than all positive numbers, larger than all negative numbers, and not zero... Is there not just a positive and negative infinitesimal on either end of zero on the number line?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 04:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha. yeah I've been dairy free for years but not decades.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [In math] What is the difference between a point and an infinitesimal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 04:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What is your criteria for a candidate, presidential or otherwise? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 03:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 23:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that book how you make your own cheese? Because I'm willing to try just about anything. I tried the shredded cheese that I think you are talking about and I'm not a fan. I gotta melt it down before it tastes good on anything. .... What about the higher end stuff, like I know there is a wheel of almond milk bree at Wholefoods for something like $10.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 22:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit - download* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is every app (on launch, not fownload) asking for permission to access phone data? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 22:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 19:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell kind of ceiling is that?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 19:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll keep an eye out for it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 18:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John Oliver did an interview [specifically about extremist anti-homosexual policy in Uganda] where he points out that words for homosexual has existed for a long time whereas the word for homophobia arrived with the Europeans. 

Part 1 - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G2W41pvvZs0 
Part 2 - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QJkiWwMKwSo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 18:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! There is no Wegman's where I live though. Wholefoods, Trader Joes, and even places like SafeWay end up with something here and there. I know about Chao and that is currently my favorite. I can't stand daiya but haven't melted it down on anything yet either so I guess that that's worth revisiting. Tofutti makes a good cream cheese but I;ll have to watch out for their ice cream. Did you know that Ben and Jerrys now has a couple dairy free flavors?!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is rubber really a good analog for human skin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 18:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard and seen that people who use a cutthroat razor have practiced with it on an inflated balloon first but I just can't understand how the skill is transferable. Great, you can not cut a balloon, but a face is different...right?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know of a good vegan cheese? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 09:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I developed an allergy so I have been dairy free for a while. It doesn't bother me anymore that I can't have a lot of things that I used to be able to but it is maddening that I have been able to find a good vegan version of yogurt, ice cream, milk, butter, and even some chocolates that don't taste too bitter. It's the cheese that no one can seem to come close to. Daiya just doesn't do it for me. Anyone else having any luck?    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 21:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Football as in American football or as in what Americans call soccer?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What topic(s) are you clueless about when people around you start talking about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 20:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 19:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PASCAL'S TRIANGLE. Look it up. There are so many hidden patterns in there, it's spooky. Really gives you an appreciation for how beautiful numbers can be. I've even got a printout in my math folder for school. It can be a good cheat sheet sometimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 19:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, they say that every love story ever written is either R J or the taming of the shrew... I also don't think that they would introduce a new character as a plot convenience just so that Liz would have help pulling it off so I'm excited to see who it could have been. And for what it's worth, Aram is the one that quoted Shakespeare and if anything, it might be double-foreshadowing for what is to come of him and Navabi.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 19:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I park it in the garage, take hairpin turns nice and slow but long bendy roads quickly (and I've noticed more right turns than left) and about half the time, I break and accelerate smoothly and the other half, pretty hard. I also drive in reverse more often that I feel like is normal for things like reparking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do my driving habits affect my car's longevity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 11:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 11:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the relationships between all the still-supposedly-alive characters will keep Tom alive at a minimum but we are starting to see the entire family tree. I'll give you that there are elements of family feud in the plot but family trees are at the epicenter of the plot so I guess only time will tell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've got a 2-part question about reposts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 11:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) What's the Reddit community's consensus on one OP posting the same thing to multiple subreddits for more eyeballs? I feel like if its applicable, go ahead but I could also see it being taboo for some reason. 

2) On the occasion that the moderators or the filter or whoever blocks a post recommends I take that post to a different sub, should I actually pursue it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 06:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Romeo and Juliet's love were forbidden, yes, but not by a single power player in both of their lives [Reddington] while the rest supported their love. Besides, R J is a tragedy, and by Shakespearean standards, that means everybody dies at the end, not the lead character with an entire act left to go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey people into fitness, how do you go about the REST of your day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 05:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of the working out I have ever done was either in PE at school or at home. I've never used the locker room showers but I always clean up after a workout if I can. Is that just something that I have to budget time for or is it a non-issue for you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 00:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly it. Breaking characters out of battling other characters in their typecast would be great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 00:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I could settle for that but the original thought was a dedicated season to pitting winners of previous battles against each other. Maybe one crowning champ per season?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 00:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sooooo where is my giftcard? I went to the site, entered my credit card info, social, all of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we get a bracket going for the actual winners of the rap battles please? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 00:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 00:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Da-yum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I found a web page where ever day on the calendar has something to celebrate, just in case you need the pick-me-up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 00:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 365 holidays, festivals, and celebrations. 
http://hubpages.com/holidays/365holidays  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 23:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> security and malware
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it alright for me to assume that links people post on Reddit are fine to go to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 23:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weather or not the NSFW filter is on, I can't help but be extremely weary of any website I've never heard of. I was hoping there was some security measures that Reddit implements.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something that is helping make your college experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 23:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one is feeding me golden nuggets and I don't even know what to ask but I am looking for stuff like money tips, useful apps, and meeting people outside of class and my neighborhood.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 23:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm school exists. Must bang dudes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If it ever reaches critical mass, identifying as a nihilist will be self-defeating. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 22:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 20:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is RES? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does my link karma number show up by my username but not my comment karma number? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 20:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 20:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What country is that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 19:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think some companies have caught onto exactly that. I think Vegas has entirely outlawed high rises with windows that can open. And I forget what Japanese company it is that just resorted to installing nets under their windows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 19:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pedialyte is the one I was trying to remember! Where the heck could I find some and stock up? I don't wanna go to the store for shit when I wake up hungover. Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 02:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a good heavy guage U-lock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 01:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. Banner and Stark had a bromance going in the first Avengers movie. And just for the sake of argument, I think it's a coin toss as to how Thor would react to being made to make a diplomatic decision amongst humans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 01:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what dimensional analysis is, but that doesn't help me with a terminology/definitions understanding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 22:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That being an ass about it is what I was originally thinking of, /u/TheAnhor ... I also live in a ESL household but I don't speak English with an accent. It's when people get pedantic that is frustrating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 08:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the heads up!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 08:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What /u/Drefen and /u/Ratagar said but also tell your friend that he could bring the lettuce from the store in for himself. Lol. I was allergic to the bread that Subway serves and so I went next door to a grocery store, bought my own baguette that I wasn't allergic to, and the subway employee made me a subway sandwich with the bread from next door. At that point, it's not the location breaking corporate policy, it's just excellent customer service.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 00:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well my purpose was just recreational. What I ended up doing was creating a composite function where the parts can all be simplified down to constants but for the sake of mashing, I didn't simplify. So for example part of my function is shifted A(x) where A(x) = d/dx(third root (e))*mod(log_2(k),e^(sqrt2)), where k=3.8 ..... That simplifies down to zero.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 21:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. But it wasn't exactly full of horcruxes either. The fact that it was in the room of requirement was an added level of security but even in there, it's hiding in plain sight from those who are looking for something else. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 21:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm mad at myself for having laughed at this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 18:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *salts a fruit salad*
Oh god! Oh god! Oh god!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 18:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drinking tea with honey and lemon like crazy. I actually stay more hydrated than normal when I am sick because that's my medicine. Symptoms usually are milder and for less time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 04:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 35% drink 2% milk  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
