<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3594</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 07:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About a week ago in that area there was a gas station (now burned down) where a couple African American teenagers had been harassing the indian clerk for weeks so he shot into the air. This caused lots of protests and lots of tension in that area.  There have also been lots of murders around that area recently.  Soooo yeah Milwaukee the most segregated city in the US!  (I say as a white male living in the sub urbs who hardly ever goes into town) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 07:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was armed but it is still unclear if he was threatening the officer but there is helmet footage that will come out in the future </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 07:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The police officer who shot the man was actually black although recently there has been a lot of shootings and racial tension in Milwaukee especially in that area </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 10:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The grammar is atrocious please pay more attention in those college classes AND PLEASE KNOW THE DIFFERENECE BETWEEN THEN AND THAN. Sad story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 04:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone tell me what the song playing during the death battle was?  I looked up all the song names at the end but i either couldn't find them or they weren't the song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 06:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one actually believes this is real, right?  I mean the writer is a good writer and if he or she were to expand this could make this into a book but there is no way this is real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 01:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least it isn't boris johnson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 07:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EVERYTHING becomes politically correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
