<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3835</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You get a 30-second advertising slot on the superbowl which you know will be be watched by hundreds of millions of people, and a $10,000 budget. How do you cause as much chaos as possible? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 22:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least it looks cool.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 21:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time to shine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 21:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst pain you've ever felt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 05:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On/off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 15:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trombone section of an orchestral performance of The Flight Of The Bumblebee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 15:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stuck in routine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 14:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What will you assume about someone based solely on their appearance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 14:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone else noticed the seatbelt on the shoulder press? What's it for? Pics inside </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 13:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/CVAHMdB

http://imgur.com/WHPIw5j

I can't imagine any reason for this, and I've never seen anyone use it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm not sure they entirely thought this through </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 18:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uni student faces prison after filming porn in a public lirary (r/nottheonion) [meta] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 22:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4/5 Dentists recommend canibalism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 15:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The extent of human radio radio signals into the Milky Way; it's not the black square, it's the blue circle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 20:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The showing times for a film on my local cinema's website produces the black dot illusion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 20:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favourite joke/novelty subreddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 02:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could really use some punctuation in here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 13:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mega what? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 13:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best subreddit with under 5,000 subscribers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 00:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your nsfw guilty pleasure? [nsfw] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 13:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An excellent explanation of how gun suppressors work, and what they actually do in real life vs in games and movies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 04:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most egregious thing Hollywood consistently gets wrong in movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 00:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most egregious thing Hollywood consistently gets wrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 01:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OP finds photos of the thieves who stole his iPad in Photo Stream. /u/noondozer gives advice on catching the thieves. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 02:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you write the setup to a joke, will others be able to fill in the punchline? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 23:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And Jesus said unto Peter, "Come forth and you shall receive eternal glory" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 22:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Peter came fifth, and won only a toaster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stephen Fry on Pedantry in Language </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 16:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stephen Fry on Pedantry in Language </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 18:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your inb4 prediction for 2015? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 02:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you predict is likely to happen in 2015? Eg company announcements, celeb gossip, major news stories etc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What frustrating law would your country be better off without? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 22:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My experience with my gym's user/password system </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 18:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Background: 
-------
My gym uses a barcoded card to allow its members entry, which you scan on a barcode reader to operate the turnstile. The gym is operated as part of the university, so I can use the barcode on my student card to get in. I recently lost my student card so had to get a replacement card from the uni, which I assumed would have the same barcode printed on it.

Today:
-------
I arrive at the turnstile and hold my card up. The machine beeps to signal that it read a barcode, and I push the turnstile. It's locked. I raise my card again - maybe there was an error in reading my card. BEEP. No entry. I glance over at the guy at reception, who asks if I've recently replaced my uCard. I smile with realisation and explain briefly that is replaced it a day or two ago. He tells me that since the barcode has changed, I'll need to reregister my card and it'll only take a second. 

"Fair enough," I think, "such are the plights of losing your card. Come to think of it - of course they changed the barcode, so that nobody can use my lost card. What good security." How wrong I was about that last part. I hand him my new card and he searches the system for my name (which takes about 10 seconds. I'd estimate there are maybe of the order of 1000 members of the gym. Even if it's searching the entire uni there are only 30k students and staff.)

Now comes the horror part. 

He found my id in the system by just searching for my name. He then scans my new card and does some typing. 

"Ah," he mutters, looking puzzled. "You've got some symbols in your password which aren't valid password letters, so it's not letting me update your card details. I don't know how it let you save such a complex password. You can change it now if you want?"

At this point I'm a little shocked - firstly at which characters could possibly be causing this problem; secondly at how my password had been allowed to be set with invalid characters; but most agreigously how he had known that my password had special characters in it?! I must have looked puzzled, because he smiled. I asked if he could see my password, and he swivelled the screen around so that I and the two people queuing behind me could see, and pointed at a textbox labelled "user's password". I was flabbergasted. Not only have they stored my password in plaintext, but they've shown it on the screen and allowed the staff member to edit it only by searching for my name. My account stores my email address and credit card details, which were also available in plain text editable form on his screen. This is all on a computer frequently left unattended and easily within reach of anybody who walked through the door to reception. 

I expressed my disapproval only by a disbelieving sigh, and dictated another memorable password with no special symbols in it to him to type into the system. He overwrites my existing password with the new one I told him (remember that at this point he hadn't scanned my ID, and was allowed to edit any of my details just by searching for my name). But my replacement password turned out to be too long - the system only accepts passwords of length 15 characters or fewer. This is getting silly. I finally came up with a decent acceptable password, and was allowed entry to the facilities. God help me if they ever have a security breach. 

I'll ask for my email and credit card details to be removed as soon as I get a chance, or whatever I can do. I know it's only the local gym, but anywhere can be susceptible to data theft, either by clever hacking or by a twelve year old walking through reception and opening the unattended computer. 

Please make sure that you're safe with your data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 22:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most frustrating law you must heed every day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 19:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst way to die? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 16:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most frustrating law you must heed every day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 02:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A law which causes you daily frustration - perhaps from work or by som you do frequently - and why?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favourite Harry Potter pickup/chat-up line? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 04:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean actual good ones, not just ones which try to lever in characters or objects from the HP world without really meaning much. Everyone knows at least a few - what's your favourite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Damning evidence of how formulaic pop songs have become </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 00:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you blow my mind in three words or fewer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 19:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What life achievement are you most proud of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 01:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Intro] Hi, I guess </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 23:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm James. I'm from the UK. I'm a student studying Computer Science in my third year. I'm 20, 172cm, brown hair green eyes. Never been to this sub before but I was summoned, and apparently people are supposed to introduce themselves, so AMA I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favourite Harry Potter pickup/chat-up line? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 22:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean actual good ones, not just ones which try to lever in characters or objects from the HP world without really meaning much. Everyone knows at least a few - what's your favourite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst sex you've ever had? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 02:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby bunny goes home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 17:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Facebook recently changed their Privacy Policy, I've seen a lot of these </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 02:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 60/30 FPS toggle for video in camera app </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 23:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For slow-motion, you can toggle the fps in the app in the corner. This is great, but I can't understand why they've hidden the option to change the HD video FPS deep in the settings menu. Why not put it in the corner like for slow motion?

Could someone enable this with a tweak? 

--------

(I know this has been [asked before](https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak/comments/2pcc4v/request_60fps_video_toggle_either_in_camera_or/), but I think it'd be a great tweak and it doesn't seem to exist) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Record a sequence of gestures/touches as a macro </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 23:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd be cool if you could use an activator command to start a macro which simulates a series of arbitrary pre-recorded touches on the screen. For example, if I want to delete 5 emails at once, I have to swipe 5 times then tap the delete button after every swipe. I could program a macro to simulate the swipe, then the delete tap 5 times. You could also use it to scroll to the top of a long UI - rather than swipe downwards 10 times, just invoke the macro and let it simulate the swipes for you.
I'm sure you could think of loads of other uses. Why isn't this already a thing?! I think it'd be a great tweak :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you get fired for if your boss/manager found out about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 22:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you get fired for if your boss/manager found out about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 11:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things you're keeping from your manager because if they knew they would fire you. Throwaways advised.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Throws ball; breaks sunglasses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 17:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What weird thing has interrupted you in the middle of having sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 15:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Throws ball; breaks sunglasses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 14:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] [Music] Pop Danthology 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 13:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most fucked up thing you've seen at a funeral? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 13:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do most people think they're better at than most people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 22:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something everyone thinks only they are good at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abra Kadabra </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 22:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most fucked up thing you've seen at a funeral? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 21:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daniel Kim's Pop Danthology 2014! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 20:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most fucked up thing you've seen at a funeral? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 23:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enable airplay of HTML5 videos from mobile safari? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 16:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically the title says it all. Is this possible? I have an airplay enabled TV, and it works fine with YouTube and Netflix, just wondered if I can play from mobile safari  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your worst experience with long-distance travel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 14:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [request] Different ringtone for iMessage than for SMS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 12:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a tweak which does this? If not, could someone make one please? :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you wish your parents had raised you differently? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 01:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your worst experience with long-distance travel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 20:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did it go wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What ridiculous Christmas tradition does your family do every year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 20:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meta] can we get a CSS popup over the downvote arrow to discourage downvotes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 01:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed it a lot in this sub - people love to downvote, and it discourages posting and commenting. I'd like to see some action taken to at least tell people they're being dicks when they downvote for no good reason.

Obviously I'm not against the downvote as a concept - trolls, spam, broken rules etc do need to be downvoted. But the downvote is not a disagree button, and it is kind of disheartening when you mean well but get downvoted, as I've seen a lot during my mostly lurking. This sub just seems to be particularly aggressive for some reason. People make honest meaningless mistakes and get downvoted into oblivion for stuff that doesn't even matter. It'd be far more contstructive to explain why someone is wrong, or explain your opposing point of view, or point out that their link is broken, or something that will actually bring some learning and help people. It just feels immature to see tiny mistakes with a score of -30 or whatever. If someone asks a dumb question, they're probably new, and downvoting them is going to scare them away from becoming active in the community, and it doesn't solve anything. Maybe the answer is in the sidebar, so point them to the resources to find out for themselves so they learn for next time. Everyone is new at some point, and everyone makes mistakes. 

/rant

**Tl;dr** plea to mods to please implement a popup for the downvote arrow to discouraging incorrect use of said arrow. 

Unless anyone has a better idea? I'd like to hear this discussed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chiropractor fixes damaged neck [x r/videos] [unintentional] [attention] [accent] [male] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 14:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> True anarchy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 03:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [unintentional] [female voice] [accent] [humming] How to pull coordinates from Google Maps. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 01:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditor doing this year's reddit Secret Santa buys his gift from the person he's giving it to; recipient sold her own gift. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 12:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Downloaded Dimmer, iPhone 6 immediately breaks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 11:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone else had this problem? I downloaded Dimmer from bigboss, pressed Restart Springboard, and my iPhone is no more (well until I restore it later anyway). Boot loop and red screen of death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Voyage To Nowhere: The Amazon Kindle Story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 16:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the one question every person asks you when they first meet you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 16:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the largest audience you've humiliated yourself in front of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 16:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is Reddit.. Really? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 16:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Change the angle at which my iPad changes screen rotation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 14:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **See tl;dr to skip waffle**

I don't know if this will be easy to change as it seems like it'll be something very core to iOS, but I'll ask anyway because it's **REALLY** annoying. 

When I have my iPad on my knee when I'm sat in a chair, I have the home button on the right hand side when it's in landscape mode. I'm right-handed and it's more intuitive to have the button there. However, Apple seems to want me to use it with the home button on the left -I'll explain. Like most people, my knees are slightly lower than my hips when I'm sat in a chair, making me thighs on a *very slight* downward slope - I'm talking 2 or 3 degrees.  When I rest my iPad on my knees, it interprets this tiny slope as me tilting the device, so it flips the screen upside down. The really annoying thing is that I have to tilt it like 40 or so degrees to turn it the right way again. I don't understand why it's so sensitive in one direction but so resistant to changing in the other direction?!

This preference for home-button-left usage is annoying. I want to use the iPad with the home button on the right (left side of the screen becomes the bottom) but I want to be able to use it on my knees without having to lock the rotation.

**tl;dr** want to change the angle I can tilt my iPad before it flips the screen upside down when I'm using it in landscape mode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the worst piece of advice you've ever followed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 16:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Change the angle at which my iPad changes screen rotation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 23:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **See tl;dr to skip waffle**

I don't know if this will be easy to change as it seems like it'll be something very core to iOS, but I'll ask anyway because it's **REALLY** annoying. 

When I have my iPad on my knee when I'm sat in a chair, I have the home button on the right hand side when it's in landscape mode. I'm right-handed and it's more intuitive to have the button there. However, Apple seems to want me to use it with the home button on the left -I'll explain. Like most people, my knees are slightly lower than my hips when I'm sat in a chair, making me thighs on a *very slight* downward slope - I'm talking 2 or 3 degrees.  When I rest my iPad on my knees, it interprets this tiny slope as me tilting the device, so it flips the screen upside down. The really annoying thing is that I have to tilt it like 40 or so degrees to turn it the right way again. I don't understand why it's so sensitive in one direction but so resistant to changing in the other direction?!

This preference for home-button-left usage is annoying. I want to use the iPad with the home button on the right (left side of the screen becomes the bottom) but I want to be able to use it on my knees without having to lock the rotation.

**tl;dr** want to change the angle I can tilt my iPad before it flips the screen upside down when I'm using it in landscape mode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dad didn't win the lottery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 15:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are you lying to your partner about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 03:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you wish you could experience, that you can never experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 02:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are you lying to your partner about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 02:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using Windows Multi-Touch [Unintentional] [ASMR Starts at 1:00] [american accent] [male] [attention] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 22:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What infuriates you about your town/city/state/country? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 15:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Include where you're from in your comment :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you wish you could experience, that you can never experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 15:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/HickoryChips provides an analogy to the way the gaming industry creates disappointing games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 16:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't even have words for this conversation (r/cringepics) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 13:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [request] Disable (or change gesture for) pinch-to-change-tab screen in safari </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 15:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I try to zoom I get this tabs screen which I never use. Surely other people must be annoyed at this too? Make it a three-finger pinch, or remove it completely. If I want to change tabs there's a bar at the top for exactly that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This tie | Decode... Hell is hell.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 12:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Programmers of reddit, what's the stupidest thing you've ever found in someone else's code? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 11:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which subreddit used to be awesome but has become worse over time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 20:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No defaults!

Also explain your reasoning, don't just write the name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [iPhone 6] [iPad 4th Gen] iOS 8.1.0 tester available </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 20:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit creates a religion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 14:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [self] Detailed calculation on how likely you are to win the lottery if you spend your entire student loan on buying tickets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 00:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do the bacteria that help to digest food in our guts, get into our guts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 19:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Knock Knock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 17:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interrupting Sheep </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 17:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Disable wired tethering? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 13:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I plug my phone into my laptop, my laptop connects to the hotspot. It'd be awesome if there was a toggle to turn off wired hotspot while leaving wifi and bluetooth on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "You are doing that too much. Try again in 7 minutes." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 23:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][word] When an animal enters a new group and it has to "pass a test" to become accepted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 23:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of like the psychology behind 'Hazing'. It's the **test of...** something, I think, or the *something* **test**.  It's usually pretty testing and requires you to show strength of character. Something like "acceptance test" or something. Anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wrapping up a funeral </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 23:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What piece of free software should everybody install on their personal computer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 00:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BioLockdown seems always to take three attempts. Anyone else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 17:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the bio lockdown tweak, and it works great except it seems to take three attempts to unlock mostly every time. When I try to open the locked app, I get the "fingerprint required to launch Photos" twice, with failed scans, then the third time it says "fingerprint required to open Photos" and works. I never that've any problems unlocking my phone (iPhone 6) with the scanner - it works first time like 99% of the time. 

Has anyone else experienced this? Any ideas? I've tried the standard disable/reenable, reinstall, looked through settings and can't see anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What news story was reported completely differently to how you know it happened? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 02:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all know journalism can distort some stories to make them a bit juicier. When have you experienced a story in real life, only to hear it twisted in the news later? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: why do most news websites insist on shoving autoplaying videos in the user's face when they know it pisses everyone off? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 01:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely, ***Surely*** they must know how annoying it is to have videos playing on the side of the screen every time you click anything. So why do they do it? I'd have thought that it generates little if any extra traffic, but they piss off their user base. I'd much rather go to a website with no autoplaying videos over one with.

I'm obviously not talking about sites where you go specifically to view the video, like youtube or netflix. I mean sites where you go to do something else, like **read** a news article, and you have an irrelevant video talking about some other story on the side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] iPad landscape folder view like on iPhone 6 Plus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 00:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As seen [here](http://www.tekrevue.com/tip/iphone-6-plus-landscape-mode-folders/), the iPhone 6 Plus reveals more content when browsing folders in landscape mode. Could someone implement this on the iPad and/or iPhone 6?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I realise I just laughed at something posted on /r/funny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 15:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rectal Thermometer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 15:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My acquaintance, everyone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 23:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If every Karma point you have were worth 1 unit of your local currency, what could you buy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 23:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^(If you're in the UK, 1 Karma = 1; US 1 Karma = $1 etc.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What "feels better than sex"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 14:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WE DID IT, REDDIT!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 23:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dad downloaded a dodgy jailbreak and now a dodgy version of Cydia is stuck on his phone. Help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 16:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's got an iPhone 5S running 7.1.1. He tried to download the jailbreak on his own but he doesn't really know what he's doing, and ended up with some dodgy version of cydia. Over the phone, I talked him through backing up his device to iCloud and then doing a full restore. When he completed the restore, the dodgy cydia was still there (before any of the other App Store apps started to re-download). 

After the restore, the "cydia" screen says 

cydia version 8.1 

if that means anything to anyone? Also,

This is a trial run of cydia for unjailbroken devices. You must jailbreak your device to get the full version

Obviously this is all bullshit, so I told him not to press anything.

I was at home a few weeks ago and had a quick look at it and it was a good imitation of Proper Cydia but it was definitely some kind of phishing scam or something. He said he didn't pay for it, but I told him never to open it. It's just a bit worrying that it persisted on the device after a full restore.

Any advice on how to remove the dodgy Cydia and whatever it might have done to the device? I'm trying to get him on 8.1 before Apple stops signing it, but I don't want to brick his phone or do anything irreversible.

His device seems not to be connecting to iTunes - it connects to his laptop, and shows up in Windows Explorer (Windows 8.1), but not in iTunes. iTunes diagnostics shows everything is fine but no iPhone detected. Not sure if that's relevant.

BREAKING edit:

We're bringing you this story LIVE from the scene folks!

He says even DFU mode doesn't allow it to connect to iTunes. He also says it's something he downloaded on the device rather than connecting to windows. When he holds an icon to make them wiggle, the cydia icon doesn't wiggle or have an x, but the rest do. He also reconfirms that he didn't pay for it.

Edit2:someone suggested looking under profiles, and we found [this](http://imgur.com/nR1bMUd) but can't delete it. He also says that pangu isn't detecting the iPhone when plugged in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something everybody thinks only they are good at? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 14:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something everyone thinks they're better at than most other people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your most embarrassing memory from when you were younger of trying to seduce a member of the opposite sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 14:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What outrageous thing has your boss asked you to do "off the books"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 22:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What makes you simultaneously happy and sad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 22:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your most embarrassing memory from when you were younger of trying to seduce a member of the opposite sex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 19:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anon stands in a club </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 17:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Somebody has created a subreddit for every future iOS version up to iOS 52 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 00:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is why I don't buy nice things [r/standupshots] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 23:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [request] Background Manager replacement for ios 8 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 15:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since the Dev recently announced that he won't be updating BM for ios8, could someone have a go? I used it a lot in 7, and I'm disappointed that it's not compatible with 8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Selling bitcoin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 14:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I bought 35 worth of Bitcoin. It's now worth about 40, yay!

Ok so i signed up for localbitcoins.com and transferred my bc to that wallet, but selling them seems to be very complicated... I filled out various forms and got an advert made, but now it says 

 The advertisement is not currently running, because your LocalBitcoins.com wallet does not have enough bitcoins to automatically fund the escrow in the case a buyer responds to this advertisement. You need at least 0.40 BTC and advertisement minimum limit.

Any advice for a beginner? What's the easiest way to sell them without complications? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] While the Siri screen is active, Siri listens for my voice so I don't have to press the button each time I speak </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 01:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So while [this screen](http://cdn.iphonehacks.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/ios7-siri1.jpg) is active, the "hey Siri" functionality will be equal to as if it's plugged in, regardless of whether the power chord is connected. It's always a minor annoyance if I want to ask more than one thing, or make a correction, and I have to press the microphone button aga[i](https://i.imgflip.com/1bhf.jpg)n. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most creepy example of the "uncanny valley" you've ever seen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 20:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stripper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 14:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drives me ducking nuts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 16:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right. I'll get the flapjacks, you fetch my ninja costume. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 17:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After being on tinder for a couple of weeks.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 01:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would nobody do if it wasn't "cool"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 13:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wrestling Move </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 18:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Halloween Candy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 18:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Karate hand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 15:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your town's tenuous claim to fame? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 13:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who live in a small town: what's your towns tenuous claim to fame? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 21:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Town's*

Too late to change now, oops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What "alternative" sexual manoeuvre is the most hilariously weird? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 01:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What can a stranger do to make you instantly want to be their best friend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 14:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When did you spend a ton of time/money organising an event, only for it to be cancelled at the last second? What happened? [stories] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 18:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone swap the numpad and keyboard-switching buttons in landscape mode? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-01 15:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favourite harmless prank? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 16:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your perfect first date? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 18:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A community for 6 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 14:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how can the sub have been around for 6 years when the site has only been around for a few months? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit receives a postcard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 13:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What stereotype about your country is embarrassingly accurate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 15:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scumbag Elderly Driver </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 20:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most cringeworthy thing you've seen someone do "for attention"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 18:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HMF a sketch of a panel of judges reviewing a footballer's injury acting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 02:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i saw a video like this a long time ago but can't for the life of me find it. I suspect there'd be a few if I searched for the right thing. 

The premise is a comedy sketch where a panel of judges (Cowell etc, not actual Cowell obv) critically reviews a footballer rolling around on the floor pretending to be injured. If you find it I'll love you ~~forever~~ ~~for a long time~~ for a few seconds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An easy one - How do I disable the "smooth movement" of the cursor in Microsoft Office? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 18:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since Office 2013, when you move the cursor around or highlight text, it doesn't move instantaneously like before. Rather, it hops to where you've clicked over the course of about 0.1 seconds, and it's **really annoying**.

I had a look for a way to disable it, but I can't find anything. Suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sub to ask for recommendations for a product category </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 01:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if I'm looking to buy a certain product, I can ask there and see if anyone has any experience with certain brands or whatever and can just give advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The average female and male faces (source in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 12:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most evil thing you can do with a roll of toilet paper? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 11:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could re-build the world from scratch, what would you do differently? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 01:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically you get to be Slartibartfast for a while and build Earth 2.0. What do you change **that couldn't be changed otherwise**? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Continuity not working with iPhone 6 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 17:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an iPad 4 on 8.0 and an iPhone 6. My iPad could send texts through my 4S on the early betas, but now I can't send/receive texts/~~calls~~ through my 6 from my iPad. They're on the same wifi network, same Apple ID, same iClound account. I've rebooted, re-logged-in, reconnected to the wifi, nothing works. Any ideas?

Edit: I can make calls from my iPad by going into contacts, selecting the contact I want and tapping the phone icon. I cannot send/receive texts though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When people don't read the other comments before commenting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 23:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red has sympathy for Green </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 23:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tablecloth Trick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 17:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tumblr on Australia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 14:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Football </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 13:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Band Practise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 13:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What smartphone app do not enough people know about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 00:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone has a cool app on their phone which only they know about. What's yours? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wish my family would understand this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 14:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iPhone 6 hands-on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 23:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What has nobody ever said before? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 04:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the greatest anticlimax of all time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 15:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From real life, not from a book, movie, TV show etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dealbreaker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 15:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What turned out a lot better than you expected? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 22:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What currently small company will be a huge success in 25 years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 21:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 23:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bike stunt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 23:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Piece of cake. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 23:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Education Pricing in the Apple Store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 22:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm going to buy the iPhone 6 when it's released. I'm in university and therefore I qualify for education pricing, saving me probably 30-40 depending on how they price it. 

Does anyone have any experience with education pricing? Will I be able to pre-order it online and pick it up from the store on release day? I really want to go to the Apple Store on release day and queue outside before it opens - it'll be so exciting and I've never done anything like that before :D 

But I don't think going to the physical store and also getting the education discount are compatible. 

Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do people think you don't notice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 20:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you do while alone that you would never do in front of anybody else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 17:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bread Dominos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 23:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carefully... Carefully.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 22:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gymnastics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 22:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hold my milk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 20:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's mine now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 18:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you do while alone that you would never do in front of anybody else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 17:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^^inb4 ^^masturbating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Reduce minimum distance for geofencing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 17:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use location-based reminders quite a lot, such as "remind me to do X when I get home". But "when I get home" is defined as "when I get within 100m of home".

Due to the exact location of where I live and very long and boring reasons, I'd like to be able to reduce this distance to 50m or 25m or something. I know the gps isn't perfect so this will introduce some problems, but it'd be better for me.

Does this tweak exist? If not, would anybody be willing to give it a go? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something that nobody would do if it wasn't "cool"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 04:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The number of points and the number of votes on a post have to be either both odd or both even. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 17:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do people think you don't notice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 16:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After hearing about a kickstarter for a bike lock which unlocks when your phone is within bluetooth range.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 02:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What smartphone app do not enough people know about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 01:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone has that one cool app on their phone which only they know about. What's yours? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/darkruby45 Pretends to be gay to help a friend. They end up less than friends after it escalates out of control. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 00:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What smartphone app do not enough people know about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 01:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone has a cool app on their phone which only they know about. What's yours? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flexible muscle-based locomotion for bipedal creatures - Software Demonstration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 00:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm just a fetus hoping there's a light at the end of the tunnel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 19:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Half of my large intestine is so grammatically perfect.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 19:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a semicolon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All karma gained from this post will be donated to the Robin Williams Jackdaw fund (please like to show your support) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 16:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first cell of the embryo divides into two </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 14:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to do Visual Comedy in Filmmaking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-16 01:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
