<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2621</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 16:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was asked repeatedly if I was joking and then it was insisted on that it's just a phase. Then demanding that I don't bring guys around and that I don't post anything about it on Facebook. Oh and the family must never know...that was my mother and I'm in my twenties. My father when he found out was surprised then said fuck your mother lol

I'm jealous xD 

Congratulations on coming out, now get out there and enjoy some age appropriate cock  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 03:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'd say most of me being ok with it came from her support  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 00:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd just hint that you are leaving to masturbate then  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 00:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I think that's more about who she is than anything  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went through the same thing, it wasn't till I was with a girl that I told I'm bi did I start to accept it. I told her and she kept telling me how hot it was and she encouraged me to try and be with men. I never really realized how much more attracted to men I am than women till after this. I think I find more women attractive than men but when I find a guy attractive it's at a different level. 

Just take your time and discover yourself slowly, it'll all be alright. At the end of the day you are still you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next time you're texting him say you're really horny and have to go take care of that. He will probably be flirty back then tell him you two should do it together  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 16:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect for anal ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 03:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, it's great lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 03:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look great! Love that cock, get it hard for me some time ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 02:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd fuck you and my bf says he'd like to get fucked by you so you're not bad at all ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 02:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look cute, would love to see that cock you're hiding  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 02:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The winter one with two guys that suck eachother in the back of a truck. The black haired guy is beautiful and if anyone has more vids of him let me know  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When looking for porn in my early teen years I found myself looking for porn that had the best looking guys and almost completely ignoring the women. It wasn't until I was sixteen that I started watching the occasional full on gay porn, this didn't become regular for me till eighteen. I tried to come out when I was nineteen but no one believed me so I just kept it pushed away. I'm bi so I decided to just date women for a while. It wasn't until recently at twenty three that I formally came out as bi. I'm dating a guy now that is beyond wonderful so everything worked out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 07:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many, many times ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 04:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol my boyfriend wants me to thank you because your life keeps turning us on xD  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 22:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are your brothers bi too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also thanks for responding :) 
It turned my boyfriend and I on lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened when you or your brothers brought dates home? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be happy to share a bed with you so don't worry about a thing. Ps I think the scar is hot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, get rid of it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been curious, do brothers have the same sized dicks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to the closest LGBT community center, they are a thing and are in most mid sized cities  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 15:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I comment a bit from time to time but prefer to read  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 03:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey is something isn't illegal and doesn't keep you up at night then why not do it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Condoms and you're golden. Good luck out there. Im bi and will tell you that dating men is a lot easier than women, but you need more for-play before you can stick it in a guy. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd just scream the I have a dick between my legs bitch, sometimes two! 

Start every conversation that way and then you're golden.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely play a horror movie the first night, you two won't be able to do anything without holding onto each other  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came out a month ago (I'm bi) and I was annoyed that no one saw it coming...like I never really tried to hide it. I had just been in long relationships with women in the past and none of the guys were there long enough for me to tell people about. 
I came out because I matched with a guy on tinder then we started texting/calling/video chatting with each other.  I haven't met him in person yet, he live three hours away, I was busy with school and he is busy with his jobs but we should be meeting next week. 

Well that got off topic.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 20:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My go to when asked to talk is to get right up to their ear and whisper 'you don't deserve it' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was really hoping it'd be similar lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've known each other for a while but just started dating two weeks ago, and thanks for the congratulations =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for top advice then I guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was really hoping there was a general playbook lol
Mostly looking for tips for a top.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help! I'm dating a guy for the first time and would like any and all advice. Thanks reddit! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm bi and just started seeing a guy, we are both in our mid twenties. Im looking for any advice you can give me, neither of us are very feminine and we like working out...there are a ton of other similarities too. 

I wanted help with sex advice, I'm not a virgin but I've only been with women, so I'd like some help. 

Also what kind of pet names could I use for him? I really like this guy and wanted to get educated 

Thanks reddit =) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 14:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to do about the same thing with a friend. If you want to move things forward then start humping him when you wake up, if he freaks out then just say "sorry dude, just woke up"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 13:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came out as bi to my friends  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 13:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> South Bend Indiana is one of the most gay friendly small cities out there (our mayor is even gay). A nice apartment rents at 700-900 dollars and it's an hour ride by train to Chicago. You should check it out, it really is a lovely place with an active gay community.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 18:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say "hey if you swing my way, wanna swing together?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 00:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah they bought it. I'm bi too but I get excited by almost anything. I thought it would stop in my twenties but it keeps going strong lol
I bring the girls I date home and around my friends so they don't know but I did just come out to one of them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 14:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friend was using my phone and opened my browser. There was some gay porn on there that he immediately showed everyone else. I said "you never been jerking it and just started clicking 'like videos' until it sends you to some weird shit?"$ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 10:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was struggling with my sexuality but after I saw this the struggle is over. God damn you're fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 05:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently I'm a rare breed, I'm very vocal during sex, but how can you not moan when someone licks behind your ear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 04:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry bro. Most growth happens at 12. Though it won't be fully mature til 16. You might gain an inch yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 04:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kohls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 04:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks fake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 04:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/realitydicks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 04:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now turn around... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 04:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was 310lbs at 6'4'' and now I'm at 260 one year later. If you ate looking to lose weight then I suggest myfitnesspal, it is great. I started jump roping, 200 a night then 400, 700, and now I do 1000 the times a week and go to the gym three times. I'd a long road to lose weight, but think about it. You had your whole life to get you this far, what's a couple years to undo the damage.

When it comes to jumping rope the things you need to know is that it hurts, but it doesn't get worse when you do more. When you feel the pain you will need to accept that amount of pain to keep going. The next day your legs will hurt worse than ever before. Take one day off then keep at it.

You might stumble along the way but keep starting again. It's not over until you decide to stop trying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 04:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too am coming to accept that I'm bi, so nice cock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 04:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good on you for this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 04:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should try r/gaystoriesgonewild

P.s. looked at your history, nice foreskin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 04:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounded...real. explains my boner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 04:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an old English name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 03:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have that same blanket, isn't it great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 03:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try r/ratemycock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 03:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey this would do better in r/penis or if you want to try it r/normalnudes but that sub is for more full body shots </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 03:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was straight till I saw your posts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 20:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, now show us your cock already! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 19:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy is right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 07:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trimming with clippers works wonders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 23:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
