<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1772</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 08:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smart, then I'd realize happiness is a matter of perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 08:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally you can think in a specific language as per its grammar but when you try to think of the right word to express yourself, it's whatever word pops in your memory first that relates to how you feel which affects whether you need to translate it over or not. When you put two bilinguals in a room that know the same languages, the borrowed words thrown around can get a bit excessive, but ultimately they probably express themselves better than monolinguals as per the extended vocabulary and grammar allowing for a wider variety of expressions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 08:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go on an internet shopping spree, order supper and go to bed with a sore tummy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 08:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calculus: so much memorization, so little practical applications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 08:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A place that can keep me glued to the internet with the least amount of distractions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 08:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Down voter explain why you downvoted if none of the above. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 08:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you build up your socialize skills, you'll enjoy socializing more until you become a "people person". As the saying goes: People like people that like people.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 07:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hard times, too busy getting laid... off" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 07:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> offending people without trying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 07:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the same way my 10 year old laptop won't run windows 10, I'm afraid not. But with the right hardware upgrades it's possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 06:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My potential manifesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 06:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever questioned loving your crush? It's that feeling except they like you back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 06:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ronda Rousey as per her domestic violence incident </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had to eat the same things every week, what would your food pyramid look like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 06:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 06:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> putting the blanket between my legs and rolling around trying to find a good head position </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 06:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing this post before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 06:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what result has nature created after 14.7 billion years? Does a black hole storage engine already exist? Can you get a black hole to respond to you?  The result nature has given us is the human brain, and programmers use it to design the AI stuff that gets more and more sophisticated. If you can find alien AI out there, it had to be first conceived by a human-like brain. Yet AI is unable to replace the programmer. The human brain is the ultimate in sophistication as the bible says man was created in God's image. If you don't hold by the bible, how do you explain the infinite past behind us that already elapsed in order to reach the present if the universe were eternal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Being constantly offended doesn't mean you're right, it just means you're too narcissistic to tolerate opinions different than yours." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The usual pleasures </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go on a shopping spree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Claiming I've been to a certain part of town and when asked for certain key details I replied "my memory sucks" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> someone overhearing my mantra which happens to be the name of a girl I like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anticlimactic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> people like people that like people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have you ever experimented </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What ever the academy decides are the parts of the year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I had to pay for my first root canal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A man discovers time travel and travels back in time only to find out his consciousness alone gets sent back which discards the memories of the future causing him to make all the same choices again and entering an infinite loop of never being able to break free of traveling back in time. Until the story fast forwards to the day after he went back in time, but this time to the wife's perspective of the world where her husband never went back in time keeping us wondering how he managed to break the loop. Ultimately the story ends that the man was delusional and he never really discovered time travel and he's lucky to have such a loving wife.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having failed to sneeze with the hiccups when you're holding in a cough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> kicking someone in the groin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the last airbender </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give it back because if I lost my wallet I'd want it back. What goes around comes around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was a year over drinking age </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not giving you the benefit of the doubt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The former as the latter is already the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like the simpsons when the clones do the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very wise advise. I've learned the same from my ex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Productive things I have to do in any case so I have time to think about the harder things. If a college assignment is due in 10 hours and it's stressing me out, I go do my laundry. When that's going I work on some food. When I'm feeling higher in energy, then I go back to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The two most powerful warriors are patience and time." - Leo Tolstoy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Milk actually isn't good for your bones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The opening of Evanescence - Imaginary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AC power </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I got a riddle for you... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keeping your room organized is a sure way to path the way to the top. When your life is organized, success comes as easy as eating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Occasionally, if I was on a tight schedule. My family was quite poor and my dad would complain about excessive utility usage until I stopped showering regularly. I had no money so I didn't feel like dating as I'd be hanging around people just as impoverished. Only after moving out I started showering daily again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Massive success is the best revenge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let it go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going a week without showering </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is a better choice? to the left where nothing is right.. or to the right where nothing is left.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the plant that eats dirty socks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a lot of head </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good quality video recorder to get a piano improvisation channel started on youtube </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 02:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> iiiiiiick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 02:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5 minutes as usual </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 02:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How to cure all disease. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 02:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Living with your parents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 02:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walk people's dogs for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 02:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But such an idea was conceived in the human brain before being put into action. I doubt a black-hole powered storage engine would be able to surpass the human brain in sophistication. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 02:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Video games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 02:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell Aristotle time travel exists! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 02:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In quite a circular manner: when you self-identify as one. The act alone doesn't steer you away from bi territory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 01:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simpsons predicting Trump running for president </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 01:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I admit to the areas which I'm not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 01:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The human brain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 01:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doing something heroic like diving, taking a bullet for a group of people provided they're not lawyers, politicians, or radiation oncologists. (My mom died to cancer.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 01:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When your memory gets so bad you can't remember your own age and have to re-calcuate it from your birthdate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 01:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one, it gets loads of traffic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 01:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mutual assured destruction, as it dooms humanity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 00:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's one step closer to perverts sneaking peaks. If that doesn't bother you, why even close the bathroom door? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 00:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, family love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 00:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zeromus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 00:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to die laughing: This is just the beginning, of a new end, the end to end all ends, a dead end. Hahahaaaaa... * cough, cough, dies*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 23:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excuse the language on this one but it's my all-time favorite:
"Gay men are fucking assholes." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 23:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you score intelligence? By asking nicely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 23:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His role in the weather man getting hit by a [frosty](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-5Rohhkg-7k) for his bad forecasts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 23:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> grim   evil, but since it only had two seasons: the simpsons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 23:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> star wars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 23:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Demotivational </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 23:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> King Arthur and the Knights of Justice. It was cancelled after two seasons before completing the storyline, leaving a hole in my childhood I have yet to quench. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 23:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Continue life and they'll show up when you decide to organize your life starting with your room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 22:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Since we're all nothing, then none of our actions exist either." This type of logic isn't helpful to the survival of humanity; it is better for us to assume our actions matter. Assume the universe wasn't created (nothing created the universe): explain how there's an infinite past behind us (the universe always existed) which needed to elapsed to reach the present. If you're familiar with infinite sets, call the elapsed time "x". What is one second before "x" if the infinite past behind us is already written? That would require another set bigger than our original infinite set, which steps into The Creator's timeline or something else relative to the top of the chain. If some sublime being found reason to bestow life upon us, perhaps we're not that insignificant after all. Or if you're saying an all-power being created us from nothingness, I have no problem with this logic as omnipotence has no limits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The constriction of God's infinite "light" as explained in Kabbalah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grammar fail. Can you rephrase? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too late, I already told my girlfriend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stem cell injections to grow new teeth in 2-3 months for people with missing teeth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put an end to drug wars, it's a complete waste of tax payer money, and use the money instead for stem cell research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 19:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting unproductive people with no ambitions of their own off their butt doing something ambitious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 11:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the captain can convince the pirates he deserves a 60% stake for being their captain, then the voting with the distribution is only arguing about what the others are expecting. If they think there will be 40 coins left among them, thus each of the 5 would get 8 coins, then the captain can give two of them their share to get two supporting votes (since the captain's vote counts, he'd have a 3-3 tie which passes) and give the remaining three nothing. Thus the captain would walk away with 84 coins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 01:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Words don't count against budget. Good job reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bread, bagels, rice are all good examples of convenient food.
Stews are pretty cheap to make. Black beans, kidney beans, lima beans, lentils these are all relatively cheap to buy. Nothing gets my mouth to water like a baked potato and yam or sweet potato. They're relatively inexpensive and immensely easy to make. The amount of hands-on work is pretty much non-existent. It's more or less just toss it in the oven, then turn on the oven, no need to even preheat it. Then go watch a tv show and check on it to see how much longer to leave it. Or heck, work on some other food. If you're into salads, I tend to grab a bag of romaine lettuce hearts. I usually break off each piece of lettuce one-by-one washing it under the faucet, then I ring the lettuce to get rid of excess water. If you have a salad dryer that works too, but I don't mind wet lettuce. Finally I toss the lettuce into a bowl and add my dressing. I use apple cider vinegar, extra virgin olive oil, white pepper and if I can find any in the fridge a bit of lemon juice. Toss the salad around so you don't get all pepper and you've got yourself a quick snack in ~3 minutes. I don't measure any of the ingredients, I just eye it. I know to put more oil than vinegar, and roughly how much oil to put on my salad based on the amount of salad present. You can also go all-out on the salad too if you've got the time. If I want to add carrots to the salad, I grate them on a cheese grater to get them to a nice shape. Cucumbers, tomatoes, onions, and an avocado are all nice additions. I'm personally a fan of grating broccoli into my salads if I can find any in the fridge. I'm not a fan of feta cheese, but I know they do well in salads. You can also add things specific to your palate as well such as cranberries or almonds (neither which I like in salads but I know others do). When you get sick of salads, I'm a big fan of tacos. All you need is some cheese and some tortillas and you can make yourself some quesadillas in the toaster oven. Or you can go all-out and grate some cheese, and cook some black beans, then either add the black beans to the tortillas watery or you can toss them in the blender for a few seconds to turn the cooked black beans into a paste. Then you can add some sliced tomatoes, and sliced olives, maybe some lettuce, your favor salsa or hot sauce (which you can make separately too by boiling some tomatoes, jalapenos, onions, and some seasoning in a pot with water, then blending it in the blender afterwards), and when I go seriously all-out I cook some rice with the tacos so I can add some rice to the tacos. It's all worth it, it's my favorite time of the week as it's the one time I feel literally stuffed and satisfied from "real" food unlike the stomach ache you get when ordering a pizza and eating most of the pie. Homemade pizza can be fun to make too, but the cost of the cheese I've found unbudget friendly. But if you were planning on ordering a pizza, it can be loads cheaper to make it yourself. 3 cups of white floor, a packet of yeast, a cup of warm water, a tablespoon of olive oil, a teaspoon of salt, stir it together and toss it into the bread mixer. Make sure you use the heavy duty spiral-looking head and not a weak cookie mixer head. Once mixed, put it onto a rolling pin pad, and roll it into a rectangular shape that can fit the cookie sheet. When the shape is about right, spray the pan with canola oil and lay the dough onto it. Stretch the dough on the sheet to fit it better, when it comes in contact with the oil it makes the dough easier to stretch. Stretch it diagonally until it fits the sheet evenly with some room to form the crust. Then proceed to shape the crust with your fingers. Once formed, pull out some pizza sauce, marinara sauce, pasta sauce or anything of the like. Straight tomato sauce or tomato paste are poor choices. If you want to make your own, a good sauce uses a combination of many such ingredients best prepared in a pot and cooked first. Once you got the sauce on the dough, grab a spoon to help distribute it evenly. Finally, grab your cheese and distribute it evenly on top of the sauce. You can grate your own cheese to save some money. Toss in into the oven at 400 either the middle or top rack. Do not put it on the bottom as it's too close to the heat source and will cook your crust faster than the cheese. Once the cheese gets golden brown, pull out the pizza with a glove and put it on the stove. Let the pizza sit for 5 minutes before attempting to cut it lest the sauce and cheese go everywhere. Finally cut with either a scissors or a pizza cutter. A pizza cutter can scratch up your cookie sheet, if you had a cardboard box delivery style you'd cut it there, or you can cut it on some other surface you don't mind ruining. In my experience a scissors cuts homemade pizza better. And finally enjoy. Some other low budget things you buy are pita, they are extremely cheap. You can then proceed to pour some sauce onto the pizza and top it off with some cheese, toss it into the toaster oven for a few minutes and presto instant personal pizza without hardly any work. You can also buy pre-made crusts in many supermarkets to work on your own pizza. But pizza can get expensive on a low budget. But if you needed pizza, you can do it cheaper rather than over spend. One of the cheapest ways to eat is to just find whatever is laying around the house and find a way to use it before it goes bad and has to be discarded. Perishables in the fridge are a great example of this. Eggs are a great example of something inexpensive yet healthy and full of protein (6g per large egg). As a big fan of broccoli, you may be surprised to find out it contains 2.6g of protein per cup of chopped broccoli. Nowhere in the ballpark of eggs (about 9-10 times less), but it adds up. I like to boil my broccoli usually in a stir-fry like pan and if I have the energy to go all-out, I'll add in some stir-fry components. I don't like putting loads of oil in my stir fries. Usually I just cook them in water for the most-part then top it off with liquid aminos about half-way in and a bit of olive oil near the end. In terms of stir fry ideas, you can toss some potatoes in the food processor, carrots, onions, bell pepper, celery, tomato, mushroom, and the initially mentioned broccoli. Then after it's ground into slices (don't shred it) toss it into the stir fry pan. Last, but not least, if you're on a really tight food budget, why spend a penny? You can eat over at a friend's and make it their problem. Go on a date and make them pay. Show up at a party and eat for free. Visit some family. You don't have it do it every night, if you did it every once in a while it adds up if it saves you a trip to the store, you do the math. Another idea worth considering is growing your own food. If you have a neighbor that grows their own food, you can do some organic food swapping. There's food for your belly without spending a cent. Snacks have a history of putting a hole in my pocket. I've found it's great to prepare trail mixes and other such snacks with ingredients like rice chex, walnuts, cranberries, and if you got a sweat tooth: m ms. You can make this stuff yourself and just toss it into a ziplock bag. If you reuse the same one often, you save money. You can also use tupperware to store it in. Finally, you'll find it's great to make a smoothie here and there. Totally worth the effort. If you have a grapefruit, orange or lemon tree, it will save you some money so you can make them more often on a low budget. If you have a neighbor with such a tree, you can probably get such product either free or very cheap from them. In my experience you can get it free if you keep in good terms with them. I hope you've found my input insightful. Happy budgeting and a good day to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 08:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's ok to be a "bad" developer if you know how to make ends meet. When stuck consult stackoverflow or google. What's more important, though, is building a portfolio. When you have something to show for so people know what you do, then they're able to properly utilize you. Either a personal site, github projects, or both are great ways to get started. Finding work can be tricky. I'd suggest make a business card and hand it out to people you meet. Anyone can find someone remote to work for them, but if you're able to meet in person, you'll have that much more success as a developer. If you want to be a remote developer, it's still possible, upwork.com is a good place to land some easy beginning projects. Landing your first job there can be tricky, take a bunch of the tests there to show your skills, and offer your rates rather low, and you'll have a shot at that first project. That first project can take a while as other people can also bid on projects. But once you land that first project, you'll be more hireable on there. Some of my best early jobs as a web developer I landed through message boards. When you give people a free taste of your skills on a message board and they need an extra hand, they can come crawling back to you offering cash. That's how I started personally. Linkedin is another way to land a job. Craigslist has some really good stuff if you're willing to go meet the person.  Once you get hired, you'll learn all the skills you need along the way to preform better on the next job. Start low, and build up your profolio. When you have a decent-looking resume and porfolio, you can land some of the higher-end jobs down the line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 21:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correspondence has really improved my chess as it helped me understand the main ideas in various lines. I'd stay away from speed chess until you understand chess better. One of the things I enjoy a lot is chess.com's tactics trainer. It's helped improve my tactics in chess greatly. But chess isn't all about tactics. I used to think it was 90% tactics or so, but not every position has tactical potential. My newer understanding is it's about half tactics and half positional play. But no matter how strong your chess game is, if you blunder on any move, you pretty much blunder away the game if your opponent doesn't blunder back. (Generally it's a good idea to push pawns when down in material for a shot at a queen.) But yeah, you can get your rating pretty high by simply not blundering. If your opponent threatens mate in 3, make sure you see the threat coming. If they move their queen threatening mate and a piece at the same time, they've just won a piece. Keep your eyes open for such moves. If your tactics are weak, you can improve your game by limiting your opponent's tactical potential. If your king is on the same file as your opponent's queen or rook, you should be worried about tactics. If your king is on the same diagonal as your opponent's bishop or queen, you should be worried about tactics. If your opponent's knight is anywhere near your king, you should be worried about tactics. Knights are by far the trickiest piece in the game. They are essentially a short range piece, and if you miss a combination, they can jump all over the board making various threats until 3 moves later you find them forking your king and rook. Another thing to look out for is pawn storms. If you're about to castle on the king's side and your opponent has already advanced some pawns close to where your king is going to castle, you should reconsider castling in that direction. Once a pawn gets too close to your king, it will wind up either ruining your king's pawn structure, or trading off the pawns that protect your king from checks. Once it's possible to check your king, you need to be on the constant look out for forks and mate threats. In the event that the pawn structure near your king gets broken, make sure to trade queens. Once queens are traded, the king can sit relatively close to the middle of the board without many problems. There are also other areas of chess worth noting. Generally you want to develop all your pieces toward the center of the board. When it comes to the bishops, you want to make sure they always have a diagonal. Never trap a bishop in by your pawn structure, especially on the side you want to castle. Keeping your king in the center is probably one of the worst mistakes you can make in your opening. If you keep your king in the center, all your opponent has to do is trade a bunch of pawns in the center to open up your king. If you can't get your bishop out, your king won't be able to castle and be in the line of fire. There are two ways to develop a bishop as there are two pawns which block it in. Once either pawn is pushed, the center pawn or the knight pawn, then you develop your bishop either toward the center, perhaps pinning a knight, or you can fianchetto the bishop taking on the longest diagonal on the board. Every player has their weaknesses, and it's important you identify what they are. Some players lose in the opening, some lose in the middle game, and others lose in the endgame. Try to keep record of where you lose the most. Generally the opening is best to learn first as if you blunder in the opening you've lost the game before even being given a chance to play the middle or endgame. Picking an opening can by tricky, but it's important you understand the main ideas in whichever opening you choose. Even if you pick a very weak opening, as long as you understand the main ideas behind it, it's playable. I personally play a solid game from a large array of openings. I generally try to play openings I think my opponent won't know to take them away from their strong-suit. But being able to play off any opening requires lots of practice. I tend to favor hypermodern openings. Many players fail to understand them, if space gets too cramped trade some pieces so you have room to move your pieces around.  The nice thing about hypermodern openings is they can transpose into pretty much any kind of opening such as the queen's gambit or Ruy Lopez. If you don't know either of those, start there. The sicilian defence is a common response to e4, if you don't want to have to learn it, keep away from e4. A common beginner mistake I see is trading off material too early. There's a saying "to take is a mistake", obviously this doesn't apply to taking back, but the concept is that if you take your opponent's knight with your bishop and they take back with their other knight, the idea is that they just developed another piece while taking back. It can be hard to understand as it's your move again and you can just develop another piece, but ultimately a move consists of two plies (your move and their move) and when you had a developed bishop and they had a developed knight, after the two ply move is over, you've ultimately traded your developed bishop for their undeveloped knight. Once you develop another piece, it's like you lost a tempo with your move. Sure, trading is fine if it achieves a goal worth the tempo loss in development, but if you successively trade both your bishops for both their knights, you're just developing their pieces, not to mention throwing away the bishop pair. Throwing away the bishop pair is fine if you're playing in a closed position and knights are preferred, but ultimately chess is a game of harmony of colors. Losing a bishop means you become that much weaker on that color. So unless your pawn structure accounts for the bishop loss, or you can adjust it shortly after the bishop loss, losing your general of that color only weakens your other bishop. If your bishop is stuck on dark squares, your opponent can put all their pieces on light squares to make it completely useless. If you've got a light bishop and a rook pawn which promotes on a dark square, you can't check the king out of the corner if he manages to get to the corner to be able to promote the pawn to a queen. Even the bishop pair is weak in closed positions. One of the greatest advances of the bishop pair is trading it off in the right position for a nice tactical combination afterwards. But yeah, chess is maybe 50% tactics, work on those so you become a better player. Know when NOT to sacrifice a piece. It can get frustrating when your opponent is able to guard against all your attacks. Attack with all your pieces, then re-position them to attack somewhere else. The theory of two weaknesses plays a large role in winning chess. Much like tennis and hitting the ball way all the way to the left, then once they hit the ball back, you hit it all the way to the right, to make them run all the way to the other side of the court. Even if they run back and fourth on time, it tires them out. Of course you don't want to be too predictable, so it's nice to throw in some variations. If their stance is expecting to run either left or right, you can hit it straight down the center. Sure, they can play a perfect game, but even Magnus Carlsen blunders away games. We're all human, we blunder. Just limiting those blunders is key to a stronger game. Even if neither player blunders, you can still lose a game. Piece activity is important. If you don't have any counterplay, you better come up with a way to get some threats going or you lost the game before you even go down in material. If your opponent has a knight near your king which you can't attack, he will be the key to your downfall as far as positional chess goes.  In such positions your best chance is usually a drawing weapon such as a fortress. But I think fortresses are one of the last things to focus on mastering. As you play more and more chess, you'll improve over time. Just be careful about burn out. Sometimes you'll lose many games back-to-back and feel like a loser before the first move is played. This is known as burn out, it happens to us all. Just give chess a break for a while, maybe a day or two, then return later when you're full of energy again. Happy times, I hope you gained something out of reading this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 19:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer the former, empty parenthesis combined with "new" just looks ugly to me. If you want to get specific, you could use parenthesis to send in a parameter like "red" or "22oz" etc. But if you have nothing specific to add, it's just a waste of indicating you want to get specific. "I'd like to order a new mug." "Anything specific?" "Yes." "Like what?" "Nothing comes to mind." 
  
C++ seems to agree with me:
http://stackoverflow.com/questions/180172/default-constructor-with-empty-brackets   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 11:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would step its foot into kabbalistic territory.  
The Tanya states that every Jew is composed of two distinct souls:  
a Nefesh HaBehamit ([animal soul](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Animal_soul)) and a Nefesh HaElokit ([divine soul](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Divine_soul)).

This article does a *wonderful* job of explaining them:
http://www.chabad.org/library/article_cdo/aid/361900/jewish/Kelipot-and-Sitra-Achra.htm

Short answer: Yes, in terms of anatomy of the soul.

Long answer: If every Jew has a Nefesh HaElokit which non-jews don't have, then if we find any person possessing a Nefesh HaElokit, then he or she would be, by definition, actually a Jew. Now if a person can be Jewish simply by being born of a Jewish mother, and every Jew has a Nefesh HaElokit, (i.e. once a Jew always a Jew), then we can enter into the territory of wondering whether a specific non-jew's mother's mother's mother's mother was a Jew. Thus such a person would be a considered a non-jew as far as culture goes (until proven to a beis din) while possessing a Jewish soul.

It is said that when Moshiach comes that he'll be able to identify all the Jews, and their tribes, etc. Many spiritual people out there can sense holiness and thus one's Jewishness. Sadly, trying to prove this sort of stuff to a beis din is seemingly futile. What are you gonna do? Find someone you *think* was your maternal great-great-grandmother and check if their grave has a star of David on it? Meh. If you can prove it to yourself, that's all that matters for you to maintain Jewish identity. If you want to be more than "culturally Jewish", I'd suggest the path of conversion if you'd like to be recognized as a full-fledged Jew.

But in the meantime, regarding what to do with those feelings, no matter who you currently are, awaken and embrace yourself. This sort of stuff takes time, take it slow, *really* slow. There's no need to prove anything to anyone. But as you feel Judaism pulling you in, you can take it one step at a time as Rabbi Akiva took his Torah learning one drop at a time.

I hope I satisfied your curiosity. May you be successful with your endeavors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 10:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second Wamp for Windows 10. Just make sure to run WAMPSERVER before Skype if you also have Skype on your computer. Starting Skype first would use the port Wamp tries to use. Once setup, visit http://localhost/phpmyadmin so you can setup a database, tables etc. (Note Wamp uses "root" with no password) I also second Notepad++. I used to be a fan of Windows built-in Notepad but it has issues with certain newline characters, the main reason I stopped using it as an editor. But I managed for years copying to Wordpad and back again. Sublime Text is probably a better text editor than Notepad++ if you want something a little bit more sophisticated. Notepad++ is more straightforward though with an easier learning curve. Once you get comfortable with Notepad++ probably worth giving Sublime Text a shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 09:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That and putting `case` in backticks did the trick for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 10:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're trying to understand where creation and divinity meet, you can skim the surface of Merkavah. It's a pretty good map of where everything is in creation to apply your kabbalistic knowledge, but if you're not a savvy kabbalistic, I'd advise to keep away from it as it can lead to hypocrisy without a strong background in theology and a basic understanding of the Kabbalistic fundamentals.

I'd suggest "Lessons In Tanya" to REALLY brush up your knowledge of the Shechinah, and where you draw the line between God in His essence, and what God is, and what God isn't, and how man fits into this, the worlds, the soul, etc. It's a very comprehensive book jam-backed with quality. If you turn the page too quickly, you'll feel like you missed something. Another good book is Meditation and Kabbalah by Aryeh Kaplan. It covers a number of branches of Kabbalah so you have a better idea of what direction you should continue your studies.

Sefer Yetzirah is a classic, and you might learn a thing or two from it, but I don't think it's down-to-earth enough to really learn much from it other than the divinity of the letters. There are ways to use them, but I don't think it's a good source to learn major kabbalistic concepts from in a direct manner.

The Zohar, in general, talks about various things, and ties them into the weekly Torah portion. Sadly not all of the Zohar pages were preserved, and generally one should work their way up to the Zohar. It tends to be quoted a lot though in other books, but most people, even the savviest kabbalists out there, admit to understanding less than a small percent of anything in there. It can be a good book to skim if you know what you're looking for, but otherwise be ready to feel lost when reading it. As you become savvier and savvier, the Zohar should start making more and more sense to catch the main ideas it was intending.

I do have plans of publishing my own book in a few (read 8) years, but I could shed light on a few things for you in the meantime. The sefirot (lit. enumerations) are branches where the root lies in Ohr Ein Sof. If we're gonna think about Ohr Ein Sof in terms of Ohr (light), we can understand the seferiot in terms of a prism. The light which shines into the prism is the source, the colors that come out are different from each other as Chesed is different from Gevurah. But ultimately the sefirot are just branches that get their sustenance from their root, i.e. the light. The sefirot do nothing but filter the light thereby achieving tzimtzum (if I had to summarize kabbalah in one word this would be it). To where did God constrict Himself? To the divine letters (I saw this attributed to the Baal Shem Tov). Which would shed some light on "God and His name are one". This is a good read: http://www.chabad.org/library/article_cdo/aid/367866/jewish/Did-G-d-Create-Evil.htm
To the best of my understanding, the relationship between man and God is similar to man and his own thoughts. Which should shed some light on Ein (nothingness) and our unity with Him and how Ohr Ein Sof fits into this. But God is not man, and His thoughts are not like our thoughts. Nothing can be said of His essence, but we can reach in a manner of not reaching without ever actually understanding God's essence, as we can strive to understand ourselves, and we are a branch of a branch etc which has its root in the divine.

I hope that answers your curiosity.
If any of the above doesn't sit well, I'd be happy to clarify whatever aspect you're interested in, in more depth.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 09:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, my life started to take a turn when I graduated high school. "Yay, I graduated! Now what?" My family urged me to visit Israel, when I got there my brothers picked me up from the airport and dropped me off at their Yeshiva's dorm. I learned there for two years until I felt like I was rotting there with neither my Torah thirst being quenched any longer nor my physical needs. The Yeshiva covered Talmud and Chumash, but I wasn't getting any Nach, the Yeshiva wasn't teaching that to me. So I moved back to America and started getting into some of the juicer parts of Nach such as Kings and Isaiah. It didn't take long until I became interested in King Solomon's proverbs. I picked up every commentary on it I could find and remained dedicated to learning anything on King Solomon I could find for a few years.

I finally felt like my Torah thirst was being quenched again with King Solomon, but then I ran out of King Solomon-related material, and I needed to find a new way to queach my thirst. So I visited my local Jewish book store and skimmed through their books. I picked up various books some of which were from Aryeh Kaplan and some from Rav Nachman. It didn't take long until I became interested in Tanya and thus Chabad. From there I started getting curious of Kabbalah and how it differed from Chassidus. As I tried to make sense of it, everything started to fit together and not only wasn't it the superstition that was portrayed to me, but rather I felt like I found my place in Torah. A place where everything made sense and there was enough material to keep me busy for a life time. I have since then found my place in Torah. I plan on becoming an author on Jewish Mysticism eventually, but I don't want to publish anything on it until I can write something comprehensive covering all angles you could ever wonder on each topic as I introduce them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two jokes walk into a bar... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 00:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's the punchline? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 00:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Myself : p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 00:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (continued from previous post) Now, there is also the concept of the unity above (G-d and the Shechinah) and the unity below (the Shechinah and creation). The Shechinah comes and goes like it did when the Beis HaMikdash stood. As is well-known in Kabbalah, He fills all worlds and surrounds all worlds. The light, Or Ein Sof, which surrounds and the light which fills are thus linked to the Shechinah.

So to answer your question, we, creation, even the smallest bug, or the most mundane rock, contain a vitalizing "soul" which gives us existence and thus has its unity with G-d in some constricted manner. Although humans have access to a Nefesh, Ruach, Neshama, Chaya and Yechida, we might as well be the most insignificant rock in comparison to G-d's eyes which also has its unity with G-d. Does a rock, which doesn't even move on its own, have a conscious identity? In comparison to G-d, the void created by the constriction is as such. So where does our consciousness come from? We have free will, yet where does it come from? Again, it's just different levels of radiance of G-d's light through which we "borrow" and consider our own due to the light being dim enough for the void to exist. Yet even the void has its unity with G-d, the so-called Rav Nachman paradox, and thus the void must just be a very dim or constricted part of G-d's light. How do you resolve destiny vs freewill? Pretty simply, G-d runs the world, and the freewill which is ours is really only a constricted part of G-d's light running the world just in a constricted manner through us, hence the destiny G-d had in mind is being carried out despite "our" freewill due to how the concept of how pluralism and identity gets lost in G-d's simple unity, who doesn't change, and contains no parts. Thus can you blame Adam's sin on G-d? Well... yes, and no. For having foreknowledge that Adam would sin and creating the world in such a way that allowed the sin to happen, you can blame G-d. But, the sin itself can be blamed on the imperfection or incompleteness of creation which allowed such a sin to happen in the first place. So how can G-d judge Adam if his freewill was destined to sin? Rather, G-d created the conditions for Adam to have access to G-d 's light in a constricted manner for him not to sin, but he sinned. The reason G-d created the world wasn't so Adam would sin, rather it was because He saw the physical world was destined for good with the coming of Moshiach and ultimately reaches its perfect state through the sin, thus the original sin was actually needed as part of the creation process. Even still, how can you blame Adam for the sin if he was destined to sin by G-d's creating the world as it is? Was Adam not created directly by G-d's hand? How can G-d's creation be imperfect, what does that say about the creator? Rather, G-d runs the world, He does whatever He wants and there's no sense of pluralism to argue and He doesn't change. Rather, a satisfying answer to this question can only be found through meditation. The two answers are actually the same answer, if you understand how G-d's unity works. If Adam doesn't exist as an entity separate from G-d, then the sin is without existence either on G-d's level, and since G-d is perfect and doesn't change, you see the sin is actually part of the creative process in which G-d intended for the world to reach and Adam sinning or not was all predestined much in the same way Messiah was predestined to be righteous even though he hasn't come yet. How do we have freewill? Whoever connects with this soul, through his merits, merits to "wear" the soul provided the right conditions are met much like how prophecy is obtained. Between various humans they don't know who among them would merit to "wear" this soul, until their merits are such that they recognize the soul that they are "wearing". There's a concept of the Moshiach of the generation that in each generation there is someone which can "access" this soul, and if his generation merits it, he would turn into the long-waited Moshaich. So you see, freewill is actually G-d's will in a constricted manner, although just without awareness of His presence so the illusion of pluralism continues. We are like a film played in a dark room, and when the lights go on, there's no more film. But as long as His presence can't be detected, it's all fun and games since watching a movie is more fun than sitting in room full of light. And just as this concept applies to created beings, so it applies in G-d's mysterious unity, and here we are in creation, watching a film and associating ourselves with the main character in the film, YOU.

So.... as far as when the bible speaks of YHVH, this is a reference to the Shechinah, the revealed or female aspect of G-d, while the male aspect who we speak of in terms of He is too sublime for anything to be said of Him. When the prophets had their visions it all involved the Shechinah, the revealed aspects of G-d, while G-d in His essence is too sublime for man or any creation to comprehend without being lost in the unity through self-nullification for the part to "understand" the whole. As far as all this goes, if everything is constricted from G-d, aren't idols also constricted from G-d? The answer to this is even the sin of the golden calf was aimed at one of the 4 Chayot of the Merkavah as seen in the Ezekiel vision. And they figured if Moses died on the mountain, they would pray to one of the Chayot to reach G-d, which apparently falls under the category of idol-worship. Thus, although the physical golden calf is made up of material which was created through the constriction which constricted from G-d, the whole point of the commandment is that we shouldn't recognize an identity as our whole, G-d, when it isn't really whole. Thus the concealed aspect of G-d nothing can be said about and is above names, and the G-d of the bible, YHVH, is the revealed aspect of G-d, who is the whole which we pray to. This is the Shechinah, which in the Beis HaMikdash we faced the holy-of-holies where the Shechinah dwelt, and even when the temple still stood, it was only the Kohen Gadol, on yom kippur when inside the holy-of-holies, that it was permitted for YHVH to be pronounced in its proper form, where the Shechinah dwelt, as the Rambam explains, when the temple stood everyone used a combination of maybe 3 or 4 words which related to G-d's revealed essence such as "Was, Is, Will be" as based on the letters of YHVH, and thus the tetragrammaton would translate over to something like "The Eternal", which everyone would substitute much like how we still use a substitution which I will translate as "my Master".

Thus you see YHVH refers to the Shechinah, the light, Or Ein Sof, as G-d told Moses, "no man can see my face and live." Surely if these words came from the concealed aspect of G-d, He would have no "face" which could relate to His essence in the first place to see. Rather the Shechinah, the revealed aspect of G-d has a face, metaphorically speaking, and it is this revealed aspect of G-d which G-d is telling Moses no man can be filled with Or Ein Sof and live without getting sucked into it since creation is constricted from Or Ein Sof, and "seeing His face" thus requires one's physical identity to be lost in the process and is something only those in Gan Eden can experience and partake of the light reserved for the righteous in Gan Eden, while those which don't merit, simply aren't perfect enough to rejoin Or Ein Sof without complete nullification. And through this you can understand the unity of the Shechinah with the righteous, as the zohar mention, while the wicked remain in an incomplete state which can't rejoin the Shechinah until it is rectified, such as through reincarnation, which even after Moshiach comes babies will continue to be born, and to the best of MY understanding, this is all my interpretation of what G-d has planned for the wicked, that they will be able to reincarnate into the messianic era to rectify their souls, since they were constricted from G-d and thus must have some manner through which they can return to the Shechinah to purity themselves just as the Red Heifer purifies those with the impurity of death on them, which prevents the levels of prophecy which existed while the temple stood. This gets into the mysticism of purity and impurity and I have yet to master this topic, it would take someone as great as Moses who understood how the Red Heifer worked, while the reputed wisest man King Solomon claimed he didn't understand why the Kohen becomes impure from the process until evening, and the whole concept of the anatomy of the Shechinah and its relationship to purity and impurity, etc. 

I hope that answers your curiosity.  
Shabbat Shalom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 23:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference is easy for the savvy kabbalist to understand, but the explanation is rather lengthy for one lacking familiarity with one or more of the fundamental kabbalistic concepts. If you've missed out on a single major kabbalistic concept, as I will explain below, the whole thing will remain a paradox. I will do my best bringing it all to your attention and you can figure out for yourself which concept you missed and know what to research. If something I say seems contradictory to your understanding, research it, most of this stuff is basic kabbalistic knowledge but I may say a few things which aren't available in books but I feel is the intended meaning of the material after becoming savvy with it. Firstly know that the kabbalistic tradition (from the verb in Hebrew meaning to receive) is actually that what remains of the prophetic tradition. This is the meaning of Moses placing his hand on Yehoshua ben Nun in order for him to attain the leadership to succeed him. Thus he taught him the keys for acquiring prophecy. At this point in time the Jews already had a great understanding of the Torah. But Moses keep some parts of the oral Torah secret and safely guarded, not to fall into the hands of the unworthy due to its immense power, and these keys make up the kabbalah. This explains how the prophets gained prophecy during the time the Beis HaMikdash still stood. After its destruction, prophecy was lost and the kabbalistic tradition was being forgotten. To the best of my understanding, Rabbi Akiva was the last, or one of the last people, in possession of the kabbalistic tradition while it was still oral, hence the story of the 4 which entered paradise. Around that time the oral Torah had to be written down, hence the Talmud, but Kabbalah wasn't meant for the masses, only specific individuals at the proper time, thus the Kabbalah had to be "coded" when it was written down in such a way that the masses could read the book and not understand it but those which were worthy could. And as more time went on, even those worthy didn't contain enough of the oral tradition to make sense of it, so more of the oral tradition had to be written down. There were a few big shots in the middle: Rashbi, the Ari, the Rambam, the Baal Shem Tov, Rav Nachman, etc, to name a few. And ultimately that brings us to our current time with several kabbalistic books available to the public.

With all the above history in mind of that which kabbalah strives to be, I present to you my version or interpretation of the kabbalistic tradition as I currently understand it, based on my current depth of study.

Firstly, understand G-d in His essence is completely unknowable and without name. On this level, His level, the concept of names has no relevance in the first place, not even YHVH, letters don't exist on this level, He is completely sublime and creation has no sense of existence on this level due to His sublimity "before" creation and there's no sense of pluralism, only G-d. As the Torah states "I, Hashem, do not change." Creation "begins" with Or Ein Sof, and the unity between G-d, referred to on this level as Ein Sof, that which is not finite, in Kabbalah, and His "light", Or Ein Sof, remember all such words are metaphoric in kabbalah as per the "language of the branches" and doesn't refer to light in the physical sense, rather it points to the concept in creation. The unity is like the rays of the sun before leaving the sun similar to the unity of man's thoughts with man. Ultimately it is not within man's comprehension to understand this unity because there is nothing comparable to G-d due to His sublimity. But we must understand we hit the limit of our understanding when trying to understand this unity. And although it is not within our comprehension to fully understand this unity, we can get a sense of the grey area of this unity where everything gets tangled by the concept of "identity" which is lost in this unity "before" pluralism existed. The concept "before" here refers to the concept of time, as we perceive it, and the need for an infinite past, something to have already existed, either the eternity of the universe or the eternity of something else which "created" it, and that something is G-d. Although "time" is often described as a creation, it doesn't make the concept invalid because creation is a constriction from G-d and His light, and thus it doesn't invalidate the word "before" from referring to climbing higher on the chain of creation and ultimately ending with G-d, who is the absolute, and the eternity through which creation was created, through tzimtzum, the constriction, and continues to exist.
(continued in next post) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chabad on americanized holidays like halloween, and thanksgiving </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 16:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the americanized holidays around the corner, I thought I'd post this thread. Has the Rebbe ever spoke on the subject? I'd be interested in what he felt he had to say. Perhaps tznius issues with halloween or concerns about wearing the opposite gender's clothes. Pretty sure kashrut concerns are pretty clear. Not participating at all. Even orthodox Jews have weak points in their life, growing up. So I'd expect him to have spoke out on the subject at some point. As far as thanksgiving, I can't think of anything to be concerned about, honestly. Perhaps extra stringent reasons not to eat turkey in the first place, maybe? Or not to feast with non-Jews, which Chabad ironically welcomes into shul whole-heartedly, it seems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
