<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1549</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 06:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was diagnosed in late May. They'd been mentioning it to me (or as it is known in the ICD-10, used in most European countries, emotionally unstable personality disorder) for a few years, since my last suicide attempt. 

 When I made the post I felt wretched but I slept for about an hour and now I feel a little better. It's like a rollercoaster in the dark; you never know how many twists and turns your emotions will take and you never see the drops coming. 

 I don't have as much of a handle as I would like. When I was a kid I had temper tantrums all the time and then graduated to hurting myself when angry, but now I try to go running. Or I whine on the internet, haha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 06:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey there. 

 No, I have not - I have a pet bunny though and she is the light of my life. 

 I cut myself, a lot. I've needed stitches quite a few times (NHS staff are sometimes amazing and sometimes awful - I've been told there are people with "real problems" and I was a time-waster, which put me off going the next time, and now my scars are pretty terrible). I started off sticking pins in my veins (really not sure why) and then graduated to the blades from pencil sharpeners, then razor blades, then I ordered a load of blades for craft knives off the internet, and then kitchen knives. I once tried to count my scars and stopped at three hundred; they are most visible on my left arm. The worst is six inches long. I did not get stitches. When it's cold it goes purple. 

  I think I must be difficult. I've very intense. Things upset me a lot (my housemates refused to live with me for a third year and I tried to kill myself, which perhaps strengthened their point).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> first post. not my first rodeo. fuck, i've let mself go </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 03:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hi

 been struggling with an eating disorder since 2012. since then two of my good friends have been diagnosed with anorexia. one was hospitalised and the other is so thin i'm amazed she's still at university. 

 my lowest weight is 130 which is currently 19lb away. i need to stopdrinking. i try to log everything but i keep telling myself "oh, tomorrow you won't eat" and then i wake up and eat. it's disgusting. i repulse myself. covered in cellulite and flab,, i can grab handfuls of my stomach because i'm so huge. genuinely amazed i don't fucking burst out of my clothes. 
 
 i am going home for Christmas around 15th December. before then i want to be 130lb. i know it's still gross etc but it might make me feel a little better. i've been at uni for a term now and only lost 6lb bc i keep binging - i live alone all my friends threw me out. i've got no excuses any more. 

 :( i don't know how i've got this huge. and every time i get down to about 142 and then binge again?! why am i so fucking weak. i used to be so strong. i've been losing and gaining the same 10-15lb for years now. i've been making the same posts on mpa for years. 

 its time. aiming for 800 cals a day - i know it's a lot but then hopefully i won't binge. might try to go sober for as long as possible nd see how much weight i lose </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i have borderline personality disorder. ama! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 03:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm twenty and was diagnosed in May but I've known about it for years. i've been self harming since i was eleven but now i've not hurt myself in eight months. i also have an eating disorder and problems with alcohol (bpd can cause these). 

 but yah. this is a fairly misunderstood condition. hoping to change that, maybe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
