<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1563</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 16:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, im a while male in his 20s going to university for computer science. Way off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 22:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would be he point of using the console command then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 07:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mental gymnastics should really be in the Olympics by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 07:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 22:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every fucking place does that. You have to be absolutely clear that you just want an oil change and go to a mechanic you trust. Sorry to say, but the real world isn't fair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 18:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey now, you're a rockstar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 18:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if you're a porn star? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 17:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously I was throwing in a small jab at COD players, but in all reality my analogy was fair. I'm basically saying that yes, COD and Skyrim are both video games but they're entirely different. Just like diving vs. swimming. Both are in a pool, but divers might not necessarily be great at competitive swimming and swimmers might not be good at diving. I don't know why Bethesda thought it would be a good idea to have a COD player play Skyrim. There are many people who have played over 1000 hours on that game, and I'm sure there's some known gamer that has put in some serious time playing Skyrim. I don't know why they chose this guy at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 17:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah pretty much. I don't really like labels any more but this election made me realize Democrats are hypocritical idiots. I've shifted to libertarian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 16:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I didn't mean it like that ha, I just meant that you don't need to have an attention span at all to play COD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 07:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once I made an illusion/conjuration mage and I would summon up creatures to fight for me while I turned invisible and just watched. It was so damn cheap.

Edit: in the arena I mean  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 07:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not even about skills. RPGs are not really about skill. They're about exploration, role-playing and strategy. It's not about how quick you can press buttons or how fast you can aim. That's what's so bad about this. My 12 year old brother could have done a better let's play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 07:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's like asking an Olympic diver to compete in the 400m relay. We're talking about an fps for people with ADD vs. an RPG which actually requires at least half a brain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 07:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should be more like, "I spent an entire week crafting iron daggers to level up my smithing." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 07:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually felt bad doing it. I was trying to find any other way to finish the quest m </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 07:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? They picked that retard to play the game? Why??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 23:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh it really fucking irks me that Beyonce and the Obamas are uttered in the same breath. Though I guess Obama is to blame for trying to be a rockstar and inviting celebrities to the White House every other day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 23:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL women are sheep and each must follow the herd, as is her duty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the dragons are only pathetic to your power because of the deal you made with Hermaeus Mora. Depending on how much you leveled your character before that point, you could be relatively weak at that point. You just have the amazing ability to bend the will of those dragons. You might get killed in one hit by Miraak if you face him, but you just so happen to have a powerful shout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this has been a million times, but the Dark Brotherhood in Oblivion was so much better than Skyrim's. Don't get me wrong, I loved the Dark Brotherhood quest in Skyrim. One of my favorites, but it wasn't as good as Oblivion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 16:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won't. There's already massive scandals but everyone is in their tribes and doesn't care when it's their candidate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why has Trump kept defending the fact that he was against the Iraq war? He wasn't in public office, he had no say in the matter, and he didn't have the intelligence that Clinton had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 02:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great connections and being able to afford prestigious universities is a great privelege to have, but that doesn't mean it's easy. You still have to be incredibly dedicated and be quite intelligent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 02:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I knew I could get any job without trying. Would have saved a lot of time and money spent at university. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 00:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Clintons have definitely had people killed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 00:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually go with LaBatts. It's a cheaper beer but it doesn't taste like piss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 00:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A huge pro of being in a long term relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 00:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Run on low and max out fps or run on ultra and drop the fps? Always a difficult choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 00:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biggie Smalls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 00:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should check out hentai </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 00:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stopped smoking weed indefinitely, so many people offer it to me and the exchange is always annoying. They think I'm saying no to be polite, but actually I just want nothing to do with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 00:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but about stuff that actually affects people's lives. Stuff that they should be informed about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 19:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a juggernaut character. Heavy armor, block and one handed are highest. So I pretty much just hold up my shield, tire them out and hit them between swings. Also use bash sparingly to knock them off balance for a couple quick hits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 18:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing you described was blind faith. Everything is a reasonable conclusion that cannot be proven without a doubt, but is reasonable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 17:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 15:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real journalism is dead, sorry to say. We only get infotainment and opinions nowadays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 15:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the actual fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought you were referring the the Blood On the Dance Floor song. I died a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's "just a theory" to describe a heavily supported scientific theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can trans/queer people please try and understand that they are not normal human beings and their opinions on what being a normal person is as irrelevant as a frog's?

Edit: this was satire making fun the original post, but ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It clearly represents that black men steal white women and fuck them with no strings attached. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 03:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAS RACIST^but^accurate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah...lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 20:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No that's just what happens when the government collects tax money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could just be changed to a Roman arena fighter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really feel the need to defend other religions because I think they are bad as well. However, those teachings are not accepted nor practiced in Judaism and Christianity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't care. I bite the bullet and am that guy all the time. I try and let others answer but I get impatient when no one does, so I'll answer even if I'm wrong to keep the lecture flowing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna be that asshole, but a Gladiator is not a Roman soldier. Otherwise great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 16:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be more tolerant, infidel. Otherwise we'll cut of your head. Thank you for understanding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 16:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus, you know, killing gays and treating women like shit is a-ok in mainstream contemporary Islam. The KKK is despised and completely rejected by mainstream Christianity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how any time anyone criticizes Islam, immediately the reaction is to attack Christianity. I'm not even Christian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, more votes to farm for Democrats. We're gonna be getting people like the Clintons in office for decades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 15:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing strawman argument you got there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 14:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is a circlejerk, but sjws. They honestly cannot be reasoned with. Statistics only matter to them when they reinforce what they already believe. Rational arguments mean nothing to them. It's either agree or you're racist/sexist/bigoted/homophobic/transphobic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 14:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Islam is a religion of peace  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 13:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can if you don't buy a new console every time one comes out, you buy your games on steam sales and you budget yourself when choosing your pc. 

Edit: also if you don't buy a new computer that often and use your gaming PC as your main computer as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 05:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have no one to blame but yourself for being a console peasant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 03:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some Wisecracking Jews? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 22:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck. I was a journalism major and recently switched to Computer Science because journalism is way too competitive and doesn't pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But...skyblivion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This gets posted every so often and the result is the same. No one will admit to being openly racist and I don't think anyone consciously believes themselves to be racist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cognitive dissonance. It's not just when someone believes things that conflict with one another. It's when someone is faced with new information that conflicts with what they already know and the mental struggle they go through because of it. Cognitive dissonance is always resolved by either rejecting the new information or rejecting the old beliefs.

 It would be like if someone believed in the Bible Genesis story, but then was shown overwhelming evidence for evolution. They wouldn't just go around believing both. They'd have cognitive dissonance and then either reject evolution or reject the Genesis story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 17:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not all atheists come to the conclusion for the same reasons, but I'd be willing to guess the atheist in this situation would be more open to reason. Anecdotal evidence is meaningless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 17:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well then, I'm ready to embrace the Apocalypse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 17:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's kind of what a fear is right? It's not entirely rational and it is exaggerated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE get irritated when your post doesn't take off, but then stress out when it does? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 17:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure mommy and daddy will pull some strings for her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wait til Hillary wins. You'll never hear the end of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've given up in these sjws. I just refuse to interact with them. They're hopelessly stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe should have worded this better, but yeah I find smoking really gross too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 06:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Applefag spotted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 06:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was nice to see the Bills whoop on Kaepernick today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 00:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it sucked. Watch Game of Thrones and you'll see that you don't need a cheap cliffhanger to keep viewers anticipating the next season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 00:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A thief tried to rob me, and while I was starting to fight back a giant came in and killed the thief for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 00:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really depends on the character you wanna go with. The resistance is great, but you can also use enchantments and potions with an Altmer to get the same effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 17:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Father says I'm to young to use a sword, so I practice with my fists! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 22:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but losing the queen is like getting shot in the kneecap during a race. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 03:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So that's what happens when an unstoppable force hits an immovable object. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. This actually pissed me off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO! Gtfo out of STEM fields you fucking sjws! We don't want your safe spaces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, look at how long it worked for Madonna. I wish it didn't work, but this is how you stay relevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly it's just a brilliant PR tactic by her. She can't be criticized now, because anyone who does is against LGBTQ folk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no way someone posted this on FB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah, technically humans are animals. We aren't plants. Well, those of us that aren't plant-kin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, no shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hated that post. Yes of course Trump would win if all men voted, just as Clinton would win if only women voted.

You can watch a number of videos showing women saying they are voting for Hillary because "it's about time we have a woman in the White House."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 05:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried today to use my temporary ID, and the only other thing I had was my college ID. Didn't work at a restaurant. I threw out all of my old ID's months ago so yeah that's all I have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 23:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The question asked what is something MOST think is real but is really fake. 


Anyways I didn't care so much that people misunderstood me. I can see that, but a lot of people were asserting as fact that I said some psychics are legitimate, and some even insulted me for it.

Edit: plus, if you read my full comment it's pretty easy to infer that's what I meant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate that argument that science doesn't know everything, therefore science doesnt always apply.


1)science is not a conscious entity

2) just because something cannot prove something, doesnt mean that thing is outside the rules of science. Nothing is.

3)there are always rational explanations for "supernatural" events </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that all of them are fake. That was referring to far to many people believe in them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's why I leave her alone about it. She doesn't make life changes based on psychics. She's never even gone to see one, though she wants to. If she was really into it then it would be a problem but we just agree to disagree about it. In my eyes, I'd rather know the truth than be comforted by something false. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like my dad. He equates actual astronomy with astrology and it's really annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 21:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe. I tend to stay away from the topic. She'd probably get angry at me if I did that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE hate being reminded to do things, but then always forget to do those things when nobody reminds you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 15:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 15:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol it's not that kind of stuff. She believes mostly that they can communicate with the dead. More along the lines of people die, but their soul or whatever still exists and certain people can communicate with them. Honestly I blame reality T.V. She watches too much of that stuff and doesn't believe me when I tell her it's mostly scripted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 15:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Research on what? Religious experiences? There's no scientific evidence backing them up. The only evidence for religious experiences is that many people claim to have had them and there are sometimes similarities between these claims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 15:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep I've had some moments spoiled for me as well. Aka the meaning of a certain character's name. It sucks but luckily there were a ton of surprises I didn't know about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use a mouse and keyboard, you milk drinker! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not going to make him more popular. Take a look at how people talk about him on social media. Look at how major news outlets report on him. Look at how many articles, blogs videos etc. that talk about how horrible he is. Half the country hates him and once he loses and some time goes by, he won't even have his base to support him. He went all in trying to win this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand not wanting to watch until it's all done, but I'd make sure you go nowhere near the internet when it does end, otherwise it's going to be spoiled for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would Trump spend so much of his own money on his campaign and totally ruin his reputation for that? Look at the things he just said about Hillary and Bill during the last debate. I doubt they would want that brought up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say most, but far too many. Psychics. 

I've gotten into really bad arguments with my gf over the idea, because she was watching some stupid psychic show and I made fun of it, and she things that some of them are real. She's logical about most things and very smart, but for some reason she actually believes some psychics are real. I tried to explain to her that what they do is nothing more than psychological tricks and that you can read lots of articles and watch videos that expose their techniques. 

Edit: incredible comprehension skills, Reddit. Thanks for letting me know ALL psychics are fake, because I totally made the claim that some are legitimate. I definitely wasn't addressing the original question and saying far too many PEOPLE think psychics are real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
