<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3359</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 21:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not, only one person gets an assist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 21:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XlZpNImkbFQ --- Watch this :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 18:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Different line-up with bigger names, also they only participated in one major.

EDIT: Also, there wasn't a big post about it since he got around $300 max for match fixing, while IBP got thousands of dollars in skins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 17:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because epsilon wasn't a top tier team or a very well known one, IBP was the 2nd best team in America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 12:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surrender at the start of a new round instead of the end of another, if the vote passes at the end of a round it sometimes bugs out and won't do anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 12:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't involves in cheating, wut? He was match fixing with other members from epsilon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 12:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do whatever you think feels right. I'm a wrist player, have tried arm for a week once but just couldnt get used to it and it felt horrible. There are still quite a few wrist players in the pro scene (like Hiko, ex6tenz, f0rest sort of i think but not sure). You can be a pro even with your wrist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 10:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone gets better at their own pace, dont worry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 22:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me, you can become a higher rank. I'm yet to be global, but know I can be if I put some work into it. I thought I was stuck in silver forever, was stuck in there for 200 hours (yes I was fucking terrible), then slowly started ranking up and made it to LEM with 950 hours on record (a lot of which are surf and afk as well though). I don't think you've hit your skill ceiling just yet, just believe in yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 19:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How to deal with derankers: +left +forward </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 02:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many people have an issue with it because it's a "noob gun"/"cod gun". I personally still prefer the AK due to me using it for 1000+ hours and only having bought the SG when properly fucking about, but I can see why people would go with the SG. Have to say tho, to play against them can be annoying as fuck. Same goes for the auto, p90 and aug, but it's part of the game so we'll have to deal with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 00:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The damage is the same as m4a4 now, I may be wrong though. Don't quote me on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 00:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He get's banned 1 second after throwing the molly because I was standing right ontop of it lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 00:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lad probably tried to put it up for $351 but accidently ended up putting it up for $3.51 and then a bot bought it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 00:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elo system only cares about wins, ties, losses and mvps. 

If you top with a lot of mvps against higher ranked/same skilled players, but you lose, you probably wont derank. 

If you top with no mvps against lower ranked players, you may get deranked.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 00:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Vanishing trick, oops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 23:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did not, they meant to change it, but it ended up not going through in the patch. (even though the buy menu does state it has a lower armour pen than the m4a4) They will keep it how it is now since they think it's balanced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 23:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glock and p2k on par? Not really lol.

The p2k and usp are on par, one is meant for tapping players the other for sprayers. (both can be used by either type of players but you know what I'm saying.)

Personally, I do way better with the p2k. I do horrendous when I play with the usp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The famous vanishing by "Rat"! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 23:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 05:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 38 min and you still didn't beat the map, rip :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 02:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TSM Stickers have been changed, names on autographs are white and so is the logo. Not the background sadly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 22:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try to get as many toxic Russians banned from competitive as I can :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 20:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buuuut... You take the karma :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 16:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, there are, but even the pro players have agreed to each other to not use the SG and AUG. The main weapons should be the M4 and AK. (and AWP) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 16:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "i have to get 20 lvls in 10 weeks"

You could've easily been at rank 40 already, even without the bonus exp.

Why do you want the medal on your smurf anyway lol? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 21:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dust2: Tie between nV/TSM, however when NiP plays on D2 they do quite well.

Mirage: I'd say VP, but TSM could take it as well.

Cache: Fnatic

Train: VP

Cobble: de_olofstone, nah jk not sure

Inferno: TSM

Overpass: de_olofpass/TSM/VP




So yeah basically what Blue said too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 21:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks pretty dank. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 20:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great video, I really hope valve decides to give first shot accuracy gets a buff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 13:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How come it's repetitive? Sure threads like these were posted for the cologne stickers, they weren't yet for the dreamhack ones though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 05:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is shadowban and how do other people know if others have one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 03:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had to test in the name of science :P

And yeah, seems like they don't scratch as well, the name is pretty clear, but it sucks that a bit of the sticker remains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 03:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only tested this once, the background seems to get fully removed but parts of the side and logo stayed.

EDIT: This was until the very last scrape  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scraped Dreamhack sticker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 03:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 03:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stocked up on them, sold 'em the day after for quick and easy profit instead of waiting and it payed off :D 30 euros profit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 01:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/HysqT - Yep, here it is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 21:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You scraped it more than 7 times, after the 7th it goes invisible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 21:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh for real? Didn't know that was patched.

And I guess you could, I personally don't though, would rather just get to a position quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 04:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't buy multiple smokes unless you've picked one up in the previous round so yeah lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 01:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can do this smoke while running lol, no need to sit still and jumpthrow it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 21:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you fucking retarded? Skip to 0:14 you spaz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 19:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These look dope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 18:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mad respect for getting DMG with such fps, the highest I was able to get with around 30 fps was nova 4 by only spraying. Currently am LEM, my main playstyle is spraying. Tapping isn't really my thing, not good at it whatsoever. The problem really just is your fps, sorry bro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 00:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On AKs stickers look good in nearly any position on most of the skins, not on ones like the fire serpent tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 16:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, in my experience it is lol. Everyone knows dust 2, everyone knows the common spots or places where people hide and shit. It's purely about good aim and out awping in my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 15:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please stop giving this bitch attention, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 15:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I struggle the most with dust 2 to be honest, mainly because it's a pure aim map and I'm personally more about lurking/positioning and game sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 19:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he was still decent, rip friberg. We will remember you, my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 13:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 12:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ This.

My old laptop used to work fine for multiple months then just gave me shit fps due to it overheating. For me there wasn't anything to do other then get a cooler (which still barely worked). So I just go a pc instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 17:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha all right, too each their own :P It can be a bit of a pain in the arse for your friend though when he wants to queue together and you're practising xD  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 17:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's just that you don't enjoy the feeling of the gun, I mean it may seem weird since it's just in a game, but personally I much prefer the AK over the M4. The M4 also just has better accuracy which may be why flicking is either for you with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 13:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you upgrade you have one month to switch back if you want btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 13:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The laughing though xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 13:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pala banter lads

Also Semmler is French? Damn, never even knew that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 13:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like Notapearing, I just jump straight into games as I get on. I'm one of those really consistent players who doesn't need warmup whatsoever (a bit of surfing is nice but doesn't really help anyway). Got from silver to LEM in a couple months of time just playing when I feel like it instead of forcing myself to do so. Never really been a fan of aim training and stuff like that, spraying I learned myself and just have a feel for it. Getting to global will still be pretty hard tho as the skill gap does indeed get way bigger between LEM/Global </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 22:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy is literally the best caster lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 22:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't this already posted before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 01:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is so true lmao. I'm mainly a rifler, but when I watch some of the "primary awpers" I just cringe when they miss the easiest shots multiple times in a row. I barely play awp and even I would be able to hit the guy lol.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 01:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're DMG and you've only gotten one ace before? I'm assuming you're a very passive support player? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 01:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just need to aim at the head with pistols and dont just spray them and instead tap fire lol. It's not that hard if you practise on HS pistol only servers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 01:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1: Howl/Fade preferably with a darkish background (maybe make both to see which I like more? :p)
2: KrayzeeK (Short: KrayZ)

Awesome work by the way 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 20:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For real? 0 derankers? Damn. I have gotten like 4 or 5 groups of derankers in about 60 matches on my alt lol. Most Russians I meet just shout stupid shit and I just have to mute them anyway (most of the time when I get them on my team, they're absolute shit) and personally I don't meet many good smurfs, but you have one every so often. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 18:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro, D2 is where nearly everyone plays. It's just cancerous as hell, one game you have russians, the other game trolls and then the next game derankers. Or you can just have smurfs/hackers on the other team as well. 

Obviously anyone can rank up to supreme by mainly playing Dust 2, but it comes down to the luck of having a good team/same skilled opponents aswell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 00:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sir please put the memes down, you may hurt yourself because of all the edginess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 00:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ayy not sure if you do colours too, but either draw a deagle blaze or just the default AK47, that'd be pretty cool. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 00:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here I am wanting a knife ;_;

JKJK, I'd actually like a butter knife, that'd be embarrasing as fuck to die to haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 19:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check the bottom right at 1:30, the drool tho lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 16:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either wait the extra couple seconds after the game is finished, or disconnect and don't click on either reconnect/abondon.. It's not hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 16:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohh haha, looks pretty cool though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 02:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maniac? Forgot about Scream joining? :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 22:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still pretty good nonetheless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 22:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One clutch proves it is still really good? Don't think it does, sorry mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 20:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks alright, rip m4a1-s tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Q] When do you guys think the dreamhack stickers will come out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 17:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 13:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> put your shaders on high/very high, that's probably why they seem dark. Or alternatively get SweetFX/turn digital vibrance up in nvidia control panel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 13:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is valve deathmatch though, not a proper HS server like he was on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 13:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Image doesnt work, GG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 12:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me personally, I mostly play maps like Overpass, Cobble and Train, the "odd" ones. I'm also more of a T-sided player, like I'll have a shit CT side getting like 10 kills, then on T-side I just get up to 30. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 00:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh haha, personally I don't play it a lot but once in a while it's fun. I mainly play de_olofpass nowadays and usually get nice teams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 21:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.hitbox.tv/efragtv/team --- should be on here later today when the stream is over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 21:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if you queue alone it shouldn't be too hard as long as you don't play dust 2, that's where the cancerous part of the community plays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 16:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is, it can be very hard to get out of silver for some people due to bad luck. Smurfs on the other team, russians on your own team, derankers, trolls etc. In Nova you start getting this less. Also, end of silver is pure p90/auto cancer because people want to get nova 1 lol.

Not coming from a silver btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 15:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Novas are still pretty bad though, no offense (Wouldn't call myself, and LE/LEM, good either). Solo queue in nova/silver is horrendous as there are just not strats whatsoever. In higher level play, people actually know a bit about the game and what should be done in which situations.

A 5 man premade is so much better though, if they're actually good and don't have that one shit talker/toxic player. They should be way more organised, but sometimes just fuck about giving you an easy game anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 15:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "alright" mate, those drops are sick compared to what I got. I hope you're trolling though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The inner Hiko coming out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 17:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 17:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is your opinion. That however does not change the fact it's a near perfect map. With near perfect I mainly mean the balance of it, which is quite close to 50/50 with a slightly higher percent on T-side if I'm correct.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 17:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming from a nova 4... No wonder. "Rush B", "Rush A long", "Rush A short" and whatnot. That's nova.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 17:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, agree and dissagree. CBA to reply properly right now though, however, I get where you're coming from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 17:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can kill 1 to 2 enemies pushing at long, that is fine. That means you also have info whether there are more players pushing or not so you can judge whether your team should rotate or not. If you back off and go to ct ramp/elevator, make sure there is someone on your team watching short. If not then either go into ct spawn and watch cross or go car at a slight off angle and kill a couple of them pushing.

On T-side, don't rush long if you don't have a long spawn. If you do have one, flash over twice. Once outside of long and one in long (You can easily do both while running to long), this way you can pre-fire the corner at the cost of you getting naded and lose some HP, or death if you straight up miss your shots. If you have a long spawn no one should be able to get to pit quickly unless you see them first.

Before pushing short, smoke off x-box, the other team may indicate that your team could be pushing short, but you can still go OR fake it. When pushing short make sure to check every single angle, however dont just rush it like an idiot and get awped by someone on site/goose. You can also use nades, flashes and smokes yourself to push in obviously.

If you want to push into B from upper tunnels you can flash in twice (also able to do so while running), this should flash nearly anyone on site because they'll turn away from the first flash then look at the second one because they turn back around. The only angles the could be at with full vision is the big box, in site behind boxes, fence (unlikely if rush from a B spawn) or on the close right next to tunnels on the boxes. If you want to push it slowly, throw a smoke and bounce it off the wall so you can't get shot from site, make sure to check back of plat and the big box before rushing in (maybe molotov either) and then when going in check on the boxes on the right, car and door. (And fence but usually there's no one here.) 

I don't get why everyone says that it's a hard map to play or that they can't get kills, because the other team is. They're players just like you and should be at the same skill group. Adapt to your opponent aswell, remember this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 23:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If GTR would go to C9, Sean would start coaching. If swag however get's unbanned, he will most likely get on the team and Sean will also be coaching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 23:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I get that I guess. Personally, my most played map is dust 2. I've had a lot of shit teammates, but also a lot of nice ones. It's mainly in the lower ranks where the cancer community hides. Once you get around MG you usually get nice players, this is from my own experience at least. I personally haven't had much trouble with derankers, but if I have them on my team, instead of whining and raging like a bitch I just play along and try to make it a fun match for myself. The game isn't about a couple pixels on the screen showing your rank, it's about fun. If you derank, even though you belonged in the higher rank, you'll rank up again in no time. I'm currently LE/LEM and to be honest haven't met many hackers at all. I get the blatant wall hacker every so often but that's about it. I don't play dust all that much myself though, I'm mainly a fan of the   "weirder" maps (Maps which not as many people play) like Cobblestone, Overpass and Train. However a dust every couple matches is still fun for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 23:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You die at mid by crossing? Use a nade/smoke, if they've been prefiring it just wait a bit before actually crossing when the smoke goes down. Not sure how you always die at mid lol. Just because you can't play some areas of the map doesn't mean it's a bad map. It's just that other players are better on it. Learn to adapt to the playstyle of the enemies and do unexpected shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 20:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing you hate it due to popularity and overplaying it? Because I think everyone can agree Dust 2 is a near perfect competitive map for CS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 05:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ikr, I have a pretty high sens, but my crosshair doesnt jitter like that whatsoever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 17:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% agree Anders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 23:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rap god or csgo caster? lel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 00:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confirmation emails bro, you'd have to have their mail account aswell if it's guarded by steamguard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 21:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yh I agree that'd be awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 22:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full control like papa biceps :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 03:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently you were able to crash servers if you bought too many lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 03:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... Rip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Valve removed spam buying. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 03:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can now only purchase 3 of each weapon in a round and only 1 zues per round. Thought I'd let people know, not sure if this was known yet. :)

EDIT: Apparently it's 5. However when I tested this offline I could only buy 3 of each.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 02:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you do one for G2?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 00:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My fps was 250+ and after the update it still is. However, some people have had their FPS drop from 250+ to 100 with a 144hz monitor (which is awful). Some have even had their FPS drop from 250+ to 60 or less which is horrendous. For some of my friends the game is unplayable due to the FPS drops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 00:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The viewmodel though...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 23:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you do some for G2? :D
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 17:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice clutch bro! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 01:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly he's on a crappy team now. No offense to Titan fans.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> INHUMAN REACTIONS! v2.0? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 14:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Skins [W] Any pin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-06 19:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a deagle blaze with 0.003 float and AK47 Case Hardened with nametag, sticker and 80% blue mag. Trading for any pin. 

YOU GO FIRST.

http://steamcommunity.com/id/AyyLmaoG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 00:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "!" Would probably be better. I don't know man, I literally just mean like a logo of a shouting russian guy with the text " ". If that's too weird or hard, just make a design of your own since my team, nor I care too much as we don't even have a logo haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 00:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems cool



Team: ! (Blyat!)

One word:  

One Image: Honestly no clue, maybe a toxic Russian dude whos shouting cyka blyat?

Preferred Colors: Don't mind, your choice.

Design Style: Image/text like I said above.

Team Vision: Talk to the enemy in fake russian accents, if it doesn't work shout  !



Ty for doing this, it's awesome :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
