<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3859</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-11 17:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yeah I agree, art is very fulfilling to the soul when it's a gift. Watercolor, btw.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Before leaving India, I left my cousins a gift to remember me by.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-11 17:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-23 22:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks, and yeah your right, the least kingcarlos could have done is tell me why it looks like shit and how it can be improved.....otherwise, a hater. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-22 18:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://a2.sphotos.ak.fbcdn.net/hphotos-ak-snc6/267924_10150230694094001_662494000_7396389_1358705_n.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-22 17:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yeah the lighting and I guess also the facial expression and ugliness lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-22 17:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually have a much better high quality pic, gimme a few minutes and ill put it up, you can see the true colors with the texture from the knife.....I just used this one because i submitted from my phone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-22 17:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually did mix my own,  ultramarine blue and permanent alizar crimson and burnt sienna but when I tried to fix up the colors in PhotoShop to look like the original , some color was lost, sorry about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-22 08:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that was pretty sick, Haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I painted a self portrait with a Palette knife </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-22 07:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-22 02:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I always tried to work hard but not smart, got a b because it wasn't done in a week, it was late Haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-22 02:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had to tally like every 10 or 20 , it was a pain some people took pics every certain number  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-22 01:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I don't remmeber the exact number but it was 117 k - Somethin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-22 01:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an old assignment from my freshmen year, it was to get 30,000 strokes and you could make anything you wanted on a 12x18. I chose to go bigger, this is 30x40 inches. The numbers mean nothing I just had to tally it, I kinda went crazy and did not plan it or anything just drew as it came to mind, used a mirror for the self portrait.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-22 01:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's cool, glad to hear your opinion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDAP with 117,000 pen strokes, yes I had to count </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-21 20:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-20 05:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought fabric glow in the dark paint from a arts and crafts store and mixed it with oils after I finished the painting, and lightly laid it down on the parts I wanted to glow, like the hair and the face the stars, the outline of clothes, it was very experimental but turned out amazing. The stars light up really nice and so does the right side of the face, that's the reason some of it may seem unfinished, I had to very careful in laying it down and did not want to mess up the original color... sadly I can't get a good pic until its fully dry. In real life, the face is not that red and theres more detail in the background. Hope that answers your question, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My glow in the dark Father's day gift </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-19 20:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My glow in the dark Father's day gift </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-19 20:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-13 09:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-13 09:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you like it, thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-13 07:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was playing backyard football and my friend and I Headbutted eachother by accident and my eyelid kinda exploded. Bloody an.everything, had to close it with 7 stitches. Happened yesterday, finished the painting today, yeah it sucks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-13 02:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-13 02:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-13 00:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry reddit, it's a shitty photo compared to the real life painting, it was done in a small room and it was difficult to get a good shot.  Here is a better pic, managed to finish today, that's me on with stitches on my eye.


http://a3.sphotos.ak.fbcdn.net/hphotos-ak-snc6/254063_10150222579229001_662494000_7316374_6224000_n.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-13 00:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/Art/comments/hy12p/golden_eagle_i_painted_on_my_friends_wall/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-13 00:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/Art/comments/hy12p/golden_eagle_i_painted_on_my_friends_wall/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-13 00:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/Art/comments/hy12p/golden_eagle_i_painted_on_my_friends_wall/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Golden eagle I painted on my friend's wall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-13 00:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-08 17:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you will be complete very soon , working on it right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-08 17:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the feedback, I actually am already planning to make the background textural using only palette knives and I wanna keep it mostly grey and white instead of warm colors, very loose like you said and the edges.....ill see. Will post final soon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-07 20:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oil paint btw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-07 20:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm done with the bird, the photo isn't so great and has some colors in the head look faded. I'm thinking something subtle for the background so it doesn't take away from the eagle, maybe a little bit of clouds and then as it goes up the atmosphere and then space at the very top, as if the eagle were sitting almost at the atmosphere. It's on my friends wall and the bird is about half of the wall. Once I finish I will take a high quality pic, thanks for checking it out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-07 06:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sick dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Before I do the background....What do you think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-07 06:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-25 10:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's oil paint </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Lennon painting practice, one hour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-25 07:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-20 19:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that show was amazing, watched it in kindergarten, used to trip me out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-19 07:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm finishing my sophomore year majoring in Communication arts at the best public art school in the nation which I'm sure means absolutely NOTHING in this corrupt nation....and after reading this post and everyone's comments and experiences.... its been plaguing me all day.....if people with masters all over cannot make ends meet....what hope is there for me? Esp cuz I'm an artist....should I drop the fuck out and stop wasting money and move to Australia?......move the fuck outta here....i can't get it outta my head... I still have two years but how much can happen by then....will things get even worse...? How am I going to survive......if there is any artists out there, how are you holding up?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-17 08:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too wtf  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-17 08:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL that just made me geek out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-10 21:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-10 00:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's 2 feet by 3 feet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-09 22:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha what's up springfield-  from springfield, currently in richmond though, VCU.  Sunny springfield, gonna be a long summer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-09 21:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks this painting surprisingly punished the work I've been doing in the past few months.....its the first time my professor ever complimented me on a piece, he called it a "breakthrough" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-09 21:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried man this was the best I got after like 3 hours ....the oil was laid so thick and it will not be dry for a while so it reflects every little light , when it dries ill take it sorry man  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-09 21:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yeah shoulda seen the riots here , it was fuckin crazy riot police helicopters throwing down tear gas people tearing down fences and destroying everything, never seen anything like it , the citys been wild ever since, it was an amazing run to watch, even after losing there was one last riot and celebration </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-09 17:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a sophomore at VCU in Richmond, Va </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-09 17:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-09 09:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I have been using the knife for two months now.... I gave up the brushes , thought I would try something new  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Palette knife Oil painting I did in 8 hours.....straight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-09 08:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-22 02:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-bxgOjSD0Cko/TYf08ldBV5I/AAAAAAAAALE/EDKfwYSbzhY/s1600/Beach.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-22 02:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I owe it to you guys. Here, a high quality pic of the painting....I realize that the first pic had very little color....

https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-bxgOjSD0Cko/TYf08ldBV5I/AAAAAAAAALE/EDKfwYSbzhY/s1600/Beach.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-18 07:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice...better quality pic woulda been better..so it wouldn't look so faded and even toned...
Contrast in the strokes and shading would have popped it out...maybe it's just the photo but if not..try having darker areas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IDAP of an Island on fire using Charcoal, crit welcome. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-18 07:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-18 05:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pretty nice...eh kinda , it was alright...didn't look stop motion... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-18 05:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, think I wanna do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-18 05:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just realized your the same person who commented on my drawing, that's sweet. It actually feels like a community on this thing, I think I'm gonna start getting on r/art more, btw I'm about to upload part 2 of my war sequence, check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-18 04:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you may want to consider the placement of the figure....by putting it right next to the edge like that, it feels kind of closed in and the way the figure is looking to the top right, I think it would make more sense to have more negative space on the right side vs left. What I am seeing is the negative space competing against the angle of the head, the figures gaze carries towards the tight space, but a huge chunk of space leaves us behind, on the left.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-18 04:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anytime, I love to help out fellow artists...thanks for checking it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-18 04:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed everything seems to bleed off the sides...Maybe if you had a certain element in your work that DIDN'T bleed off, you would be able to add more interest to that element and create contrast, making it either more important, or even a focal point.....like the girl on the bottom right..the way I look at it, the giant orb/planets in the middle are overpowering the work for sure, but I still notice that there is the girl in the corner and my eye seems to follow the other few afterimages of her to the left, then it bleeds off, bleeds back on to the orbs and carries my eye to the top right. I still get a sense of a journey with that girl, so if you hadn't bled her off on the bottom right, she,which represents the journey, would have been a little more important then the destination, which is the orb transformations/rotations around the planet. Don't take it in a bad way, you don't even have to change anything, just thought i'd share what I got from this image.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-18 03:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it is not but yes I have seen his work, my teacher showed it to me while I was working on this, thanks for the comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-18 03:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah sure, I actually started the whole thing using vine charcoal to get a medium gray tone.

 After the paper had that tone then I started adding lights and dark...I used my fingers to blend....to get the smooth areas and then used kneaded erasers to bring out the light areas. 

To bring out the darks I used charcoal pencils in basic outlines of where the darkest spot would be, and then used my fingers to blend the darkness in with the medium tone.

Its a process of working from biggest areas to smallest, don't try to render little parts at a time, or else you will feel overwhelmed.  

Try to take on the drawing as a whole, The blank sheet at first, The medium tone next, and then see if you can find certain areas of what you are that are lighter or darker, and then after determining that, I was able to find where to use the charcoal pencil(darkest darks) and kneaded erasers(whitest whites).

Hopefully it doesn't sound confusing...hard to explain, easier to show.

Might just depend on what medium you are working in....What are you using? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-17 23:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hehe it's ok, it's probably better you didn't know me... I got two gold keys for two of my paintings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-17 23:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a relief, well did you ever see a kid always painting in the hallways near the cafeteria...that was me. I was the art freak of the school, heh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-17 23:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well....your names lolnoodles...and if you do know who I am, then you know my nicknames noodles......please tell me you didn't just make this username to follow or stalk me, I've had enough stalkers and clingers....borders on frontier? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-17 21:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it would be nice but I'm here til Saturday and Back to a really busy semester....but summer breaks about 6 weeks away...maybe then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-17 16:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha yeah ain't shit to do around here, I've been sleeping for the past 4 days in the same place, everytime I get up, I'm like "GOTTA DO SOMETHIN", and I end up going back to sleep. The only thing people really do here is SMOKE their brains out, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-17 07:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha upvote for effort man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-17 06:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha that's awesome...yeah enjoying peaceful quiet Springfield for springbreak, Lee 09'     VCU Arts 13' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else from Springfield?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-17 05:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly everyone I know here pays no attention to the news and important events around the world...Egypt, the revolutions...protests...tragedy in Japan,etc...no one here bothers with whats going on in the world so I assumed they would never near Reddit. It's really sad. Surely there's SOMEONE in Springfield who keeps up with reddit??maybe a few people??just curious.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-17 05:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's beautiful, enjoy life;] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mushroom cloud I made in Charcoal, War sequence:Part 1 of 3. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-17 01:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-16 08:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome dude...making me appreciate my walls right now..esp since its raining </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-16 07:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your last image doesn't work....So I don't really know what your end term goal is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-16 06:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  I'm majoring in Communication arts and most likely will minor in painting, so it might take me a couple more years since im a sophomore right now. I wish i could stay in NYC for a couple days to paint....I'm not really a specific type of painter, I love painting everything, portraits to landscapes to abstract.... and I like your palette, gives the buildings a very humanly feeling...you can also add me on Deviantart but I don't go on much anymore....same username as my reddit.  So what exactly do you do with the landscapes you paint?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-16 06:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, I'm glad everyone liked it. I just managed to find a nice place to paint like this today in my boring town and will try in the new 2 or 3 days to have it done, for you guys at redditart!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-15 17:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will but gimme a few days...I'm on spring break and its in my room at school...as soon as I get a better pic ill reply to you again...in the mean time you can check out my other work www.noodos.blogspot.com ,there is a lot of work so you'll have to click older posts at the bottom of the page to see all.  Sorry for the disappointmenting quality of this painting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-15 16:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the artist look up, ill check em out. Yeah I'm going to try and find the painting..I have mountains of artwork in portfolios laying everywhere....its actually a pretty small painting , probably a good reason I was able to finish in time, I'm an art student and although I am not majoring in painting, I try to average about 7 a week...sadly there is not very nice  potential landscape matter where I live..I will try harder when summer is here for I will be in India..ere , right now I'm focusing on palette knife and its techniques.....but you can definitely check out all my work....www.noodos.blogspot.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-15 16:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Www.noodos.blogspot.com/         there is a lot of work on there...some is very experimental. Enjoy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-15 06:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow thank you, I think your comment just took my breath away for a moment. Glad people appreciate my painting=) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-15 05:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah thanks, i agree. I used to paint from photograph and there's a huge difference, when painting from photo, it seems very robotic and you can't capture the natural essence of what your painting. When I painted this, i was not trying to merely replicate what was before me, but put my own vibe into it and not have to worry about making it perfect down to every detail.Also the colors were changing fast so i was not worried about that either. Sand was getting on the canvas and it was painted very carelessly, and I think that's where some of life really came from. I encourage all artists to paint from life, thank you for the feedback, I had been submitting art into Reddit without picking "Art" and wondered why no one liked my paintings, I know now. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-15 04:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your right I took it awhile ago with my psp camera....very noobish of me, I'll upload a high quality pic soon, I appreciate the feedback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-15 02:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I used oils. Hehe I like making things creepy/chairoscuro through brush strokes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went to the beach, and ended up painting it at sunset </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-15 01:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-15 00:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry didn't answer your question but yes it did make a better finished product. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-15 00:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, actually I imagined it would. It led me to pour out my hunger through the knife strokes and focus on the texture of the bread and mouth-watering grape jelly. It also had an effect on time, this was done in about 2 hours. Normally I would tighten up the painting at the end and make the edges crisp, I didn't stress rendering the details because I was hungry and for once, did NOT over work the painting. thanks for the feedback </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Painted this PB J sandwich with a palette knife while starving </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-14 23:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 17:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha maybe I ended up making the paw too small for that type of perspective?..thanks for the feedback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 17:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha your right, never thought of that.. I'm glad you read it as a baboon, people always mistake it as a bear, thanks for checking it out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 17:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, its funny you say you can't afford it, I just started selling my work to my friends for like 50$ a peice, Haha. I appreciate the feedback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Painting I did to give off a sense of anger. Does it work?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 07:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-06 11:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn man I wish you luck...rest in heavenly peace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-12 17:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yea your right I almost forgot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-12 07:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing I'm indian living in the u.s, I watched every single day and saw terrible videos or cars running people over...people being shot...I heard the calls from people in Egypt when the internet was taken... It sends goosebumps through my body to have seen this struggle....to have witnessed such a great historic revolution. We're all lucky to be alive in such times, I'm so proud of you guys. I can only sit here in awe and respect.....people talk about things getting done, but you actually went out and DID it, and look, your struggle was seen by everyone and had a ripple effect on the surrounding nations. Let your people know.....the world is proud of you, not as seperate nations but as a race. We will ALWAYS be in this together. Take care and congratulations!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-28 18:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My phone usually fixes everything for me. Whatever, I don't have time to sit around trying to go on people over little things . Have fun  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My oil painted wood sculpture...lucid dreaming  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-27 05:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-27 02:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahah that's really inspirational, not to mention hilarious. I understand. Cheers, I await and look forward to future comments as I post more art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-21 05:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-20 20:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha your right there isn't one I don't. But I guess I just meant it was pretty inspiring and I was in the zone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poured my soul out painting this to Nujabes"Mystline",check it out reddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-20 16:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-16 05:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahahhahaha how did you find me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-13 19:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha that's funny I was actually exploring surface of many different things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going out of my Fuckin Mind Oil painting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-13 06:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 21:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 of 3 for my cudi series request </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 20:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean who?.......kid cudi?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 14:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Sikh and Hell Nooooooo I have never heard such a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 13:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot..I appreciate the criticism. I did this 2 years ago..I didn't know perspective til I got to college. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 13:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 12:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made it in highschool so there may be a few issues....but yeah I wanted her to be ancient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 12:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was actually a request from a friend. I don't plan on sell out to making paintings of crap haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Grasp" Oil painting...one of my best...national award winner  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 12:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 12:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol yeah I know nothing bout twilight I just needed the money  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 12:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow awesome I should post up my better ones thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 11:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 18"x24"  Oil painting...sold for 100$  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kristen Stewart oil painting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 11:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
