<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2069</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Were Mae and Moolah really awful people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heard these two both refered to as awful people. Never heard any actual stories though. Can anyone here elaborate? I noticed Bryan Zane mentioni g how sleazy moolah could be so was curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont care about the rewhiners </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a win is a win :)

Fuck the remainers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats....not a good sign </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened to blues and bullets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite rough edges i really enjoyed the first two episodes. And now...nothing. Havent heard a thing about any more coming. Does anyone know whats going on with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, Ill be fine :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed ghosts of mars  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John carpenter is directing GOAT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Troll? I voted leave because i think it will be better long term. I dont regret it. The EU are full of arrogant bullies. so fuck them and those who support them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats a retarded argument to make. I bet you enjoy plenty of things that were fake.

And the eu is the rotting leg we are cutting off to save the rest. Quite an apt description </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck the EU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its enough. You mean its not the decision you wanted, right? Just say that.

Over half is a majority. You lost. Accept it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should have punched him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dogs people. All day erry day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played marvel heroes beta...and it kinda sucks :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about in europe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UK  rest of europe. Blee dat bruh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No its not, the vote was fair and square. A majority is a majority, major or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know what happened to Blues and Bullets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Id seriously like another steve blackman run </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aside from jbl getting his shit pushed in, i liked blackman a lot. His gimmick was no gimmick needed, he was a bad ass and thats how he got over. His hardcore matches were insanely fun
Anyone know what hes up to, or if theres a remote possibility? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck frank rising on blackest friday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of the challenges really fucking screwed me. Im so pissed off right now. I eventually did them all, only to get to the final winery. One hit kill bullshit fucked me up and o ran out of time.


Never playing it again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ok this is getting stupid now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 10:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No new info on not a hero. Im really itching to play more RE7. I will be so disappointed if its a short dlc . As much as i enjoyed banned footage, i hope this is a good few hours.

I heard that the outsourced company didnt do a job capcom was happy with. Does anyone have links about that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone reading the wwe comics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 10:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After years of terrible efforts, these new comics are actually solid . They stay in kayfabe and embrace the comic book side of wrestling which may come off as goofy on tv. Even if you arent really into comics, give them a try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [no spoilers] mass effect andromeda really won me over </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 04:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a really really rough opening few hours. The meaningless tasks felt too much like busy work, and the new crew didnt seem interesting. I hated the vaults too.

But i persevered. And though the opening hurt it overall, by the end i was excited for the future again. The loyalty missions and story from landing on harval onwards really caught my interest.

I dont know if the developers read this stuff. I know it was probably discouraging for them when intially it was kinda crapped on. But as people got more into it, it seems like me they ended up loving mass effect all over again.

I never would have thought during first few hours id be singing the games praises. But once i dropped the meanial tasks and focused on story and loyalty missions, the game really became more like classic mass effect and i truly hope we get more in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Brood appreciation thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 04:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the Brood. Gangrel was poorly used, but loved him too. Best entrance ever. Blood bath.

Lost boys is one of my favourite movies so these guys were right up my street.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bray wyatt wanted to bring Gangrel into the wyatts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anyone else get the action figures? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im so in love with this show. I picked up most of the figures aside from dorian grey. Makes me sad we never got to finish the monsters with Dracula :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wwe 2k ps4 players. Wanna make a community? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like we can add friends, organise tournaments, etc.

Would anyone here be interested? Would be nice to have a decent community of fellow wreddit ps4 players </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [no spoilers]improvements for next game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would you like to see improved?

For me the key phrase is less is more. There were too many meaningless fetch quests that really slowed the game down untill i decided just to focus on main missions and loyalty. Some side missions were worth it but usually added some story to it, not simply "place five hundred beacons" or checklist quests.

My game go so much more enjoyable focusing more on the meaningful side quests as well as the main.

Of course some of the animation and human graphics could use work too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even if you never read comics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just had to say even if you dont usually read comics, give the penny dreadful ones a try. IMO they really nail the show as well as they possibly can. Great writing and art. You can tell they put a lot of effort into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best chant use ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rewatching the roman braun segment, i didnt notice untill today the "you deserve it" chant aimed at a battered roman on the stretcher. 

I completely cracked up. It was the best use of a chant ever, especially such a usually overused chant.

The sad thing is. Wwe are gonna squander strowman at the alter of roman lames.  Youd think anyone remotely creative would see the reaction and go with it, but wwe stubbornly pushes it down our throat anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MEA Spoilers]After 11 hours, I finally started to love the game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a very very slow and rough opening few hours. I felt .and still feel there were too many useless fetch quests and menial tasks. But around Haral mission, and the start of the loyalty missions, i REALLY got into it.

It really felt from that point that it was like the old mass effect. The writing really got much stronger. I ended up loving the new crew. Some truly hilarious moments.

I felt the first few hours really tested my patience and i would have quit had i not been so invested in the series. Im glad i didnt because it really really blossomed into something great. The opening hurts it but it made a magnificent comeback </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> anyone notice the mass effect andromeda prometheus influences? Spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished it yesterday. After a slow, very slow and tedious opening few hours, i really got into and enjoyed the game a lot. 

I noticed too, a lot of the heavy influence of prometheus. Maybe its just me but i noticed similar themes. For example

A mysterious creator race who all seem to be wiped out that seeded the galaxy with life

The kett ship designs and armour seems very HR Gigerish

The exaltation process using genetic modification to mutate species like the black goo in prometheus

The kett take on genetics of species they exhault, much like xenomorphs take on the traits of their hosts.

Some of the landscapes are very similar to the planet in prometheus

Maybe its just me? But i thought overall it was really cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MEA Spoilers]Mass Effect andromeda prometheus influence? Mild Spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished it yesterday. After a slow, very slow and tedious opening few hours, i really got into and enjoyed the game a lot.
I noticed too, a lot of the heavy influence of prometheus. Maybe its just me but i noticed similar themes. For example

A mysterious creator race who all seem to be wiped out that seeded the galaxy with life

The kett ship designs and armour seems very HR giger esque

The exaltation process using genetic modification to mutate species like the black goo in prometheus

The kett take on genetics of species they exhault, much like xenomorphs take on the traits of their hosts.

Some of the landscapes are very similar to the planet in prometheus
Maybe its just me? But i thought overall it was really cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass Effect andromeda prometheus influence? Mild Spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After 11 hours, I finally started to love the game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Tom savini helped designed the Rowan sheep masks and HHH and Stephs Mania skull armour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ok I misjudged Mass Effect Andromeda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British man arrested over us gamer shot during "swatting" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Horror in wrestling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im a huge horror fan so i dig the horror elements we occasionally get. Taker, Bray, even to a lesser extent boogeyman.

Post your favourite horror style gifs and moments. 

It was super cool for me to learn tom savini designed kalistos mania mask. And john carpenter is, or was , a huge wrestling fan so thats cool for me to know.

Id love a wrestling with wregret show on this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] I hate the temple missions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In MEA. Do I have to do them to get outposts and missions? Really dont like them, so badly designed and dull. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I HATE the temple missions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congrats idiots, you all caused world war 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game sequels youd love to see but probably wont. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theres a lot of games id love sequels for that alas sadly wont ever happen.

What are some of yours? Here are my dream sequels.

A true sequel to the 2009 ghostbusters game.

Ghosthunter 2. The first is underrated, sony cambridges best imo. It still makes me sad how such a cool, creepy game was barely played and remembered.

Darkwatch 2. It was in the works and got cancelled which was a real shame.

The darkness 3 i loved the first two.

Clive barkers jericho.  Cool gameplay, great story and character design. And ugh that ending. Id kill for a sequel. Mercury steam have only improved over the years since too.

Wwe all stars 2. I loved the first, a refreshing arcade style take on too serious wrestling games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They should make ORC backwards compatible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im really itching to play it again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where is all the hype for get even? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like an interesting game doomed to faliure because its not easy to describe.

Trailer

https://youtu.be/boGPCX3TVys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally got hold of those mattel retro wwe figures! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got brock, cena and warrior and waiting on taker to arrive.

Love these figures, as someone who grew  up with the hasbro figures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom savini created an awesome mask for mania </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minecraft John Ceeeena! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 12:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rule fucking 3 is retarded </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 11:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Darkness and its sequel deserve way more love </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So is scorpio getting exclusives? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Im really struggling with Mass Effect Andromeda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not difficulty or anything, just trying to finish it. It just feels so uneventful. The big open maps really dont suit it, too many meaningless side quests and just doesnt seem to be any real plot. I wanna finish it just because its mass effect but damn its been disappointing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait for No more Heroes is killing me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God I love RE7. I cant wait for the dlc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I felt kinda bad for dracula </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know he was the bad guy so to speak. But i really do think he loved vanessa and accept her fully. He didnt need her to be anything other than what she was. He truly loved her. And when she died, he probably could have finished off the others as he was handling them easily, but it seemed to break his heart.

I dont know, does anyone else get the feeling he truly loved vanessa? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At Mania, Mizryse won </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure they lost the match. But miz looked strong and actually was quite dominant,  and super over. And cenas proposal was exactly what miz said all along. A show for the cameras.

And then the smackdown send off lol.

Miz is one of the crowning jewels of wwe. Too bad the nincompoops in charge have too big a hard on for roman lames to notice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The comic is excellent too </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will also say the comic is quite brilliant too. I just read the first trade and it really feels part of the canon and crosses over very nicely to the show.

Im really excited to see how the comic continues the show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How was Nathans Dad a bad guy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the show! And even though season three felt understandably rushed to a conclusion (i dont buy they knew it was ending then), this still bugs me.

Ethan dad wasnt a good guy. That was clear. But i at least understood why he went to the lengths he did. What ethan allowed to happen to his mother and sister was evil. That really was hard for me to reconcile with me liking him as a character... his dad may deserve what he got but his sister and mother and brother didnt.

This kinda made me actually cheer for drac a bit to be honest. He was at least honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone playing This is the Police? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Im glad I am no longer a lapsed fan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wwe was my passion as a kid. I loved it so much. Im 33 now. And around 2002 my interest died. Not that i stopped following, but i def didnt keep up as much as i should and i could miss a month or few months without caring at all.  i was a big benoit fan and that also hurt to see what happened to his poor family. I was not done but not really interested beyond i guess nostalgia of the good times.

I was also tired of bitching about wwe and disliking the product. Nothing was changing, they werent listening, so i decided to just stop watching instead of keep complaining. Its the same thing im doing now with walking dead.. its ok to have negative opinoons but when it was all i was seeing l figured its just not for me.

then i got back into it. Im still not where i used to be. I probably wont ever be. But i at least feel the love for it again. And though theres still crap creative on raw and typical ego based decisions. I found stuff to love.

I CRedit this to a few factors.

nxt. As someone who bashed hhh and still feel his ego ruined many a career and feud, he nailed this and made up for it almost. Though the booker t and rvd squashings wont ever be forgotten by me. 


Rusev , Daniel Bryan, CM Punk and the Miz are some of the performers who remind me of wrestling at its best great characters and workers

I guess im trying to say im glad i feel love for it again.

The southpaw thing imo is wrestling at its very best. Passionate performers being themselves. Ironically without wrestling, it was steepd in the history and unique traits of wrestling to be infinitely watchable.

The miz has been on fire for months. His promos are some of the best out there.

And the newer divas like charlotte and becky helped, as well as other nxt talents like finn.

So glad to be here rambling with yall! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The episode with yuri and citizen z is so underrated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know not everyone likes z but i always found him likable. The episode with yuri ("what is wrong with dog") is honestly such an underrated episode. The sense something is off and not right is powerful and the twist executed excellently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Athletic women with muscle: would you ever date a fat dude? If not/so, why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Athletic women with muscle: would you ever date a fat dude? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is arizona sunshine still coming? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not heard anything about it in a while for psvr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love this game but have zero idea about the story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I wish there were a full campaign or remastered original KF for ps4 because i dont get it.

Are the zeds flesh eaters? Is it a virus? Can people turn? How are there infinite clones?

So many cool things i love but its not even touched even in audio diaries or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are miz and maryse the heels again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. Not only are they hilarious, we know cena and nikki have sabotaged careers. Alex riley for one.  And miz has a point, inthe gm is related to these two so there goes impartiality. If this were a regular show, surely the people telling the truth who havent hurt others would be the heroes?

Yet its obviously gonna lead to a loss. And cena will propose. Which ironically is exactly the point miz made in the parody, where the cameras have to be on.

Miz is a true gem and should get more respect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Problems unlocking trophies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so on ps4 ive twice gathered all collectibles on nuked, no joy.

Anyone else having issues? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was this game a sales success? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 10:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope so, it was genuinely one of my favourite games this gen and the following improved and expanded it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I admit i only like the lords of shadow trilogy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not saying the originals are bad. I always loved the concept, but i wanted a big sweeping gothic epic story and never felt anything delivered untill the lords of shadow trilogy, which are some of my favourite games.

People say it didnt feel like old cvs. I cant say because ive barely played them. But i loved it.

I am a huge horror and dracula fan so it was nice to get three titles in the series.

Any other fans of this sub series of cv? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I prefer fear to walking dead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im a huge zombie fan. I found that walking dead has become stale. Recycled plot, and just the zombies are not a threat and basically soap opera window dressing. I just barely can be bothered to watch any more.

Fear is flawed. But i like that the zombies are still a threat. I also like the different settings and scenarios. The mexico setting was quite special. 

I only wish this series had been more focused on mankinds fall, instead of rushing it completely. And into delving into the zombie virus and epidemic itself. I know they didnt want to , but at this point, i think they should. Because no one has ever showed much interest in it or even been that startled that hey the dead are coming to life. And i find that a bit jarring. I sure as hell would wanna know whats up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My experience in 2012 with a medium </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posted this in paranormal too


Ive had a few, most not convincing at all.

In 2011 my beloved mother died. We were very close. I was devestated. But ive always been undecided on god, afterlife, etc. I never dismissed the ideas but cant say i ever believed. 

There have been a few mediums ive seen. Most were meh,
But one was able to tell me a lot of different things, including my brothers job, my mothers initials, and medical problems a friend of mine was going thru, all without me saying a word. She insisted i didnt say much untill she told me so as not to influence her. I still to this day cant figure out how she did it, and im very aware of cold reading techniques.

What surprised me is she was in an unassuming little stall in a shopping center. There was no big hurrah about her. And she had hundreds of letters, all i different handwriting, pinned to her wall of people she helped. 

Anyone have any convincing encounters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone had any good encounters with mediums? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive had a few, most not convincing at all.

But one was able to tell me a lot of different things, including my brothers job, my mothers initials, and medical problems a friend of mine was going thru, all without me saying a word. She insisted i didnt say much untill she told me so as not to influence her. I still to this day cant figure out how she did it, and im very aware of cold reading techniques.

Anyone have any convincing encounters? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else collect wrestling figures? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep im a nerd.

I used to have all the wwe hasbro figures as a kid. Collected jakks till around 2002 when my passion for wrestling waned. I always followed it, but for a few years my interest was minimal

Few years ago i picked up some mattel figures and was pretty impressed. I dont buy many , especially as its hard to get newer releases in my area. But still go out of my way for certain figures such as bret The GOAT hart.

It especially gave me a kick to see they recently made a hasbro homage retro series which i hope will come to uk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huge zombie and z nation fan! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 14:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imo its far more entertaining than walking dead. That show is a soap opera and zombies are basically window dressing. Z nation does so many cool things with the genre.

Im really happy to see other people who love the show. I wish there were more merchandise like figures.

Also murphy is amazing! Im glad they didnt make him a bad guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whatever happened to the overkill walking dead game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ok i just saw a gameplay designer for Bioware racist tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know this is a stupid question but does science completely dismiss an idea of the afterlife? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats this south paw wrassling thing about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 15:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone fill me in ? And not in the paige way


Ive heard about it but dont really know much about it.  I am not as in the loop as i used to be with wrestling though im still a fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brad and xavier = best tag team ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 15:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Games on paper you should have loved...but didnt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which games are out there that you personally felt you should have loved, but didnt? Not even outright hated. Maybe just felt like you should like them more than you do. Elements on paper that took your fancy and seemed up your street but for some reason didnt fully grab you.


Mine.

Bloodborne. I love the asthetics. i love the horror. I love the concept of hunting monsters. But ....i didnt love the game. I am not someone who seeks hard games out. I prefer a good story and fun time. And as much as i appreciated elements of the game, it didnt win me over. I dont have he patience for it which is a shame as its well made for what it tries to do. Apply this to the dark souls series too.

Dishonored games. Solid games. Finished both. But yet...both have things i love. The world, the graphics. The design are all gorgeous. I love the whole rat plague setting. The intrigue, the supernatural. But i felt the game, as someone who played agressively, tried to force a stealth tone. It wasnt really as much of a choice as they made out. I mean you could be agressive but felt like you were being punished for it, especially with the high chaos bad endings.

Both how to survives, im a huge zombie nut. I like mild survival mechanics. But i found both games very mediocre. It takes a lot for me to not bother finishing a game but i couldnt finish the sequel. The first was frustraiting for random difficulty curve.

these are all games that on paper were perfect for me. So i feel a bit sad they didnt work out that way for me.

You guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain Umbrella Corps and the mangas new lore? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played the game and hated it so didnt bother finishing campaign. I cant bring myself to play it again.

I also am not a fan of manga. I tried to read it but reading backwards irks me. Can someone explain heavenly island and masahawa desire to me and how they are linked into canon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am i the only one that loved the followings endings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see them get hated on a lot. I especially like the "bad" ending because it opens up story possibilities and is also in keeping with the zombie film traditions its inspired by. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this coming to consoles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a console only gamer this looks awesome. You got yourself a buy if it ever gets ported </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i love Sir Patrick and Ginger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 18:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this sub, Im a huge fan of Sir Patrick and have always been. And seeing his love for Ginger has been heartwarming. I suffer major depression but every time I see these updates it warms my heart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why didnt we get a sequel to clive barkers jericho? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theres many games i felt deserved sequels. But only a few still to this day bother me.

One of those is clive Barkers jericho.

Im a horror fanatic. Ironically though never been a huge barker fan. But i loved this game. I thought it had refreshing mechanics for a shooter. Such as telekenetic sniper. 

The story (apart from a super lame ending) was really cool. Really nice alternate hellish versions of history as levels. ANd i really liked the characters. Two dying at the end surprised the hell out of me.

I really thought there was huge potential for a series.

Mercury steam also went on to do the castlevania lords of shadow games which i love. But ill always have a soft spot for jericho too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lets talk Enslaved </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Horizon reminds me of underrated gem Enslaved Oddessy to the West </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your thoughts on audio diaries and collectibles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot can be pointless, like the feathers and flags in assassins creed.

But some can add real value to world building and telling stories in a universe.

Horizon Zero Dawns is a recent great example. They were all thematically linked to the worlds history. The view points especially i found very moving as one mans personal story as the world crumbled.

Ive always dug Resident Evils files too, especially itch tasty.  And dead island was another game i felt did it well with postcards, audio files, diaries. Etc.

Whats your general attitude? Do you collect them? What are some of your favourites? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Killing Floor 2 getting further DLC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 19:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved this game. But i notice its not had any dlc at all. Is it going to get any more?

It reminds me of left 4 dead. I would have loved a full campaign, it seems like they have a lot of lore for it but nowhere in the actual campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Killing floor 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 03:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your favourite xbox original games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 11:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved Buffy The Vampire Slayer. I was a huge fan and actually brought my xbox for that game. The collective were a damn fine developer. Shame they never finished the Harker game they were working on. The sequel was fine too .

There were plenty of others. Call of cthulhu has one of the most tense sections in games ive ever played.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone remember ps2 game Ghosthunter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 11:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forgotten games: Clive Barkers Jericho </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am i the only one who HATES the souls style games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a shame to me because i LOVE the asthetics. I love the monster designs.

I have tried all threee dark souls and bloodborne. I really wanted to like them especially as im a huge fan of horror.  But i found them so frustraiting. I just dont find it fun to die over and over and loss any progress i make.

I honestly dont see why they couldnt add an easy mode. People would still get the hard mode they love, but a mode with modified damage and hp for monsters for people who just want to enjoy the lore and world.

Its a shame to me because these are games i SHOULD love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The stamina system needs work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 03:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are genuinely great movie games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 21:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First post here!

I know movie games get a bad wrap and mostly rightfully so.

But there are some great ones.  Someone brought up the warriors and king kong, both really good games.

X men origins wolverine unleashed was brilliant too. Better than the movie its based on and a truly true to character game.

I actually thought the Van helsing game was pretty damn solid, and the constantine game.


Theres a lot of movie games i really enjoyed. Your thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You guys ever play the 2009 wolverine game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 03:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was awesome. R rated as hell. I cant help but think a sequel based on the comic old man logan would be great.  Ironically enough years before the DOFP movie, it had scenes set in days of future past universe.

Great boss battles too. Even a few references to Hulk with the WENDIGO gamma radiated enemies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lets talk 10-8 rounds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bisping and Bravo get into heated argument </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 04:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dana to Woodley "you aren't a money fight, shut up and fight" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hero Bisping trash talks GSP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 09:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are we allowed to buy sell trade in this forum? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im a huge collector but that old collector problem has come up. Space. I have to get rid of a lot of old stuff and have no real idea how to do it.   Are we allowed to in this forum? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What we become, a danish zombie movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 08:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys! Long time lurker. Im a huge horror fan and wanted to contribute.

I love monsters and zombies in particular. This is a really good movie. Its a slow burn but the creeping dread in the background of the story of a situation spiralling out of control really adds to the horror. And the zombies are actually a threat.

I really reccomend giivng it a watch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I loved the Order 1886 and would love a sequel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know i might get downvoted but i did. I know it was too short, and sadly there was a lack of content but i loved what was there. There just wasnt enough of it. It felt like it ended a third of the way into a deeper story.
Loved the world and concept. Much like penny dreadful a favourite show of mine.
I really would love a sequel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i loved the order 1886 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> State of Decay is the most underrated exclusive ever IMO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that game.  Im both a horror and zombie fanatic and that game and the expansions for me were close to a perfect experience for a zombie apocalypse. A narrative with more depth is all i could ask for more.

I feel it gets unfairly forgotten or dismissed when talks of exclusives come up. To me its worth its weight in gold and despite the rough edges the experience of it is proof of gameplay and design overcoming technical shortcomings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A guy asking for a female opinion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else dying for Castlevania Lords of Shadow trilogy on BC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never cared about the old CVS to be honest. I found them too dated and wasted a really cool concept . But the lords of shadow reboot blew me away and is in my book a classic. Id love  to be able to replay the trilogy on my xbone. Anyone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any ideas about the virus? Potential [spoiler] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there anything known about the harran virus or its origins?

Closest we get is, as far as i remember, in the following. At the dam we see the mother and her group in a flashback ingesting the chemicals that slowly turn you into a sentient volatile. Is it possible the dam was the outbreak starting point?  Was it a viral weapon?

Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cant beat EMD or Main House 2 on jacks 55th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 12:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GSP is a coward </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 09:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hello fellow MMA fans! New here, long time lurker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This sub loves GSP too much. Conor was right about him being fake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
