<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3274</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally just went on to destroy the skull crushas, and it worked. The AI seems to be afraid when you have more units than them and they don't even bother attacking you when your troops are wounded. 

So raise some more units and go destroy the orks so you don't have to stay in couronne for 20 turns, I see it as a trial by fire : if you manage to pull it off you're off a great start (and it's a game you can always try and try again if you don't succeed the first time) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They work really well with your men at arms IMO. What I do is that I group my peasant archers, my men at arms and my grail reliquae together on a high position (with the lord and a damsel of life or beast if I have one in this army), and the trebuchets behind.

That way your peasant units won't flee because of the leadership bonus provided by the grail reliquae and the damsel. 

The grail reliquae are really only here so you are ensured your peasants won't run away when they're attacked by the enemy, which happens way too often to my liking. 

Then I just charge them from behind with my OP grail Knights and usually the enemy disband under a minute, unit by unit, charge after charge.

The grail reliquae also isn't bad at fighting, but I prefer keeping him safe, only sending him to fight if an enemy unit managed to pass my wall of men at arms.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm happy for your mom and siblings (and you) that you did this. Remember, your father (and grandfather) have lost the battle. If they really molested and abused your family, there is no chance they're going to escape the law. 

It is sad to see cases like that, but I'm happy you did the right choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6.5/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
