<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2423</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trust me, I'm a dolphin. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 06:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Progressive really like Popstar's CMZ scenes or what? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 20:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by doing something courageous. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 06:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone been able to access their Middle Class Scholarship on MyCSULB yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 17:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw on webgrants4students.org that I got awarded the Middle Class Scholarship nearly a month ago, yet it hasn't show up on MyCSULB yet for me to accept it. I'm probably going to need to hit up the Financial Aid office at some point this week, but I figured I'd ask around here first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kether Donohue explains Lindsays violent outburst on Youre The Worst </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hayden Christensen Joining Bruce Willis in 'First Kill' (Exclusive) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 04:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Flairpost]Why isn't there any flair for the Dumpster? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 18:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NOW SHIPPING! Uncharted 4 7" Scale Action Figure Ultimate Nathan Drake NECA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 03:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now shipping! Uncharted 4 7" Scale Action Figure Ultimate Nathan Drake NECA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 03:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black-ish, Season 2 on iTunes FREE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 15:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has the Middle Class Scholarship shown up on MyCSULB for anyone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 05:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw that I was awarded the scholarship at webgrants4students.org on 8/5/16, but it hasn't shown up on MyCSULB.

Wondering if it's because I only need the Fall Semester to graduate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sausage Party Orgy Scene (WTF) [1280x720] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 03:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FUCK! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 06:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always see what I want, crystal clear, in my minds eye, but I can never actualize it! It's so incredibly frustrating, that there is a disconnect between seeing something in your head, and get the desired effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a stand that will work with Marvel Legends Venom? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 23:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have one of the SH figuarts stands but Venom appears to be too big for it. Is there a better stand that will help me achieve a web swinging pose? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   _  Stranger Things Take My Energy   _  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 22:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix picks 'Stranger Things' scene for first 360-degree video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 22:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So how about that Stranger Things? Good Show, huh? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 05:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you guys think it's a good show too? It does 80s nostalgia right, has a wicked score, and it shows Hollywood that reboots blow, new stuff can do 80s nostalgia too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we get a moratorium on all these "Stranger Things reboots, Hollywood, 80s, nostalgia, gets it right" articles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 23:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is no new Book release. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 05:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Obliviate!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Er, is there a higher resolution image of this poster? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 02:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is their an HD image of the poster that comes with the Target Exclusive release of The Cursed Child? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 02:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title says it all.

I'd like to use it as a desktop/iPhone wallpaper, but I can't find it online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Marvel Legends Venom being repacked into new cases? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 15:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw it pop up on Amazon. I added it in my cart, but it was sold out, by the time the screen loaded to show me my cart. Note this was actually Amazon selling it, not a 3rd party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Naughty Dog, your matchmaking is a load of shit right now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 23:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been stuck in matchmaking 20 minutes with the same people in the lobby. I find people and the match loads to 97-98% and then nothing. Fix this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone been able to find an image of NECA's Nathan Drake figure from Uncharted? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 22:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the figure is at SDCC because I've seen images of the box, and a  rather useless wide shot of their Video Game case, but I have not been able to find one close up of the production figure itself. Curious to see how well the normal head sculpt turned out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hot Toys TFA Luke Skywalker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 23:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hot Toys TFA Luke Skywalker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 23:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hot Toys Teases TFA Luke Skywalker- Full Reveal at Comic-Con! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 06:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hot Toys Teases TFA Luke Skywalker- Full Reveal at Comic-Con! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 06:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boombox (ft. Julian Casablancas) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 20:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else having trouble staying connected today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 22:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the servers acting up or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Spider-Man: Homecoming' Adds 'Nice Guys' Breakout Angourie Rice (Exclusive) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 06:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Mildly Related] Star Wars 8 wraps shooting in July. Mark Hamill out of Job. Perhaps Time for Flash, unless Barry fucks up timeline again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 06:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else That doesn't Care About the DLC Relic Shenanigans? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 01:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already got my favorite characters in the series with the base game, and I don't really care for the vanity items or the guns much, since I'm very proficient with the MPWhatever(the gun in my flair). I'd much rather ND gouge the shit out of those things than hide maps behind paywalls like they used to.

Also, anyone see the new map lately? I only played it twice Wednesday, and I've never seen it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone notice that Comedy Central never airs the Andy Samberg/ St. Vicnent episode? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 21:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that episode under some weird contractual stuff that prevents it from being syndicated?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tried buying the DLC Vanity Chest and I Got Boned. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 22:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got stuck on a Please Wait loading screen that wasn't going anywhere after 10 minutes, so I closed the game, opened it back up, now I lost over 6,300 relics, because all it says is "Connecting..." where the relics are supposed to be, and I can't access the store because I get a bunch of loading pinwheels where the pictures letting you know what you're buying are supposed to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need 3 units to graduate. Any easy, fun, classes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 05:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking about doing Intro to Acting, but seeing as that's filling up, I'm starting to think that I'm going to be screwed out of taking that thanks to the absurdly long wait for 2nd round enrollment, and I was hoping I could get a back up class lined up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hot Toys: Han and Chewbacca (The Force Awakens) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 00:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been rereading the novels again, and I'm loving it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 06:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It feels like I'm visiting old friends again, and it makes me happy to see them again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Amazon always lower the price on something after you get it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 19:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just bought a few Lego sets that I've been eyeing the other day that have maintained the same price point for ages, and just yesterday, they dropped in price. This isn't the first time it's happened and it's starting to get super irritating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Run, Barry, Run! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 22:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> gg Gg ggG GgGg GgG G gggg gg ggg ggg ggG Gggg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 04:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Does Sanders honestly still have a chance at being President? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 04:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ggG GGG ggGg gfG GgGg GgG GgGG GGG ggG gGg ggg g gGgg ggGg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 02:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> gg Gg ggG GgGg GgG G gggg gg ggg ggg ggG Gggg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 07:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> quack quack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 07:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Popstar Never Stop Never Stopping- I'm a Weirdo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 06:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Strokes single tomorrow! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 02:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else ALWAYS on the losing team? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 20:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get put up on the losing time so often my Win/Loss ration is 0.4. I'm not even a bad player, too. Often, I'm the one carrying the team. Sorry, just had to vent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bishop Briggs - River [Indie] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 05:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hot Toys Yoda 1/6 Scale Figure- $199.99 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 05:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What can I do with a film degree with a specialization in screenwriting, if I'm never able to get my scripts sold? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 06:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to be graduating from school by the end of December this year, and lately I've been having serious doubts in my writing abilities. I was wondering if anyone here had any experience with this sort of thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PS3s Helped Resist Samaritan! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 02:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a stunning move, PS3s have been utilized to help keep the Machine on life support, harkening back to the days the US Air Force used them to build a super computer. What a time to be alive! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone had their hits approved by Work Skills First, Inc.? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 03:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did all 5 of their long tedious hits last week and they still haven't approved them. Really looking forward to those ~$40. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else living in fear that DC will cancel this show so that us simple folk won't be confused by having 2 different Flashes at the same time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 22:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In The Terminator, what Sarah Connor did to the Terminator was pretty messed up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 00:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, think about it, the guy was just doing his job, right? Would you lead a pizza delivery guy around the city, while he is trying to give you your pizza, only to crush him in a factory? No, because the pizza delivery guy is doing his job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hot Toys Stormtrooper Finn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 12:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The Walking Dead might be the most popular show on television. But at one point, it was something better than that." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 00:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just saw the main guy pussy out of asking the main chick out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 06:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why isn't Darrel Hammond a part of the main cast? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 20:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's probably gotten more screen time than Sasheer Zamata has gotten all season long. He also appears literally every other episode these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tame Impala - The Less I Know The Better [Psychedelic Pop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 01:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This sub is dead go fuck yourself reddit. I'm hanging up my moderating cowl. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 21:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone suggest an easy capstone for a film major? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 06:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except for Film and Music, since I already took that. Currently got FEA 486 Alt. Media, but I've been reading that that class is a major drag so I'd like to switch that out.

I'm going into my final semester so I have to find a final capstone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This subreddit is about everything that we want it to be and more. Do not defy us. We will go on a power trip and ban thee! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 04:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Come to us brothers! Welcome to jekstroem and my VALHALLA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 23:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Robin is a generous creator! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you guys like reading Shakespeare? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 07:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite one is the one with the twins and the boat at the beginning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gwen Stefani - Hollaback Girl (Dirty Version) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 07:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NEW STROKES SINGLE! "Give it up" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 06:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if Hartley is actually Eobard Thawne? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 03:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if Barry's meddling in the past, changed time so that somehow Thawne managed to kill Hartley and use that future doohickey to become Hartley? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know what the deal is with iBooks and Batman Vol.8: Superheavy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 04:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So a while ago, I pre-ordered Superheavy part 1 from iBooks, and now it appears to have been pulled from the iBooks/iTunes store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is reddit in love with describing everything as a "gem"/"hidden gem?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 05:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (   ) What's Your Unpopular Opinion? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 20:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are you guys aware that Amazon has been price gouging on some figures? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 02:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was on Amazon yesterday, and noticed that they had Resistance Outfit Rey and Han Solo available, only to find that they had set the price north of $15. 

This was Amazon, not a third party seller that was being fulfilled by Amazon.

Just wanted to offer a heads up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump fucking blows. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 00:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else get an email to complete a mandatory sexual assault class? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 00:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else having trouble buying Batman Vol.8: Superheavy from iBooks/iTunes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 19:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had mine pre-ordered, but when I try to download it, it tells me it's not available in the US store. It was supposed to be released digitally today, and it's nowhere to be found. I cancelled my pre-order so I wouldn't be charged for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else having an issue trying to buy Batman Vol. 8 on iBooks/iTunes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 16:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had mine pre-ordered, but when I try to download it, it tells me it's not available in the US store. It was supposed to be released digitally today, and it's nowhere to be found. I cancelled my pre-order so I wouldn't be charged for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All the spoilers have really only confirmed my suspicions. This movie is going to blow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 01:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indiana Jones 5 Officially Announced With Harrison Ford and Steven Spielberg Returning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 19:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Images from new SA 3.75" Wave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 02:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://forum.rebelscum.com/t1126709-2/#post19776072  - Captain Phasma

http://forum.rebelscum.com/t1127293/#post19776076   - Leia (D'Qar)


http://forum.rebelscum.com/t1127292/#post19776074  - Han Solo (Starkiller Base)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Touchscreen on iPad mini 3 not working! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 07:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've tried doing everything I can think of to fix this. I turned it off by holding the home and power buttons, I tried updating it to the latest firmware by doing a hard reset via iTunes, and then I tried restoring it to factory settings via iTunes when that failed. I've tried each of these things multiple times and nothing seems to work. Has anyone here ever encountered this issue? How did you solve it? Is the Genius Bar my only hope?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iPad mini 2 unresponsive touch screen help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 23:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, so my brother's iPad mini 3 (sorry just notice the touch ID bezel) has an unresponsive touch screen. I've already tried holding the power and home buttons together multiple times and that's not working. I can't do a reboot because my brother in his infinite wisdom, never connect the iPad to the iMac, so the devices don't trust each other. Any other tips? Or are we just going to have to wait until the battery dies on this relatively new iPad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I read Harry Potter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 00:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been a lifelong fan of the movies, and I've been wondering if I should give this book reading thing a shot. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A dank meme has died tonight. Good night sweet prince. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 05:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feeling pretty crummy so I decided to order SH Figuarts Obi-Wan! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 06:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I'm really grateful for Amazon Prime's same day shipping! I should be getting it tomorrow! Now I've got to bust out my Black Series Darth Maul. I hope they are in scale with each other, I really don't feel like forking over $70 for another 6 inch Maul.

I'm really grateful for Amazon Prime's same day shipping! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think Amy Poehler is hot. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 21:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I've got a little crush on her thanks to old SNL reruns on Comedy Central, and Parks and Rec.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone gotten their Crowdsurf bonus this week? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 01:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They mentioned something about it being delayed, and that we would receive it by midnight on Tuesday. Tuesday's come and gone, and still nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NECA on Twitter: "FIRST LOOK at the Uncharted 4 Nathan Drake action figure coming in late Spring. Retail pre-orders go live today! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 21:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crowdsurf has been slow this week right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 00:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very slow week for me, and it doesn't help that I've got classes starting up these past few weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to believe: This is the son of Scully and Mulder, because the moral of this story is you can't trust the system! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 06:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorry, but I have to ask: Has facebook started showing when people are online? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 06:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorry, stoners: Chuck Lorre is developing The Big Bang Theory of weed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 04:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bongzinga! Chuck Lorre Presents His "Pot is funny and that's the only joke" Sitcom! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 02:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ahmed Best as Jar-Jar Binks Doing the Taken Phone Call Monologue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 02:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> But um, anyone, you know, hate, um, those, you know know, um verbatim, uh, you know, Crowdsurf, uh, hits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 03:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really hate these verbatim crowdsurf hits. I have like no motivation to do these when I keep having to back track to add in an um, or repeated word. It takes me so much longer to finish their hits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Box Office: 'Star Wars: The Force Awakens' Opens to Record $238M for Cosmic $517M Global Launch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 18:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Forget: Donald Trump Wants to Bang His Daughter - The Daily Show with Trevor Noah Video Clip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 18:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Inside Out suffer from the Nolanization of America? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 19:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All the deaths in this show could have been avoided... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 06:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to see more dumpsters saving people on this show. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 05:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I ran into my old high school crush today. How do I play it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 04:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I ran into my high school crush today at school. We've got some history together. We were friends in high school and things ended sort of awkwardly when I confessed my love for her (cringe) towards the last few weeks of school. We've texted before, and I always got the impression I was annoying her so I stopped a bit after that. Now three years later, I see her sitting alone, studying. She sees me too, and I go to her. We talk for about half an hour before I need to get to class, and it seems like we're both enjoying each other's company. I've got her phone number, but I'm terrible at texting, and I'm hesitant to make any romantic advances based on how things went last time. So how do I play it r/askmen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where is the guy who has three ways with his brother? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 07:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw you on tonight's episode of Nathan For You! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Tasteful Transformation, With Dubya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 06:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tasteful Mouth Movement, With Dubya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 06:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Tasteful Lunch, with Dubya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 06:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tasteful Sax Man with Dubya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 06:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Tasteful Toothbrush, with Dubya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 06:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dodging tastefully, with Dubya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 06:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Catching Pokemon Tastefully, with Dubya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 06:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dancing Tastefully, With Dubya Dubya 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 06:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dancing Tastefully, with Dubya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 06:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Winking Tastefully, With Dubya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 06:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by going to class. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 00:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> stupid movie watch link for class dumbass </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 22:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Walking Dead might pull some serious bullshit, keep [REDACTED] alive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 18:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skywalker Family the Focus of the New Trilogy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 22:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I thought it was supposed to get better! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 21:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started Mturking this passed August, and I was pulling in about 90-100 each week. I kept hearing how it was supposed to improve once schools got back for the fall semester. Well, were balls deep into September, and it's actually gotten worse for me. Each week I earned less and less, and I was just wondering if it really is going to get better. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Apple remove the ability to drag and drop music to your device on iTunes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 23:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't been able to do this with all my up to date tech since around the time they launched Apple Music.

It's a real fucking inconvenience too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Cringe] Who thought this was a good idea? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 23:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I shadowbanned? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 03:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Amazon going to be a part of Force Friday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 05:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
