<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3240</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 19:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10 years old, won a Chef Boyardee stuffed pig from the school cafeteria raffle. You were entered any time you bought school lunch, and since I ate the school lunch everyday, I had pretty good chances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 19:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Independence. As a kid, I HATED going to public school and being told what to do. I know why things have to be that way (10 year old me would probably have not made good decisions), but it was so annoying for me. The moment I graduated and turned 18, I was like a whole new person. I got to choose when and what classes I took, I no longer had a curfew, and I had a job in which I earned my own money. Even now, despite having taxes and car payments and rent and having to work a lot, I would choose being an adult with personal freedom over being a teenager stuck in a controlling system any day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 08:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be yourself, just don't curse or talk about politics. At least, that's my advice to any guy I bring over to meet my parents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 08:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makeup, this stuff is expensive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 19:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little late to the party, but for my 10th birthday my mom gave me an address book. I'm only 20 now so address books were basically obsolete by that point, but I still used it a little bit. My senior year of high school, my drama class did a Secret Santa. I watched everyone get cool gifts. Someone in the class names James got two gifts for some reason. My name is Jane. I never got a gift. Someone misread their paper slip and got James 2 gifts. My teacher felt so bad that she dug through her whole office and handed me a huge package of unopened nilla wafers and a funky pen. I appreciated my teacher a lot
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 01:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coldplay is my favorite band and I feel this in my soul. I remember when MX came out and telling my friends they sold out. Even though I liked it, it wasn't /them/ you know? I hated Ghost Stories ngl, most boring album, and everything else is radio filler anymore :'( I know the lyrics to every song they made before that album and I couldn't even tell you 3 songs on Ghost Stories despite owning the CD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FT: Arceus LF: Diancie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 00:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [event6] Hi so I have literally never ever used Reddit before in my life and I've only perused it maybe like 5 times so I'm sorry if this post is not in compliance with your rules, I read them all so I'm doing my best ;-;

I'm a casual player and I just really want Diancie because I think they're cute and I missed the event, but I have an extra Arceus since I have one in each game (Omega Ruby and Y). I don't care about IVs or stats or any of that stuff but I can give you all that info for what I have if you want it.

OT (for both of them): GT
ID No. (both): 08016

Stats in Y: 276, 276, 267, 254, 276 Nature: Bashful
Stats in Omega Ruby: 269, 276,276,255, 256 Nature: Serious

Both, of course, come with the same moves which if you don't already know them are Judgment, Recover, Hyper Beam, and Perish Song.

Okay well hope this is all done right, if not, sorry, just a regular girl wanting a cute Pokemon to feed Pokepuffs to (///A///) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
