<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1369</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When was the last time America's freedom was sincerely threatened by a foreign military power?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-28 21:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today being memorial day I have seen multiple facebook statuses and tweets thanking the US troops for protecting our freedom. Does the taliban threaten American freedoms? Did the Iraqi's threaten our freedoms? Did the Vietnamesse even threaten our freedoms? How can so many people believe that we need such a powerful military to protect freedoms that aren't threatened?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the difference between American teenage girls and Muslim teenage girls? (offensive be warned) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-27 05:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One lives in America, the other lives in Pakistan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did BoubleO and Guude meet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-26 02:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering how this famous bromace began. Looking through BdoubleO's videos I can't seem to find an explanation. Could anyone link a video explaining how they met?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My suggestion for future UHC seasons  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-21 01:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The next season of Ultra Hardcore could introduce sponsoring. Viewers could pay to send items to certain players. Items could include food or weapons. This money could be used to donate to a charity, like Childs Play. There should obviously be a limit on donations to decrease some popular players from getting too over powered. 

Doing this could liven up the series while donating money to a good cause. 

I'd love to hear your input! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb! (Or any other Minecraft coder)! Could you please explain how hunger truly works! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-16 21:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In light of Etho's [video](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xn6RbDL5bBE feature=g-u-u) on hunger it has become evident that we really do not know how the hunger system works. As an important aspect of the game, enlightenment is undoubtedly neccesary. 

Please Jeb, Dinnerbone, Jon, or even Notch could you please explain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/Mindcrack, you are feeding the trolls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-13 20:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently there has been much talk about the situation with Etho. That needs to stop immediately. By voting a [post](http://www.reddit.com/r/mindcrack/comments/tkhus/my_thoughts_on_the_situation_with_etho/) to the top and flooding it with comments you have given the trolls what they desire the most, attention. 

We are making the situation worse. 

To avoid further conflict I argue that we must ignore trolls who post any aspects of any Mindcracker's personal life. I call for no more comments, posts, or any talk related to this controversial topic. 

We must look towards the actions of Etho as guidance. His decision to stop comments on the episode in which he explained his profession is proof that he would like that particular discussion to end. Let us all follow his lead.

Right now I believe the future of this subreddit hangs in the balance. To ensure its continuation we must reject this unrelated information and continue to focus on what is important, the submission of community based content and discussion on mindcrack events only. 

Please take into account the consequences of your comments and posts, continuing to give attention to certain issues will ultimately lead to the degradation of this community.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neil deGrasse Tyson  EDIT: sorry, didn't realize this was a repost </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-11 23:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I found my Grandfather's yearbook from 1954, I thought you all would be interested  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-08 22:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Docm77 - Episode 87: Learning To Count </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-07 23:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CIA thwarts new al-Qaida underwear bomb plot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-07 22:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some great series that have been completed and are available for marathon viewing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-06 22:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am looking for some great shows that have completed their entire run through and are available for marathon watching. Netflix or HboGo ready series are preferred! 

P.S. Here are some of the shows I have gone through and loved: 

The Sopranos, The Wire, Battlestar Galactica, The West Wing, The Larry Sanders Show, Monk, The Civil War </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are Reddit's thoughts on the legalization of polygamy?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-04 00:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a community with a fairly large liberal base that is made up of young people its easy to see how gay marriage is widely accepted here. 

That got me thinking, one of the major arguments for gay marriage is that government should not dictate love, should that not include polygamy? 

Can anyone present a valid argument for or against polygamy?

(Devil's advocates welcome!)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favorite Sea of Flame OOG moment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-03 19:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never fishing again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-29 05:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IAMA Request- Someone who has used the Miss Travel service </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-25 04:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could be either an "Attractive Traveler" or a "Generous Traveler."

Link to the site: http://www.misstravel.com/

Video description that was on the front page: http://vimeo.com/40110285

1. Why did you decide to use the service?

2. What did you think would happen on the trip?

3. How much is MissTravel involved in the actual trip? (Did they charge a fee? Do they ask for travel updates?)

4. What did you think of your travel mate?

5. Would you recommend MissTravel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw this on r/spices, thought it would fit in great here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-18 05:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My girl, touching my balls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-18 02:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CAN YOU USE SILK TOUCH ON IRON ORE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-16 02:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PLZZ HELP! DOES SILK TOUCH PICK AXE WORK ON IRON ORE?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone knows the water hole is the place to be </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-15 19:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In honor of the new server I present to you my Ladder Wars Arena  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-15 18:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Ladder Wars Arena  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-15 18:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tips for a visitor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-09 22:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High Schooler here. I'm currently visiting and am wondering what to see and where to go. What should my self guided tour consist of? Suggestions for lesser know places would great as well. Also if you have any Blacksburg restraunt suggestions please tell. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favorite quote from tonight's episode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-09 03:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do people still use this site when 9gag is so awesome? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-01 07:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Santorum signs legislation banning all porn  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-01 06:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two days after the House passed the updated American Decency Act President Rick Santorum fulfills his campaign pledge to rid the US of all pornography.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A man was seen pointing a weapon at Hanover schools  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-28 23:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 : How does The Onion get away with blatantly lying in their articles?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-14 22:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand they are a satirical organization but does Rick Santorum not take an issue with [this?](http://www.theonion.com/articles/rick-santorum-relieved-no-one-has-asked-him-about,27630/) 

Couldn't he sue for libel and easily win? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This November Vote Joseph Kony for President! #Kony2012  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-07 02:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just kidding, he stands no chance against Ron Paul. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Civil War Alternate History </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-26 16:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this thread we will discuss alternate outcomes of the American Civil War. How would the South go about winning? How would the course of the war be different if major battles were won by the other side? Could the Confederacy last as an independent nation? How would the world be different?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> War with Iran?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-26 02:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As military tensions rise between the US and Israel (and their allies) what do you think the possibility of a war with Iran is? How do you think a war would impact the globe?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you be interested in a new Subreddit dedicated to intriguing conversations?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-26 02:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its called [Reddit Talk](http://www.reddit.com/r/RedditTalk/). Its a new Subreddit focusing on interesting conversations. 

I was inspired to create it after stumbling upon specific comment threads that were having interesting conversations, or "talks" about specific subjects.

This new community will make it easier for Redditors to have acces to and freely contribute to conversations that interest them. 

Reddit Talk does not limit thread topics but instead allows for anyone to create a new post with the intent of having a thought provoking conversation. 

So what do you think? Please suggest any ideas!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do you see Reddit in 10 years?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-26 01:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The internet moves at a lightning pace. In the span of 10 years we will most likely see a lot, popular websites may fall, new ones may rise. In your opinion what do you think the future holds for Reddit?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit Talk: A Place to engage in any type of conversation  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-25 22:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Discussion Threads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-25 22:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In almost every comment section I seem to come in contact with the conversation seems to be full of wit and intrigue. The sad fact is that those conversations are normally lost and receive little recognition. 

A remedy to this is a proposal for a new sub-reddit dedicated to conversations. This would be different to AskReddit in that the purpose of the thread would be to discuss varying topics. For example: How WWI directly led to WWII, NASA's future, The history of China, etc. 

I believe Reddit users are keen and would love to take part in highbrow discussions without the corruption of karma desperate posts. 

Here is the new subreddit: [r/RedditTalk](http://www.reddit.com/r/RedditTalk/)

Feel free to start a new conversation. 

EDIT: Does anyone know how I could spread the word on the new subreddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would happen if the South were to "rise" again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-20 23:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine a Second American Civil War, the South secedes and there would be a new Confederate States of America! What would occur?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Villager Logic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-20 22:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am unfriending anyone who likes these posts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-17 02:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attack of the soap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 01:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMA Request: Stephen King </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-14 21:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets make this happen [/r/stephenking](/r/stephenking) 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/Minecraft upholds its rule banning [FIXED] posts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-13 21:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
[An Update on Our [FIXED] Submission Removal Trial](http://www.reddit.com/r/Minecraft/comments/pnm1o/an_update_on_our_fixed_submission_removal_trial/)

The Moderators of [/r/Minecraft](/r/Minecraft) believe this is best for their community. The rule states that no [FIXED] posts or other submissions should reference another within 24 hours of the other being posted. 

What do you think about this? Should more subreddits do it? Should the members of the subreddit be allowed to vote on this change? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE think that a community run subreddit should be allowed to vote on rules governing the community?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-13 20:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This question is in regards to [this](http://www.reddit.com/r/Minecraft/comments/pnm1o/an_update_on_our_fixed_submission_removal_trial/) new post reaffirming the rule that bans [FIXED] posts. 

How does [/r/Minecraft](/r/Minecraft) feel about requiring rule changes like this to be put to a vote! After all Minecraft is one of the most community oriented games ever made and we should not restrict the aspects of community especially in a community created subreddit!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legalizing rape is linked to lower rates of rape | e! Science News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-12 20:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't argue with science!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Reddit so mean? Seriously, why do so many popular posts have so many downvotes?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-11 03:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Example Time! 

1) [This post](http://www.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/pjufw/im_a_chemistry_teacher_and_im_moving_at_the_end/) has almost 13,000 upvotes but more than 10,000 downvotes!

That means 10,000 people went out of their way to show their distaste! 

2) [This post](http://www.reddit.com/r/AdviceAnimals/comments/pk3qq/prepare_for_your_world_to_be_rocked/) manages to get 6,000 upvotes and 4,404 downvotes!

How is this possible? Why is the difference between the upvotes and downvotes so slim? Can so many people dislike popular things so much or is half of Reddit made up of spiteful 9gagers and 4chaners? 

There is no other voting system I know where this happens! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My campaign posters for the Junior class presidency  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-11 01:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What local advertisement annoys you to no end? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-08 01:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me its The Auto Connection's ads. 

Heres an example:

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uTSa4cbcDHY

Every time this plays I want to neuter the dog.

So Reddit, give your local businesses some help by letting us all laugh at their attempts. 


**BONUS:** Here are more for your enjoyment! 

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fi9yp17jDX4 feature=related

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UK7dKMyRreo list=UUrydJK_-IxH2Kl6gUHigQlw index=29 feature=plcp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your most downvoted post or comment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-07 23:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit, what has been your most downvoted post or comment? It could be a serious argument that wasn't well received or just a terrible joke that went over poorly. 

I'll share mine:

http://www.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/nfpgj/people_are_actually_googling_on_the_google/c38rbuc

I still support my argument, even though it completely wiped out my comment karma. 

EDIT: My comment, that received -400 karma, appears to have been deleted so here it is: 

**Origina post**: 

http://www.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/nfpgj/people_are_actually_googling_on_the_google/

**My comment**:

Lol, this dude!

http://i.imgur.com/kJN0c.png 

http://www.facebook.com/olafurw?sk=wall

I was just making a point that to black out your name in a photo of a Facebook post, that is a public page, doesn't make a lot of sense. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix Success at its finest  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-07 01:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please don't shoot up Jesus with heroin  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-01 03:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Persecution  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-29 21:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scumbag Captcha  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-29 19:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bestiality may be a sin, but it sure is fun to watch!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-29 00:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMA Request: A Convict Who Was Spared From the Death Penalty After New Evidence Surfaced or a Successful Appeal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-26 04:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For every 10,000 Upvotes the mods or r/theredditor will give me an iPad 2. Screw the system and make this happen! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-25 02:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a [link](http://www.reddit.com/r/theredditor/comments/ov5ws/the_redditor_challenge_1/) to the [/r/theredditor](/r/theredditor) post. 

The Redditor is a downloadable magazine focusing on cool reddit posts, its actually pretty awesome but the iPad 2 is cooler so give me the upvotes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Al Capone's "luxurious" cell at Eastern State Penitentiary  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-25 01:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A women and child jump from a burning building to save their lives </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-24 22:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/pickle if you do not return the banana hostages I will chop you up into little pieces, fry you, and then eat you with a side of ranch dressing!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-23 01:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/pickle if you do not return the banana hostages I will chop you up into little pieces, fry you, and then eat you with a side of ranch dressing!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-23 00:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the worst act of procrastination you regret the most?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-20 21:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently sitting in class and the block has been dedicated to mid term studing. I have managed to get a hold of a lap top and found my way onto reddit. 

Right now *I could be* studing with my peers to prepare for what is sure to be a difficult test but instead I am asking you this question: 

What is the worst act of procrastination you regret the most?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An articulate argument for SOPA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-18 02:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My reaction after stumbling upon the r/pickle and r/banana war </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-17 02:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its physically impossible to UPVOTE this! Here, try!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-15 20:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Downtown Bangor, Maine [340 x 225] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-15 18:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Battleship Potemkin (1925) [836  1200] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-14 18:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New r/circlejerk feature gives you karma for upvoting!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-11 02:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I demand to be a mod, the people want it! Listen to their screams! Do you hear it? Do you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blackout! Black! Black! Black! Black! Black! Black! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-11 02:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Whiteout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout!Blackout! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unintended Blackout Consequence   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-11 01:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that there are 17 million living descendants of Genghis Khan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-10 05:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: A Brief History of China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-09 22:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did it begin, who were the leaders, what important events happened? Please explain in chronological order.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You hear, a soft hum, glass shattering, a baby cry out, a dove sing. But you ask yourself where is the coconut? WHERE IS THE COCONUT! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 23:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: The Cold War separation of Germany  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-08 20:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So after World War Two Germany was spilt into East and West Germany, who did this and why? I also know that Berlin, which is in East Germany, was spilt into East and West Germany. Why? What did the US (and its allies) and Russia (and its allies) attempt to gain from doing this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Maine related books are crucial to understanding the state?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-06 04:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know of Henry David Thoreau's The Maine Woods, but what other books are there that give a great portrayal of Maine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I hate the two party system!"  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-04 02:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible for a Presidential candidate to run for Congress while also running for the Presidency?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 23:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are you at home on Reddit on New Year's Eve? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-01 04:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] [TV SHOW] Premium cable show that centered around a teenager working at an ice cream stand  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-01 03:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe it broadcasted during the early 2000s. It might have been a show created for a younger audience but I think it was on HBO or another premium cable channel. I believe the premise revolved around the life of a teen working at an ice cream stand in a smallish town. Does anyone have any idea what this show was, or did I just make it up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christmas dinner conversations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-27 00:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wikipedia Faces </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-24 22:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "well, whats the fourth worst day of your life" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-22 04:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scumbag 9GAG </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-21 22:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They have a plan and they want OUR help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-21 02:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Celebration of CaptainCrimson's Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-20 05:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you may have heard the great CaptainCrimson has died, murdered by evil men. 

As a tribute to his succes there will be a celebration of his life at **SPAWN** at 4:00 pm Eastern Standard Time. All are invited to attend! 

Anyone who was inspired by CaptainCrimson should speak on his behalf. His closest comrades will be giving the Eulogy. 

Spread the word far and near!

EDIT: THIS IS A PVP PROTECTED AREA

EDIT 2: THIS EVENT IS NOW ON DECEMBER 20, 4:00 PM EASTERN STANDARD TIME

EDIT 3: THE CHURCH HAS BEEN REMOVED SO THIS WILL NOW TAKE PLACE AT SPAWN! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ken Burns on his famous "Ken Burns Effect"  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-20 03:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AT T kills T-Mobile merger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-19 23:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kim Jong Il </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-19 04:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Racist Christmas?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-18 22:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, I was raided!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-12 02:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unimpressed Slave hates oppression  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-11 23:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Third World Success </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-11 18:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Philosophy Poem, look closely  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-05 23:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Cheap Alternative  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-05 02:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Successful Black Man gets a promotion  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-05 02:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lincoln (2012 film) on set photos of White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-05 01:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This question keeps me up at night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-04 06:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've never been more intimidated by a pop-up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-30 01:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Come play with me, big Sis!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-28 23:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Personification is a Bitch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-28 04:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting Black to our "Roots" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-28 00:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's get r/treepics back to its roots! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-27 22:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Hiss of the Creeper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-16 21:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> G? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-16 00:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is G? 

When you really start to think about it and analyze the importance of G you will soon realize, we are all G. 

I'm G.

You're G.

Everything is G.

G is not just an understanding of the universe but a structure that embodies everything that has ever and will ever occur.

G is G.

G  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manipulating Mother's BFF </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-12 18:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manipulating Mother gets a divorce </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-11 23:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manipulating Mother causes nightmares </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-11 22:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Introducing Manipulating Mother </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-11 03:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that there is an African American English dialect known as "Ebonics" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-11 02:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tech Impaired Duck puts the punchline in the title </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-09 00:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ordinary Muslim Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-08 02:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not Again! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-07 05:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A god that barks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-07 04:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Annoying facebook girl doesn't understand sentence structure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-07 04:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scumbag Captcha  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-07 01:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rick is a Nazi? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-06 19:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It makes captivity fun! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-06 03:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Princess Hamster  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-06 03:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please leash your Rabbits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-06 03:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE Think a large scale Los Santos is beter than three smaller unrealistic cities?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-05 20:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe a larger, more to scale Los Santos will be much more realistic. I mean think about it, larger mountains, bigger airports, taller buildings. What do you guys think?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If only they would RSVP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-01 03:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fountain Drink Rage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-25 02:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pale Blue Dot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-24 23:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forever Alone just wants to be honest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-23 21:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditor's Wife doesn't understand that it's just a Jersey Thing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-23 20:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Technology Impaired Duck doesn't change the fonts default size </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-23 05:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Most Interesting Man in the World tries some pasta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-23 05:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fancy Crab joins the protesters  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-22 06:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As long as you're okay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-20 05:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Annoying facebook girl can die now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-18 05:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forever Alone's wife hates facebook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-09 05:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new sub-reddit to discuss how alternate historical events could have changed our world. /r/WhatCouldHaveBeen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-08 23:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would the world be different if Nazi Germany had won World War ll? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-08 22:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How far would Nazi control go? Would the Cold War have happened? Would major events unfold differently, and if so, how? The questions are virtually endless. 

Tell me what you think! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> XBOX Live 99 Percenters  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-01 20:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I see you! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-20 01:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My First Rage Comic, complete with a misspelling.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-18 07:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
