<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2777</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 23:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Voting for Solitary Confinement and Form of the Dragon on the same day is EPIC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 10:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nirkana Revenant is a good card, but she's not Superman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 02:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Good luck finding  (Coldsnap) Snow Covered Mountains"--alternate reality Kevin Mackie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 02:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they get 2 extra life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 02:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dealers at Frank and Son in SoCal used to sell the packs for $2 and the individual basics for $1. Source: memory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 01:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I want purple Swamps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 12:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remembering what 7 times 8 is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 12:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blockade Runner vs Courier Hawk: am I voting for who does that pose better?

Never mind, Heat Shimmer did it best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 23:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hence my use of the word "could". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 22:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I thought that part was pretty intuitive. You have a deck, you buy a "booster" pack that could contain cards to strengthen (or "boost") your deck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 21:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoulda went with "breastplate stretcher". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 01:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the power is always X, so it'd be a X/X-1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 14:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was little I asked my older cousin what it meant to take something for "granite". We were outside and he told me look at the sidewalk, there's granite all around. It means you don't appreciate something because there's so much of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I especially like that your Mox Pearl is the only white-bordered one. Fitting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> !!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eldrazi Displacer.

Also, Disfigure really gets bricked by Pendlehaven and Gitaxian Probe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, it depends on what is meant by "2". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If my 241 undoes your 241, is that a 24141?

Also, doesn't that just simplify to a 141? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inb4 "False Defeat defeats Defeat" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, "Shock and Shatter" is a phrase I often say while casting Kolaghans Command. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 18:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was not advocating for four Decays, merely reminding op it's a possibility. They gave three reasons why they might prefer BG over Jund--I was trying to point out that one didn't really count (imo). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 10:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe  he played a mirror with Bread Nelson too, I wish we could've seen that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 10:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man some of you guys go all out. I don't even have matching versions of all the cards. For example: two regular Lilianas, one signed, and one RPTQ promo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 09:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stock Jund plays two Decays I would say. So you cut two cards for the other two Decays. That means you are cutting two red cards at most--I wouldn't say that's reason to cut the whole color. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 09:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, you are allowed to play 4 Abrupt Decay in Jund. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 21:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 21:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 13:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor Zodiac Pig, we hardly knew ye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 13:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few years ago I read an article (maybe on Star City) about a variant format where you only use 4 cards. My friends and I talk about it from time to time and I'd like to read the article again--I have no idea what it was called, nor do I remember who wrote it. Does anyone know what I'm talking about? Thanks.

I think one of the example decks was: White Chancellor, Black Lotus, Lab Maniac, Gitaxian Probe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 06:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That deathtouch cop though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 06:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask for the full 100% prizing for first and second. The intangible of the invite is worth enough to a lot of people that they'll accept. I literally saw this happen a couple months ago. First place got "just" the invite and second place got about 300 store credit.

At the PPTQ I won neither my opponent or myself cared about anything but the invite and we both wanted to get the other to concede gor all yhe prizes. We ended up playing where first got the invite and second got all the prizes (about 200 credit).

Also, the possibility of running into someone that doesn't care about the invite in the finals is just one reason to not split before the Top 8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 14:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In before Lotus vs Jet round one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 10:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maindeck graveyard hate isn't  unreasonable. Merfolk won GPLA in may with a Relic in the 60.

http://mtgtop8.com/event?e=12485 d=271903 f=MO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 09:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently had three Cages but no pressure. They just Life from the Loamed a bunch a Grave Trolled me to death. I switched to Leyline after that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 04:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Derp, for some reason I kept thinking of MM2013 as M13 as oppossed to MMA. I'm just reading this like "what the heck was in that core set to make the packs so valuable." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 22:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should only play durdely decks that, you know, do nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 00:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait for Island vs Snow-Covered Island. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 10:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys, I'm really torn! Should I vote for Wanderguard Sentry or Sokenzan Bruiser? Please advise.

Edit: Seriously though, this is a ton of fun so far.

Shatter vs Gruul Keyrune? Well, one destroys the other.

Two cards I don't know? Which has better art?

Zodiac Pig? My god, this thing is adorable. Anyone who votes for Hunted Phantasm is a monster! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 00:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wanted a "changeling" land with every land type. So it would tap for any color, be fetchable, give Domain, but also power up Tron and Post. It even has a built-in drawback that it can't be bounced to Rith's Grove. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know on the old version you could basically play solitaire. Is that still possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 23:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally I can implement my Mai Valentine strategy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 09:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is double triple like a triple-double? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
