<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 04:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you park your car in Harvard Yard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that happier students get higher grades </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 15:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 16:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk to your primary care physician, who can give you a referral to someone near you who is accepting new patients. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Juror 83 Is First Tsarnaev Juror To Speak About Trial Experience, Death Penalty Decision </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 16:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Juror 83 Is First Tsarnaev Juror To Speak About Trial Experience, Death Penalty Decision </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 16:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Uber Driver In Boston Held Without Bail On Sex Assault Charge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 20:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 20:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife works at [Psychological Care Associates](http://psycare.info/), a large practice with offices in Stoneham, Chelmsford, and Woburn.  They are competent, accept insurance, have a large staff so you won't have to wait a long time, and have psychiatrists on staff so that if your therapists recommends looking into medication, you won't have to go looking.

If you have a physician, they will usually know therapists in your area who are competent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 02:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I like Meritage at the Boston Harbor Hotel.  A bit old school fancy, with a great view of the water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is any of this crap yours? Lots of stuff emerges after the giant snow pile melts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 02:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 17:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is /u/lilsarg complying with the [/r/boston rules for journalists](https://www.reddit.com/r/boston/comments/2psvoc/journalists_of_rboston_please_read_this/)? Sure doesn't look like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boston.com hires a couple of adults to run the place, and "become one of the most powerful storytelling entities in the country" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 17:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How 'The Hobbit: The Battle of Five Armies' betrays Tolkien's Christian themes - and his religious fans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 14:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 14:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to [BostonGlobe.com](http://www.bostonglobe.com), which is a serious news site run by journalists at the Globe, and not by a [Harvard MBA](https://twitter.com/murraytheman) with no media experience.  And as pointed out elsewhere on the thread, just browse it in an incognito window and you won't hit the paywall.  

Or consider it like a kickstarter and throw in a few bucks to subscribe to make sure you don't get stuck with only Boston.com. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inmate sues prison for not allowing him to worship Satan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 19:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maybe Pope Francis isnt after a lurch to the left; he has nominated conservatives to a key theological commission </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 14:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Religion losing public influence, Americans not happy about it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 18:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great insight from unsung hero David Ross </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 01:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 22:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It says "no title found" and doesn't suggest anything.

Having a og:title tag for Facebook is pretty much standard these days.  So it shouldn't mess up Reddit - I've submitted plenty of other links that had both tags and had no problem with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does reddit check for the title? Anyone else find that their stories won't suggest a title properly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 20:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I try to submit stuff to Reddit, and click the "Suggest Title" button, it often doesn't work.  Sometimes it does.  The pages have title and og:title tags.  Any idea why this would happen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
