<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject366</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 06:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing about finding people to test is that I require honesty, so typically I ask close friends and people I know professionally.  I respect the opinion of a small number of very experienced people over 100 noobs.  In fact, the reviews of most vibrators are almost all 5 stars.  It isn't hard to give a mediocre vibrator a great review if it is your first one.  Vibrators are like bacon, even a bad one is still pretty great.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 06:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, 

I would like to get on the calendar on Tuesday April 23rd at 9:30 PM EST.  I will stay on for two hours to try to answer all of the questions.  

My proof is located here:
http://www.priveco.com/tomnarpresis.html

You can see the second paragraph discusses my planned AMA.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMA - Vibrators.com and ShopInPrivate.com CEO Tom Nardone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to take so long to reply. I am new to Reddit and didn't figure it out.
In our office, it would be no big deal.  It can be difficult to find a company that will work with you though because some folks are afraid to put adult products into their work environment.  We had a difficult time finding a company to make us lollipops for Bachelorette.com.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to take so long to reply. I am new to Reddit and didn't figure it out.

There is a company that makes wood toys, but I'm not a fan of the material because it can harbor bacteria.  They are called Nob Essence (nob, ha!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to take so long to reply. I am new to Reddit and didn't figure it out.
I've met the folks at TSX, they are very nice people who understand that most of what they make is novelty items. They are really sweet people though.  I've know about Bad-Dragon but I have never met anyone from the company.  Their site creeps me out a little bit and I'm pretty thick-skinned.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for writing.  Women do much of the sculpting.  Most I've worked with are not supermodels.  They use the protoypes to make production molds.  It isn't really as sexy as it sounds.  Most new items aren't really ground breaking.  There are thousands of different products in the marketplace.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll see if we can encode a better quality one.  Thanks for the compliment and the advice.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to take so long to reply. I am new to Reddit and didn't figure it out.

I'll try to answer it all:
Yes. 
Yes.
There are many wireless toys on the market.  There is even one that sells on our site for less than $20.  http://www.vibrators.com/waterproof-remote-control-bullet.html
None of them have any security measures built in.  I'm not sure the customer cares.  What harm would it cause if one of them were hacked?  Drained batteries?
There are trade shows were manufacturers meet with retailers, etc.  
It is a weird business.  It is sorta fun too.  Thanks for asking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to take so long to reply. I am new to Reddit and didn't figure it out.

I am going to schedule an AMA soon.  I'm still sorta figuring it all out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to take so long to reply. I am new to Reddit and didn't figure it out.

I'm more of a vibrationist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to take so long to reply. I am new to Reddit and didn't figure it out.

Bad-Dragon.com is sure an interesting company.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to take so long to reply. I am new to Reddit and didn't figure it out.

The designs end up fairly easy to smooth out.  Also, as the printer resolutions get better, the same digital design will produce a smoother product.  

Thanks for writing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to take so long to reply. I am new to Reddit and didn't figure it out.

There is no way out of this business.  Once you entered our industry, you could never find work anywhere else.  You would do better to try to get experience elsewhere and then enter the adult products business as the boss of a company.  

I hope that is good advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to take so long to reply. I am new to Reddit and didn't figure it out.

I started an online store that sold embarrassing drugstore items in 1998.  ShopInPrivate.com launched about 6 months prior to any other online drugstores and was sorta successful.  We promised total privacy and people used that privacy to buy sex toys.  Soon thereafter Drugstore.com, CVS.com and Walgreens.com launched and we had to make money, so we were happy to privately sell sex toys.  Eventually we acquired the Vibrators.com business and we also own Bachelorette.com (bachelorette party supplies).  

My bio is here: 
http://www.priveco.com/tomnarpresis.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to take so long to reply. I am new to Reddit and didn't figure it out.

They do, although I don't think they are a major player in the industry.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the offer.  Sorry I took so long to reply.  I wasn't up to speed on Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apologize for taking so long to reply.  You are very welcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, I apologize for taking a long time to answer you question. Here goes..

Dildos are generally thicker than vibrators because dildos are purchased to feel penetration.  Women (and men) who want vibration don't usually need the thickness.  There are exceptions to this, but in general dildos are sold thicker and with deeper ridges than vibes.  

It sounds like you might actually enjoy a realistic vibrator more.  http://www.vibrators.com/real.html  Personally, I don't understand why people don't buy more vibrators and fewer dildos, but you some folks like the term dildo, like person who started this thread.  He could have called it Vibrator Engineer.

Finally, Silicone is the current material of choice for well-researched individuals due to its lack of porosity and ease of keeping sanitary.  

They make a couple of squirting dildos.  
http://www.vibrators.com/squirtingdildo.html

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, I apologize for taking a long time to answer you question. Here goes

This is me:  If I were lying, I would pick someone more handsome.  http://www.priveco.com/tomnarpresis.html

tom@priveco.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, I apologize for taking a long time to answer you question. Here goes

Most toys are still sculpted in clay and then cast from there.  Sometimes they use a live person, but even those molds are worked over, especially the female ones.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 05:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, I apologize for taking a long time to answer you question.  Here goes:

I think the industry is shrinking away from highly controllable motors because the customer has largely ignored them.  Customers don't seem to enjoy a large number of functions, nor programability.  Also, when using an adult toy, there is very little way to see what you are doing.  The controls need to be operable blind.  Companies are moving back toward keeping it simple and i think we will find a continued push toward this.  

Companies like Smitten Kitten and other boutique retailers are more a reaction of the changing gender of the buyers over the last 20 years.  Women now buy the toys and they aren't afraid to spend a large amount on them.  Retailers with a female bent have sprouted up to fill the need.  

I'm not aware of any wireless standards for the wireless toys.  I suspect that the manufacturers of such just piggyback off of some other existing technologies.  I suppose we will continue to see that in the future.  I doubt anyone will find some great need in sex toys which will require a unified wireless standard.  Mostly, they are just turned on and off.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-30 06:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IAMA Dildo/Vibrators Engineer.  My name is Tom Nardone and I run subject366 Inc.  We own and operate Vibrators.com.  In the past I worked for Sikorsky Aircraft a helicopter company as well as Ford Motor Company.  You can find out more about me at subject366.com.  Here are your answers:
1.  Most dildo molds have been around a while.  Early ones were usually cast from clay sculptures, but some were made from famous dudes' junk.  These days prototypes are done on 3D printers and then the molds are made from there.
2.  I usually don't lead with my profession, but I don't lie about it either. It doesn't hurt that I own the company, so I've been fairly successful.  It would be tough to explain why I did what I do if it didn't pay well.
3.  Dildos and vibrators materials have come a long way.  Silicone is really popular these days because it is the safest materials, but dildos are made from latex rubber, elastomers, glass, pyrex, ABS plastic, wood, stainless steel.  You name it.
4.  There is a company out there called TSX (I believe) that makes all sorts of animal dildos and stuff.  They make the weirdest things I've ever seen.  Giant stuff like horse dongs.  
5.  Dildo designers usually do pocket pussies and artificial vaginas as well.  Fleshlight is one brand of those.  

What does the future hold?  We are all working with 3D printers to do prototypes now, and when they are available in peoples' homes, I imagine that people will print their own sex toys.  MakerLove.com is a project that a couple of people are working on to provide free dildo designs for your 3D printer.  

There you go.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
