<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject398</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I own the domain name "Iflinch.com", nothing there yet, what should I use it for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 05:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 04:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't bother me a bit if the other guy doesn't use theirs, nope, not a single fuck given, so I don't always use mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 03:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 62 yr old male here, haven't cried in years. Yesterday at around 10 am I had the privileged to help with my daughter's home birth. The little guy got stuck for a while and I cried when the mid wife freed him and out he popped. Cried from joy and relief. Both Mom and baby are doing fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 02:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you, but I'll take another Grandson and the experience over gold any day. :-) Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 00:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it's been more like 36 hours but I got to participate in my daughter's home birth. 9lb 2oz boy named Lennon. Everyone is is doing fine. I'm a 62yr old man and I cried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 13:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Annnnddd... I was earning $1.65 an hour working in chemical plant at the time. My weeks take home pay was right around $50.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 01:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NICE! I learned something today, thanks. Proves one is never to old to learn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 01:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking Kilmer always causing trouble with his muddled speech. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 00:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A huckle is the handle of a coffin and to bear is to carry. So the Lunger is saying he would gladly help carry Ringo to his grave. The line makes more sense when you know old south slang. I'm not smart I just happen to be old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 00:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Annnd... they are wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 00:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The line is "I'll be your huckle bearer." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 14:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The link = http://redd.it/23ulai </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's going to be very disturbing, I know it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 14:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 15:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always ask "Why?" to everything, everyone and yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 14:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Puppy Breath </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 03:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is worth a lot. Thanks for sharing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 03:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Dad isn't always the sperm donor. So... Was your Dad your Dad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 03:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know how that goes. I had 2 extra nipples and so does my oldest son and his 2 boys and my daughter's son has one also. My Dad didn't have any... I am not his. My second son didn't have any... He's not mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was your Dad your Dad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 03:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 15:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, It is surprising how many Grandmas were "tramps". My maternal Grandma had her first kid at 13 years old to a carny who was in town for a week. He (my Grandpa) went back, did the "right thing" and they had 7 kids in all. That is why I'm here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 15:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started to figured it out in high school. I looked and acted like my dad's best friend and his kids, who were my best friends. The genes gave it away then I asked my last remaining Aunt on my Dad's side and my Uncle on my Mom's side after my parents had passed away. Both confirmed it. This story gets really weird if I tell the whole thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 05:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Dad had this happen to him 62 years ago today... It was me. Not sure he ever knew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 13:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My son owns a glassblowing studio in Kent, Ohio (The Missing Piece) with 6 full time torch workers. He and the other more experienced workers have helped train quite a few Glass workers in the last year and 3 of them have recently went full time in the studio. All 3 started out a few months ago knowing nothing about the art. One of the best compliments the other glass blowers will give a novice is "You suck... Again." Meaning you have learned the tecs and improved to a point where you can get better. So, you suck... Again. Keep going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 02:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How big is it? Wish there was some size reference... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
