<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3750</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 02:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, the comments have put a shadow of a doubt in my mind, since im extremely sceptical </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 15:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Perks Of Being A Wallflower
Have no idea why but that movie did something to me and i cried for hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 15:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last ping pong match with his dad killed me, especially because my dad died when i was 6 and wouldnt say goodbye to me cause he couldnt cope with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 15:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am i the only one who instantly remembers Top Gear and Clarkson warning the other two about Honey Badgers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 14:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stopped playing back in 2012, and i was never tremendously talented. I know how to tune string by using the above ones, but i cant tune the E wire first because my sound perception and hearing is shit cause i didnt care about playing then and now i just want to learn a few simple songs with basic cords. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 02:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Turkey has never bowed to anyone, never conquered by anyone? You just fucking said the allies were everywhere.Your strongest presence was the ottoman empire, from the 10 century and forwards, before that you could have been and were conquered by anyone who wanted to, its just they didnt want to. Ottoman empire was strong but doesnt change the fact that you terrorized the people in a ridiculous manner, raping stealing etc. Your main army was strong, but the other parts of it and your other population were peasants. You were the last nation to get rid of the Feudal system, back in the 19th century, which was the base of your country. And you know what the feudal system revolves around? Yeap, peasants and land. You can try and braveheart your country all you want, you were peasants, acted wildly, and when you finally changed that and became a civilized country more or less, you support Erdogan to bring you back to those times. You evolved like all the other people, dont go backwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 01:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, after five years, mind you 5 years after the war ended you managed to get the allies to leave, by signing a treaty and shipping off your last sultan(rightly so). My country was under you savages for like 500 years more or less, we fought the entire time against an enemy larger than us by millions, and when we finally beat you no one said we kicked you back. And now you want Erdogan to bring back that way of living, based on terror and torture. Theres no room for wild peasants relying only on islam in the 21 century, so fuck off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 00:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading your comment you seem to think that you are defying the whole world and that nobody can touch you. First of all the coup seems to be a ploy by Erdogan, second of all he is a dictator who tries to bring the country closer to the one which it was when it was founded which is wrong, since everything evolves, you cant have a stubborn, idiotic nation in the middle of the world, set back by its laws and leaders, cause they are smallminded people with narrow understandings. And last but not least, the allies defeated and occupied Turkey, so read your history books again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 02:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats a small group of people you are close to, its like saying Kobe was considered short just cause he played with Shaq. Dont get me wrong i get your point that you are short compared to them its just this theme here is based on a larger number of people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 23:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Montenegro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 23:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, im from the balkans, no one considers 188 cm short bro... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 23:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Montenegrin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 23:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Montenegro ftw bro! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 13:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im 181cm, which is like 5'11" or something and have been called short...thats what happens when you live in a country where 6ft is an average height </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 00:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As i wrote im only 18, but imma do something in computer sciences or political studies, maybe even bussines, still have a year to decide </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 00:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ill keep that in mind thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 00:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, thats exactly the kind of answer i was looking for! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 12:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im familliar with the Visa process and all of that, my main worry is how hard it is to adjust for immigrants jobwise, finding a job in your expertise, any discrimination against immigrants (thus the orange man reference), and is the life standard as good as they say. UK is so fucking expensive and i know that first hand, plus moving there from the sunny mediterranian isnt my priority. Canada and the Aussies are my backup options, but the US is my priority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 01:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that, i liked the theme of loft though, it just suited me i think. I feel like i have to give the movie a shot to surprise me at the end, even though i wasnt interested the first part of it. For instance during my Guy Ritchie phase who is still my favourite director, i found the first 15,20 minutes of Snatch a bit dull but i endured and now i love the whole movie, although i still prefer Lock Stock which is in my top 5 of all time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 01:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If i had a good recommendation sure why not, but i tend to watch every movie i turn on in one sitting and try to finish it, so playing it safe is a good bet for me, and how i usually watch movies. Although whenever i find a foreign movie i have to be convinced to watch it but the likes of Loft (the belgian one) and Intouchables have opened my mind.Also im the kind of guy who when he finds an actor he likes or a director, watches his movies in a row until i drop dead so unless the story is very intriguing cast and possibly the director is my main guideline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 01:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first one was amazing, the second one was dreadful and the third one was decent but wasnt enough to pull the trilogy out of the hole which the second dug up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 01:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to IMDB even David Beckham is in it... But its Guy Ritchie, he could make Gary Busey fit the role of Romeo in a Romeo and Juliet action movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 00:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cast and a short description of the movie if im not already informed. I stopped watching trailers a while ago because they might make me biased towards a decision that isnt the correct one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 01:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i forgot the rice my bad.. It seems that balkan in general is linked with this dish and it originated in Serbia i think. However where im from, Montenegro we use the leaves of vinova loza, grapes used to make rakija similar to schnapps or however you spell it, its a strong alcholic drink </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 23:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blazers matched Crabbe just now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 18:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didnt say otherwise, but he is originaly from my country, since he was born there. Thats exactly what determines where are you from, your citizenship, nationality and where you live is different </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 17:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ffs relax it was a hyperbole, but i feel so shit now, and especially bad since Raonic is from my country but is playing under the canadian flag so its like a triple blow to me right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 17:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well im officially never watching tennis again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 00:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured id get a bit of a backlash from the brits but its understandable. I said could since i wasnt sure, and since when has dry humor became an excuse for having dumb moments? Its like the new sarcasm for idiots, and since i watched quite a bit of his interviews and his guest appearance on mock the week he seemed to laugh a lot and make facial expressions and comments which didnt point at dry humor such as Harrison Fords interviews.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 00:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While we are at running shots, i dont think there is a player in the world who can hit a better forehand without his feet set. And also i believe his running backhand is better than the standing one, since he always adjusts for more spin and ends up either hitting it with the frame or getting a much bigger arch, while running he hits it pretty much flat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 00:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah in the fifth, althought there was a similar in the fourth so i dont know which one do you mean,but for this i didnt believe he would get it over the net, he barely put any power on the ball just some wrist action a hit an amazing passing shot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 22:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or he could be a bit stupid sometimes... We all remember all the other players answering to the question " With what do they eat their strawberries" or something like that with the answer "cream" however Andy replied " With my fingers"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 18:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a point from Tsonga </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 18:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats why i hate it so much, Nadal and his fucking play-to-backhand strategy have scarred me, after he won the tiebreaker i thought it was gonna be 2008 and the lost fifth after an amazing tiebreaker again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 18:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear, the same, everytime he missed it i yelled "Slice it ffs" and when he pulled of that couple of amazing passing shots down the line, i was literally left speechless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 18:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am i the only one who gets anxious when Fed hits a backhand, i just dont trust that shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 17:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not always this tough rooting for Rog but today i almost died. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 17:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If youre a Fed fan, its better you didnt watch it. When it was 0-40 in the third i almost cried, and in the 4th set tiebreak i was on my knees on the floor the whole time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 15:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it funny how whenever im watching Federer win i want to play tennis again but when he loses i never want to speak of tennis again let alone watch or play it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 23:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like even now Kyrgios isnt a kid like he used to be. Yeah sure, he sometimes gets angry, but now he does it like an adult, even politely, and by politely i mean passive agressively, asks the umpire and does swear and trow hissy fits. I could be wrong tho, i didnt really watch him much this wimbledon
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 00:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today at work, after six exhausting hours of running around, and lifting stuff and shit, i literally leaped in the air and yelled "He will win his eight" when they told me Djokovic had lost, for the rest of the day i couldnt bring myself to stop smiling so if he wins it, ill probably weep aswell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
