<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1497</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cooler and denser air into the intake is always better for efficiency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's 'fascist' about it? Why can't people understand the meaning of that word? It's not hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mate showed me some Chinese two dollar coin forgeries the other day. There is literally nothing they will not (poorly) copy at someone else's expense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another islamic triumph!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. The juices 'escaping' is not a concern with any meat. Like people carrying on about 'sealing' a steak to 'retain' the juices. It's nonsense. You cannot seal a piece of meat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but it gives me gas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only in Britain. No one else would call a paki an Asian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean in muslim dominated areas anywhere in the World? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twice, you mean. I see no problem going for a third time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it needs to be leveled for a third time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But muslims are so progressive! We need more of them in Western society, for some abstract reason. Surely, this type of behaviour can't firmly be rooted in their fundamental teachings... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't pretend you don't know what I'm talking about. I'm onto you... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever had an abscess? When you do, you will learn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you talking about, FFS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shame they are so often confused with fucking muslims. Sikhs are alright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just educated yourself on muslims at the same time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd kill to get me some grits, here in Oz. They were fucking great when I was in the States. 

I like the Kool-Aid, too. But when I first tried it, I didn't realise you had to put your own sugar in. I wondered why it tasted like arse. Yeah, some of that blue shit or tropical shit would be good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're talking about Chechnya, for fuck's sake. What part of that do you not understand? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. I think I understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erm, yes, they do have conventional warheads on some of them. I'm asking how many they keep ready compared to nuclear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I got it going straight away. Didn't think it would be so easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's all race to conclusions before we find out WTF actually happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yawn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucker's got the biggest crop of ganja since Robert Trimbole. I fucking know it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say anything 'bad' and you're instantly banned, anyway. We can't have people saying what they think, after all... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you explain that a bit more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally think the immigration issue could be (should be) ever so simple - persons coming from countries most like our own get ALL the places. ALL the priorities. That would instantly preclude fucking arabs, muslims, Sudanese, Lebs, Nigerians, etc.

Let the places allocated be filled by *worthy* people. People like us. White people. There are untold numbers of those kinds of people who should be here but instead of the others, but no, we pander to the fucking bleeding hearts club. Why? It makes no social or economic sense.

We need immigration. To a certain extent. That's just a fact. What we don't need is pieces of shit coming here and turning OUR place into what they just left behind. Fuck. That. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll never say hello to you - ever again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but I still like doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as they insist on artificial sweetening, they're shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Have you seen the latest shitfight over in /r/Australia? A store owner had the hide to put up a sign outside his shop that forbade niggers of a certain type/age from entering, on account of repeated and rampant theft. There's even a video to go with it (showing said negroes) and half the people in the thread are all indignant that he should dare stand up for himself. What a fucking joke this country is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am also fucking hopeless at games. And when I set the fucking thing to easy, I really mean I want it easy. Like a walk in the park. A piece of cake. I play games mainly to just see what happens and to look at the cool graphics. Easy should mean EASY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish we could have packets like that (no warnings and shit) in Australia. I can't even remember the last time I saw such a pack that wasn't part of my collection. Shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rustic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is that stem hollow or solid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I were anywhere nearby, I would go out of my way to give him some extra business. He did nothing wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going cunt-up wasn't really a possibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. It's garbage. What is it with this minimalist crap? The World isn't a fucking IKEA store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FeF2QiwyDGM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 12:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even though it shouldn't make headlines. If whites are the ones doing the wrong thing, fucking say so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 12:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I hate shoplifters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But we have to destroy a lot of things. Fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many conventionally armed ICBMS do the US (and others) keep at the ready? I always wondered that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, bugger me. I was always told Win 8.1 wouldn't do it. Well, that certainly makes it a lot easier. Thanks again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you stop being a faggot and just fuck off? All you wanted was to start shit by being an unhelpful smartarse. And you got it. No one here cares what you think, do or say. Especially me. Why don't you find someone else to annoy with your lmgtfy crap? I got some actual answers from some non retarded people. Why are you even here? You clearly don't want to help, so kindly fuck off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free software for mounting .iso files in Win 8.1? Looking for some recommendations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 09:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was using Demon Tools but some people say it's spyware/malware. Does anyone have a favourite program they could recommend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it true that you can only get packs of 20 in the US? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 09:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dunno where I heard it but someone told me that. Any truth to that? We have packets containing many different numbers, here in Oz. 20, 25, 30, 40, 50 and other weird numbers to keep the cost of a pack at the same price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got my Witcher 3 .iso. What mounting software would you recommend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 08:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I said, I've downloaded it as an .iso but Win 8.1 does not support mounting .iso files, natively (or so I'm told). Anyone know of some reputable mounting software that isn't adware/spyware/malware?

And where do I put my save game files? I was halfway through playing it on an other PC that dies. I managed to get the save files but no idea where to put them, now. Does anyone know?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are there folders called "program files" and "program files(x86)"on Windows computers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 12:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does there have to be two of them? Isn't one enough? It seems to make absolutely no difference which one you save things to. Or am I missing something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why doesn't the search function work? I have just tried it 100 times in a row and it has failed every single time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 12:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is ridiculous. It's a fucking joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which add-on for FireFox would you recommend to stop sites autoplaying videos (except youtube)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 09:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am fucking sick of this shit. I'm sick of fucking (especially) news sites and others autoplaying things at high volume. I've used NoScript before but that ends up being more trouble than it's worth, as it disables everything.

Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here is a rubber duck floating on a fluidised bed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 09:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here is a rubber duck floating on a fluidised bed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Ubuntu 16.04] Having a problem entering the password I created to turn off UEFI secure boot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm very new to this and I have a strange problem. First, I was unable to use the apt command, due to a lock file being in place. I followed some instructions I found and after I fixed the problem, a blue screen came up that said I needed to disable secure boot. It said I had to create a password and next time the computer started up I would be asked for it.

So I make a password, restart it and the blue screen asking for my password appears. But I can't enter the password. 

It says please enter character 8, or character 4 or some other number. But when I type the password, nothing happens. Hitting enter makes it say enter another numbered character.

WTF is going on? I don't know how to enter this password. If I just keep hitting enter, it eventually says invalid character and gives me the option to continue booting or try again.

Does anyone know WTF is going on? I'm using an ASUS F555U laptop if that helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mounting an .iso file? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 14:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got the game I want but I'm not sure what to do with it. I assume I just right click -- mount? (Win 8.1). But where exactly should I put the .iso before I do that? Does it really matter? The game is Witcher 3.

Never done this before. Should I be using special mounting software or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I swear I have seen throttle bodies in a couple of diesel engines. How can that be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 14:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where I used to work we would do minor things like top up fluids and shit. I swear that on a couple of the diesel utes there was a throttle body (or what looked exactly like one). I didn't have long enough to pull it apart and inspect it though. WTF is going on? Since when does a diesel need a throttle plate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I built a gaming PC last year. Can someone tell me how good or bad it is? I don't really know what I'm doing. I just spent what I could afford at the time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 12:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm perfectly happy to hear all opinions. I just want to know where it stands in the scheme of things and more importantly, what I can do to wring the most out of it.

OK, so have the following components:

GigaByte Z170-HD3 mobo

Core i5 6600K processor

8 GB DDR4 Hyper-X Fury RAM

GeForce 960 4GB graphics card

1 TB HDD (not solid state)

40'' 1080p screen (using HDMI input)

I put it together and it all seems to work fine with Windows 8.1. I like playing Oblivion/Skyrim, Fallout 3/4/NV, Witcher 3 and the S.T.A.L.K.E.R. games.

I can set them all to maximum settings without any crashes but I wonder if I'm truly experiencing them totally maxed out. I really don't know what the frame rates are - people seem to talk about that like it's the most important thing. Is that the case?

I know my HDD is a piece of shit and I'd dearly love a solid state one but I won't buy it until I can get a reasonably good one. Obviously, more RAM wouldn't hurt.

So, am I really getting the best out of these games and what changes within the nVidia graphics card settings should I be looking at? I haven't touched any of that stuff. Dunno what half of it means.

Opinions? Other subreddits to ask my questions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't find my saves. I know where it's supposed to be but I simply can't get there </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 09:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My PC died and I had to reinstall Windows (8.1). I reinstalled SDV and created a save. Now I cannot locate it. I know it's supposed to be in appdata\roaming but I cannot find that directory. What do I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please help my tiny little brain to understand why statistical power increases the ability to reduce Type II errors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 07:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep arriving at Type I when I look at the table. I know what the answer is (increased power reduces the chance of a Type II error) but I just can't get it through my fucking head as to why that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know the hardware requirements for Mandelbulber? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 05:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just installed it on Ubuntu but I can't seem to find any references to how powerful your system needs to be. Does anyone know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's going on with VLC? I've had a number of problems with the latest version and on different devices. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, it was causing Ubuntu to freeze if the mouse was not moved enough. Now I'm having it 'freeze' (but keep playing - the picture and sound stop but the counter continues) on both Windows and Linux - with the same files.

WTF is going on? VLC used to be rock solid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would someone mind having a quick look at my terminal output with regard to not being able to use the apt command? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm havin a major problem in Ubuntu 16.04. Here is what's happening:

When I use sudo apt-get or sudo apt it says there is a lock file. I don't understand why. For example, this is what "sudo apt-get update" returns:

    E: Could not get lock /var/lib/apt/lists/lock - open (11: Resource 
    temporarily unavailable)

    E: Unable to lock directory /var/lib/apt/lists/

    E: Could not get lock /var/lib/dpkg/lock - open (11: Resource temporarily 
    unavailable)

    E: Unable to lock the administration directory (/var/lib/dpkg/), is another 
    process using it?

Nothing has so far worked. Another user, /u/_-Justin-_ has suggested a few ideas, the first being to try this command:

    sudo lsof /var/lib/dpkg/lock

So I ran that command and got the following output:

    lsof: WARNING: can't stat() fuse.gvfsd-fuse file system /run/user
    /1000/gvfs

    Output information may be incomplete.

    COMMAND  PID USER   FD   TYPE DEVICE SIZE/OFF    NODE NAME
    dpkg    2308 root    3uW  REG    8,6        0 6829072 /var/lib/dpkg/lock

I'm not sure what to make of this. He also gave some other commands but I don't know if I should run them or not. The original post is here, with the additional commands he suggests:

https://www.reddit.com/r/linux4noobs/comments/63d5mt/cannot_use_the_updateupgrade_commands_lock_file/

Does anyone know what's going on? I can't update my system at all (with my limited knowledge) and it's getting to the point where I am considering re-installing because I can't work out what to do. I want to use Linux and learn about it but I simply can't do it like this.

Is there a better place to ask about this? I don't want to annoy people but I really need this sorted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Win 8.1] Is there a way to force windows/programs/whatever to always open on the screen you are currently using? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using two screens. One big one for games and stuff and another small one for things like reddit.

If I click on (say) file explorer, I want it to open on the screen I clicked on, not the other monitor. Why it doesn't is a mystery to me. I'm constantly having to get up, got to the other monitor and drag shit back to where I want it. 

Is there any way to stop this behavior? I always, always want the window to open on the monitor I'm using, no matter what it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't get administrator privileges in on my new Win 8.1 install. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 10:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fucking ridiculous. I have never had this crap before. I just did a fresh install and I don't have administrator privileges, even though my one and only account clearly says 'administrator' next to it. I can't even save a file in program files. 

How can I change this? Nothing I've found online will work. I had full privileges before I did a reinstall and I certainly didn't have to beg for them. They were there from the start.

I need admin privileges, full stop. The system is useless to me without them.

How do I either force them on the account I have or make a new account instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm noticing that an increasing number of sites are able to 'ignore' the blocks I put on elements with uBlock plus. How can this be fixed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using the 'block element' tool. It used to be extremely effective but it's failing pretty badly of late. And it's pissing me off. I'm using FireFox.

For example, I block autoplaying videos on some site and when I reload, they are back. I disable scrolling banners and they reappear, next time I'm on that site.

How are they doing this and how can I beat them? If I don't want to see it, I don't want to fucking see it.

And are there any other appropriate subreddits to ask in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cannot use the update/upgrade commands. Lock file stopping it. I have been trying for a week, now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have posted about this before and the issue is still not resolved. I simply cannot use sudo apt-get update or sudo apt full-upgrade. I continually get the message:

    E: Could not get lock /var/lib/apt/lists/lock - open (11: Resource 
    temporarily unavailable)

    E: Unable to lock directory /var/lib/apt/lists/

    E: Could not get lock /var/lib/dpkg/lock - open (11: Resource temporarily 
    unavailable)

    E: Unable to lock the administration directory (/var/lib/dpkg/), is another 
    process using it?

I have tried various methods with regard to removing the lock file (I don't understand WTF I'm doing, anyway) and nothing will work. This is getting extremely annoying. 

Ubuntu 16.04
    
     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to follow some instructions I found with regard to a 'lock' file. Would like to ask some questions before proceeding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 12:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I try and do sudo apt full-upgrade I get an error:

    E: Could not get lock /var/lib/dpkg/lock - open (11: Resource temporarily   
    unavailable)

    E: Unable to lock the administration directory (/var/lib/dpkg/), is another 
    process using it?

So there is some problem with a lock file. I dunno what that even is. But I can work it out later. So, I found a page where this guy has the exact same error. I want to follow what he did but I have a few questions.

Firstly, why does his terminal user name start with:

    root@kali:~#

What is the ~# stuff? Mine starts with ~$. Why is that and does it make any difference?

Secondly, he says he enters the command:

    rm /var/lib/dpkg/

And gets an output of listed files. When I do that, it just says:

    '/var/lib/dpkg/': Is a directory

No lists and nothing happens. I thought rm means remove?

When I copy his next instruction:

    rm /var/lib/dpkg/lock

It does indeed ask me if I want to remove it:

    rm: remove write-protected regular empty file '/var/lib/dpkg/lock'?

So should I go through with this? Not knowing what that file is is worrying me. I'm terrified of fucking things up. I can't afford that right now.

So, what is this file, why is it in use, why is it write protected and am I safe to remove it? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I use the "assistive technologies" route to upgrade Windows 8.1 to 10, will it ask for a product key? Because I have no idea what or where that key is </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 10:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got my computer as is, with 8.1 on it. No idea if it is legitimate, or otherwise (although I have not seen any warnings or anything like that). I have no idea how to tell.

I want to upgrade, using the assistive technologies loophole. But if I try that am I gonna get halfway through and then be asked for a key or something? I have no idea what the key is, I'm not the one who built the PC and installed the OS. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking to permanently delete some files from a portable hard drive. What programs are good for beginners? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got some files I saved on a 500 GB external HDD that I want gone. But not all of them gone. Only some. And I do mean *permanently* deleted/overwritten/whatever. Someone else will be using this after me. 

Is there an easy to use program for beginners? Like some kind of file shredder that does not need extensive use of the terminal (I'm still learning terminal commands)?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pretty sure my Windows 8.1 PC is running pirated Windows OS. I bought it as is. Will it let me upgrade to Win 10? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 07:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Log time since I installed any Windows OS. The PC runs fine and I've never seen a warning about non genuine software. Will it upgrade to Win 10 without problems, even if the OS is non genuine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got a new external HDD. Should I format it before using it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 12:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can plug it in and use it straight away, of course. But is there any benefit in formatting it first?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will the built in VPN just work straight after you install the browser? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm told Opera has a built in VPN. That would be handy for getting around restrictions on my uni site. Will it just work automatically after I install the browser? If not, is the set up particularly hard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone from Australia? What do you think about Port Royal tobacco? I've only tried the Rum   Wine flavour. Anyone tried Kentucky Bourbon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't see it that often. I've thought about trying it but I always forget. What's it like compared to rum and wine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pirate Bay blocked in my country. How do I change DNS settings in Ubuntu? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pirate Bay blocked in my country. How do I change DNS settings in Ubuntu? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preferably with the gui. I'm not very good at the terminal, yet. I looked in the IPV4 settings and the method is "Automatic (DHCP)". All the other boxes are blank. I'm a bit nervous about changing anything without help. I know I need to change something to ''8.8.8.8'' but I'm not sure what. I'm in Australia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is my signal strength so poor with Ubuntu? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 11:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same laptop (ASUS F555U) gets great signal with Windows and fucking shitty, intermittent signal strength with Ubuntu. That goes for my wireless router at home and my university public wi-fi. What's going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My 8.1 system has crashed. Unrecoverable. So what should I do? Should I buy 10? I want to use it for gaming, sometimes, but mostly watching videos and web surfing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sick of fighting with this shit. I've held out for as long as I can. I like using Linux for web browsing and so forth but I want to play games, as well. Windows 8.1 has died on me for the last time. How much does it cost for Win 10 outright? Can I purchase it and use it for both my desktop and laptop?

I like to play games sometimes but that is not the main concern. I really want a system where I can reliably dual boot it. I have a (main) system with the following specs:

Core i5 6600K, 16 GB DDR4 HyperX RAM, GeForce 1060 card, GigaByte 1070 mobo

What is the best option for me? Can I buy 10 and use it on both systems with the same account or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do weather reports work? What does it mean when I see "80% chance of rain"? 80% overall? 100% in 80% of the area in question? What? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know where I can find the FireFox bookmarks in a Windows partition using Linux? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using Ubuntu to retrieve my data from a Windows 8.1 HDD that will no longer boot. I can access it but I can't find the FF bookmarks. Are they hidden or something? Where are they? As far as I know it was the latest version of FF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know where I can find the FireFox bookmarks in a Windows partition using Linux? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using Ubuntu to retrieve my data from a Windows 8.1 HDD that will no longer boot. I can access it but I can't find the FF bookmarks. Are they hidden or something? Where are they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm using Linux to rescue my files after a major crash. Where are my bookmarks? I can't seem to find them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 11:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'm using Ubuntu to view the Windows partition. The PC was running Windows 8.1 and I'd really like to get my bookmarks back.

Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Had a problem with Wondows so I'm trying to use Ubuntu to recover files. But when I try a live USB, it won't boot - "invalid magic number" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF do I do now? Windows 8.1 will not boot. There is some major problem. I fucking need the files. So I burnt a live USB of Ubuntu 16.04. As soon as I hit try Ubuntu, the magic number error comes up:

Invalid magic number

alloc magic is broken at 0x6630d4a0: 660cdd60

What the fuck am I supposed to do?

I can provide specs if needed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Had a problem with Wondows so I'm trying to use Ubuntu to recover files. But when I try a live USB, it won't boot - "invalid magic number" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 06:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF do I do now? Windows 8.1 will not boot. There is some major problem. I fucking need the files. So I burnt a live USB of Ubuntu 16.04. As soon as I hit try Ubuntu, the magic number error comes up:

Invalid magic number

alloc magic is broken at 0x6630d4a0: 660cdd60

What the fuck am I supposed to do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a good .iso burning software for Linux? I want to burn an Ubuntu .iso </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 12:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used various ones with Windows but what is everyone using with Linux? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I delete files in the Windows partition with Linux, will they be totally gone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As in, not moved to any temporary place like they would be if I deleted them in Windows (the recycle bin)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HELP - My PC with all my uni stuff on it has just totally shit itself. Cannot boot at all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 11:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It started with the mouse suddenly not working. Then the keyboard. So I just held down the power button until it shut down.

When I start it back up it says it is 'attempting repairs'. The repairs don't work and it gives me the options to refresh/restore/etc. I don't have an install disk and I don't want to completely refresh because all my shit will be lost.

So I choose the option to restore from some recent point (only one to choose from). It completes that operation and restarts, only to start up the same repair bullshit. Just an endless loop.

WTF am I supposed to do? I fucking need the files on that hard drive. My games, music, documents, photos, everything.

What the fuck do I do to get this heap of shit to work?

System specs are: Core i5 6600K, 16 GB ram, Gigabyte mobo, Windows 8.1. I can get other specs if needed.

I really need some help right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The older I get, the more nervous I am about asking how my (similar aged) friends' parents are, as they might be dead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 10:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone help me out on a very simple question on validity/reliability? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 09:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Q) Identify whether the error will affect the validity and/or the reliability of the measure:

"Participants are weighed wearing whatever clothes they happen to be wearing when they walk into the laboratory"

That's all it says. My thoughts are that the measure is neither valid nor reliable. Assuming they want the correct body weight, the clothes give an error that is not repeated (it's different for each person), so the measure cannot be reliable and since you are not measuring the true body weight, it's not valid, either.

Is that correct in any way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know what is going on with this missile guidance system? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 13:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got a new laptop. Plugged in headphones and they don't seem to work - the sound just comes out of the speakers like normal. Am I doing something wrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel pretty stupid but the headphones work fine with my .mp3 player. But plugging into the laptop doesn't work. Is there a setting I need to change? I'm trying to watch a video in the library. Win 8.1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are turbojet/turbofan engines unable to cope with supersonic air hitting the compressor assembly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 12:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are numerous ways of preventing it - inlet cones, ramps, etc. But why do you get compressor stall when going supersonic, in the first place?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plot to hit German shopping centre with multiple suicide bombers is foiled after police are tipped off about 'imminent attack' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 13:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's going on with the turbine side in this pic I found of a marine turbocharger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 12:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://dieselgasturbine.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/06/ABB-MXP.jpg

You can see the turbine entry but what's up with the mesh on the exhaust side?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have any World leaders - presidents, prime ministers, chairmen, kings, queens, etc., just given up because they didn't like it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 12:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened? What became of them? Why did they choose to throw in the towel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTF happened to Eagle Boys pizza? No stores around Newcastle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had high hopes of getting may fave pizza tonight and they don't seem to be around Newcastle anymore, unless I am making some mistake. WTF happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having trouble connecting to the university network. Can someone give me a hand? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've managed to connect to other networks no problem and I can connect to the uni with Windows. But Ubuntu just won't do it (apart from the guest wifi). There are many settings I really don't understand and so I have no idea what to do. 

Can someone give me a hand? I can provide the settings I have and the variables I can choose from.

It's Newcastle University in Australia. Connection name is newcastle.edu.au </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are .gifs taking so long to load? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 11:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just today. All day. Any .gif I try and watch is agonisingly slow. Yet youtube and torrenting remain unaffected and behave like they always do for me. What's going on? I can provide specs if needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When did we first start using the term (or comparison) as big as a shoebox, or would fit in a shoebox? When did shoes start being sold in boxes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 04:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How were they sold beforehand? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else finding downloads from the uni exceedingly slow, today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure it isn't my connection. I can torrent, watch youtube and all that shit perfectly fine. I can't get any more than ~30 kB/s for echo videos. 

Anyone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Jack Ketch was so sadistic and/or inept at his trade of executioner (no one could tell), that even the bloodthirsty crowds of the 1600s were often outraged at the suffering he inflicted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is dementia treated/handled in various societies both now and historically? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 06:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I install Unbuntu first, can I still dual boot Windows? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 05:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Windows 10 laptop that is giving me a terrible time trying to boot from USB. I wanted to install Win8 and then dual boot Ubuntu on top. But I can't get Win8 to boot, no matter what I try.

I can boot Ubuntu (I can get it to boot that from USB) no worries but after I do that, can I then dual boot Windows 8? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to install Windows 7 on a Windows 10 machine. It won't boot from the USB drive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 04:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've asked /r/techsupport with no real answers given. 

Anyone know how to force a Windows 10 laptop to boot from a USB drive? I've changed the BIOS settings and the changes are completely ignored. If I disable the Win10 boot option entirely, it just starts up the BIOS when switched on.

This is ridiculous. I do not want to use Windows 10. I want to install Win7. I don't know what to do. I used Rufus to create a bootable USB drive and it just won't work.

The laptop specs are: Asus F555UJ-XO044T Laptop Intel i5 6200U 15.6" 1TB 8GB RAM 2GB GT920 DVD Win10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What program would you recommend to make a bootable DVD? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 04:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Rufus would do it but it doesn't seem to be able to do a DVD. I'm using Win 8.1 and I want to make a bootable DVD. What trustworthy programs are available? AnyBurn says it will make an .iso but will it be bootable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having trouble getting a Windows 10 laptop to boot an .iso file </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got a refurbished Asus laptop with Win 10 installed. I want to install Windows 7 from a bootable USB drive. So I created a bootable USB drive with Rufus.

But when I change the boot order, it simply ignores those changes and goes straight back to Win10. If I disable the Windows10 boot option altogether, it simply goes back to BIOS when I restart it.

Fuck this shit. I want Win10 gone. Now. What is going on here? It was hard enough to find the BIOS settings and now this. What do I have to do to get this working?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL acetylene gas is dissolved in liquid acetone or DMF. This makes it much safer to transport and use, as it can violently polymerise at elevated pressures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 11:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I get info on Lumin (mianserin) and its safety with other drugs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 07:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mianserin is an old tetracyclic antidepressant I take at high doses (140 mg/day) in conjunction with lithium. How dangerous are things like amphetamines and opioids for me?

I (luckily) found out not long ago that lithium and LSD do not go well together, so I won't be taking that any time soon.

But what about these weird old tetracyclics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What is a 'port' (with regard to file sharing) and why are there seemingly tens of thousands to choose from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 10:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know the name of the arcade system that came out in the 90s and was a linked, multiplayer Mechwarrior type simulation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 06:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sat in a full cockpit that closed around you. You could choose from quite a number of mechs and then battle the other players in a linked game mode. There was no single player. At the end, you got a printout of how the battle progressed - you shot player A in the left leg, he hit you in the torso and so on.

It was fucking awesome. I played it in about 1995/6 in Sydney. Been dreaming of playing it again, ever since. It was very, very advanced for it's time.

Anyone know what is was? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When and where was the standard bottle cap decided upon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 07:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean the caps you use a bottle opener on, not the twist top variety. Wherever you are in the World (I think) the bottle caps will all be standard with a standard size opening tool. Be t a bottle of beer, Coke or anything else, it's standard.

When and where was that size first marketed and who standardised it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
