<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3944</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 01:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I dunno. I feel like Gallade is better... Mean look, hypnosis, false swipe... Smeargle is way too weak to not get murdered by legendaries. Only advantage is really soak.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 18:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super secret training always gave evolve stones and pp up.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 18:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Japanese only. Best bet is to wonder trade. I got mine from a forum trade.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 17:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did no one play X/Y..? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 17:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can breed anything... Getting it is a different story. Go into wonder trade and keep going until you get a snivy. It will probably have HA. Should take like... 10 minutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 17:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could try Dusknoir or Golurk. Dusknoir is really strong with some decent options... Especially night shade (surprisingly). Golurk has such low speed it's hilarious. And can learn gyro ball...  Dusknoir could also reset trick room so your whole comp doesn't fail if Aromatisse gets KOed immediately. Trick Room Golurk would basically be handing out priority Dynamic Punches. It's incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 16:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dragon Pulse, Glare with any decent Hidden Power isn't too bad. I'm not even going to bother listing the fourth move... That which shall remain unnamed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neptune approves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 05:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 00:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like Talonflame but instead of Brave Bird it's Leaf Storm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 18:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no way I'm the only one who doesn't get it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 18:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Master Contests. Don't even need to win. Just 1-3rd place. Talk to the entrance NPCs. I seriously have gotten 8-9 and I've only done master contests like 15 times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 17:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can't be competitive because it won't have a pentagon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 17:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Destiny Knot will only pass down5 IVs from both parents. This means you could get that spread, but it could overlap with the pokemon holding the power item. This could cause Attack stats from both parents being passed down, the power item parent taking priority. But the chances of getting those IVs aren't too bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 17:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ground*.. Plz mercy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If your city had a gym, what type would it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 17:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title. My city is full of... "Traditional southerners"... So probably Ground. Looking at you 
Diggersby.

Fail edit :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 17:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Distant Combat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 09:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like you're trying to create a theory ex nihilo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 06:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My experiences have ranged from 40-1400. I refuse to hatch more than 1400 eggs for a damn shiny Speed Boost Torchic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 07:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something went terribly wrong...? Or my sight just isn't what it used to be but I can't find Greninja... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 22:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cotton Guard is broken </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 07:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really really don't like the new voice acting. Charizard in the old Pokemon (don't know the season) roared like a bear/lion... Now charizards sound like a high pitched goofy voice saying "CHAW-CHAWZARD"...

On topic though, I think most pokemon had a cry that incorporated some part of their names; foreign or otherwise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 05:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I do. I've passed 23,000 people so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any way to "force" a streetpass? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 05:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister went to school today, got a friggen Eon Ticket, so I promptly overreacted and tried to streetpass her to get one as well... But the thing is, I'm not street passing... I tried trading with her, giving her a "nice", putting both DS's into sleep mode... Basically just trying to force interaction between her DS and mine... Any way to do it? Like, would I have to go out of range then back into range?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
