<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3183</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help me find this track please...so crack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 00:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey TwoX, I wrote an article on Janay Palmer's attack by Ray Rice. I think you guys may like it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 10:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> October is Domestic Violence Awareness Month and the video was pretty shocking. I felt it gave us a look into domestic violence we don't normally see. It also gave us an opportunity to address a scary reality for many woman and men.  
  
I copied and pasted the text below. If you do enjoy it, check it out on Beacon where I published it (crowd sourced journalism, pretty cool check it out anyway). This was one of the first subreddits I subbed to when I first joined,I was so glad to see it existed and was solidly active. I'm really glad I can finally add something substantial (relatively).  Check it out [here](https://www.beaconreader.com/matthew-romagnoli/behind-the-closed-door-a-closer-look-at-janay-palmers-attack-by-ray-ray-ricebb), please, if you liked the article!
  
The only thing lacking from the video of Janay Palmers attack is sound. If there was sound we could have heard how they were having a fight, seemingly like all couples. We could have heard what Rice said when he aggressively got in her face outside the elevator and how she responded. We could have heard the ominous ding of the elevator door closing. We could have heard if Rice made an emotionally abusive or threatening comment as he closed in on her. Then we could have heard the terrifying sound of Rices fist making contact and Palmers head hitting the railing. Thats not how normal couples resolve a conflict, thats how a criminal does.

What else we might have heard though, before entering the elevator, was that the fight may have not been so normal. He very likely could have been verbally abusing her, which possibly was the cause of the confrontation in the first place. We probably would not have heard the lady walking by saying anything either. She very likely told herself it is not my business. Unfortunately domestic violence, or intimate partner violence (IPV), is still considered a private issue. Both of those titles lend themselves toward suggesting its a private matter. There is a private element of domestic violence. Domestic violence happens behind closed doors. That makes it so incredibly frightening and lethally dangerous. The video of Palmers attack, calling it the Ray Rice Video puts the spotlight on him and not the victim further minimizing her, gives us a deliberate look into the actions of an abuser.

Outside the elevator Palmer reaches and mildly slaps Rice after he says something, in an intimidating manner by projecting his face toward her (not to justify any intimate partner violence).The 58, 206 pound Rice doesnt even flinch from her slap. He does not budge an inch, except in her pursuit. He doesnt immediately react and strike her then either. He deliberately follows her to the elevator. Once inside Rice closes in on Palmer. He takes notice of a lady passing the entrance of the elevator and waits for her to pass by completely. He then strikes her the first time, steps back anticipating her reaction and, when she charges him, swings again knocking her out. It looks like something they had been through before. It also looks like he was thinking it through compared to reacting in the heat of the moment. We can only speculate on what we see. Ultimately the reality of what took place is reprehensible.  

This video is a small window into the thought process of an abuser. Often the abuse we see in public is the tip of the iceberg. What happens privately is often far worse. This mere glimpse behind the closed door shows us an ugly, violent, and dangerous reality.

This most likely wasnt the first time an incident of abuse, verbal or physical, transpired between the two. Its very possible it was situational couple violence, which is a type of domestic violence where violent acts occur after escalating from a fight. According to Michael P. Johnson and Joan B. Kelly, situational couple violence lacks the coercive pattern of control seen in other relationships with domestic violence. Their paper, Differentiation Among Intimate Partner Violence (pdf), even says men involved in situational couple violence do not differ from non-violent men in measures of misogyny. Unfortunately, no matter the type, the woman is more likely to sustain an injury from any type of domestic violence.

This video at a minimum sheds light on the issue of abuse in a larger context but demands a far larger response from everyone exposed to it. Behind that closed door is an NFL full of Ray Rices. A recent Daily Beast article exposes an alarmingly long list of offenders within the NFL. As reported in the Dallas News, black women are three times more likely to die at the hands of a partner or ex-partner. According to a study designed by Jacquelyn C. Campbell, a leader in the field, access to a firearm creates a five fold increase in intimate partner homicide. With gun violence already plaguing many of the black communities in America this only compounds the problem. Unsurprisingly, both Plaxico Burress and Aaron Hernandez, the two more well known gun-toting NFL players, both were involved in domestic violence incidents.

Possibly most troubling of all, this hasnt exactly been behind closed doors at all. It only took this horrific video for us to pay attention, which is often the case with marginalized groups. Now, maybe, that the light has been shed we can start taking this issue a bit more seriously and giving it the due attention it deserves. Undoubtedly, its a complex issue with partners often choosing not to press charges and even going on to marry their abusers. The muffled sounds of domestic violence seeping under that closed door can no longer be ignored. If this video has done anything, its opened that door wide and we have seen, quite clearly, what goes on behind it.     

We also would have heard his, probably, nonchalant tone matching his seemingly calm demeanor afterward as he drags her body out of the elevator. Most likely offering some half assed excuse as to why his fiancee is laid out unconscious. Rice has claimed domestic violence is not an issue in his relationship and this was a one time thing. Im skeptical. Maybe it has remained verbal and has not erupted into violence yet. The abuse or control could even have been recently emerging and still unrecognized. Maybe, as a couple, they are in the minority and it is situational couple violence. Either way, even if it is not an issue within his relationship, there is clearly one within the NFL and certainly one within many homes. Now that we have seen how ugly and dangerous it can be, even if it is a one time incident, its an issue that needs to be addressed. 

October is Domestic Violence Awareness Month and we are becoming aware of more incidents of domestic violence seemingly everyday. Its important to be able to recognize the signs of domestic violence or abuse and to take action. Safe Horizon, No More and the National Domestic Violence Hotline offer great resources. Consider making a safety plan to leave if you are the victim in a domestic violence relationship. Some services will help you escape if you feel you can not leave. Look locally for events to help raise awareness and dont hesitate to speak up if you fear someone you may know is trapped in an abusive relationship. The National Domestic Violence Hotline is reached at 1 800-799-SAFE (7233).      
  
check it out and share it on [beacon](https://www.beaconreader.com/matthew-romagnoli/behind-the-closed-door-a-closer-look-at-janay-palmers-attack-by-ray-ray-ricebb) if you liked it. October is Domestic Violence Awareness Month, so get the word out!
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mid century ads x-post /r/design </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 17:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 26[M4F] looking to bullshit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 10:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anyway i enjoy, well love really, good conversation. i don't really want to get into the shit i or you like that much, because that's kind of boring conversation tbh (generic really is the word).  
  
prefer a female, not sure why, just do. i guess i love the woman's mind or something. i'm an attractive guy, a writer, love my job (that's not writing. other than that, you'll have to ask me.  
  
pm for kik
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ya know </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 11:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this game. Not too many games to i regularly play for years. And I always look to try and challenge myself, something new, ya know. Recently I went wide with brazil for the cultural win. It was also on a new difficulty, King. It was successful. I was trying to figure out what to do next. Sometimes, going for the old fashioned domination win is just as fun!  
  
Any recommendations on who I should conquer the world with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Hey, endgame questions... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 09:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,  
  
I really was looking forward to this game and really was enjoying it. I've really turned into more of a casual MMO player (gamer in general). Half way through leveling my free month finished so I took a few weeks off to let them hammer some bugs out. After that resubbed and started again but kind of lost my oomph for playing. It wasn't so much that I ddin't enjoy the game, I do. It's challenging (which is a breathe of fresh air), i'm loving the crafting/challenge of crafting, and even leveling my tempalr (despite it being a bit easier/semi repetitive at times, can alwayus pick up a new weapon/focus on different skill line, which is awesome). 
  
That said, I like the game. What I'm weary of is the V level grind. Also, from what I'm hearing the endgame theory is a little skewed and you lose the freedom you had leveling with your builkd. I get that there's some obvious changes to make  to be competitive but like everyone wearin clothe seems a bit silly.   
  
I don't know, I guess I'm asking how the endgame is. How's the theroy? How's the reality? How are the trials? Are they raid like and challenging? How's the role o the healer? Also the 4 man group quests, is there room to heal?  I know this game isn't as clear cut with roles, and that's okay, I enjoy it. I guess as a casual player it seems intimidating to grind that much for an endgame that I'm uncertain about. So, help me out deciding to sub for another month (which I mostly likely will, just have enjoyed the leveling process), shed some light on the endgame/your experiences. And anything else ZOS has lined up I guess that I'm not aware of. I'd love to hear about some of your experiences in the trials, I've watched some videos and they do seem pretty cool, I'd just like to hear 1st hand accounts. I guess I don't want only PvP to look forward to. As much as I enjoy it and tend to be good at it, I tend to favor group PvE though. I'm sure I could grow to love PvP though if the pvE got played out.  
  
Anyway thanks for your input, honesty, and help guys! Hope everyone has enjoyed the game as much as I ave so far.

Best,  
  
DC

                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                               </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cool mini Doc on the far right movement in sweden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 15:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You're a juror for an exceptionally long capital punishment trial. The deliberation is equally long and seemingly more arduous, resolving in a guilty verdict. Upon leaving the courthouse you overhear a conversation and immediately realize you've made a mistake. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 18:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~edit:~~  
  
edit2: i've said too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Okay, so the upside of Stakes Day...I made $314 profit, tripling my starting money. How'd you do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 03:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started with $125 in a new DRF Bets account (taking advantage of the sign up bonus which also gave you two free $40 bets, i believe the offer is still live actually)  
  
I hit a p3 starting with palice malice as a single and finishing with Tonalist. I also hit a decent DD starting with Tonalist and finishing with the strong favorite in the 12th race. Other than that I had a couple smaller exactas for $20-$40. The xpressbet guide to the Stakes actually had the trifecta (one of the analysts nailed it).  
  
So anyone else make some money?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ya know, not for nothing... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 07:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there are not many games with the persistent appeal of civ. Yeah, sure, I played WoW for years but that was an MMO and had a million expansions. This game still appeals to me and I still play it though, not too many games have that kind of enduring power. It really is something  else that, for years, I've (or it has) kept my interest and continue to want to play this game. Other games I still fire up but not nearly as much or if I do it frequently they have been released in the last 6/12 months.  
  
So, hear hear! This one's for you, Civ 5!  
  
Best,  
  
DC Romo   
  
ps - BE looks pretty cool, although I love the historical element of civ, it should be fun and different.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                               </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey DRF Bets has a great sign up deal and... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 06:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might be able to make some referral money off it. It's late and I'm going to bed but I'll psot the link and my referral number in the morning.  
  
They are offering $20 wager + $20 wager on the Belmont stakes (might be 40 and 40 iirc). Plus they are offering $125 paid back to you after you wager $125 in the first 30 days. It's a sweet deal, especially with the Stakes coming up.  I'm a big fan of DRF?Xpressbet (and you can call and ask them to switch between the two without much trouble at all).  
  
All I ask is that you wait till tomorrow so I can possibly get teh $#0 or $50 referral (and if I win anything significant ($100+ sounds good) I'll make sure to kick it back, always remember a good deed ;) ).  
  
ANyway, figured I'd let you guys know. Plus, obviously they have their formulator for PP's, which is unparalleled with the databases it gives access to. I really don't think anyone seriously handicapping could use anything else. Just to clarify their PPs might not be as good as Brisnet (which I think are just trumped up with their added "analysis," always felt less is more imho). Formulator though is fantastic. You can really dig and see patterns you wouldn't find anywhere else, unless you have an insane amount of old forms at the house or something, and even then that would be a lot of work.   
  
Also, small update. I know I've mentioned of starting a blog/tutorials to show how to cap and stuff. I'm still working on the website atm but want to start some handicapping tutorials this week, one before the stakes and then one for the stakes. Anyone recommend any good video capturing programs on the cheap/free (preferably)? I'm presuming a game capturing video software would work. Any tips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, I guess I shouldn't be surprised but I'm not sure how it works as an ad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 07:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hey mostly do pvp or pvai? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 04:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey what do you guys play?  
  
I play mostly pvp. For a while I had a good group to play with so we did custom games too which were a lot of fun. I find the game can be a little difficult without playing with a friend (or even just someone on vent).  
  
Thoughts or anything? Anyone looking for a partner? I usually play soviets and usually play team (even though random teammates leads to losses and being pretty damn good at 1v1). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eminem's hosting a new rap battle league...here's the original Smack DVD battles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 00:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great View...while we're at it let's compare UI's and list our addons... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 05:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Okay guys, take a breathe. The bots won't be here for long, here's why. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 09:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Zenimax isn't a bunch of inexperienced idiots. They opened up scripting for modding (to keep with a solid modding community of Skyrim and TES to be honest I don't remember much of a modding for other Elder Scrolls games but, I digress...)   
  
I'm sure they anticipated this would happen.  They knew it would be widespread. They new it would be an issue for gold, items, and everything that could be done to make some money. I'm sure they are going to put a stop to it. Whether they are gathering IP's for permanent bans or coming up with a solution for the end of public dungeon bot camping (after x time in a public dungeon or kills of a boss gold loot turns to 1 ?). Or x number of chat messages over x number of characters 5 times in a row results in a DC/warning for the first offense, I digress.  
  
They aren't stupid. We all agree that they did a pretty damn good job with this game. A lot of us would argue they hit a fucking home run. It isn't like anything I've experienced before really. It is truly its own experience as far as a "game" goes *certainly doesn't feel like any game I've played before though). People who make something like that aren't stupid nor short sighted (dat crafting system, lol).  
  
So they certainly anticipated this. They aren't naive. They open up LUA(?) scripting. I'm sure they are aware that botting was going to happen. I'm sure they have some solutions in place. What I reckon they are going for is some sort of solid permanent or semi permanent fix until the problem arises again instead of just putting a band aid after band aid that the botters can figure out how to work around. Instead they implement several changes and a solid fix on top to get rid of 95% of them or make them ineffective in one fell swoop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> this is a little frustrating... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 06:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> alright, this isn't a bitching post about the verification thing. it is what it is. the $15 nature is a little different but whatever.  
  
so on my way home I grabbed a prepaid visa card and put $16 on it. Figured this will solve it. And now it still isn't going through. I'm wondering if anyone else is having any success/failure with prepaid visa cards.  
  
I don't want to hear the get a bank account shit. I'm currently between jobs/trying to get my business off the ground (cash is tight, don't want it linked monthly to it). Anyway I got a lot of shit going on and was planning on using game time cards.  Looked around everywhere for them and (surprisingly, thought my area would have them) couldn't find any.  
  
I should be getting some money into my paypal account tomorrow from a client and guess i could try that. The whole thing is just a little frustrating. Like I'm trying here Zenimax and just want to play.   
  
Waited years for this game, got a tease, and now...bleh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> well, i'm hopeful... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 16:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  later this morning, eastern US time.
  
 well it's already 10:20 a.m. EST. we're pretty much into 'later' this morning. So, 'technically...' We should be ready to rock and roll and minute now. . .  
   
ahhh, the worst part is I have no desire to play any other games while waiting.  
  
tick, tock...the mouse ran up the clock... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> sooo guys, time to talk about add ons yet? haha </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 06:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess so right? I mean the conversation will happen eventually. Any that I need to have? I honestly enjoy the game as is but are there any that are jsut hard to paly without? I heard there's a pretty good one for combat with floating text that seemed cool, i wouldn't mind seeing my dmg done or an xp bar (preferably an xp bar alternative honestly).  
  
so what are we using? what do we think of them? what have we heard? gossip up boys and girls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3 day early access is live! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 12:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just bought it on amazon and I'm creating my character now!   
  
yay!  
  
I just creamed my pants maaan....!!!  
  
and i took some melatonin and tart cherry to help me sleep. well it worked, quite well. i fell asleep in my chair at my computer. woke up to the ESO site and longing. and then the amazon thing went through. like what? woot woot!  
  
I fell asleep expecting April 4th. Woke up and in 5 min I was making a character!
  
Edit: I forgot to add that if you want to play send me a PM.  Im not sure where you choose the mega server? But I'm in NYC.  
  
Or just keep an eye out for D C around daggerfall, friend, over perhaps watch your back enemy.  
  


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just need a little bit more to get myself started... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 12:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey,  
  
I'm Matt and I'm a recent college grad. I'm trying to get my business started. Me and my girlfriend are looking to start an advertising/marketing business. We have put a ton of work and time into this already (as well as a bunch of our own cash). I'm an English Major/writer and she's and adobe pro. We have a lot of our stuff planned out and built/designed. We have even picked up a few clients to work with to help pay for it along the way. We are trying to hit the ground running though with a full web presence, business cards, listings, a couple of our own adverts, some SEO promotion, some more traditional promotion. We've reached out to local businesses and the local Chamber of Commerce too. We are like right that.    
  
When I first embarked on this trip I had a little bit of money. I thought I could use it to spend the time to write a book and pursue my dream (wouldn't have lasted that long but would have been a start to get some serious writing done for a little bit) or to start our business. I've worked my whole life and I work hard. I enjoy it. I also enjoy applying myself creatively. It is something I do extremely well. I choose to invest everything I could into getting us off the ground. It may have not been pursuing my "dream" but it felt like I might be able to craft a life that would lead to living the dream by waking up every day to a profession doing what I love, being creative.  
  
We are planning on doing a Kickstarter possibly but since we are so close to doing it on our own I thought I might try here/start here first.   
  
We planned out the bare minimum of what we need to hit GO and it's $1,500. A figure we are more comfortable with is $2,000 but we'll get by with what we can. Anything would help really and we'd be able to put a few hundred to this or that. We've already invested 1,250 on our own towards some initial web development, Adobe, and networking. 
  
So come help M M Ads get off the ground. Or MMad Ads or MeMa Creative Group. We are still kind of, er, opinionated over the final design/name (so we have a bunch of spec work missing it, it's kind of funny).  
  
We can show you some design work we've done in the past, link you to some of my journalism work if you'd like to see that, show you our driver's licenses if that's what you'd prefer. If you're in NYC and willing to meet up in person we'd love to do that too. Equally importantly if you can send any work our way as a means to generating revenue we are absolutely open to that (Banner ads, Print ads, article/journalism writing, web content, web ads, ad campaigns, local business, corporations). Posting here was a bit of a debate in itself since we both felt it kind of embarrassing that we weren't able to do it totally on our own. The cost of living in the big city and life in general has made it difficult to do so though.  
  
If you are interested send me a PM and I'll message you my/our Paypal. If you'd prefer to meet in person or do it by other means, please just let us know. I wasn't sure if it was best practice to post my Paypal up here but if it is let me know and I'll add it right away. Otherwise I figured it was best to send a PM and we could personally field any questions/alleviate any additional concerns.  
  
Since we aren't starting a typical brick and mortar shop and have invested a lot of time and some of our money we've been able to keep costs low. Just a bit more to get going. We're trying to cut out our niche in the world and make our mark.  
  
Thank you for your time and consideration.   
  
Best,  
  
Matt and Meghan  
  
Sorry for the wall of text wanted to be thorough, upfront, and as honest as possible.
Tl;DR Need another $1,500 to get our advertising/marketing business up and running. Send us a PM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RELIC!! it's still crashing! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 08:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finally got it working by deleting my subscriptions after the first patch. I finally got in to play a game. Then this most recent patch came out and it's crashing again. It starts up and the somewhere during the loading screens it "minimizes" to the start bar but is stuck there. I think it pretty much crashes but I'm not sure if it totally is crashed. Please help...   
  
Guilt trip time: This is one of the few games I LOVE. I played the original COH and thought it was the coolest, most awesome RTS game ever. I waited years for COH2 and love it. I appreciate playing it and all you do for it. I just wish I could play my favorite game...:(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> looking for a civ to go wide that's a bit of a challenge? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 09:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> title sums it up. I'm looking to play a civ and go wide with a bit of a challenge. Not one that makes going wide too easy. I just finished with Brazil and had fun winning culturally. I'd like to possibly use some of the newer civs but it isn't exclusive. I'm also partial to Dido because I had a game where I was playing well and got screwed. Dido I was thinking of going with the shoshone too.  
  
So what say you, /r/civ?  
    
edit:  
So I'm definitely going to try out venice (going wide seems to be part of winning with them and then ethiopia. they are both civs I've wanted to try for a while.  
  
For now though,  

i'm starting up a faith based game, going wide with arabia, that might be challenging (remember a decent religion based going wide strat on here a while ago w/ byzantine) .    
  
I just realized that winning, on a new difficulty (king, cultural win), with Brazil was a challenge in itself. they are a pretty specific, particular civ and i did really well with them. I think the real challenge would be to move up from king and see if I can win, so I think I'm going to try that and maybe go with the Shoshone, they seem interesting to play and are different than how I usually play. I usually go somewhat wide without much fighting/war/army but at the next level past king I'm going to have to really be diverse and use all my benefits and that includes their pathfinder unit.  
  
Thanks for the help/input!  
  
Indonesia is also on my to do list now too, as for India, well, they get the D...in his mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been wondering about packaging my work... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 18:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've mostly been working and sending copy as GoogleDocs unless they've provided a template or the place the copy is supposed to end up.  
  
I was wondering how you might package some of your different projects for  your clients.  
  
I was also wondering, do you regularly work with a go to designer for stuff or expect the client to have that taken care of? I do some design work myself so it has made it easier but I avoid the crossover because it can get messy with rates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Faux News Brings the Truth (catchy eh? Cool vid of something that looks pretty damn near impossible to explain) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 18:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is pretty wild. There's a large glass container and it slides off the counter, to the floor, and shatters. It looks pretty heavy/bigger so it makes me doubtful it was the wind but there is always the possibility of a natural cause. The shape and everything though would make it pretty difficult for a wind gust to move without moving anything else around it (that is if the door to the store was open this time of year too and without noticing that?)  
  
Anyway check it out, cool stuff (relatively).  

http://www.myfoxny.com/story/25053800/store-surveillance-footage-shows-eerie-footage[1] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YSK that if you just click I'm Feeling Lucky at the Google Homepage it will automatically give you a random topic to check out after clicking it a second time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 20:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You leave the search space blank, click I'm Feeling Lucky and it gives you a random topic to check out. Google sort of tells you how you are randomly feeling (could feel? something you should feel something about?).  
  
go check it out, it's pretty cool. I'm feeling Stellar brings up a page about the Hubble Telescope and there's some other cool results.   
  
edit: i know this isn't making or breaking your day. I know it isn't paramount to your existence. It isn't climacteric knowledge. we all browse the net randomly at some point or another. this is different, unique way for you to do so, in a somewhat random fashion, to help you find some new and probably educational things. for it to be truly random use it in incognito mode or clear your browsing history otherwise you'll be directed toward something familiar. use it to learn about something different or brush up on something you know a little bit about.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey, after last patch some guys had problems with the game crashing, i'm one of them, any help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 09:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game isn't so much crashing. It is still running is just gets stuck minimized. But it only started happening after the last patch. Any ideas on how to fix this?  
  
I can tell it is still running because when I click it to restore it I can hear the "sega" thing as it opens up. it just won't open and stay open. sometimes i get a green box momentarily but that's about it.  
  
i really want to play too... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts on playing king, war, and some other ish...you know how it goes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 09:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just want to say, this was one of the first subreddits I found after joining reddit, one of the reasons I fell in love with reddit, we have an awesome sub...    
  
So I posted here, jesus maybe over a year ago about moving from prince to king. I ended up only playing a game here or there for a while so I kept it on Prince since I was keeping it more fun. One of my main issues was that I played prince really well. I dominated prince, just as is, to the point of having my choice of victory. When you get to King you need to focus your play a bit more, focus on your victory, use your benefits of your civ *thoroughly.*  Also, every element of the game comes into play. One of my big realizations was that I needed to stop focusing or building wonders like I did. They have their place and benefits but like the other elements of the game you need to focus/build the wonders that are relevant to the city, how you're playing, etc.  
  
That also goes for war. I hear people often complain about the end game they have to resort to war. Now I don't know if this sentiment persisted through BNW but you definitely don't need to be in this position. Now on King you're going to go to war at some point and honestly in most games you should probably end up at war. This will avoid that end game war and it's also realistic. War has always been a part of history, particularly in the greatest empires. Going to war at the right times, right points, can be immeasurably beneficial to your civ, and position you to avoid that end game war. It's another added element to King, going to war at the right time, right civ, and with the right goals. You don't need to be militaristic/war-mongering maniac. Similar to your wonder choice, choose your times to turn your civ towards military production and war. Use it strategically, like your choice of monuments. On king use it to take what the other civs have created with the added benefits they get from the difficulty level (this realization held a lot of weight with me).   
  
I always started well on King but the other civs would pull away. I now know how to keep them in check if need be. I also understand the importance of starting position. Being next to another leading civ can hurt you. Or a bullying civ can start the war thing at a poor time.   
  
Essentially you just need to be on your toes with your strategy. Make your moves at the right time. It's another tool at your disposal, so go ahead as needs be. Nothing forges the foundation of a a timeless, great, emperor than conquering some bastids'.

M </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So my game crashed, second time through I didn't make the same mistake. I hate Songhai. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-08 23:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So overall verdict that we've logged a decent amount of hours? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 09:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm saying yes. It feels like TES, it feels like an MMO and while there are some flaws overall it's nothing that can't be changed or fixed. I think with so much hype, anticipation, and time (omg changed release dates felt like blizzard) people were looking for any and every reason to bash this. Most forums are all haterade (now I know forums in general attract those people imo). I think they struck a decent balance and brought TES into an MMO with ESO. I'm having fun, and admittedly the beginning is a bit boring but that's the start of any game. And yes it's buggy, it's a beta, that's what beta's are for. Nothing that won't be ironed out by launch. I think it's worth a shot that's for sure.  
  
My biggest gripe? and i think it's only because I logged years of Wow is the UI, or rather the lack thereof. Now yes I know TES games are, I played them too but this is an MMO and the chat box's tabs are hard to switch between without a cursor. I kind of like seeing my health bar and stuff. Now again it is probably left over from other games where PvP was more random and my health didn't regenerate as quickly. Certainly not a deal breaker.   
  
The other thing would be the action bar. I'm only picking 5 skills? Fa real? I guess some become less important as I level. Also I can switch em out when I enter a dungeon to heal (4 healing, 1 dmg?). So that works I suppose but wouldn't mind filling out the other unused number keys for actions. I've pretty much been playing first person but zooming out all the way in third centers the camera which is cool, or you can go over the shoulder. Both are viable. The quickslot is awesome. My staff attack is cool. Also using skill points is really intricate. My weapon, my skills, my racials...so much, it's awesome and going to make for some unique  character builds and some thinking. Everyone  is unique   which is such a relief from most games where only your armor distinguishes you. I think it's good (obviously) and my gripes are nothing an add on or two won't fix (lol). Especially with the modding community present in TES games I don't fault them for leaving it to be made, modified and crafted instead of saying this is how it's going to be. Looking forward to going live!  
  
Also...I enjoy the combat too. Almost more than TES originals. Fighting a group is interesting and my knockback skills matter on who I target. Switching between targes is a breeze. I can deal dmg with m staff to the target in front of me, turn cast a spell on the left, and go back to beating the wolf in front of me with my staff.   
  
Shit I'd go as far to say...hmmmmm, it's fun! haha.  
  
so what say you, /r/ESO?  
  
M  
DC-Romo  
  
edit: so just got the heads up on the UI/action bar expansion at lvl 12 (some busy bees out there huh?...lol who says busy bee anymore...?) So that's cool, and I kind of thought something like that might happen at level 12/15 or something.   
  
I'm also curious how you guys do your UI's? I keep my chat box locked so it's there and the action bar always showing. I play First Person so the health bar above my head doesn't matter but sometimes I put it up and use 3rd person to run around a bit but usually don't. I guess it's left over from my other MMO days (cough, wow) and I'm used to a more detailed, and cluttered UI, so this is refreshing. I guess I kind of just like to see my skills there and know what I'm capable of, and in a sense how far I've come maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2:55 Back UP!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 08:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nough said, go back to ESO and not sleeping bitches... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2:46 EST Servers Down Again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 08:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also in general it seems pretty buggy considering we are a month out from launch...  
  
edit: that said, as an MMO player from UO, to WOW (from launch), and a couple others since and in between...  
  
I'm pretty fucking excited and looking forward to this. It feels like ESO, it feels like a damn good MMO, and while the beginning area is fucking boring the first 10 lvls of any MMO are boring (of anything, the first 10 levels of my life were boring) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OC] Sleep lil Babe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 07:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey i'm looking for critiques, feedback, anything. it's been a while since i've written some poetry.    
  
Go to sleep little babe  
The last words muttered  
Rocking my innocence asleep   
Somewhere between the age of 15  
And Scotch or Valium or Heroin  
Sleep well little babe  
You need not wake  
Bear witness  
The blanket excuses  
These bountiful abuses  
Creativity at its finest  
Not nearly its kindest  
Wooden rules bent kindly  
In jail cell protection  
Of whats most precious  
Trust us  
Not whats left us  
Only the next peasants song   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey looking to play? Battletag: Romo#1498 [x-post /r/diablo] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-15 12:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I have a lvl 29 witch doctor that's just starting nightmare...i think my stats are a mess but I'd be willing to start anew with a new character or pick up from here or near by if anyone is up for it?I just got back into it so let me know, would love to meet/quest.hang around and bullshit while playing, whatever's clever.  
  
battletag: Romo#1498 (not sure if you need to include the hashtag?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey /r/queens, here's an obit for a friend but i'm sharing to bring to light his cause, People for the Pavillion with the goal to preserve the 1964 world's fair site (x-post /r/nyc), i thought /r/queens would appreciate his cause </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 08:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lost a friend, in his memory I'd like to bring to light his cause to /r/nyc People for the Pavillion. here's an obit and a bit about it... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 06:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only posting this because it is receiving national attention... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 19:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ANyone read about this house? Fox news did a story on it and thought some of you might find it interesting.   
 
http://foxnewsinsider.com/2014/01/29/9-year-old-indiana-boy-given-exorcism-after-string-strange-incidents  
  
Normally I wouldn't do it but since it is getting mainstream attention and is officially documented thought we might want to talk about it.  
  
Sorry mods, by all means flag and take down if it isn't cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> possible water damage? RMA? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 11:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SO, and I know this sounds ridiculous but not really in a sense, since it happened, but I used my nexus in the rain and now when I get a phone call I can't hear anything.  
  
I mean it was really raining out, like fucking torrential downpour and I knew to protect it from getting wet, and I feel like I did but some raindrops hit the screen. It wasn't soaked or anything, and certainly not saturated as if it were submerged. Anyway I took it out after I received a text, read teh text and then called the person. Some drops got on it while it was horizontal and they were like big rain drops. but I figured a fw on the screen weren't the end of the world. I guess there was one that landed like toward/ on the speaker hole from where you hear people during a phone call. When I went to call the person it worked for the first en/20 seconds of the call and stopped. I put it in rice thinking it may be able to dry the speaker out and work, so we'll see.  
  
Am I the victim of some seriously ill fate? Everything else on the phone works fine, speaker phone works fine and I suppose I could use a headset if I had too. It just seems shitty that I can't use my phone in the rain because this could happen. It looks perfectly normal without any issues.  The screen is fine. Like everything else is fine. I just don't hear anything during calls.
  
I also don't want to hear shit about this not being what happened. If it were something else I would just say it and ask about the best way to lie about it because reddit is awesome and I know you guys would help me like that if I needed it. I'm really more curious if anyone else has had issues like this and if it seems plausible that that could be the cause (anyone know anything about speakers?) or if maybe it is a software issue? Would the speaker be effected by a few big drops a water properly placed? I've used other phones n the rain and usually have problems with the touchscreen more than anything when it gets slightly wet.  I mean nowadays we barely talk on the phone and everything else really works fine, so I'm really not that mad because phone calls are such a small part of this awesome beast. Any help guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was England's Naval contribution in the Revolutionary War/American War for Independence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 06:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From my understanding its navy was in disrepair to some extent (did the revolutionaries just have good timing?). But in a historical context their navy played quite the role in creating their empire, why didn't it contribute more successfully to a positive outcome in Britain's favor in the American War for Independence (or did it but not enough to make up for their losses on the ground)?  
  
I understand the American's gained supplies through their privateers and France, but could they not successfully embargo such a large coast/so many ports as effectively?  
  
Sorry if my questions are off base, I've read up on it briefly and based it on my knowledge of naval warfare. Any light shed on the topic is much appreciated, it was something that occurred to me that seemed odd/out of place considering how much England's navy contributed to their history as an Empire, it feels as if it fell short in this instance.  
  
Thanks for your time and consideration, love the sub, and truly appreciate all that you guys add to reddit and the readers.  
  
p.s. I did search pretty extensively but the terms, navy, naval, rev war or Amer War for Ind. kind of made it difficult, still I did not find much, I found stuff related but not this topic specifically, forgive me if it has been answered and just direct me to the link, I'd hate for you to have to repeat yourself, certainly don't want you to feel like I am wasting your time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Fresh/Hype/Dat Crack] Joey Bada$$ - Two Lips </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 19:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ! Hey guys a thank you and an apology, sincerely. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 11:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Love Letter To /r/Cigars  
  
I owe a huge thanks to /u/thepickledgent for his bomb, back when a bunch of us were hit during his carpet bombing. It was the reception of my first bomb and while we all jokingly admit to the utter chaos and destruction the bombs cause, this one was real and quite the first. It came in the middle of a few trades. I was rushing to get to the  post office to send my halves and that arrived while I was trying to get my addresses straight. Instead of looking up one of the addresses I just figured I'd grab it off the package. I check it and 'Oh, hmm, but I thought the guy lived in state x, not y.' I was flabbergasted and confused. Finally double checked online, got it right and got the package out in time. Well done sir, and thank you for my first bomb. I was utterly violated.  
  
I also owe a thanks to /u/Juggernaut665 for my verification trade (dude i thought i checked it received months ago, just did it soooooo sorry). He hooked it with some solid sticks and jolly ranchers, my favorite candy (the hard ones but i've grown quite fond of the chews too ;), ahem, ya know... j/p!). You're the man, big ups! Thanks to /u/I_forget_my_userids for a side deal of premium delicious smokes. You hooked it up bro and the timing couldn't have been better, I was flush with sticks at the time, and since, have fallen on more frugal times. You hooked up it up with some excellent smokes that will hold me over till this degree and my portfolio can land me a job that earns some real money (can anyone bomb me a pr/marketing/journalism position in nyc? just kidding mods, i saw the side trade sticks only post! but seriously pm me). You're the man! Another big thank you is due to my friend and comrade in arms /u/d_r0ck for a *real* **solid** trade. I made his weekend a while back and he d_r0cked my world (see what I did there?) He hit me with my first undercrown. We traded only the finest among one another, a true gentleman, scholar, and aficionado! You're the man! 
  
And /u/Garandir, are we ever finishing our trade? I want you to get your +, holla at ya homeboy! I'm waiting on your move boss!  
  
You're all the shizznit! Love you guys.  
  
I also want to thank everyone who participated in the haiku contest. The winner's sticks are being sent out tomorrow. I want to thank you all for your patience. You've been saints, and it is much appreciated. Particular thanks to our AOTM /u/givequicheachance for getting on my ass and wrapping up the contest, albeit with delay, but not painfully so. He reminded me to keep on, keeping on during hard times. Something that is a huge help when things seem to be moving like your in molasses. When life is surreal. Thank you all, congrats to the winner and runner ups. If you aren't aware or are curious [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/cigars/comments/1nka6h/contest_haiku_contest/) is the link with the updated results. Thanks again, to all of you.  
  
Now for a bit of a sadder story and an explanation in regards to my tardiness with the contest's finish announcement, absence in general, and delay in thanks for all these great guys, their trades, and bombs. I recently lost a good friend suddenly. He was a great friend who was truly loved among friends and family. He was also a fisherman. Someone who I spent hours upon endless hours with on the water, fishing in the surf from the beach, and sharing beers with him at the bar (and on the beach). Anyway, a bunch of guys left him lures and fishing tackle but one of the last conversations I had with him was about smoking a cigar together. I told him I'd bring him a cuban or something nice and we'd smoke together, maybe go to the racetrack or fishing or having a fire in my backyard. So I thought long and hard about what to leave, I wanted it to be unique. I decided on the Baitfish vitola of MUWAT. It reflected on the last conversation I had with him and it was something he would have ***loved.*** As a Fellow fisherman he would have got the biggest kick out of the small cigar being called a Baitfish. Just his personality loved obscure, interesting and unique things. He was a unique guy. I gave one to his brother too, who laughed when I told him it was called aBbaitfish, because he knew he'd love it for these reasons. By the end of last week the reality among his friends was stark. We had truly lost a brother, a dear friend, and a loved one. He's captaining his own boat, cigar in mouth, sun rising, and calm seas ahead. I love you Mark. Rest East Friend.  
  
 So thank you guys for your patience, it has been a long week. Thanks for reading. You'll be getting your winning sticks shortly. Sorry for the delay in thanking those for the trades and the bomb. Sorry for the lack of photos, I don't have access to a camera at the moment and have smoked a bunch of em anyway, lol. So thanks guys and thanks /r/cigars for being such a great place to keep my mind clear and always for bringing a smile to my face. 
  
tl;dr: over due thanks for bomb and trades, explanation for delay on haiku contest (not abridging it for obvious reasons) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [CONTEST] Picking WInners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 15:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feelin' lucky punk?  
  
Well with this contest, if you're going to win, you'll answer that with a definitive ***'Yes.'*** This isn't going to be an easy contest. With a little determination though you'll have taken the reigns and steered yourself to the positive leaving little behind to fate. Uh, What?  
  
I want to know who the best handicapper on /r/Cigars is.  
  
I'm going to pick out 5-6 main races over the weekend of October 12th, plus an additional 2 bonus races this coming weekend and you'll get to pick one race of your own (if turnout is good and people are up for it, the contest will run the duration of October with races picked out each weekend except for this one, it'll be the same two, let me hear what you think). You'll make one selection per race. The horse you pick will have an automatic "$10 win bet" placed on it. The winner will have the highest payout of everyone playing. Anyone who plays the initial two races this weekend will have a small bonus consideration in the event of a tie (and solid preparation/races to review for next weekend).  
  
If you've never handicapped a race before nor do you plan to, that's okay, guess away. The public picks the winner correctly 33% of the time. It usually doesn't pay that well but they're right. I recommend you start [here](http://helloracefans.com/basic-information/how-to-handicap/) though. The [fundamentals](http://www.cynthiapublishing.com/MitchellArticles/dm20001013.htm) of handicapping are based around [class](http://horseracing.about.com/od/helpfornewfans/a/aaracetypes.htm), form, speed, and pace. A good tool to figure these out for a horse are its [past performances](http://horseracing.about.com/gi/o.htm?zi=1/XJ zTi=1 sdn=horseracing cdn=sports tm=141 f=20 su=p504.6.342.ip_ tt=2 bt=1 bts=0 zu=http%3A//www.drf.com/row/fan_ed/DRFFanEd.pdf). There's a plethora online but if you're feeling [ambitious](http://www.anddownthestretchtheycome.com/2013/1/4/3837832/recommended-reading-horse-racing-books)(or I've piqued your interest) this isn't a bad list of reading material.   
  
Personally those websites aren't bad but you really only need to poke around on www.DRF.com. That's the go to place. Read the articles I've provided and then stick to DRF, that's my recommendation. Also you are going to see past performances cost money, ***Do Not Buy Any!!*** I will be providing all the past performances for all the chosen races (if you live near a track there might be paper copies of the DRF around town; it's an expensive paper and you need to buy it for the day of the races you are playing and it's only available the night before at the earliest.)  
  
Okay, so that's the background. Now back to the contest. It's simple really. Whoever has the highest payout after all the races are finished will be our winner (if we run it through the month it's the same premise). There will also be a runner-up for second best and a winner for single highest payout on a horse. The odds will be the final odds of the racetrack the horse is running on. I'll check the results and adjust the payout for a $10 win bet and that will be your payout. Your accumulated payout will be your final total and determine your placing. In the event of a tie I'll consider if any of the initial two races were played, if the person won, then I'll look to single highest payout among the tied competitors. Worst case we'll split a prize (or double one, we'll figure it out).   
  
You can leave your selections in a comment below for each race. If you play the initial two this weekend clearly distinguish the races with the date. I will post the initial two races tonight. They will be from Belmont Park and they will be graded stakes races run this coming Saturday.   
  
The races for the following weekend of the twelfth will be posted shortly as well. You won't be able to handicap them till next week though. Use the time to brush up on the basics and give it your best shot.  
  
As for prizes...  
  
I'm going to put together a bunch of cigars. Obviously our high roller will be receiving some high rolling cigars, 5-10 clubhouse /graded stakes class(super premium) sticks. The runner up is looking at closer to 5 grandstand/claiming level (less premium) sticks and the single highest payout on a horse will get 2. And a hug.   
  
The winner, if he/she pleases will also get to place 5 $10 live win wagers through me on races of their choice. I'll put the wagers in for them, on the races they want, and forward any positive outcomes. So the winner is also receiving a $50 gambling gift card (essentially). The runner up will get one $10 wager. Maybe if we are in hangout or around for the days/races we can all watch in giddy anticipation of the outcome. I'll certainly post if this turn into a well paying contest.   
  
If anything was left out on here, I probably have thought of it and just forgot to write it. Let me know if there are any questions. If there is interest beyond these two weekends we can consider extending it through the month of October as a sorta "fantasy handicapping" thing on the weekends.  
  
If you want to play but don't want to handicap, that's fine don't shy away and feel free to guess. I'll be posting some limited info on the races, enough to make a guess from. If you want to take it more seriously, feel free, that's why I provided some links.   
  
It's all in good fun, so try to enjoy yourself, that's what this is about. I thought this was neat since racing and smoking go together at times. A good cigar at the track, ;), hmm!  
  
 Have Fun and Good Luck!  
  
edit: shout out to /r/horseracing.  
  
open to everyone with a plus. I'm going to check with the mods about earning your plus through the contest by submitting a cigar ("wagering" it) to the prize pool or something.   
   
guys do to the lack of response we are passing on this weekend, if it gets a few more before next wed we'll still be a go for the weekend of the twelfth.   
 
 This will be open to everyone as well, U.S.. If you want to participate internationally that's fine if you are willing to cover shipping costs in the even you win.  
  
edit2: If anyone wants to, do two out of the three stakes at Belmont Today. Since someone asked, that's what I was planning but I wasn't going t, due to lack of response. Since a few of you are interested I figured I'd throw it out there.  
  
8,9, or 10th at Belmont Today, Pick 2 races out of the three.  (I Don't expect anyone to do it under such short notice)  
  
Looks like we didn't get a good turnout. I don't think I'm going to scrap it altogether since  I wrote all this out but for the couple of you who are interested I'll throw out a few races for saturday but all for fun. Due to the low turnout it isn't really a competition among three people. Do not think I'm doing this because I don't want to send sticks out, it just isn't much of a competition without competitors plus it's too easy to end up chalky and miss the bigger payouts with so few people.   
  
Or if we want we  could handicap the pick4 together ono saturday at belmont or SA. Or Handicap the card together and see if we can make some money together. I'm going to be playing Belmont Saturday anyway.  
  
The races I'm thinking are:    
  
All times listed are Eastern
  
Belmont Race 2 Claiming 15k 1:22  
Keeneland Race 4 Claiming 50k 2:41  
Keeneland Race 6 Allowance N2X 3:45  
Belmont Race 7 Knickerbocker Stakes 4:02  
Belmont Race 8 Allowance OC 4:34  
Belmont Race 9 Athenia Stakes 5:06  
Keeneland Race 9 Queen Elizabeth II Challenge Cup G1 5:21  
Santa Anita Race 7 California Distaf Stakes (Cal Bred) 7:07 (estimated)  
  
Might as well do the 10th at Belmont too (5:38) to complete the 300k Guaranteed Pick 4.   
  
Do whatever you can, I know it's a lot. I guess concentrate on what will give you the biggest scores. I'm mostly going ot be handicapping Belmont, that's where I play and where I've been making my living lately. I do play the other tracks at times though. Santa Anita also has a guaranteed pick 4 as well, I'm not sure if keeneland does.   
  
Good luck. Since  we aren't taking this as seriously as before if you want to post you picks beforehand and maybe we can talk about the positives and negatives, I'm certainly up for that.
  




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [CONTEST] Haiku Contest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 06:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title pretty much says it all. Write a haiku, leave it in the comments. Make it a Haiku about your favorite stick or place to smoke, a memorable celebration or remembrance cigar. I won't limit it to just Haikus, another form of Japanese poetry is the Tanka. Often Haikus or Tankas are written in conjuction or together as groups or series. Just to review a Haiku is 5 syllables, 7 syllables, 5 syllables per line (5 - 7 - 5). A Tanka is 5 - 7 - 5 - 7 - 7.  
  
If you can't get the haiku or tanka to work I'll take any form of poem.  You could do an English (classic shakespeare) sonnet or a petrarchan (italian) sonnet (google it, pretty simple). Free verse works too. Just write something.  
  
* Write a poem, Haikus, Tanka and structured poems will be favored more but anything will be accepted.  
  
* Cigar related entries will be favored more highly.  
  
* A Haiku is 5-7-5, a Tanka is 5-7-5-7-7. Google sonnets and learn about them.  
  
* Plus members, U.S. only   
  
* I'll take into consideration comment votes and positive feedback. Ultimately I'll be the final judge, I'm EMC (English Major Certified), so relax, I got this.  (published poet/writer too)
   
  
*  Get writing! Leave your poem as a/in your comment below
  
Have fun with it and tell us about your favorite cigar in 17 syllables (or whatever cigar related memory, event, whatever or the view in front of you while you smoked or that high you felt while smoking after your first son or daughter was born or just write about anything!!)!  
  
edit: just so people are clear present day it is generally accepted that people aren't super sticklers for syllable count and if something is close or sounds like it might (or "should") be a syllable it'll slide.  Do your best and act in good faith and all will be well. There will be a Top Prize and maybe a runner up, we'll see how things go.  
  
As for prizes, got some sticks to sell ya, yeah man real quality stuff, *imported ;)* Yeah just meet me around the corner, that alley right there, yeah man, just go in. Hey waddya doin? It's cool man, *trust me.*  
   
  
edit2: Great stuff guys. Also don't hesitate to post again if that moment of brilliance strikes you as haikus run through your head nonstop now but you're all like, damn yo i posted one already. no worries post your second one, just improve from the first.   
  
We'll wrap it up in a week, Wednesday 10/9/13
  
Partagas Serie  
D. No. 4. Or Perhaps  
A Montecristo        
   

  
Alright guys, contest is over. I'm going to mull it over and decide o someone to win a few sticks and a runner up. couple others might receive a stick or two if we find some unique circumstances, something exceptionally unique or pointed.   
  
Great job! PM's are welcome for your own opinion as to one that is good or you appreciate, and of course up and down votes.  
  
  

***WE HAVE A WINNER***      
  
Hey Guys! We have a winner! Sorry about the delay I had some personal emergencies to deal with and reddit was the last thing on my mind. It was a tough decision, to put it lightly.  
  
The winner is /u/aphex732 with:  
  
A sulfurous scent  
The world dissolves as vapor  
My being exhales  
  
I believe it really encapsulates the feeling of smoking a cigar at the right time in the right place. It also stays true to the haiku form with an eastern mentality. He'll be receiving a small package of cigars shortly, some time next week. The decision for a runner up was tough as well. There were a lot of good poems that could have won so picking a runner up was as difficult. I didn't want to hurt anyone's feelings so I figured it'd just be better to send the winner an extra stick, i'm sure you guys understand and would see this as fit.  
   
Just kidding!! On the contrary there were multiple runner ups. Now among the runner ups, if you guys feel one stands out more than the others chime in but you guys/gals are:  
  
/u/QuickAF77 - a close second for many of the same reasons i choose the winning poem, great job.  
/u/givequicheachance - for a clever poem that made me laugh.  
/u/ImAStruwwelPeter - for an excellent poem that was a real pleasure to read.  
  
you three will receive a stick or two in the mail shortly.

Other honorable mentions that might make good targets for those in a giving mood ;) are:  

/u/mailmanmalone - for painting a vivid picture of times passed.  
/u/avrus - for a simple but thoughtful poem that made me feel good.  
  
Thank you all for participating. All these poems were great and a lot of fun to read. i hope we can do this again soon. Again I apologize for the delay the last two weeks have literally been hell. Thanks for putting up with the delay.  
  
Cheers Guys. Much Love! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bomb Making Materials Delivered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 18:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got some [supplies](http://imgur.com/a/kp0iB) to put together a bomb or two.  
  
Hide yo kids, hide yo wife.  
  
Vudu Test Flight from the Famous Smoke Coupon  
2 My Uzi Weighs a Ton Baitfish 5 Packs  
L'Atelier Special Selection 46 Box of Ten  
Olivia Master Blend 3  
Illusione Holy Lance   
Plasencia and a House of Montague Sample cigar
  
Not pictured is the Leather Travel Humidor that I received as well.  
  
Already cracked into the baitfish and the Master Blend, both were great. Not sure what I should smoke today, any suggestions?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Punch Corojo 10th Anniversary, yummy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-26 09:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I smoked [this](http://imgur.com/aOHGdXY) last night, made a fire and had a couple Angry Orchard Hard Cider.   
  
I also had an Olivia Serie V which was alright, I'm not wild about the Serie V. The Punch 10th Anniversary Corojo was excellent though.  
  

I have to thank a lot of the guys who posted pics of yourselves sitting with a stogie and a fire, it reminded me of how much I enjoy sitting out like that.                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                           </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Latest Additions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-22 21:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are some from my latest hauls. I'm in a rush so I'll come back and include more details (vitolas).  
  
For now though we have some Gloria Cubana Gilded Age Churchills and Toros. Arturo Fuente Don Carlos #4 (recent haul from Famous Smokes, love that site and cigar monster).  
  
Then we have a bunch of Cubans.  
  
Cohiba Siglo II and Esplendido  
Monte #1 and #4  
Punch Corona
St. Louis Ray Reserva Especial 
H. Uppman Magnum 46 and 50  
RyJ Cazadores  
Partagas Serie D No.4   
Quai D' Orsay Corona Claro  
Juan Lopez Corona (5 5'8 x 42, all coronas)  
  
SOB (smoked or bombed/gifted): 1 Epicure No.1 and No.1, 1 RyJ Churchill, 1 Monte #2, 1 Monte #1, 3 RyJ Short Churchills, 1 Magnum 50, 1 Partagas Serie D No.4, and a maybe one or two more cubans.
  
Totally forgot, [here](http://imgur.com/a/p6Tom) is the album.
  
~~If anyone is familiar (or check history) with my posts they are usually super detailed with vitolas that include length/ring size. I'll be back in a little bit to make this one like all my others. I hope this suffices to hold the post over till I get back (mods?)~~  
  
Sorry it doesn't include sizes, I usually like to include them so people who are newer can have an idea of how big the stick is in case they want to try it (applies to experienced smokers too since companies can make their vitolas to their own liking). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyer/Crist Seminar Tom(Today) 9/21 12:30-2:00PM; Anyone going? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 08:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be there. Anyone else going? I'll also be crushing out this pick 4 and if the pick 6 looks opportune I might take a weak stab at that (i've been kicking myself after cappin' the 500k+ carryover and not playing, i had it...)  
  
Also it runs through the first 3 races so there's a good chance these guys will be throwing us a few picks and while the horse will be bet down there's a good chance that you'll be able to put together some exactas or trifectas.  
  
Anyway, if you're heading over there and catch this, send me a pm with a # if you want to meet up or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> oh man o man...i just love cubans, don't you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 10:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you do. But what do you do when you decide to order some cigars and don't nessecarill want to shell out $200 for an order of cubans (or are a freshly graduated looking for steady pay writer, next in line but yet to be hemingway?).  
 
Do you guys smoke anything else? If so what do you recommend? I'm starting to have the realizatoin that most of the non cuban cigars I smoke cost as much as some of the cubans anyway. Am I just being silly with these divergent thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hey 14" U.S. $300-$600, light image editing/design work, Have a question about the Lenovo U410 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 09:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking at [this](http://outlet.lenovo.com/SEUILibrary/controller/e/outlet_us/LenovoPortal/en_US/catalog.workflow:item.detail?GroupID=445 Code=59RF0387) lenovo. I mostly need it for writing, blogging and journalism work. That include some light photo editing and design work. I mostly work from my desktop but if I'm buying a laptop I'd like to be able to work from it if need be.  
  
My question is the 6GB RAM. It has the 2 video cards; are the 2GB RAM and 4GB RAM dedicated to each card or will the computer draw on the whole 6GB if needed? Sometime photoshop eats up ram and while I don't plan on using it for intensive work I'd hate to not have enough memory. Or if it had 8GB RAM with 2 video cards and 2x4GB RAM, I imagine it would draw on the whole 8GB if needed, right?
  
I feel like i should be fine for my intended use but I feel like that if I can work from it I will (it's almost a curse being able to work away from the pc, because if you can do it, you will and are expected too but I like what I do so no complaints).  
  
I was also considering the Thinkpad S230U, i5, 4gb Ram, 500GB 24GB SSD. The price of the original Lenovo I posted though is great and really what I wanted to spend in the first place. Plus I love the red color.  
  
Thanks guys, you have been great through this whole process and it's a relief I'm almost done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just bombed the deli guy this morning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 23:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry guys, I'm joining and just signed up to earn my +/ Before I did though I did some personal bombing. The deli I go to in the mornings is a pretty chill place and the guy who owns it always talks about fishing and recently we've been talking about cigars. So I went in and hooked him up wit ha few smokes.  
  
I also just hit my friend with a package, he's a bit newer to smoking but the sampler from cheap humidors seemed up his ally so that's on its way now too.  
  
All that said, I'm also waiting to hear back from my verification trade partner and you guys are next. You could try but you'll never be ready. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Done my homework, just want to check these will meet my needs. Looking for advice. U.S. 14" screen, $600 Firm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 20:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted before with parameters that were near impossible to meet and since then I've done some more homework and found a few machines I think will meet my needs (and got realistic about budget). I started looking only for a machine for word processing/web browsing and then I thought I should be able to work more comprehensively from it if need be. That includes some photo editing, design work and some limited video editing. I mostly use Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop and InDesign and occasionally Dreamweaver.   
  
I found a few machines I think will be more than sufficient but I'd like an opinion on them and to insure that these will in fact meet my needs. I'd also like to hear feedback on what you guys think would be the best buy. One of the issues I have is that the messenger bag I use can only fit a machine with a width less than 13.5" SO I've limited myself a bit with that.
  
They are:    
  
Dell Latitude E6400 http://www.neweggflash.com/Product/N82E16834300051  
  
Dell Latitude E5410  
http://www.neweggflash.com/Product/N82E16834200938  
  
Dell Latitude E4310  
http://www.neweggflash.com/Product/N82E16834300051  
  
Dell Inspirion 13z  
http://www.amazon.com/Dell-Inspiron-i13Z-3636sLV-13-3-Inch-Laptop/dp/B00ANKN04A   
  
Toshiba Satellite  
http://www.neweggflash.com/Product/N82E16834216043  
  
Asus Q200E  
http://www.bestbuy.com/site/Refurbished+-+Q200E-BSI3T08+Notebook+-+Intel+Core+i3+1.8GHz+4GB+500GB+Touchscreen+Win+8+-+Steel+Gray/1307221723.p;jsessionid=F106556D71F330478974328D7411FD3D.bbolsp-app01-124?id=mp1307221723 skuId=1307221723 st=asus%20q200e cp=1 lp=1#tab=specifications  
  
I have a desktop to work from by I've been finding myself away form it and it would be convenient to be able to work without it at times. I'd prefer not to spend more than 600.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking for a film... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 16:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a film about a woman who is doing a photo shoot on the beach. The beach has a history with slavery. The woman, who is african american then has flashbacks and participates in the slave history that occurred there learning a lesson on exploiting herself when her people were exploited here many years ago.  
  
I don't think it was an "educational film" but I had seen it in university. I was just wondering if this sound familiar to anyone, I'd like to be able to find it, thanks.  
  
Matt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recent Haul(s) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-02 15:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's an [album](http://imgur.com/a/C5Jc4) of the recent cigars I picked up. I popped into a small smoke shop by the G train Fulton stop on my way to dinner, I had left my cutter at home and hoped to pick up a cheap one. Anyway I had forgotten about the place and went in there having bought tobacco there before. I wasn't aware they had a humidor though. Well after noticing the humidor I checked out there selection and it was pretty solid.     
  
The last picture is a recent order from Cigar Monster. It's 3 5 Packs. My Uzi Weighs A ton, Olivia Serie G, and The Romer y Julieta Capulet.  
  
Alec Bradley Black Market    
Partegas 1845 Black Label Tubo  
2x Ashton Cabinet (Belicoso)  
Rocky Patel Vintage 1990  
Rocky Patel Vintage 1999  
Arturo Fuente Double Chateu Fuente (i think, I grabbed this from a different shop real quick the other day)  
Rocky Patel Decade    
Perdomo Fresco
La Gloria Cubana Serie R  
Punch Rare Corojo 10th Anniversary    
  
and then my first stop at the smoke shop (penultimate picture)  
  
Partagas 1845 Black label  
Alec Bradley black Market  
Rocky Patel decade
  
Sorry if I'm off with any of these I rushed this post. Anyone who has seen some of my past posts know that I usually include Vitolas and keep it detailed, neat and orderly. I have been meaning to get this up and wanted to before I smoke anymore of them. There were a couple more that are already enjoyed.  
  
Oh yeah and two Drew Estate Java's. I kind of grabbed them in a rush and figured if I'd like any flavored cigar it'd be a coffee flavored one and thought I'd have it in the morning. Smoked one, the other is moments away from the trash bin. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> P3 at the Spa and then P4 at Del Mar...as Ice Cube said, today was a good day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 22:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saratoga Race 10 Pick 3, $2 (total $4): 7/3, 14/7   Paid: 373
  
I played it after capping the Pick 4 for normal sunny/fast conditions and realized the spa was the slop yesterday. I got knocked out of the P4 in the first race, readjusted my handicapping for the slop and played this.   
  
Del Mar Pick 4 $2 ($54 total): 1, 5, 7/ 1, 2, 6/2/3, 5, 9 (i also played this for .50 with the 1 horse for the last race $9 total I think)  
  
Paid: $964
  
  
Not a bad day. Feels good too ya know. If you hit one you know you did it but hitting two, two different tracks, it is a nice reminder that I can cap something.  
  
edit: actually let me be clear this was for Saturday (the woodward and del mar derby). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monster Mashup is killer today, deals on a bunch of stuff that /r/cigars tends to like </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 03:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.cigarmonster.com/  
  
Liga Privada No. 9, A few Arturo Fuente deals, Undercrowns, RP's, Boveda Humidity Packs, and a few samplers that are pretty solid in their own right.  
  
Enjoy fellas, don't break the bank! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moisture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 10:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it matter of the size of the crystal humidifier I'm using. If it's rated for 250ct. but I only have 50 sticks in a smaller area, will it bring the humidity too high? I have a boveda pack that is a week or so old to use, and it seems to have been working well so far but thought i'd switch over to the humidifier.  
  
I've read the wiki and I'm pretty sure I'm alright but figured I'd ask, can't hurt.  
  

Any tips on using the crystals otherwise?  
 
 Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just giving a heads up on CUNTINT/FoH orders... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 06:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case you didn't receive the email...They had sent out an email updating people who have made recent purchases that they have been slow to ship due to volume from their sale last week.  
  
Figured I'd let you guys know in case the email ended up in the spam folder or something and you're wondering why it hasn't shipped within the week.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cigars International CotM Club? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 20:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Figured I'd ask you gents if you've had any experience with CI CotM club? I imagine they send some decent sticks. As a new smoker I think it would be good to try for a few months (I may have just found my answer) in order to broaden my tastes.  
  
So have any of you subscribed in the past? Currently? What's the scoop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just picked these up! First stop to my local lounger/shop, Maxis Cigar Lounge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 07:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got my summer sampler!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 21:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free short stories? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 04:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I'm wondering if we could maybe compile a list of links for short stories that are out on the web. Obviously I'm not looking to start of list of illegally posted stuff or places to pirate books. I'm looking to just create something so everyone can share one of their favorites or gems that they have hidden somewhere on the net or even a favorite poem posted somewhere.  
  
I was coming just to ask about where I could find some and thought that as a community we could all benefit from this and thought maybe we coul jsut make a list and then compile it later. We'd certainly be helping the authors by getting exposure and views to the sites that may kick benefits their way. We also get to enjoy stories, find some new ones perhaps, and maybe find some places that have some of our own favorites or classics that are now easily accessible so we don't need to fish out that short story collection from our (often unorganized libraries).  
  
So how about it /r/book where the ish at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lions of Summer - Vanity Fair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 18:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> capital cities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 13:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey just a quick question about BNW. I was a bit late really getting into my first game (release happened around same time as COH2) and I just started playing. I picked Assyria to try out a new civ and I've been leading. Isabella and I were allied and she backstabbed me early. Brought the heat but not much siege equipment. I held her of (barely). I really thought she should have captured my city. The health was low, she still had a melee unit. It almost got down to pretty much zero. Did they change city strength or at least make it more difficult for capital cities to be captured? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> well this is it...time to keep on. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 22:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so for a long time i've tried to convince my parents to use some measly savings to allow me to write a book.  kind of like an advance but from some money i received as an inheritance. like 10k. i had big ambition. get an apartment, write my book, get 'er done.   
  
of course that wasn't going to happen. then one of those shitty inspirational quotes struck me. along the lines of, if a writer waits for ideal setting, he'll never write anything. I just finished my coursework for uni and i'm applying for jobs, something i don't plan on stopping. I've also been writing. A lot. SO I said fuck it, i'm doing my novel.  
  
And that's basically what I told ma. I said, listen I'm doing this over the summer, the next two months really. you can help me out or not but I'm certainly not going to work waiting and squandering this opportunity. A time when I have nothing going on, can wake up 8 hours a day, and write this damn thing. Come the second week in august I'll start shopping around for a catering job.  
  
Before I can blasted as spoiled and rich, I've worked since I was 14. I became an EMT at 18, a paramedic at 20, and only stopped working last August to take up an internship writing for a local news group. Internship finished, school finished. I have a few months and I'm going to do it. I'm 25, time to get on. Miles Davis didn't play the trumpet on the side, Micky Mantle didn't play baseball on the side, spielberg didn't shoot movies on the side.  
  
My writing shouldn't be second to anything. So here it goes.  
  
Plus I think it may have convinced her to throw me a couple grand to live off for the next two months, which would be nice. if not, i'll be rolling a lot of cigarettes.  
  
I guess I'm just excited, to have decided to do it, ya know. It's just one of those things. A it of a relief actually and it has never been more socially relevant (my novel) than in the present. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey I made a steam group for redditors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-26 02:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously invite yoru friends who aren't redditors as well. I figured it would be nice to be a part of an active group for this game anyway.  
  
  
So come on by and join it, hang out, chat, and lets play! Here's the link:  

http://steamcommunity.com/groups/COH2redditgroup  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know this comes up from time to time but what are the absolutely finest short story collections that everyone must experience in their life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 11:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this comes up from time to time but in light of the askreddit question regarding the most beautiful classical pieces, what are the most beautiful crafted short story *collections* that everyone must read in their lifetime?   
  
Name the collection and, like a movement of a classical piece, name the story that shines the brightest, drew you to the collection or is just simply a damn good read.  
  
sorry if it pisses people off, just thought i'd break the "library" trend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:Why people feel the need to circumvent a "would you rather" question instead of just answering it straight on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 11:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the title sums it up but if someone could shed some light on this. I know it is obviously related to a recent askreddit post (so sorry if that upsets you) but I'm curious why we have that response.  
  
 For example someone poses would you rather have a million bucks a year for the rest of your life or a lump sum of 70 million and people feel the need to respond with an answer like well if I take the 70 and put 30 in some bonds i'll make 750k a year on interest and almost have a million a year *and* 20 million to play with after taxes.  
  
I know that isn't the best example but I think you understand what i'm saying.   
  
Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Summertime Livin' (and it's easy)] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 10:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once heard summertime livin is easy  
And young and dumb  
Brass monkey fun  
Nothing of that, is a fallacy  

But you see growin up  
Makes you shave that scruff,  
And 40s and handball  
Just dont make the cut  
 
Which is a damn shame, Ill tell ya,  
Cause when we were young  
It was all fun  
And youth, was youth proper  
 
Young, young, Young.  
And what we lost wasnt just innocence,  
That was long gone  
Virginities lost on the convent lawn  
 
Fights and not the soda-type sugar rush, coke nights  
And so many handcuffs but not for behind locked door fun  
But metal bar celled locked to a bench expensive lawyer shit  
No longer just kids fun  
 
So none of us are quite yet done even with  
So much of that hung up  
But together we grew up on those kegs  
In those parks  
 
And now where we are we can thank  
Those healed broken knuckles and  
Running from cop muscles in our legs  
For who we are, better or worst  
 
But really just for luck  
That were the couple who made it this far   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Maybe There Is A Problem] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 10:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I thought creatively I was constipated,    
Like Ive been taking too many pain meds, for a broken heart,   
Days in a row cant shit type constipation  
That you cant go to the doctor and say      
Hey, its just self-medicating, give me a god damn laxative!     
Who wouldve known Id even make it this far  
That monkey on my back throwen a wrench in my spokes  
Of my only transportation, that beat up bike or other stolen three  
Especially since I havent had my license for more than a year, consecutively.  
That was never me being me and I cant give you an excuse  
For the booze and dope and smoking all that shit that Nancy suggested  
I just say No!   
But if you have been down that addled path  
Its as dark as it looks  
And at a certain point when it keeps turning left  
You look around and see the circle you keep making   
With the same beat up boots  
And you stop draggin them on the floor  
Clinging to childhood underwear drawer  
Empty of all the goodies from the night before  
And life kind of feels like the walking dead  
But I cant make sense if youre the zombie or am I  
And Im just slowly dying  
Or is this what its called  
When Im just 21st century surviving   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wrote this up real quick in this early hour with talented vs good writing on my mind </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-10 11:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently, read an article differentiating good writing from talented writing. You see and experience good writing all the time. Your (hopefully) office memos, school reports, and any other document youve crafted for someone elses eyes will consist of good writing. Writing technically accurate. Writing sans spelling errors. Writing how writing is supposed to be done. Im sure I could go off on a tangent on our poor standard in this field (especially as a writer myself) but Ill save you the diatribe. Talented writing youve experienced too. Talented writing youve read in your novels or in an essay. Its that writing that feels right. That writing that works so inexplicably well its transcendent. Its that writing from Salinger or Nobokov. That writing that makes you understand a pedophiles lust. Like really? You read Lolita and you understand where hes coming from. And for some fucked up reason you kind of root for the guy, because hes made you understand a human emotion on such a universal level. All because he can manipulate words and your mind with skill no less than a virtuosos.  
  

The article gives a few authors accounts on talented writing. They all talk about the finer points of what elevates that writing to another level. Theres no doubt, as the [article](http://www.brainpickings.org/index.php/2013/05/20/good-writing-vs-talented-writing/) (many of you may have read this already) notes, theres something poetic about talented writing. The talented writer is overly descriptive, in the most positive way possible. They pick up on things no one else does. In a recent conversation it was discussed seeing our inner monologue as if it was written word. Theres a way to piece together a scene or an event that others cant.   
  

That is what makes talented writing. As difficult as it seems to be to pin down exactly what enables someone to do that, Id like to give it a shot. Well, I think, I can definitely speak on one part of what makes this happen. It is something natural. It is also something fostered. It takes work. Time and work. You just dont sit down and magically put out The Sun Also Rises but there is a way a talented writer creates a scene, develops a character. It comes from some place deep within.   
  

The talented writer is able to put into words what lust is. What desire is. He or she can conceive unrequited love. Theres an advanced understanding of basic human emotion. It certainly is something natural because it comes from a natural place. Not only do writers experience these strong emotion, they know how to write them down.    
  
 
Thats simplifying it. So lets look at an example. Men want many things. Nothing throughout history has been sought after more and is the most relatable to every guy with a touch of testosterone than a women. On a very basic level a women understands this too, on both levels. She understands what it is to be sought after and to seek her own lover. More so than understanding love itself is lusting after another. Great stories abound about someone seeking power or riches, and too great stories abound for those seeking another but also, every one of us, knows what it is to seek that person.    
  

That person that makes every inch of your skin scream to crawl after her. An hour in her presence is near unbearable. She cant hide all those right curves under a dress. The second the compliment leaves your mouth your mind has already taken her out of that dress. When you take those delicate fingers in your hand, press close and give her a kiss on the cheek, your toes beg to curl and you might just explode at the thought of that same hand leading you away. And the scent. Always just right. Her perfume, her smell. It matches her dress and it matches her hair, its what beautiful smells like youd swear. Its more than just right and perfect isnt quite enough. Youd swear she studied fashion, shes always put together but you know it's something natural. That kind of beauty never tries. How natural would it be to have her, to know her. Letting everything fall away. Letting it all melt away in purely adultered lust. A night out, a couple drinks, skin on skin, lips on lips. Her tongue on your neck as you softly grab her ear between your teeth. The exact kind of summer sweat you dont mind. Chills down the spine, orgasms so shaking you dont want to move, let alone trying to. Its feeling a lust so guttural, carnal doesnt begin to describe where it comes from. It starts to become not if or wanting but when and how when you lock eyes. You look through her to expose every inch of those unfettered thoughts that are so wrong but you know, youd make feel so right. But you still dont know if youll ever her get her, so close but a couple worlds away. Her man, your girl but those delicate touches and embracing looks cant help but force you into a near frenzied drive for her.   
  

I dont know how I did, explaining lust but I know where I wrote that from. Its understanding that feeling as a passion. Its experiencing that. Its letting what naturally comes, to come, and let it out. Its strong and raw. Sometimes wrong but at a basic level, on a human level, something can be so right about it. Thats where talented writing comes from. I cant say for sure if Im a talented writer, I sure as hell try. I do know where you can rake talented writing out of though. When you sit down to put those words to paper know that place youre coming from. Know that feeling. Know that feeling and understand the passion behind it, then youll be able to write it down in an universally understandable way.   
 
On a side note, understanding that passion will make you more dedicated to getting it out right too, and that will motivate all that rewriting, that this essay surely needs.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [askreddit] HaHaGoodLuck explains the moment he decided against suicide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 10:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got a question regarding an interview I have tomorrow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 21:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only was notified about the interview today, they apparently are moving pretty quickly with this whole thing. I was wondering if someone could shed some light on something I'm a bit unfamiliar with. I'm an English Major with background in social media and journalism. I didn't embellish my resume or anything like that, I was pretty straightforward with what I am capable of doing.    
  
The company does business to business campaigns and it something I am certainly not familiar with. I took marketing classes but never got into that. They were pretty forward in the advertisement about working with potential employees and training but still I don't like not feeling knowledgeable on a subject.   
  
They talk about outsourced marketing too, which is really foreign to me. I'd love if anyone could shed some light on both these topics. I started doing my own research but reddit tends to have some knowledgeable folks hanging around.   
  
THe position is for account executive, and i'm somewhat familiar with that just not entirely so in this context. Any help is appreciated. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game Friday 5/25 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 07:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey me and another guy are trying to get a multiplayer game together for tomorrow night around 9 or 10 Eastern. Anyone interested?  
  
As much as I'm enthralled about setting up a massive 6v6 game I'd be skeptical of everyone's connections and all that nonsesne, plus it would probably take forever. I'd like to keep it to 2v2 or 3v3, depending on the response. We have 2 already, first come first serve. Leave a comment below if you want in but please be serious. We'll start tomorrow at 9 or 10 and probably play late into the night till we finish. We can even work out any other details or anything else we may want to do something interesting  or risque perhaps?  
 
SO holla for a dolla honey boo boo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> graduation present </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-19 03:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/ltG0i
  

Romeo and Julieta, Partagas, Cohiba, Ramon Allones, Montecristo; Julieta no.2/churchills
  
honestly I probably can't appreciate what I have here. But I will learn to like I have with other finer things in life. I just graduated from college, BA in English. My girlfriend's dad gave me these 5 as a gift. Not sure what to try first, I'm not super familiar with cigars outside of being able to recognize them. Any input is appreciated.
 
i think he's making a good case for father in law.  
  
edit: sorry for the first album, wrong photos uploaded, lack of context </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Allergic Reaction on Hand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-12 04:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request, Nassau/Queens] Graduation Pizza Would Be Much Appreciated! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-12 03:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heyy guys, it's that time in my life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 11:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To ask yall for a job! No, I'm kidding but I am searching and have a resume available. I'm based out of New York and I'm looking to move up from my current position. I'm a strong writer with a solid work ethic. My understanding of the online news era and multimedia approach to comprehensive story coverage has grown immensely over the last year and I'm looking to apply my skills at a higher level within the field. I've been applying to jobs but it can be tough just applying cold via the internet. So if anyone knows a particular place to look I'd appreciate the heads up. I know asking for a referral through the internet seems like an absurd idea but check out some of my writing samples [first](http://mineola.patch.com/groups/around-town/p/mineola-bicycle-holds-second-annual-womens-bike-ride), [or here](http://newhydepark.patch.com/groups/around-town/p/new-playroom-donated-at-cohen-childrens-medical-center), [or this one](http://mineola.patch.com/groups/around-town/p/former-mineola-resident-publishes-first-novel). Due to the website being in transition it may be difficult to search for more articles but I've published over 50 stories, all with my own photography and video.  
  
I enjoy Jazz and classical music. I also love to fish when I'm not writing. Writing really is a passion of mine and see myself dedicating my life to it. Over the last year though that passion has really grown from solely writing to a multimedia approach of covering things. Whether they are stories or creative projects. If anyone knows of something particular going on I'd love to hear about it. If you want to flesh me out a bit more I can forward you a resume. My linked writing samples pretty much dox me but if I can help from directly posting my address and phone number I will. I appreciate anyone who steps up and anything sent my way. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Different idea for a scenario </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-27 09:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking, this is a bit different but would be pretty cool. What if (it may be done in a mod already) they did a scenario with zombies. Like a OCC maybe or something like where you had to reconquer a land. Make the enemy vities just produce a unit that attacks but can take over your own unit. I guess it would be war heavy and the creative process needs to be expanded upon, maybe we can do that here, but while the idea just popped into my head I figured I'd just get it out.   
  
Definitely could be worked from both angles separately or together. A defensive scenario defending your city with limited offense to secure your city or make it an offensive scenario to restart civilization. make cities have negative populations or something that you need to kill before you can take and restart. I don't know lets come up with ideas and let the devs know to make it DLC! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Couple ideas I've been kicking around towards play </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-27 05:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i KNow moving up in difficulty, especially across the king threshold can be difficult for people. Myself included. I have been holding my own and I think it is only a matter of time really now, and in one of my games as long as i survive a science win is almost inevitable. Anyway short rant aside, I've been thinking returning to Prince though and playing for a particular win might help. My problem was I always dominated on Prince and didn't see and benefit in playing it anymore, to the point Civ got boring but I found King difficult. This is in part to my willy nilly approach on prince, since I was up so much I could dick around and on the higher levels you can't do that. You have to go for your win and do it. I was thinking if I kicked back to Prince to practice going straight for a science or culture or whatever it would help my with my King play and the victory I'm pursuing.  I'm curious as to what other people think, or if others ever return to the preceding difficulty that they are comfortable playing on while they are trying to move on up.  
  
Also I was wondering if anyone feels the scenarios help your play. I know they always helped in other games but I wasn't sure about them in Civ and since the games can be engrossing I always just went straight for a normal game. It isn't like oh let me bang out a couple scenarios before I get into my game (or at least that is how I felt about them). If they are helpful or only a particular helpful, I'd love to know what your experiences are and which ones can benefit what parts of play style. They all seem pretty domination/war heavy but doesn't mean certain aspects or some diplomacy might not be had.   
  
Oh and if you could get back to me ASAP so I know whether to play a scenario tonight or not, that'd be great...lol just kidding. Thanks again, this sub is one of my favorites in the large website and even massiver interwebz. Thanks guys and gals!  
  
TL;DR curious as to other peoples experiences while trying to move up to a higher difficulty if they return to a lower difficulty to help their play in pursuing whatever victory they are after (and to help play in general on higher levels, like going back to prince when trying to beat king for the first time) Also do scenarios help your play style, and if they do which scenarios help and what aspects of it. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick Question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 06:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I've been getting better at King. I've posted before on improving my play on King over prince. I usually dominate on Prince, winning however I feel like it by the end of the game but going up to king have found myself not being bale to even keep up. Well I've been keeping up now and am within striking distance to win now, most of the time.  
  
So I'm doing better but I sto;; need o work on a few things. I've done better managing an army early on, that was one of my flaws as I got better I'd do so at my defense expense and get wiped off the map. With that base covered I'm thinking I next need to work one 1) keeping a runaway civ in check and 2) Some mods look like they would help, like infographics. I don't know if I want to sacrifice the challenges though. How do yall feel about this and how do you guys play it? 3) Have the scenarios improved your gameplay at all?  
  
my main question is about the mods vs giving up the challenges thing though. Any feedback is much appreciated and thanks for the help so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hey got a question? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 06:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I've seen similar posts but I still haven't been able to figure this out. Sorry if yall feel offended by the question because you've answered it before but I need some help.  
  
I absolutely own on prince. Like dominate. I can win with a shit ton of science/culture/military/gold/all of them if i want. When I up it to kind I can't win. At first I didn't play well at all but now I've become pretty good. I'm usually in the top half of civ's and within 100 points or so except for the rare occasion of a runaway civ on top. So I'm within striking distance it feels but except for the beginning of the game where i'm often on top. ANyway as the game progresses the only way to surpass the top civs though seems like war. Now i don't expect to go the whole game without waging some war but it seems like the only option. Even if I focus jsut on science or just on whatever and even if i don't declare war and only maintain a modest army, i'm declared on. Any tips on playing or chanhes you make while going up in difficulty particularly?  
  
I think that one of my problems is being very widespread as I build and research. I try to do it all ya know and I know you need to be more focused at higher levels. Any tips on what improvements are necessary per city? What population I should shoot for per city? I usually play wide sometimes i play between wide/tall and rarely tall with only a few cities (mostly because  I find it very difficult). I usually play standard game speed, sometimes epic or marathon when I have the time. I play standard map size, sometimes i mix it up with random or go large or small. Very rarely do I play duel or tiny it's always between small and huge. Map type is random often but usually try to play something like continents or earth. I want to play the mod real earth map but not until i knock off a bunch of achieves. Sometimes I up the city state or civ amount for my game size but don't often as i play wide and while I used o be more aggressive militarily I'v toned it down. I honestly think that has been my mistake because i usually have my hardest time when I'm declared war on. I am never really killed but it sets me back since I ave to divert resources to constructing an army since I haven't been consistently including it in my development. That's because I find it harder to keep stay competitive while diverting too much time too troop building. I've been player my empire bigger and bigger lately and that's made it easier. Taking time to construct troops with a city or two but not enough troops apparently because damn civs like war. So maybe I identified my own problem rubber ducking this out to yall but any tips are appreciated. Particularly while upping difficulty. Maybe I felt since I was moving up I should learn to be more diplomatic and play less militarily since it can feel a lot like starcraft when I'm only army building. But I knwo this game is far from SC and that's why I love it. I also knwo an army and war is an essential part to a civ and has bee nthrough history so don't knock me on that comment. SOrry for the wall of text.  
  
tl;dr need help improving my play while upping difficulty from prince to king. i own on prince, never lose, go to king and i'm mediocre. play standard size, standard speed, usually wide play style, random but usually continent like map type  
  
edit: yeah so basically i just need bigger armies the harder the play style and i may have really enjoyed civ iv if i played it. but i'd have to say even though micro managing for a cultural victory would be sweet, in reality if you are going to be the best civ you should have a bad ass army, everyone has done it through history what makes us exempt in civ5? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [There's two type of people in the world. Jeopardy people and Wheel of Fortune people. You want to be around Jeopardy people." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 08:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Resume Critique </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 10:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any help is much appreciated...  
  
https://docs.google.com/document/d/1D8vLnQS3BP-tLrXljy-RKoZm6x6-20beCb0v4fOagC0/edit?usp=sharing  
  
i left off the self started tutoring/editing work i did in college and my first restaurant job, which i made assistant manager at...just no room to keep it one page.       
  
  
Thanks Folks!

-Matt

edit: updated version: https://docs.google.com/file/d/0B3U9X_sUHTivYUo1RzZleVFQUTg/edit?usp=sharing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He only prefers *Bear*Berry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 04:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-17 05:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think websites and people who are writing about the Road to the Derby Races need to start including how many points the race is worth next to the races. For example:  
  
*This weekend we have three upcoming races. Derby Prep Race 1 (10) Derby Prep Race 2 (10) Derby Prep Race 3 (30)*  
 
editL i'm glad i wasn't hung since the prep races are guided by dates but we still refer to races in the near future and past. so idea is still ~~relevant~~ applicable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think this would be an interesting read, I just have to figure out how to write it. Meet my idea about writing on racetracks.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 12:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an idea for a book I'd like to write and I was wondering what /r/horseracing[1] thought. I'd like to group 8 or 10 tracks together (by location probably) and write about them. I know horse racing is a tight knit community but dwindling fan base at the same time but a lot of racetracks helped sustain certain areas and they are intertwined economically, socially, and historically. So if I spent like 3 days at Lexington I could write about the town and going out on it eating, how places are linked to the track, who is linked to the track and how. Just make it an interesting travel read on some smaller, some bigger, towns and particular areas of America that has history with the racetracks.  
  
  
  
I'd also spend a day or a day and a half at the track. Write about wins, losses, the handicapping and overall focus on the track itself. Its paddock, its stables, the backstretch, its own history, any unique features (infield of pimlico or backyard of Belmont, Fair Grounds holds Jazzfest etc.) Definitely include some handicapping though about how certain picks worked on the track and why they didn't. I'd like to make it a fun book of ups and downs and wins and losses along my travels. How far i made it on my gambling. I'm sure when I end up struck out somewhere I'll have some existential reflection to do. My experiences of self discovery among the people i meet will make for interesting material. Hopefully and importantly (as travel writing) I can introduce people who aren't familiar with horseracing and show them how extensive the sport is, how much fun it can be and tell a damn/fun good story.  

So I'd have like 10 tracks, visit and write about the trip, ideally a road trip but maybe several smaller trips and do a few tracks per trip or maybe even individual trips to each track. Ideally one road trip would be the best. Make it a fun book about smaller town America. About the racetracks that helped build these towns and shape America's early landscape, and even its later landscape. The smaller B B's and stuff and then also write about my day at the track there and the handicapping and everything and more about the rich atmosphere of whatever track, the history and beauty of any outstanding. I'd also keep a blog and maybe do some webisodes on the net. I would consider travelling with my cousin and definitely with my gf.  
  
Is it something you would consider reading? Any ideas on how to get funding for something like this? Does funding for a project like this exist? Can I kickstarter it? I'm not asking to get 5k and go to CD and blow it all gambling, I'm look for money to help pay to get down there and for me to take the time to write.Any funding I get would go mostly to travel costs, I'd pay for my own gambling. Any tips on how I could get this done on the cheap? More importantly how does this sound as an idea to you? Does it sound interesting? Does it sound like there is something of worth here? Any feedback would be great. I mean this essentially is my dream, horseracing and writing are two of my biggest passions in life. To be able to write about horseracing, horses and the different tracks would truly be a dream come true. I grew up on Belmont and have always loved the uniqueness, the beauty and the general feel of a track. On top of the history of it (as I enjoy history too) which is equally as unique. I almost think of it as 10 racetracks you should visit before you die or 10 towns built on racing. Any ideas or feedback is much appreciated, like I said this would pretty much be a dream come true for me. I know this wouldn't make a very good query letter but I'm just writing this informally to you guys (of this awesome subreddit, love it here) to get your opinions.
  
  
Thanks a lot. Really trying to make this happen.  
  
  
TL;DR I'd like to write a book about the racetracks in america. Their history, the towns connected to them and the track itself. Spend some time in the town and then a day at the track and write about the experiences. Preferably do it over a road trip. Looking for feedback, any ideas and any tips on how to find funding for it. Thanks again.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Floating Periods, some advanced engineering for the classical era! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 12:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a little advice... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 10:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyways, I'm coming back. Why I ever stopped playing, I'm not sure. I think I got caught up with school and this was hurting my grades...as I look over at the clock and it's 5 am atm, haha.  
  
I'm wondering, I was never really into too much DLC but I've been reading and want to give some of it a shot. Should I just go for the GOTY upgrade (I already have G K's) or should I just selectively grab a couple here and there. I'm looking at the prices and at around 7$ each I might as well just get the GOTY edition, or wait for a sale and try and grab it cheap. 
  
 Any recommendations? Should I pass on GOTY cause it's not worth it and just DL the civ's on my own and for for free DLC? So far I have infoaddict,~Korea~ I D/L North Korea...lol (is there a reunification scenario in the GOTY), Perfect World 3, Play the world, (got it on accident hope it's somewhat cool at least and well made) and maybe one more that isn't significant. I'd like to pick up the other civ's though like Babylon, SPain and the Incas. That's 12 bucks right there, do I make the jump for GOTY, is it worth it or am I set with what I got? What perks do I get from GOTY in addition to the civs? (I read it but not sure what they are applied in game) Any help would be great! So glad I found this subreddit, sparked my entry back into this lustful, love obsessed relationship I call playing civilization. Thanks guys!   
  
Hi /r/civ I'm Matt and I'm addicted to civilization!  
  
edit: I think I'm going to go with GOTY, I'd still like to hear input. Also does the DLC from GOTY disable acheivements? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is a pretty cool idea and just trying to help with some exposure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 09:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I first came to reddit the first thing that popped into my head was "I bet some people play Axis and Allies on here." Then I came here and was slightly disappointed. Nah I'm kidding, I found a great place (i mostly lurk) and since have played Settler, 7 wonders, CAH, and Ticket to Ride, and have a to-play list. It allowed me to reach out and I found [this place](http://www.gamerterrain.com/?page_id=2) near my town. (don't click it yet!)
  
Okay enough back story (sort of). I also am a local journalist and the owners of the above place have also done something else really cool. They opened up a restaurant called the [Game Master Grill](http://www.gamemastergrill.com/) that is board gamed themed and I had [to cover it](http://mineola.patch.com/articles/playing-with-your-food-at-game-master-grill) since it was new in town. You can go and get dinner, food is excellent btw, and buy a game and play. I asked him and you can bring your own too or just play one of the small dice or card of board games that he has there while you wait for your food. You can play/eat/eat/then play/show up start playing and throughout or take a break to eat, if you want to take a while go on a slower night and hang out. They'll even deliver a board game with your order. It is a really neat idea and a cool place.  
  
Generally it is a fun store and really nice. The staff will all teach you games. I've ate a couple times there and they helped teach my girlfriend a couple games as well,as taught us both some small games, when we didn't want to stay too long, to play while we waited for our food. They even have a neat zombie dice game! The place hasn't picked up too quickly though and could use more exposure. The owner is a greatguy who worked in the restaurant business for 17 years, got an opportunity to open a board game store a few years ago and took it. He is a veteran, a good guy, and passionate about board games, particularly about teaching people how to play new games. I want to see if I can help the place out by showing you guys a cool place you'd appreciate (maybe spurn a new idea for a restaurateur out there) and get him more exposure. Tell your NY/Long Island buddies about it. Go yourself if you are in the area, check out his site (the menu is super neat and creative with the titles of some dishes).  
  
Again here is the site for the restaurant [Game Master Grill](http://www.gamemastergrill.com/) and this is the, linked above too [article] (http://mineola.patch.com/articles/playing-with-your-food-at-game-master-grillhttp://www.gamemastergrill.com/) I wrote about the place. I don't need "views or anything" I'm actually an intern so I don't even get paid. I just thought the article was relevant to help spread the word. I was going to just make a post like check out this place, with the link, but I wanted to be upfront with my intentions and let everyone know a little more about the place. So thank's again guys for anyone and even if it's only one person chcking it out! PM if you have questions or anything.  
  
edit: formatting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trunk Show @ Henri Bendel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 08:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey /r/nyc my friend is having a [trunk show at the Henri Bendel](http://marker.to/PM7nES) store on 5th Avenue between 55^th and 56^th streets. She's a really solid designer and does jewelry and accessories right now. She works for some great designers and is trying to get out on her own a little bit. ANy support, even showing up to check outher stuff would be great! I know valentine's day is coming up and she makes greaqt jewelry at affordable prices. Just figured I'd let people know, plus it's in a great store if you want or need something for v-day you can just shope there and check out her trunk show on the second floor.  
  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Streets - Stay Positive - YouTube </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 10:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does religion soften us in the face of tragedy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 02:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying we "explain away" things that are tough to understand, especially in the face of extreme evil but the potential is there for a lot of people to do so. Is it possible that because we rely on religion so heavily at times, that maybe we aren't turning to science soon enough, and create a distance between ourselves and what has happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey /r/atheism, help me out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 12:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for an e-reader? I know it's been asked before but it's been a year since it's been asked and tech changes, opinions Reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 11:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I said I'm looking for an e-reader and I want to be able to email, make notes and not strain my eyes. As for games I'm not a fan but I would download some apps I suppose. I mostly would want it just to read books, email, and mark up those books. So what does reddit think since the advent of Sony's e-reader and now that Kindle and Nook have been out for a bit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] A typewriter [NY, US] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-11 10:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's a bit odd but it's something I've always wanted. I also know they're cheap but I'm in school and interning and am just flat broke really. It would brighten up my holidays and it's just something I've always wanted to be able to write on. that's my passion, that's what I love to do and I always wanted a typewriter to do it on. It doesn't matter make or model really, I'd just love to type away on one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey my resume </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-09 05:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://docs.google.com/document/d/1Z-lVmnS7ESXal7Gf7N8-HT9mcuO94JrL0Ows2D-EH78/edit  
  
or  
  
http://imgur.com/zQnrQ  
  
It's my pretty basic and old resume. I'm redoing it as we speak was just wondering what people though about it. It's landed me a few jobs but i'm redoing it to be a bit more effective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My next move? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 03:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I currently intern (aka free staff writer) at a local online paper. Do all my own picture/video editing and writing. Upload it myself. A pretty independent thing. I've written for my school's paper. Not some bs stories either, usually community oriented or larger scale regarding politics. Also have done movies, music, restaurant reviews (started there, as a timid kid who didn't know how to write).  Now I have a pretty solid portfolio (which I could use tips on where and what to use as far as putting it online) and I write well. I know that doesn't always get you where you need to be but could I realistically look at some of these bigger papers/websites next? Or am I looking at this local/smaller publication for a couple more years? Am I destined to freelance out of college? I'm 25, have freelanced on occasion but nothing particularly worth noting atm and I'm graduating in the spring. Any tips where to look next? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Nassau County/Queens County, New York] I'm on probation and was pulled over driving with a revoked license in Queens. Will the tickets show in Nassau? (More inside) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-01 10:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title sums up the basics. I was pulled over in Queens and given two tickets, speeding and ID only. I'm on probation in Nassau and currently my license is revoked. I shouldn't have been driving but was in a tough spot. I actually had a licensed driver in the passenger seat but she was feeling ill and I had a final to get to get to. Stupid on my part as i have never driven since I lost my license. I have a good rapport with my PO and have not been violated yet. It honestly wasn't even a question about telling him and being honest, this thought of them not turning up and going unnoticed just crossed my mind. I'm supposed to contact my PO within  48 hours of police contact and this happened yesterday at ~3PM So could I get away with it? I know if he runs my name it will pop up but he doesn't really have a reason too. Any advice is appreciated, I'm most likely going to tell him an be honest up front. Follow up question is if he visits me within that 48hr window and I tell him then will I be immediately placed under arrest because I do have a obligations tome evening. So any advice? Would I be able to sneak by with these, as in just pay em and forget about it
When he does find out will I be arrested immediately?  
  
edit: wanted to add, I didn't want to call my own lawyer immediately because he is a very close family friend and listens to my parents wishes instead of mine, if it were up to me I would have served my 30 days and avoided 3 years of probation at the beginning of all this.  
  
edit: i'd also like to add i only received two traffic tickets, i wasn't charged with a misdemeanor or DAT, one ticket for ID only and another for speeding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ultra Orthodox Rabbi's trial begins...thought texas was bad? this is pretty extreme when it comes to protecting the accused  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-28 11:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suggestion for a new game to buy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-22 04:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking of buying a new game. I had written out a post and then must have deleted the txt on accident. So I'm going to keep it abridged now.  
  
I own: BF3, Civ5 w/ expan, Skyrim, SC2. D3, Witcher 2, WOW: MOP  
I'm considering: Blade and Steel, Shogun 2, Dishonored and Walking Dead
  
I enjoy anything that is all around a solid game. For that reason I'm passing on the new COD, the social aspect is usually why I buy it and play with my friends for two weeks but other than that I'm a BF3 (premium chea!) guy now. I'm also open to DLC for the games I have already or expansions. (I didn't buy Dawnguard) I've really have been enjoying multiplayer and that's why I've shied away from buying that. I'm pretty open minded as long as it is a solid game. I'm not the biggest fan of platform action/shooters but I did thoroughly enjoy the witcher. Also I enjoy WOW due to the game play and multiplayer. I do enjoy my RTS and strategy games in general (tried re-installing Company of Heroes).  That's why I'm considering going for Shogun2 even though it's old, i knw i'd enjoy it. So any suggestions? What have we bought recently? Anything I could really capitalize on with the steam Sales?  
  
Thanks guys n gals!  
  
Update: I think I'm going with Shogun 2. It'll probably be the one I get most out of and will also build my anticipation for Rome 2. Borderlands 2 and Far Cry 3 and Dishonored aren't ruled out but may be Xmas gifts rather than immediate buys. I've really fell out with FPS and really only look forward to HL3, now that I've thought about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My ears feel hot, how sexy do they look when that happens? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-22 03:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ears get hot sometimes. When they are all hot and bothered, how sexy do they look and whats the influence on my libido and the opposite sex? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Had a not so odd realization this week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-19 11:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Writing is hard, hard work. Maybe because it always came to me with relative ease but this ish is tiring and draining. I always felt drained after really working on something but I was always younger and maybe never noticed. Lately I've written quite a lot of stuff. Stuff that is good and worthy and I'm like shot.  
  
It's something I've always known but when I was younger and pooped out a short story I didn't think much of it. Now that I'm looking at this as a profession I'm like damn man, you bust your ass, have a cookie. It's kind of silly but helped me appreciate what people and I go through to put out consistently good stuff. Also made me want to work harder to continue at the level or past it. I'm just acknowledging something that I've been aware of but haven't truly experienced as really tough, especially when I took it to a much higher level. So cheers to all you hard working writers, we probably don't get enough credit for the mental work and we are surely underpaid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Article I wrote about what Obama's election means for America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-19 11:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://docs.google.com/document/d/1S3-Nyfu2j27j7o4-5Xm63s7HRo9UhcNBD3IOSAuf_jY/edit  
  
enjoy, love to hear feedback </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I have a script and I'm trying to shoot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 11:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently wrote a screenplay for class. It's solid and I'd like to shoot. the end game here is film festivals. I'm not being arrogant but the screenplay is good. Ideally I'd like to go as cheap as possible DIY. I also was considering doing it right though and trying to get funding through Kickstarter and Investors. I'm new to the film thing so I don't even know where costs lay.  
  
Anyone want to get on board? I want to register the script before I start emailing it out but if you wanted to meet up and read it I'd do that. Let me know if anyone is interested.  
  
It's going to happen one way or another. It needs to be made, it's good. So hop on board! pm me for my email. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Hey, Walt] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 06:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By: Matt R.

Theres beauty in nature  
Thanks, Walt,  
I figured that much out by now  
What was the matter?  
Too scared to look in?  
Never found that tick  
Stuck behind your ear  
Or what made you think  
We would care  
I get that, Walt.  
Theres beauty everywhere  
But did you ever look  
At a dead tree or stick  
A little twig  
And find the decaying mind  
Something worth reveling in?   
As a fungus comes over us   
Breaking each bit down  
Long after the ticks had its fill  
And our friends and family moved on  
Long after Im gone   
They will look to you for beauty  
Too scared to look within  

edit: formattng
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> you are in college work on your vocab, homie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 12:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL black male high school dropouts are more likely to be incarcerated than graduate with a four year degree and more are in jail than hold paying jobs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 04:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [It's Been A Month] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 17:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't really do it  
Only after a couple,  
More like a few,  
Stand myself up  
Stupor to the mirror and look.  
   
So easy for most!  
I dare not even in the morning  
After coffee and toast!  
I'm not sure why,  
Caring not to see myself cry  
   
It's usually late at night  
And I guess with some delight  
I do it and comb my hair,  
As my mom once did while I was young  
And I still do when approaching an interview  
   
Knowing that parted left hair  
And put together tie  
Will get me through any lie  
I mostly dare to tell myself  
In the end it's only me thanking me  
     
But the face in front of me  
As my hands go up  
And through my hair  
Is just that, mine,  
My pockmarked face  
   
Of no delight  
And the glasses I fought so little against  
The little blonde left over from August   
The stubble still after 3 days, an Irishman's delight  
And an almost tear swelling in my eye  
   
I look at me and think  
What I passed up due to hard work  
And what I could have been, passed  
And what is coming  
I feel my heart beating too fast, I check my pulse  
I'm right, I'm plainly, scared  
Dreadfully frightful of  
What I've entered  
Or opened and begun  
Of what kind of man I've become  
   
I've heard I'm good  
But refuse to believe it  
Selfish as I am, doing as I please  
I push those away who share love for me  
And continue on my path, tossing it aside like trash  
   
And I sit a half a bottle in  
Just to sleep  
And pretend for peace of mind  
My own scary dreams on rewind  
  
edit: spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not the mental image I need when playing at 4am </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-30 13:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [How It's Supposed To Be] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 11:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never understood how movies made those scenes work  
You know those ones  
Where one person sleeps and the other looks on  
After they made love  
  
Because every time I do so  
After  a one night stand I just feel awkward  
And even when its someone I love  
Like Im prying into something personal  
  
Even though we both know  
We just known each other   
As intimately as we would ever  
Despite sleeping together  
  
On the second date  
Before you let yourself down  
To how you should be when naked  
In front of each other  
  
Instead showing how you think  
People should see you stripped down  
To nothing  
Despite their really being nothing to see  
  
And just action to be taken  
And thats what we miss  
In film, when nothing has happened  
And despite being yelled, no action taken  
   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [US] I have a scroll for you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-11 16:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking to give this scroll out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 how to play a holy pali? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-05 12:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've kind of been put into a bind this upcoming school year. I need to make sure I secure funds for off campus housing. Any tips on the best way to go about this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-29 05:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would hate to take out more loans but due to my age (24) I am allowed to get the federal loans at a reasonably low interest rate. I have a little bit of money saved and I'm not adverse to work. My schedule is going to prevent me from getting too much work in the fall semester but in the spring I'm hoping to secure a 9-5 since I'm graduating in May/June and only taking two classes in the Spring freeing up my time. Even if I don't get the 9-5 I'll waiter to make rent, I've done it before.  
  
Right now I'm at home though and my parents are moving so I wouldn't be able to keep my current job. If I want to finish school I need to get my own place. I was considering moving out before I learned they were moving but decided against it due to my schedule and fear of not working enough to make rent. i'm thinking I might need to rely on loans to help me out for a few months in order to finish my degree. Any tips on making sure I get the money or any other solutions?  
  
Thanks.  
  
edit: spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey I'm taking a class called Literature of Disbelief this coming semester. ANyone care to shed some light on this reading list? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 00:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is my reading list.  
  
1.	D.H. Lawrence, The Man Who Died (use the Vintage edition of St. Mawr   The Man Who Died)
2.	Mark Twain, The Mysterious Stranger (provided in the Course Pack)
3.	Anatole France, The Revolt of the Angels (use the edition by Wildside Press)
4.	Elie Wiesel, The Trial of God (use the Schocken edition)
5.	Peter Shaffer, Amadeus (use the Harper Perennial edition)
6.	James Morrow, Blameless in Abbadon (use the Harcourt, Brace   Co. edition)
7.	Rebecca N. Goldstein, 36 Arguments for the Existence of God (use the Vintage Books softcover edition)  
  
ANyone care to shed some light of what I'm in store for here. I'm an undergrad but the professor invited me into the course after I took an undergrad course with him. Not only am I glad to be working on a grad level (undergrad is frightfully boring) I'm thrilled about the topic. ALso the professor is great so this should be a lot of fun. I've started 36 Arguments for the Existence of God and I love it. I'm an ENglish major with an above average vocabulary compared to other ENglish majors (did that make sense?) and I had to crack the dictionary a couple times for some of that vocab (nothing too crazy though and the few times were mostly for refreshing the memory.)             
  
So can anyone tell me which of these might be bores? I'm reading the bottom two before the semester starts since they're long. ANy others maybe I should tackle beforehand due to content being complicated? Any of them going to stand out and be great reads compared to the rest? I'm familiar with Twain's above but can't rememebr if I've read it some it must not have been recently.  
  
Thanks bunches and I hope this is in the right place at /r/atheism. Also if we can have any discussion about 36 AFTEOG or any of the other reads I'd love that. Cheers.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a 24 year old male from NY who has parents who don't support my career choice. Not only do they not support it they do not give it any validation. I'm thinking of moving out to genuinely pursue it, Any adivce? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 22:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To expand I'm an English major. My parents don't see any worth in being an English major. They do not see any viable career path in writing. They think if I choose to be a writer I'm choosing to go 'suffer' to do my writing. I understand they worry and care and want me to be able to support myself but you can support yourself writing. It's hard work but I have an excellent work ethic. I've worked since I was 14. my parents don't really see it that way. They always hark on me about what I'm doing.  
  
A big reason I think has to do with after I went to paramedic school I didn't want to pursue that as a career path. When I was about to get on the FDNY I went out drinking and got another DWI. Almost instead of telling them I don't want to start a career path that I'll be miserable in I got arrested so I couldn't do that. I know it's weird. They don't see it like I do. I firmly believe in following your dreams. I don't think you can put a price on happiness. My biggest issue is my parents don't  agree with that. They will say they will but when I choose to make a decision towards a job I'd like it is shot down with tons of negativity. This negativity is really taking a toll on me. I'm becoming depressed. I'm questioning my ambition and ability. What kills me the most is I'm an excellent student. I'll be finishing my bachelors this in the spring with a 3.5 GPA, worked the whole time since I was young and my parents don't see me making it all unless I follow a job they see as worthy.   
  
What they don't get it that I really need their approval for some reason. I always do stuff so that they'll see me as significant. Their approval is monument to me. I've brought this up to them and the whole situation. How I seek their approval, feel I don't get support from them and how it negatively effects me. I'm sorry if I'm coming off as whiny but I'm an adult with a job and all I ask my parents for is to support me with my decisions.  
  
I'm thinking of getting out of my house because it feels like it's becoming to negative for me. It's tearing my apart and down and I see nothing good coming from this environment. I haven't even touched on how they scoff at me creatively pursuing a career. I graduate in the spring and I'm looking for a job in my field, hopefully before I graduate. They fiercely disapprove of me moving out. If I did I'd ideally be moving  to Brooklyn, closer to school and where I'm going to look for a job. Obviously if I had to I'd take a job in a restaurant or bartend to support myself. They don't see me as being capable to do anything it feels like. I'm not sure if I should take some money I've saved up, about 5k and just get a place and figure it out or if I should tough it out till after I graduate and am working. I'm just not sure if I can put up with almost another whole year here. 

I've generally been pretty independent and capable individual. I grew up on the border of queens so I wouldn't be going to the big city with no clue to handle myself. I believe in myself to be able to do it. I'm thinking I just need to cut the string, that they are holding me back.

Edit: added last paragraph and changed spelling above
Edit2: Thanks for even these few responses, they have helped a bunch  
  
Edit3: Thanks for all the info. I recently weighed my for and against and figured I would try and hang on a little longer. My parents also think they are going to be moving a little sooner than everyone thought. I figured that I would have trouble making rent with my workload at school this coming semester. My schedule turned out to not be so forgiving. The spring semester I'll have plenty of time to work. With my parents news of moving though I may be forced out a little sooner so I may just have to manage with my little savings or something. Thanks for all the info though, much appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [I'm Not Lost (yet)] Some dickin' around poetry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 08:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh so many times they swore their support  
And I fought, not that, just its delivery system  
   
Thats not what I need I said again and again,  
Well tell us what it is and it wont fall on deaf ears  
   
So I thought Id scream it just in case  
But to no avail nothing changed, just the date  
   
And they all feared and said whatll you do  
With that English Degree that was all too useful  
   
I can write I said and I swore  
But mental work was given no reward  
Compared to physical labor  
And shed blood sweat and tears  
   
Even though thats what I give at 3 AM  
To this keyboard, paper and screen  
   
And even when I worked for a seventy hour week  
They told me in that business the work was too hard  
   
So you can see how I was left awfully confused  
With little outlet to be me I turned for the worst  
   
And almost let my imp get the better of me  
But I learned more about myself than I ever could  
   
And finally put my foot down and said this is what Ill do!  
Ill be me and write and love and fuck  
   
Ill eat, sleep and wear that stuff on my arms  
And when its said and done Ill be proper and glee  
   
For no one not you or her  
No one but me   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Maybe There Is A Problem] Just some more fuckin' around poetry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 02:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I thought creatively I was constipated  
Like Ive been taking too many pain meds for a broken heart  
Days in a row cant shit type constipation  
That you cant go to the doctor and say  
Hey, its just self-medicating, give me a god damn laxative!  
Who wouldve known Id even make it this far  
That monkey on my back throwen a wrench in my spokes  
Of my only transportation, that beat up bike or other stolen three  
Especially since I havent had my license for more than a year, consecutively.  
That was never me being me and I cant give you an excuse  
For the booze and dope and smoking all that shit that Nancy suggested  
I just say No to!  
But if you have been down that addled path  
Its as dark as it looks  
And at a certain point when it keeps turning left  
You look around and see the circle you keep making with the same beat up boots  
And you stop draggin them on the floor  
Clinging to childhood underwear drawer  
Empty of all the goodies from the night before  
And life kind of feels like the walking dead  
But I cant make sense if youre the zombie or am I  
And Im just slowly dying  
Or is this what its called  
When Im just 21st century surviving

Edit one and two: formatting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Summertime Livin' (and it's easy)] I was just fuckin around and started writing some poetry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 11:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once heard summertime livin is easy  
And young and dumb  
Brass monkey fun  
Nothing of that is a fallacy  
 
But you see growin up  
Makes you shave that scruff  
And 40s and handball   
Just dont make the cut    
 
Which is a damn shame Ill tell ya  
Cause when we were young  
It was all fun  
And youth was youth proper  
 
Young, young, Young   
And what we lost wasn't just innocence  
That was long gone  
Virginities gone on the convent lawn  
 
Fights and not the soda type sugar rush coke nights  
And so many handcuffs but not for behind locked door fun  
But metal bar celled locked to a bench expensive lawyer shit  
No longer just kids fun  
 
So none of us are quite yet done even with  
So much of that hung up  
But together we grew up on those kegs  
In those parks  
 
And now where we are we can thank  
Those healed broken knuckles and  
Running from cop muscles in our legs  
For who we are, better or worst  
 
But really just for luck  
That were the couple who made it this far     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hating God The Untold Story of Misotheism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 10:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any NYC Axis and Allies players want to get a game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 08:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYC Axis and Allies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 13:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
