<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2159</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What chiv is all about. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 02:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quarterstaff techniques </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 06:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Give a man the power to combo and... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 20:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why parry when I can just keep stabbing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 23:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this what EU duels look like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 03:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have no idea who'd want to watch this but there are a lot of good duels in here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 18:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> das footwork </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 21:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1000 Hours of Chivalry (Brandistock duels) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 18:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's all about the footwork. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 20:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Be careful where you dodge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 06:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> brandistock.avi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 22:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The matrix! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 05:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is the player animation quality poorer during cutscenes than regular gameplay? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 06:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is bugging the crap out of me. During cutscenes, my player waddles like a duck with her feet spread wide apart, has awkward posture while standing, and never seems to do any natural movements while in conversation. This is contrary to the NPCs that look fine and move fine during cutscenes, as well as gameplay where the player's walking and standing animations look great. Anyone else notice this?

Oh, this is on a female mage, if it matters. I haven't tested on a male character yet.

EDIT - I mean, just look at [this](http://i.imgur.com/QvpLM7Z.png) standing pose. It's just wtf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everybody get up, it's time to slam now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 17:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This game was MADNESS. Fucking knife guy! I love this game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 19:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4th Prestige in, I have decided this is the best submachine gun class there is. Holy crap. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 06:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disclaimer: this requires a professional gun variant of the ASM-1.

Alright guys, this shit is redonk. It's seriously good (at least for my playstyle). I've almost exclusively used SMGs for my time in AW and I have a few hundred kills with most of them. A couple thousand with the MP11.

http://imgur.com/a/tI7db#0

The mother fuckin ASM-1 Rigor. +2 Accuracy, for -2 Handling. Accuracy reduces recoil of aimed fire and handling only affects your hip fire. That's fine, I rarely shoot from the hip with this thing.

[See here for more attribute information.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aCUdAjFpk1g list=UUk8cNb10L5rmV9xB13ADCWA)

Attachments: Foregrip + Rapid Fire + Stock.

This thing has minimal recoil. Normally, you throw rapid fire on an SMG to make it a hip fire monster as the ADS recoil is significant. NOT THIS THING. Even without the foregrip it's still a manageable amount of recoil. With it though, this gun is a laser beam of rapid fire from the highest damage SMG in it's class.The +2 accuracy from the Rigor variant really shows off here. I thought about throwing a laser sight on here, but nah. The stock provides the gun the mobility that a laser sight would offer, but also building off the gun's natural strengths. The hip fire is still decent, it does have rapid fire so you'll at least be able to spam bullets if you need to before you can get a good ADS. Oh and, in case you didn't realize, do you know what happens when you have fast fire rate and minimal recoil? You now also have a long range weapon.

As far as perks go, these seem pretty standard/self explanatory. You could probably swap Low Profile for Overcharge if you wanted. I may do that. For the Exo Ability, I use Overclock for Kill Confirmed and I use Ping for Hardpoint or other objective based game modes.

The playstyle of this gun is very much SMG with the added bonus of this thing being able to act like an assualt rifle at longer ranges. The first few bullets of a burst fire faster, so if you have multiple targets to shoot at, I start a burst for each of them if I can (assuming you killed the first guy).

I'm going to upload some footage tonight of me playing with this and I'll post it if there seems to be interest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kill Confirmed is now to 85 tags. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 05:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It now takes 85 collected tags to win. Just noticed this. Awesome change, imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys, the Bal-27 is more balanced than you may realize. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 20:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just think, while your opponent is reloading his Bal, you'll be able out dps him! 

ez gaem

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They say death follows in his footsteps, but he never looks back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 18:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CGI Animated Short Film HD: "Dark Noir" - Red Knuckles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 02:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apparently the pursuit of perfection is insufferable! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 16:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd say this start was above average. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 04:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/xvdHppO.png

Almost makes up for all the games I don't get wild growth. *Almost*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Wolf's Head Medallion came in today! (Shoddy phone pics incoming.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 23:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened to the mage(s) that created witchers in Geralt's early life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 21:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, we know that the witchers of Kaer Morhen guard the mutagens and potions required to mutate people into witchers. We also know that the witchers of Kaer Morhen do not possess the knowledge or magical capabilities required to use these mutagens. Many years before Geralt's time, Kaer Morhen was attacked by an anti non-human mob and Vesemir was the one of the only survivors. So, we know there were mages around after this assault to create more witchers. Best guesses to Vesemir's age are 300+ years old. I've seen Geralt's age guessed to about 106 at the time of The Witcher 2. I can't know for sure, but I'm going to assume that the other witchers of Kaer Morhen are about the same age as Geralt (give or take a few decades). So, it seems that 100 years before the end of the series, the mage(s) that created Geralt and Eskel and Coen and all the current witchers must have fled or been killed. They couldn't have been killed in the assault on Kaer Morhen because witchers have been created after that. I've read through the books series twice now (fan translations) and I cannot recall Sapkowski ever saying anything about what happened to the mages that would have been around for Geralt's transformation. Does anyone know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is that guy standing in the back? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 17:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Titanfall is so fun. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 22:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the shotgun, you can really use all the mobility you have in Titanfall to your advantage both offensively and defensively. I present to you an EVA-8 Montage: "This is My Weapon". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 18:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rule #2 - Always Double Tap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 22:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The dash core works especially well with arc cannon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 19:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I didn't mean to do it, I swear! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 16:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook probably will let Oculus "operate independently on our own vision"... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 19:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facebook will probably step to the side, providing resources and funds into letting Oculus build the best VR headset their little hearts can make. Maybe a "suggestion" for a feature here, a "suggestion" there, but ultimately the R D will be all about Facebook providing the means of Oculus building the best CV1 that they (and we) could possibly imagine!



But then, when it's done, Zuckerberger will snatch it out of their hands, slap FB's logo on the front and do whatever he god damn well pleases with it. I think Luckey has been bullshitted by a multi-billion dollar company with speeches of independence and the promise of him being the top of VR that maybe it made him forget who he was dealing with. Maybe FB took advantage of the man's vision and determination to put out an excellent product. Maybe Luckey just doesn't give a fuck beyond having the ability to build a VR headset. Who knows?

I think Palmer Luckey has been bullshitted in a big way. Maybe he had the best intentions with this deal, but it's probably hard to see clearly with $2b waved in front of your eyes. The thought that being acquired by such a scummy company would (by itself) cause a lot of indie devs to back out of Oculus development probably never even crossed his mind.

Oh well. Like Notch said, this will likely make more competition in VR. More competition is always a good thing for accelerating innovation and bringing consumers the best products at the best prices. Will the next big gaming VR headset be the Oculus? I doubt it. But I'm sure someone will come to our rescue.

Gaben save us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't see enough people wallhanging. It's a great way to have a vantage point over a room or objective! People don't look up I'm the walls for pilots.... yet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 13:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't hear enemy footsteps at all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 23:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is odd to me as there is a perk to silence your footsteps (among other things). There have been numerous times I've watched the kill cam and seen an enemy chasing right behind, miss a kick, keep running to me and then land a kick or finally shoot me. And yet, as a headphone user, I heard absolutely nothing. Anyone else have this "issue"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nvidia Shadowplay, anyone have it working? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 00:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It worked during the BETA, now it won't show up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else getting poor framerate and/or lots of camera stutter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 21:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an i5-2500k, 8gb RAM, and a GTX 770. I don't think I should be dropping below 60 which it does... quite often. 

Only using 2x MSAA and Very High textures. No vysnc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Archer is harder than melee, they said. I couldn't win a FFA as an archer, they said. Light xbow isn't point and click, they said. Silly archers, this shit was too easy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 16:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 358MB Chivalry MW BETA Update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 17:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems to be a balance patch from what I can tell. No patch notes yet but MAA dodge now takes 25 stam, so 4 dodges instead of 6 before you run out. Bubble is still the same, as far as I can tell. Didn't test anything else. I'll edit this post when they put out patch notes.

EDIT - [Here you go, mah good friends.](http://forums.tornbanner.com/showthread.php/18709-BETA-Chivalry-Medieval-Warfare-Patch-21)

EDIT 2 - Apparently there will be a part 2 to this beta patch coming out soon. Check the OP in the link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My only goal in life is to make dead as many archers as I can. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-23 17:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want a MOBA style base capture game mode for Titanfall. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 03:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given that Titans can get some decent diversity in fighting styles/weapons, I think Titanfall could have a ~~good~~ fucking brilliant competitive scene. I mean, am I crazy or are they setting up a MOBA style shooter anyway? We have minions already in the game, monsters we know will be in the game, turrets we know will be in the game. And, afaik, one of the devs in Respawn worked for RIOT. I think they would be insane to not at least try and pull off a MOBA style base capture type gamemode. If it were even remotely balanced, this game could spawn a competitive community like no other and, if it did, I would probably never stop playing this game. It'd be everything you could want in a competitive shooter and it'd REALLY set it apart from games like CoD and BF.

In case you're unclear with what MOBA style would mean, there are minions that would fight and push forward in lanes where enemy turrets will lie and, very likely, enemy teammates guarding their turrets or advancing the lane on their own. Turrets will do lots of damage to players. There would be monsters around the map to supply your team with buffs, this could also be a place to commonly meet enemy players in battle for these kills. After a lot of fighting, you would have pushed up on a lane so much, there aren't turrets anymore and you can enter the enemy base to take shit down.

Obviously, I don't think this exact model of MOBA would work for Titanfall, as this game is a whole different genre with different pacing and the need of level design. My point is is that I see a really good oportunity for Respawn to make a highly competitive (as well as casual) shooting game that could really set it apart from everything else out on the market.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My absolute favorite character from TW2. Best in game dialogue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 03:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Titanfall is awesome. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 22:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BTW, you can one-shot an enemy titan by dropping your titanfall on it's head. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-16 22:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Custom TO Map Malric's Manor. Footage from the subreddit campaign event the other day! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 04:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Sheath your sword, elf. I'm here to talk." One of the best cutscenes from TW2, also a Shadowplay and Ubersampling test! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-03 18:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What choices do you plan to make in TW2 as your carry over save for TW3? (Major spoilers about everything) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 01:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another way to word this question: how would you ideally leave off the TW2 in preparation for the Nilgaard invasion and TW3? What significant choices and events stand out to you that should be considered?

We can't even be sure what will matter or what will not matter for the plot of TW3, but there were some choices made during TW2 that seemed they could be pretty substantial for the defense or aid of Nilfgaard's invasion. For instance, who you left in charge of Temeria? Likewise, which monarchs died and which lived? What mages are still alive (like Sile or Cynthia)? Did you let Nilfgaard have Dearhenna's spying device and notes on the virus that took down the Vrans? What other significant events can you think of?

I just beat the game for the upwards of 7th time and I cannot be sure. Mainly this is just for discussion. :)

PS: I played it for the first time fully with the FCR mod. It was better with the mod, FOR SURE. It gave the game some more replay-ability and I would even suggest it to people who are on their first run through of the game. I feel like I should make a separate post about my experience with the mod and how it improved pretty much all the aspects of the game with only minor inconveniences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Witcher 2 - Remember Why the Elves Fight. Sometimes it's the passing conversations of characters that can speak deeply. "Just like this garden: beautiful and sad." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 06:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CD Projekt Red Co-Founder says "start saving for an upgrade" for Witcher 3. This game will be a pinnacle of the master race in more than one way. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 20:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just set up a new Medieval Warfare FFA server. But with a twist! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 01:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, I play a lot of FFA and decided to make my own FFA server that was less of a clusterfuck and more of a interesting combat challenge. 

The server name is Rathion's Melee FFA Challenge (No Archers), should be easy to find in the server list. It's based in Chicago and hosted by NFO.

The difference here is, it's a 12 man FFA, so more easily manageable encounters. There are no archers, it's only melee combat. Also, there is a limit per class. There can only be a maximum of 4 vanguards, 4 knights, and 4 maa. There's also a 120 ping limit to the server (thank god).

It also has every FFA map in the rotation that is currently offered, but I may remove some and/or add some custom maps later on. 

Come fight with me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just in case my brothers are unaware, this is my favorite site for high quality wallpapers! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 05:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First World Problem of having a Master Shrine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 06:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Be careful where you walk in Elektro. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 06:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Medieval Warfare - Who doesn't like slow motion decapitations and fancy drags? My "Beast" Montage! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 19:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I proudly present: "The Beast" (A Claymore Vanguard Montage) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 19:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After multiple vanilla playthroughs (Witcher 2), I now question why they didn't make the game like FCR by default. Here's some fights in the prologue with FCR v1.2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 23:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Graphics Card! Finally can run the game with Ubersampling and... wow (Witcher 2 Prologue Spoilers). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 05:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peasants couldn't handle Ubersampling even if their peasantboxes could handle Ubersampling. (Witcher 2 Prologue Spoilers - Bonus Video in Comments!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 05:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a bad feeling about supporting Early Access games... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 23:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I've just dealt with one-too-many shady publishers/developers, but early access games just sounds like a bad idea more often than a good one. Sure, the idea is to get money flowing to indie teams while they make some cool games that people are willing to fund the development of, instead of AAA publishers giving the teams a check and advertisement space. And, during this steam sale, holy shit were a lot of early access games funded. DayZ (which I bought) is leading all of the sales charts against AAA that are even 75%+ off. Hopefully they won't, but after such a huge payout (which is probably close to what they would have hoped for on a FULL release) who is to say they don't just take their fucking time in development and leave it in Alpha forever while mooching their Early Access sales cash? I dunno, man. I supported a good handful of early access games this sale, as did a lot of people I know. I hope it doesn't bite us in the ass. This early access funding system seems exactly what the gaming industry needs to boost indie sales and encourage innovated games to be developed. Maybe if there was a refund option for early access games (at least while they remained early access).

What are some of your guy's thoughts on supporting Early Access games? Especially big titles like DayZ (which is OMFG so much fun). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been handcuffed here for like 20 something minutes now. Man look at those graphics! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 05:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first time playing this game has given me one intense story to tell. What an amazing and surreal game DayZ is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 23:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was my first experience in the game DayZ. I knew what the game was about and I had a basic idea of what I was getting into, but oh man... I had no idea I was going to experience something like this. 

Luckily I had help. If not for the people in my Teamspeak channel, I would have been lost in the woods for days, starving of hunger, with no sense of direction. There were five of us in Teamspeak. Of those five there were 3 rookies (myself included, Billy, and Tom), 1 novice (let's call him Soldier) and one pro (let's call him Captain). Our first objective? Meet up in a town north of Kamenka, a town called Pavlovo. As I explored the local buildings and fields around my spawn (and being greeted by my first hostile bullets to the face), I started grasping the basic concepts: don't starve, don't get shot, get storage space, fill the storage with supplies, and don't trust anyone. After a couple of lives, I made it to Pavlovo with some food, soda, and a backpack.

I was the first to arrive. Soldier and Captain were on their way and close by, "fully geared" they said. They'll meet me in front of the church. Why waste time? I went to check out a barn that was in sight. Nothing to loot, better head back, I thought. "Rathion, if that's you, go prone!" I froze. My heart jumped. "Rath!? Go prone!" I found the correct button on the keyboard and laid on the ground, nervously. "Good, let's get you a gun while we wait for the others." As I stood up, I got my first up close look at them. These are some rugged motherfuckers, I thought. The type of people you don't want to fuck with. Assualt rifles in hand, axes on their backs, with gas masks and helmets and ballistic vests and cargo pants covering them completely. I was glad to be on their side. One of them started eating from a box of cereal.

From a close-by military base, we picked up, for me, an M4. A little ammo was graciously supplied to me by Captain. We continued to search for supplies as the remaining two members of our soon-to-be squad were close-by. They had some food and water, but no weapons. Another M4 for one of them was found! We gave that to Billy. No more ammo to give out, though. "This place is dry.", Captain exclaimed. "There's a town north of us that could have some good stuff. Let's head there." The five of us hit the road as a pack. Captain made a comment, "This is a nice little army we have here. It'll do." Humorous to me, I appreciated the site of our squad trotting along the road, 5 people with 4 assualt rifles in hand, I thought no one would dare fuck with us.

We arrived at our destination, a larger town named Zelenogorsk. Captain took lead. "Keep your guns drawn and ready. Let's look for supplies and stick together." First building: a new-old ballistic vest, second building: a little food, third building: a whole lot of nothing. We moved forward. The city opened up a bit to what looked like an abanded parking lot in front of a large white building. Captain and I went inside to have a look. "I don't see anything on the first floor", I exclaimed and started up the stairs. Noticing my hunger message popping up, I pulled out a can of sardines and started munching. Captain also grabbed a bite to eat. "Put your guns down!" My heart sank. I didn't recognize that voice. Was it from Teamspeak!? No, I don't think so. "Put the goddamn guns down!" I looked around and I looked at Captain, we were alone in this building. He started moving to the back door, I went to the front, the way we came in.  "PUT THE GUNS DOWN NOW!" Through the door I could see Soldier and the ammo-less Billly with their guns pointed to my left across the parking lot. Soldier yelled into the mic, "Be cool, man! Be cool! Put the guns down! You're gonna get shot! You're gonna get shot!" As I leaned around the corner, I realized the situation. Solider and Billy were facing off against a squad of 3 visible surivors, all very armed. But these hostiles didn't know about me and they didn't know about Captain who was working a flank and no one was going to put their guns down. My heart felt like it was going to burst through my chest.

Crack! Crack! Crack! I see muzzle flashes from their vocal member. I fire into his chest, he drops. Billy drops. I see Soldier is burst firing from the corner of my eye, another hostile drops. The third hostile I saw turns and runs back, full sprint, into a field behind the large white building. There's a vantage point on the second floor, I remember! I turn and run upstairs as fast as I can. Captain shouts into Teamspeak, "There's another one!" I hear shots fired as I look out of the window. A ragdoll hits the ground and relaxes into the grass behind the building. A hostile survivor is fleeing into the distance, so I pull up my gun. I didn't get a shot off in time before he dissappeared. "Loot the bodies. Fast! Take everything you can!", shouts Captain. From my vantage point I tell them I see three dead hostiles. The one I shot, he looked geared. Was I supposed to feel excited about this? "Why can't I press F on his corpse?", I ask. "He's probably unconscious." Captain walks over with his pistol and puts a bullet in his head. "He's all yours." I took everything. 

Tom managed to remain hidden from the battle. Probably a wise tactical decision for someone without a weapon. Soldier, Captain, and I were unharmed. We lost Billy. Solider and I exchange celebratory raves as the adrenaline wears off and Captain lets us know that we should move on. So, we got our shit together and left.

This game has given me an experience like no other game has done so before. One that I will not forget and one that I hope whoever reads this enjoys hearing about. No other game has been able to deliver such an intense and surreal situation to me that I was able to be a part of and help determine the outcome. I imagine this won't be the last time DayZ gets my heart racing and I look forward to having more stories to tell. 

Cheers.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cracking an egg underwater! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 07:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cracking an egg underwater </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 07:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ello, poppets. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 00:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll see what happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alright ChivalryGame, let's have a talk about this subreddit... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 00:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, let's say I'm a new Chivalry player and I'm really starting to like it so I come around to this sub to check out some discussions. Here is my first impression of the community based off the past month's worth of posts: "lol noobs are bad" and "DAE HATE TORN BANNER".

I've been meaning to type up a thread like this for a while. Man, reading posts in this subreddit has become exhausting with all the negativity spouted at every aspect of the game (most of which is unfounded, circlejerk style criticism). Are there things to complain about? Sure. Should these be the focus of everyone's attention all the time? Perhaps not. 

If I didn't know any better (like a new subscriber), I would assume that everyone who plays this game fucking hates it. The only things that get upvoted (besides the: look at all the noobs I can kill screenshots) are posts like "Deadliest Warrior sux becuz lmb spam" and "QQ I want more mods, torn banner QQ". You know what? There's so much lmb spam in deadliest warrior because everyone sucks ass at it just like noobs lmb spam in MW. And jesus christ, mods are just starting to roll out and be fun, have some patience, this isn't Skyrim.

Ugh. This is an innovative, cheap-ass ***indie*** multiplayer action game from a team of rookie developers built on an old engine that's used mainly for shooter style games. Deadliest Warrior is a fun $15 mini game that gets TBS an extra flow of money to keep motivation (and looks good to future investors/publishers). Panic parry isn't the devil, like many high ranking people may spout, and (in my opinion) helped the game much more than people think. But the weapon unlock bug sucks, so that's okay to bitch about at times.

This game is a blast and we need to focus on the fun and joy that it brings. That's the point of gaming, no? Our community needs to be about getting people better at playing, finding people to play with, and sharing the good times. I'm tempted to make my own subreddit called chivalryfun for this reason. Reddit is a powerful tool that can really help or hurt this game progress and get better with both content and playerbase. And right now, I don't think this sub is helping at all. For anything.

tl;dr - Too many grumpy people bringing down the man.

EDIT - Examples would probably help my cause.

http://www.reddit.com/r/ChivalryGame/comments/1rsgxx/am_i_the_only_one_around_here_who_didnt_buy_dw/

http://www.reddit.com/r/ChivalryGame/comments/1szt0e/anyone_else_tired_of_dw_already/

http://www.reddit.com/r/ChivalryGame/comments/1swecq/is_chivalry_medieval_warfare_going_to_be_fixed/

http://www.reddit.com/r/ChivalryGame/comments/1tmlex/disappointed_with_the_lack_of_modcustom_map/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had a blast playing the Mana Warfare MOD. Here's some of the awesome moments I had with friends! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 22:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think this knight has a little too much mead... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 01:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chivalry - Basic Tracers Guide for Deadliest Warrior (Mostly Applies to MW as well) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 19:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Medieval Warfare - 5 Minutes of Death and Decapitations! Six-Eyed Bull FFA Montage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 19:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a Unicorn Fart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 05:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any of you guys like Tech N9ne? (Deadliest Warrior Montage) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 06:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deadliest Warrior - Bloody Murder FFA Music Video (Warning - Intense Footage May Leave You Woozy) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 00:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What song(s) cannot be played loud enough? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 23:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some songs were made to be played loud and some songs get better and better the louder they are played. I have some good audio gear. Blow out my ears, Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deadliest Warrior - Has anyone hit 100 kills in a match yet? I have. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 08:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I like to break into people's homes and move their refrigerators around. (Deus Ex: HR) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-30 06:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I run into this problem too frequently. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 19:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How To Build An Xbox One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 08:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deadliest Warrior - Kanabo Club Shenanigans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 18:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deadliest Warrior - All Hail the Poke Stick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 08:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deadliest Warrior - Rampage Mode With a Twist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 06:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deadliest Warrior - Secret Triple Thud Attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 03:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deadliest Warrior - "Combat Essentials" Basic Tracers Guide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 20:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pirate Duels in a Nutshell [fixed] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 22:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samurai Duels ft. Rathion and Stosif Jalin. Rank 0 and still puts up a good fight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 21:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Deadliest Warrior Patch! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 19:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deadliest Warrior - FFA Footage with lots of deaths from the Yari spear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 01:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BETA footage of Chivlary: Deadliest Warrior I recorded. Intense Samurai combat in Free For All. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 16:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How about some PC exclusive gameplay? Samurai footage from the Chivalry: Deadliest Warrior BETA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 15:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samurai Yari Spear FFA Gameplay! Deliciousness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 15:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deadliest Warrior is awesome and here's a thorough summary of why. wall-o-text critique of Chiv: DW. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 05:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deadliest Warrior has SO MUCH POTENTIAL. Especially with the prospect of an SDK. Here's the thing: this game is much different in a lot of ways from Medieval Warfare. Where MW is like a game of delicate swordplay, DW is a riot of badassery built off the same combat system that I love very much. So, I see people trying to relate the performance of the classes in DW in the same way you would scrutinize a class in MW, which isn't exactly fair to the new classes' purposes. Deadliest Warrior has the finesse of the combat system from MW but, with the game sped up so, and with the larger maps, the roles of the classes has more variety than simply their ability to cross blades.

First, I want to talk about pirates. If an excess of people play pirates, it's not because they are OP, it's because they are awesome! In groups, a firing line of pirates is a tough situation to take down. A few things I might change about pirates are their fuses. I would make the fuse of the gun (the delay when you fire it) to be a random time. Maybe the gun will go off right after pulling the trigger, maybe there will be more of a delay. This variation in timing will add an edge to aiming and make it less point and click for them. Also, maybe a chance for the gun to miss-fire (the fuse not to light). What would be more fun than charging up to a pirate, hoping he doesn't shoot you, the gun barrel right in your face and click! A 5% chance of miss-fire happens and you laugh heartily as you chop off the pirate's head. Yar har and a bottle of rum.

Ninjas are another class that does well in groups of themselves. A traveling pack of ninjas is a hilarious sight of  shhhh, and no sound. A lot of people have been calling ninja the new man at arms. While there are similarities, the role of the class is different in the two games. With such a fast paced game as DW, the squishiness of ninjas plays a bigger part of their lives than it does for MAA. In 1v1, ninja's rolls can go either way for them when it comes to avoiding damage or taking it. And spears are very deadly against them. All I would change for them would be a way to hold the ninja star in the ready-to-throw position to aim better and the tear gas stuff, if TB wants that to be a free hit, only one tear gas per ninja. Having two and using them both correctly can be a free kill. No no.

Vikings are pretty cool. Not really my cup-o-tea but I have given them a thorough play. I think, to be more effective, their special ability (which increases their attack speed of the combo each time they land a hit) needs to be more noticeable in the first couple hits in the combo. Otherwise it's pretty worthless in a game as faced paced as this. Perhaps a health boost, too? I feel the role of a viking is more knight-ish and support damage. So maybe trade the Samurai's huge armor with the Vikings.

So, Spartans and Samurai. These classes have both a similar role in DW. I think that once Samurai vs Spartan (the game mode) is balanced, these classes are balanced within the game. A good Samurai/Spartan should be more powerful than the other classes in raw combat. These classes are the damage dealers, the badass warriors, the front line of combat. I do think Samurai need a health nerf. They shouldn't have that much armor as a knight. I thought Spartans were under-powered at first, then I played them more, now I think it's going to get really bloody once people start getting better at the class.

For Knights, I don't have much to say. I think they fit into the classes of DW very well and their roles are about the same as from Medieval Warfare. Knights do have crossbows which is a good point to bring up because the idea of archer hate shouldn't really exist in Deadliest Warrior. All classes have archer qualities and that's because classes need to be able to handle more in this game. Another difference from MW.

The main problem I see with this game is simply team balance. People bitch about Samurais winning but that wouldn't happen (necessarily) if they didn't outnumber everybody. TB needs to work a class limiter into servers to keep the teams even. The game mode is Ninjas vs. Spartans vs. Pirates and there are 24 people in the server? 8 per team sounds like the way to go.

So, what does all this make Deadliest Warrior? This game is like a TF2/Counter Strike style of Chivlary. Even more so with an SDK in the picture. The gameplay is fast and dynamic. Groups of enemies trekking around the large maps makes a much larger variety of combat encounters that can be crazily satisfying to come across and participate in. I can play the same game modes over and over and each game will be very different and I have a blast all the time. Lighten up, guys! I know there's a lot of mixed feelings about Chivalry and Torn Banner but just go with the flow and have fun! We may have a great time-piece of a game on our hands. Now, off to play some DW.

Cheers, Rath.

P.S. - I HAVE SO MUCH GAME FOOTAGE. I don't even know what to do with it all. It's all so awesome but I don't have time to edit anything together. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seriously, why does this game keep deleting my cars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 22:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The impound lot has not worked for me as (I assume) it is supposed to. I'll have a nice modified car in my garage, I'll take it out for a spin, die from something, it's gone forever. Or, I'll take my car out to a mission, the mission makes me drive another car, my car is gone forever. Hell, sometimes I'll turn on the game and my garage will be empty when there definitely should be cars in it (which is what made me make this post). I have about 20 hours of game play now and I've lost 7 or 8 cars that I've spent money on, put in my garage, saved the game and yet they never show up in the impound when I leave them somewhere. It really makes me not want to play anymore, but it's so fun. :( Am I doing something wrong? I'm tired of wasting money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When the six-eyed bull plays FFA. Good footage of the day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 17:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chivalry TDM Game Clip - Holding the Log Bridge [1:02] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 23:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TDM Massacre in Darkforest. I went 18-2 .[4:36] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 18:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've decided to start recording my gameplay of chivalry, some moments are just too priceless to keep to myself. Here's the quality test for my channel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-21 16:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a new player to chiv, I've gotten to lvl 30 and now there are some things I'd like to discuss. Please join me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 08:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, to start things out, I'd like to say that I haven't had this much fun in a multiplayer game in a very long time. Wow! I'm hooked. I've had this game since release but only just started playing it (2 weeks ago?), so I have no experience pre-patch, as people say.  Now that I have a good feel for the game, I want to share my thoughts on aspects of the game that people seem to like, not like, or maybe aspects people haven't really mentioned before.

*Pre-patch vs post-patch Combat*

When I first started playing, I was having a great time but this was a major topic in a lot of games that I joined. And it really dampened my spirit as a new player. The way people were making it seem, the game was now dumbed down and worthless. I've read up on people's opinions about the patch changes and I have a gist of what is different, but it's hard to grasp. All I can really say here is that from a new perspective on the game, the post-patch balance and combat system works very well. Combat is very fluid and doesn't feel like I have to "exploit" it to better my opponent. Classes have strengths and weaknesses, but good players can hold their own and pick of the slack of their class as well as expanding the on class' strength, allowing them to really stand out in the battle. But, the "dumbed down" game's sporting of decent noobs adds a good static level of balance to the matches and players, so you can still get your ass handed to you if you step out of line.

*Customization*

Am I the only one around here who doesn't have a problem telling the difference between Agatha and Mason Order? Seriously, the amount of people raging about the color customization is concerning. The only time I attack the wrong team is when they are covered in blood and look red (and even that happens rarely, pay attention to the cursor), but I did that pre-patch anyway. I think the customization is fantastic and I hope they expand on it.

*Game Modes and Maps*

I want more game modes! Steal some ideas from CoD - I don't care :P. But seriously, I'm having a blast in all the game modes. All of them. What I do want to see are bigger maps and larger objectives. For instance, game modes where there are points to capture and hold around the map and maps big enough where there are different ways to move about to these points. I think some wooded maps would be fantastic and more open maps like Moor (spelling?) would be really awesome if they also incorporated flanking paths on the sides that people could fight through. I dunno. Thoughts?

*Closing Thoughts*

I'd like to be able to bind some of the commands (like Yes, No, Thanks, etc) to the numpad. I don't have a problem with the community, I think it has a healthy balance of nice people and stupid people, which works for this game because you get to chop stupid people's heads off and vote kick is used constantly. I think a lack of stats being kept (like kills/deaths and all that CoD stuff) keeps the game from getting too stressful, but I wouldn't mind if they added stats. Oh, and I would pay a lot of money for killcams. 

Well, I think that's all I had to say. It's 2am here, so I probably missed something, but I'll check in the morning and see. Please share you thoughts on what I said and/or add input of your own on how the game could be improved. 

Add me on steam! It' t_rathion. You'll see me in game as Rathion or subject2159. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some of your most memorable quotes from The Last of Us? *spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 03:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the lines that stuck with me the most was at the fight with David after he locks you in:

"There's nowhere to go! You want out? Gonna have to come get these keys." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking for an awesome The Last of Us poster, suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 12:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title says it all. It'd be nice to have some Last of Us on my wall. Is there anything good out there yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nicolas Cage.avi - [1:33] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 22:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think we'll see a successful emulation of the PS4? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 18:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, I love my pc, but Sony has always had terrific exclusives that demand my attention. The PS3 will likely stay without an emulator, but since the PS4 is based on an architecture similar to pc's, how likely do you see emulation?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GG </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 10:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The secret to high fps in the nexus is... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 20:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... turn off "show names" on other players!

Standing around before nexus, went from 10 to 30 fps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I guess he just didn't realize that I was afk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 01:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got to meet Tic, Tac, and Toe! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-24 22:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The guilt of introversion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-30 05:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's good of me to have found this place. I've long since needed to rant in places other than my own head. Perhaps you guys will understand what I have to say. It seems otherwise there are few who do. I will not apologize for the depths and length of this nearly-essay style post (it will likely be a, sort of, stream of thought), as it matters little if people read or respond to it in any form. This is for my own interest and self preservation. I do, however, wish (and encourage) that some may read and share their thoughts and concerns. My name is Troy, by the way, and my introversion will likely destroy my relationship with my family.

I have been pushed to the point where I am so disconnected from those around me that I simply do not care anymore. I've been home from school for 2 weeks now and it has stressed me to the point of frustration and resentment. I am the complete opposite of my family and the majority of people I come in contact with. They simply do not understand me; my family, especially (and ironically). Everybody always seems to think that my interests are of less concern to me than other people's interests. Which, to me, doesn't make very much sense. In my parents eyes, my opinions are meaningless and my endeavors matter little in the flow of my life.

I grew up in a southern and more conservative domain. It has always made me feel uneasy for reasons that, until recently, were unclear to me. Having since been off at college, I've built a much better understanding of the world being outside of such a sheltered and controlled environment. In doing so, I have become much more settled in my introverted ways now that I can more clearly understand the point of it all. Admittedly, this is probably worrisome to my parents for me to have changed so much from the child they tried to raise (which makes me feel guilty). I hold no ill-feelings for my parents either. They care for me more than anyone else in my life and have always wanted the best and tried their best in my interest. All this makes the whole situation feel much worse.

I much prefer to keep to myself. I am socially inept in many ways. To put it simply, I just do not understand most accepted forms of interaction. Unless it's someone relatively close to you, the conversations are often meaningless, mind-numbing, and trivial. I usually have to mentally prepare myself for social gatherings and conflicts (and it doesn't really help). Unfortunately for me, these interactions are the forefront of most people's lives. Some of whom cannot comprehend my pleasures of solitude. I am therefore forced to avoid all contact with people that I am not already comfortable around. Being home for the holidays has thrown that cause down the drain, however.

Why must I be forced to feel so guilty for what I find comfortable in life? My father's personality has always made him unapproachable, in a sense. It's more of a one-way stream of commands, than healthy discussion. Therefore, I have been bound my entire life to work through my issues on my own. The independence I have construed from such has allowed me to form my own perspective on things that is now much different from that of my parents and close family. Why must I feel guilty for that? My goals in life are much greater than they realize. And they cannot be accomplished under their supervision and scrutiny. My parents simply do not understand me and I feel sorry for that.

Being home has made me fully realize the extent of my introverted ideals. My father insists that all time spent on the computer is time wasted, while my mother insists that being critical and philosophical are meaningless attributes for a person. While at home, my father forces me to help out with him in his business which puts me in a constant state of interaction with various people throughout the day and it kills me (also because I have feel like it wastes a day). By the end of it, I am so drained of energy that I cannot focus on what's important to me that I learn for my future. Between that and the impromptu gatherings entailed by the holidays, there are times where I want nothing more than to tell everyone to fuck off and my attitude reflects as such. At this point, it is usually stated that I am being a butt-head.

My apartment at college is wonderful. I live with people I get along with and I can remain undisturbed if I please. It is since then I have realized how much my family and home life impedes on my ability to progress myself and stay sane. My parents still insist (and constantly offer) that I commute from home. No. My goals in life will lead me away from all this. The means to accomplish those goals are, in fact, contingent on my separation from all this. I care for my parents and my family, but my dependence on them is purely financial. Sooner or later, that will change. When that happens, I fear they will not be prepared for what lies after. And for that I feel very guilty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manhunt 2 All Original Uncut PS2 Executions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 23:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does it take to "port" a game to linux? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 14:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're all waiting for Steam on linux to start supporting more games, but what does it actually take for a game to be ported to linux? To get a DX11 title (like BF3 or BO2) to run under OpenGL, what needs to happen? Does the game's engine need updated or is it more on the driver side of things?

Basically, my question is: what is the difference between a game running in Windows and that same game running in Linux? TF2 could be a good example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions, ideas, and discussion about Steam's Big Picture mode. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-06 19:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed that, with the Steam beta installed, I was able to select Steam from my log-in page (where you select your session) and it booted into big picture steam mode. Does this load Steam as the desktop environment, replacing Unity? 

I see where Valve is trying to go here. I've read things in the past about linux consoles for android, and I think that's what Valve is trying to do now. Steam now shows games with native controller support for use with the big picture mode (which also works with a controller).

I like this direction. The only games I use mouse/keyboard on are online FPS games and MMOs. Most other games (single player games, more or less), I prefer to use a controller. So, considering I use Windows for BF3, BO2, GW2 and Linux for single player games, it would be cool to be able to have a Steam desktop environment specifically for gaming.

Anyway, I have to go to a review session right now. I have further points I'd like to address later, but I think this can be a good place to talk about where Valve is taking Steam as we're waiting for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I like gaming on linux because it forces me to play older games. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-16 01:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing a lot of early-mid 2000s FPS games and am having a blast. What are some games you guys still like to play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, besides procrastination, how has the internet negatively impacted your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 07:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, I'd say the lack of trusting people which translates into my social interactions in real life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher Hitchens and the importance of the freedom of speech and expression. (x/post from r/TrueAtheism) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-31 23:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chistopher Hitchens on the importance of the freedom of speech and expression. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-31 23:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've put a lot of work into my audio setup. Thought it would interest you guys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 17:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes, it's just too hard to keep it in. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-23 20:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Christian friend saved me from Mormon missionaries. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-26 01:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So there I was, sitting on the couch, browsing r/atheism and reading about Obama's defense of free speech when, speak of the devil, I heard a knock on my apartment door. I opened it, expecting someone I knew. Standing there were two young men holding bibles who quickly greeted me with, "Hello, we're Mormon missionaries and we're going around trying to spread the word of God."

For a moment, my brain just stopped responding. I haven't been in this situation before, as some people on here have, so I was completely unprepared. Thankfully, my friend, who is a Christian, heard the introduction from these two and came to the door to talk. I wasn't sure what to say, or what would come of it, but my friend quickly started talking to them about his church and how we both attend and are active Christians. After some quick religious small talk (as it were), we respectfully parted ways.

After they were gone, I turned around to see my other roommate dying of laughter at the expression that was on my face when I first opened the door. And my savior of a roommate laughed and said, "I knew that if you had told them you were atheist, they would have wanted to come in and chat. You're welcome."

Oh man. That was scary.

Just thought I'd share this moment of life with you guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My new college apartment station. It's all black. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 21:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pshhhhh Who needs multiple monitors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 02:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just got back from college. Battlestation rebuilt! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-17 02:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
