<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2519</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 10:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He had been a governor before president at least  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 22:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They come like seriously close to making out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orc armour looks better  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I totally agree - and hating Glenn? Have you watched all the seasons ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best support gun since the update ! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 07:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I generally believed the best support gun was the B.A.R storm but after playing a game of operations with a KD of 59/20 I have found the new best one. The Lewis Gun low weight with AA sights, while utilising the bipod effective, is a beast.

It's really accurate at long range and kills quicker than the BAR at close range while being fairly accurate, it's hip Fire ain't bad neither!! the perfect balanced weapon for support !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 07:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brexit in the U.K. (Where I'm from) showed how racist rural areas are. London is like LA, progressive and tolerant. Trump election did a similar thing. It makes you depressed thought I was proud to be British but England let us down. America is too big and too divided to be a singular entity. Racism never really died it just went underground and like you say, you know they don't like Obama because he's black </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 05:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They probably feel he is the worst because he is black </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 05:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean online ? I played it a tonne back in 2013/14 and nearly 100% it. I bought it again recently and it really holds up. It's hard to go back to the old style of AC gameplay from Syndicate but the Ship aspects help it hold up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 05:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Trump is the problem - it is him being an incompetent clueless president that will enable people with bad intentions to get their laws passed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 05:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picking Yen over Triss - I just want both !!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 05:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I agree with what you said but on the communist things. Their is/was literally a group of Communist Islamist who blend the two together to create a new ideology. Think it was in Iran pre-revolution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 05:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Guaranteed to die' - you are guaranteed a high chance of death but the amount of soldiers fighting compared to the actual deaths is not even comparable. If you look at allied deaths or Nazi Deaths in WW2 compared to the amount deployed there is definitely no 'guarantee' that a infantry soldier is going to die in war </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 13:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roses are red
Sugar is used to sweeten 

Gordon Ramsey's dwarf porn star look a like found in a badger den half eaten... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 13:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbf he has never really hid away from this. He said he was going to do the biggest tax break (or cut I forget) since Reagan and he was proud of it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 08:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is pretty generic tbh a rich guy who has had everything handed to him wants to do something himself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 03:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Vito is a dick because he lost his family, the mob killed his best friends and then exiled him to New Bordeaux? Seems pretty obvious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 03:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe your not paying enough attention to why characters act the way they do ? Don is quite stoic most of the time to keep up appearances. Also the way people spoke to eachother back then was abit different - I mean would you ever just hang up the phone without saying bye or whatever ? They never do in Mad Men  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 02:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His character wasn't that interesting. Rich guy who was jealous of Drakes accomplishments and wanted one of his own at any cost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 11:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liverpool haven't win the league in a quarter century lmao!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 11:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These people being called Islamist always annoyed me. Extremist is a better term Islamist means many things -you can be a communist Islamist  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 11:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't hate him... until now!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 10:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel it's average at best - really disappointing for me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 01:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good on him, hopefully other people in the running will do the same - why would Giuliani make a good Secretary of State!? I'm not even joking, I a 20 year old student who studies history at uni would make a better government official than these clowns. Hell I'd make a better President than Trump-not because I'm special, I'm pretty average-but the people he is choosing are utterly incompetent and unqualified in every sense  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House of Cards... Star Wars edition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay does anyone else think that a Netflix House of Cards spinoff following the exploits of Palpatine and his cronies would be amazing ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 19:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have a Donald Trump like character but as a third party candidate that Conway and Underwood have to work together to destroy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 15:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a difference in the cost of wars and maintaining one of the biggest and most advanced armies of all time that has over 1.5 million people working for it. One missile is essentially worth at least half a million  dollars  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 13:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But can happily increase spending on its armed forces?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Favourite US President ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 10:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 10:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love history I love video games - I have time for both  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 10:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the U.K. We have had the NHS since 1948. We built it up in the face of crippling debt we had to pay the US back. The richest country in the world can't even (apparently) have this Medicare program?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 06:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You basically answered your own question. The two can kill because they are drained of emotion. Harrow does talk to Nucky about remembering the people you've killed etc so it does affect them . Before Jimmy dies he says he has been dead since the war so why would he feel anything when he kills?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Richard Nixon's letter to Trump about him running for Office, 1987 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 23:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 23:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wolf of Wall Street is better than both but was really just focusing on Wall Street (1987) and the Big Short </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wall Street Vs The Big Short - which is better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 22:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently watched both back to back. I feel Wall Street is the better movie with some really good characters, while The Big Short takes the subject matter and makes you really angry at everyone involved as well as the governments of the world who didn't do much to solve the problem.

So in your opinion which is better as a film and which tackles the issues better? 

Money never sleeps!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wall Street vs The Big Short -which is the better film and which deals with the issues better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 22:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just realised Olga's fatigues look very like Snake's in MGS3 - any connection ? Or just fatigues all look the same? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 22:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even the gloves and thermal type sleeves are the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 20:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have naps ! Always works for me. When u start you will never go back!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The games you have all said are older than Gears. Also Gears online is way more hardcore and not as accessible. It's is also rated Mature so I guess that is another factor  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 08:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes you just need to get out the house and feel like you doing something productive  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Returning player - haven't been on since before 1.2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 08:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 07:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was pretty polarising in Europe - what part of the world are you from ? Was a big deal for the Clinton administration so was probably a big deal with the US public too  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 05:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Andrew Garfield can't stop his character from Hacksaw Ridge influencing his life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 05:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the same and it's not bad too me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 05:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harry Truman (the future president) pushed his troops in his command to the last minute and many died. What a waste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 05:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ISI formed in 2006 - Bush' invasion created them. The US pullout allowed them to get a lot stronger  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 14:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao ! I struggled at first switched to assault and now I'm 1.7 kd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 03:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He took money away from aids treatment to give to gay conversation therapy - disgusting man and I bet he is actually in the closet!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 02:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't the one with white hair gray fox ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 13:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Him and Ted were great wish Bernie wasn't so old  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 04:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was looking at the electoral map in 1960 - Johnson won Kennedy the whole south of the US - what did Tim Kaine bring!? Fucking nothing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> General Tulius is the establishment! He wants to force cultural Marxism on Skyrim by integrating the dark elves, orcs and Khajit into cities with Nords. He is also in bed with the Thalmor and has given them private speeches to the sum of hundreds of thousands of septims!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ulfric: we are gunna build a wall, yuge, and I am going to make Morrowind pay for it! They are sending the worst dark elves, they are criminals, they are rapist, some I assume are good warriors.'

'I Ulfric J Stormcloak am calling for a total and complete shutdown of Khajit entering Skyrim'

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 23:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skyrim SE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No that's not true. They were also used for bombing raids (they bombed London) but often had to be so high up they missed a lot of their targets  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #justww1things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 15:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's true but again - micro transactions make them way more money than dlc ever could so in a way the free maps are just to silence any opposition. Like in GTA V - they cancelled single player dlc because of micro transactions but because every update in the game was free you can't complain even if those updates arnt that good  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 15:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you can pretty much do that with every pack in the game. They based the whole game around this shitty system just like Halo and Uncharted did before them but they took Even more stuff out to sell it in randomised packs. I've been playing horde and the like and still just have JD, Kait and del! In Gears 3 had about 8 characters for each side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 14:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he actually won it's just the Supreme Court wouldn't allow a recount because they were all republicans  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 14:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yes thank you Coalition for basing the whole multiplayer around shitty micro transactions. Especially when we only got three characters to start with !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 04:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vote Warren G Harding !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 00:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Obama didn't even need to crush a union!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 00:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol someone is triggered I'm not even going to justify this with a real response. And FYI that sentence does make sense. Job of an editor to correct my mistakes not everyone submits perfect first drafts like you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 23:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michael Moore is the worst case for me. He is absolutely ecstatic about her and wants a 'Women' to be a world leader. Hey buddy in the U.K. We had Thatcher who is nicknamed the Iron Lady for a reason-just because she is a woman doesn't mean she'll be liberal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so I'm my experience a lot of people have hidden behind the fact she is a women to deflect criticism. I am not god, I haven't read every article ever but in my experience I've have seen it.

Most people don't trust Hillary in a poll back in June 66 per cent of her backers said she was untrustworthy. No it's not all but the feeling is she isn't trustworthy 

As with impeachment - Obama didn't have any major scandals - Clinton has two pretty major ones so there is definitely more plausibility she will be impeached 

Donald Trump decides the Republicans greatly. If a republican husk like Paul Ryan or Romney ran today they'd win because the right in country would get behind them. A lot of states that a usually a sure thing for republicans are being contested by Hillary. Trump is also a moron so he scare away a lot - I feel a Kasich would win pretty easily 

She isn't a progressive - Her view on things shift constantly. Take in 08 she ran as a pro-gun anti gay marriage Democrat- changed a lot since then. Again plays into her trustworthiness. Bernie was always consistent. 

Hopefully that clears up a lot of my 'lies' and republican attacks - this article is my opinion - if you want to write one on why she is such a great progressive who will be a great Pres I will be the first to read it   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see you are just blindly supporting Clinton - nothing to say about Honduras, Iraq, Libya? Nothing to say about the Clinton foundations and ties to Russian Oil ? Anything to say about her support of Goldman Sachs? No because they are all indefensible for a Democrat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is exactly right! Blind Clinton supporters don't understand that - we have to make her introduce the policies we want not let her pivot right on her own when she wins  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and no. Clinton wouldn't offend all of our allies but Trump wouldn't threaten his best buddy Putin  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton is a terrible candidate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 21:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nixon discussing various issues in foreign policy in 1992 - interesting insight and how many of these issues are still relevant. Weird how much Republican intelligence has decline in terms of foreign issues e.g. Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 00:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lancers are obsolete </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 20:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been a Gears player for many years but for multiplayer I feels Gears 4 is the first one where I feel forced to use the Gnasher. I remember in Gears 3 being able to use the Retro Lancer and in Gears 1 just using the regular old one to great effect. Now I feel like there is no way to use it effectively when everyone is using shotguns. It makes he game worse in my opinion - I don't know if I've have just got worse or need to get used to Gears 4 but just wondering if anyone felt the same?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Platoon vs Full Metal Jacket: which is the better 'Nam flick? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 02:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've recently watched the pair again back to back and have to say Platoon is the more emotional and gripping of the two. Just really shows the hell of War a lot better and the hopelessness of it all. I find Chris to be more emphatic than Joker ever could be. Oliver Stone obviously had the benefit of actually being in Vietnam (I know Kubrick has Michael Herr the war correspondent help him write the screenplay) 

Full Metal Jacket is still great and I appreciate its format (lack of narration just makes it nice and fluid) but it's a bit more out there and stylised. Still a great movie though.

Anyway which do you guys like more and what do you think does the job of portraying the war better?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How an Assault can deal with pesky horses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 02:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to deal with those pesky horses... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 00:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone played the AC games in this order back to back - AC4, AC Rogue, AC 3? And what was it like ? I've played them all but might want to do this type of play through </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 23:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've wrote an article on the unparalleled depiction of racism that is in Mafia III and how it pushes the medium of video games forward as a whole. (For the UK's biggest student magazine) I worked hard on it and would appreciate any feedback. Really feels this is the best part of Mafia III as a whole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys just joined the sub-just bought Skyrim on Xbox One and got a dlc code for an outfit in ESO. Does anyone have a PS4 code to trade with me? (It's the Dragon born outfit) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 06:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone who got Skyrim today have an ESO dragon born outfit code on PS4? To trade with the same code but for Xbox One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 22:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xbox 360 save compatible with Xbox one? Yay or nay? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 16:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys I got a code for the Dragon born outfit for ESO on Xbox One - anyone care to swap it for the same code on PS4? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 15:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BF1-Artillery make a great anti-air gun! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 04:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Bomber was destroying our team-I took matters into my own hands...who says artillery isn't a great air defence!? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 04:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People playing operations on PS4 - you know you can mark enemies right? Well do it once in a while !!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 02:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would be your dream mash up of a released game and film? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 22:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if you had to choose one film to be done by the creators and in the style of an already released game ? 

Mine would be Blade Runner done in the style of LA Noire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else find 64 player operations annoying? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 16:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get me wrong the scale and spectacle of 64 players is amazing. But I find I always die annoying deaths. Feel it gives players the opportunity to sort of do their own thing and not play the objective. I get sniped constantly from the side or the back when I am taking on the objective. Maps like the Suez Canal are the worst for this as it's pretty much an open desert. Anyone else feels this way? In smaller game modes like rush I get a lot less frustrated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Musical Easter egg! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 06:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The song 'White Rabbit' can be heard on the radio in game. It is a song usually associated with going on an acid trip. To avoid major spoilers I won't go into details but one mission requires you to drug some people at a private place. The people get really high and one of them plays the entirety of White Rabbit on a grand piano which you can listen to! Just though I'd share. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feel this new Mario meme needs more appreciation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 20:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I bought the game at launch liked it a lot but kinda became frustrated... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 12:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I bought Gears of War 4 and played that for a week (great game). Went back to Mafia and now I'm absolutely loving it. Clearing a district a night has been great and really addicting. They really pick up a lot after the first 3 and the mission are way better aswell as the new weapons from my associates. The gunplay is so fun! 

The game knows when to feed me a great moment to make me play another hour. Like when a sweet song kicks on when you are helping Alvarez or Enzo. Can't wait to play so more just two districts left! 

(Also for Fargo fans anyone else feel like you are playing as Hanzee?)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Injury advice-save me a trip to the doctors ! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 13:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Micro transactions... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't inherently hate them in games but GOW4's suck. I know I can unlock them in game but maybe give me a couple more starting characters? Not just three from campaign mode. Not too much to ask  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nice touch the coalition ! (Gears 4) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 17:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gears of War 4 comes with codes for all 4 previous gears games for Xbox one and some cool stickers! Miss when games used to have cool stuff in the cover. Witcher 3's was so great!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just rewatched Nixon vs Kennedy. Kinsey and Joan-what is going on there!? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 22:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They just had a chat when everyone had fallen asleep and their conversation kinda hinted they had something in the past. 'You have a big mouth' 'I do. And I'm not proud of it' - anyone know what exactly happened or speculate that they had some sort of romantic relationship ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just overheard an NPC in Mafia 3 when it started raining... 'It's wetter than a cucumber in a convent'  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 02:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M1a1 (carbine) with the Model 1887 (Terminator gun) are a beast combination!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 15:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else pair these together ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it wrong to have a different opinion on Luke Cage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 20:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've posted some negative things about he show in the comments and I'm down voted in droves. What happened to having an opinion? 

My view basically boils down to this - It's okay but really doesn't know what it wants to be. Luke has completely changed from Jessica Jones. He is so cheesy and I'm not a big fan of Coulters acting in this season but thought he was great in JJ. The show doesn't have a proper identity. I'd loved that it didn't refrain from the nitty gritty of Harlem and it felt abit like the wire-(and I loved the soundtrack)-but Luke is such a contrast it was just really jarring. Here is a man who has had a terrible life but his character doesn't reflect it. Matt Murdock and Jessica Jones have much better and more complex personalities that reflect their inner demons. It's just my opinion. I absolutely love everything Marvel Netflix has done prior but just felt Luke Cage himself was poorly written and his relationship with Pop was so forced. You only knew him for 7 months Luke! Cottonmouth and the others had know him for decades!! Get over yourself 

(Waiting for the downvotes)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AC Unity - that opening... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 19:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've just been playing a lot of Syndicate lately and thought about giving unity a second chance. Wow the opening is so amazing. Not in spectacle of anything but it's just feels great I really want a medieval Assassin Creed again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lydia Fry... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 20:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would the USA have benefitted from organically separating itself from Britain ? First as a dominion then as an independent state in the Commonwealth-like Canada. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 03:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So disappointingly the upcoming Ezio collection doesn't actually remaster the games in the newest addition of the engine-which has me thinking what game would you like a total remaster of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 16:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say AC3. I absolutely love the time period and world map. The Frontier section  is amazing and I love all the wild life. Would be great to see it in AC Syndicates engine. The original would be cool too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorry if my MGS1 knowledge is hazy but does Liquid know Snake killed Big Boss? And if so does he hate him from stealing that kill from him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 23:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Just on a side note wasn't Liquid in Foxhound?)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Favourite piece of Assassins Creed lore? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 23:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is lots of great historical fiction in AC but my favourite has to be the shroud from Syndicate. The fact it's was the cloth Jesus wiped his face in before he was crucified only for the shrouds healing power to bring him back from the dead is really cool! What you favourite ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rocket League... Rugby? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 20:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds cool but could anyone work out how it would work - I guess kicking it in between the posts could be the goal and just make the ball like the cube one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> URGENT HELP NEEDED (Rank wiped) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 06:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soo I've just upgraded my PS4 hard drive from 500gb to 2tb. I've just downloaded rocket league to find my whole rank has been wiped I am now 1 and a rookie. I used to be an expert !!! My online rank is still the same - anyone know how I get it back ? I'm so depressed - all my stats have been wiped aswell  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting back into older Metal Gears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 14:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I play V regularly but recently been thinking playing about the other games in the series again. Started new games on Guns of the Patriots last night and omg it's so hard to get used to the controls and older engine. Like feels unplayable (I know it isn't) anyone have any tips for me ? Or just that I should keep playing it ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jumping back in. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 04:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I recently bought a new hard drive and can finally reinstall the Division. Gunna start playing again with my bro and we have to do the last mission of the game. What changes should I know about and what can I do post game now without he underground dlc? (I last played in earlyMay) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've bought all the DLC's and played them a ton... still haven't been Lando, Dengar, Bosk , Chewy or Nien Numb... (sorry for my spelling of SW names) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 22:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is Bobby Charlton. Manchester United's all time top goal scorer and England's second (behind Wayne Rooney). How much does he look like Don Draper/John Hamm!? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 02:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate running... anybody else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so I started running about 2 years ago, now I do about 10km 4 times a week but I absolutely hate doing it. I mean I like the feeling after of being tired and feeling healthier but hate going. Literally have to drag myself to the gym/park and I get so depressed thinking about having to do another one - I can't be the only one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did the (Mammal Pod) know who Venom was? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 05:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did the Boss AI know Venom wasn't Big Boss? It's facial recognition (if it has any) can't be that good can it?

She says something like 'You're not Jack'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Metal Gear Solid and actual history-who knows anything about the era your playing in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 05:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So as a history student and a general history buff I'm usually pretty aware of what's going on in Metal Gear's world in terms of the real world history. Whether it be 1970's Latin America, 1960's Cold War, the Angolan Civil War, the Cyprus dispute, the Soviet invasion of Afghanistan. I love Metal Gear pays attention to its time periods and teaches me stuff on the occasion. But my question is: how many of you who play understand the context and if not does Metal Gear help you learn it or do you simply not care?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BF1 - heavy tank overpowered? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 22:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So after coming of the back of scoring 27-0, 32-2 and 36-1 almost exclusively using a heavy tank I feel it's way too powerful. Maybe it's because it's an open beta and people don't understand how to destroy it and most enemy tanks I'm come across are really bad. What does everyone else think?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sean Murray - 'aimed to be the next Kojima ended up being the next Molyneux' how valid is this statement? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 02:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you trust Konami US with the series? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 04:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just thinking about the future of metal gear after survive and if the general audience trust Konami (especially the US branch) to make a true Metal Gear game. They seem to have a good relationship with David Hayter so perhaps we could see a new game set after or before V with him repising his role ? Built on the foundations of V's mechanics. If passionate Metal Gear fans worked on it is Kojima necessary ? I would personally love a new game with the real big boss set after V. Meeting Gray Fox, Sniper Wolf, Naomi etc could also see some cool intersections with ocelot and Eva. Alternatively could see Snake's missions in Vietnam ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Boss will - noble goal or unrealistic fantasy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 21:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've been thinking of the Boss' will making the world whole, unified etc Now I am just wondering how many of you guys think she was on to something? To me it sounds nice but is wildly unrealistic. We are becoming closer and a world through globalisation and the Internet but nothing could ever unify everyone. Like MGSV sort of shows there is too much hatred, too much thirst for revenge and so many different agendas. Even in the fiction of MGS I don't think her vision could have ever happened and only things like Outer Heaven show a glimpse of what it'd be like  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opinions on how to make running easier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 17:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am 20 year old, 6'2 200Ib, in shape guy. I run 10k 4 times a week but I always have to have breaks at various stages throughout. My legs can't take prolonged running and the most I can usually do without stopping (solely due to my legs hurting) is about 3k and the most I've done is 5k. The actual time I run during the 10k is about 40-45 mins but the breaks I'm forced to take bumps that to about 60. I've recently ordered some shock absorbing insoles to help but does anyone have suggestions on how to lessen the impact on my legs? Eg running technique </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ocelot's Mother-does he or Snake know who it is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 06:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if it's ever touched on properly but does snake or ocelot know that he is the son of the Boss? I mean with all the information gathering Ocleot does he must know and wouldn't snake see the resemblance? I know snake knows the Boss had a child. Can anyone help me out?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ciri's Cousin... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Next MGS : Vietnam? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Metal Gear Solid is a very educational game series ! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 05:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
