<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1239</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 19:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly liked the tragedy ending the best. Sad, but such is the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 19:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, pretty bummed myself. Trying to enjoy dark souls agin now but honestly realizing that it merely pretends to be everything the Witcher was in lore, story, role playing, and combat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 00:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit I thought I was the only one. Punched a mirror cabinet when I was angry after finding out a girl was cheating on me and scratched my arm up (scratched, not cut). Between that and my terrible mood and not wanting to talk to anyone, Doctor interpreted it as a suicide attempt. Cue being told I can either sign myself into institution or be forcibly confined to a ward for six months. Choose the first and had to lie and pretend I had been tripping out on Ambien I found in the cabinet because they didn't believe I was "just angry" and were hanging that 6 month stay over my head if I didn't comply. Was there for most of a week until I actually met with the psychiatrist and he said I was 100% fine. Still worried that medical record is going to bite me in the ass someday and keep me out of a job or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 00:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And thank God that people are finally realizing Religion is bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 00:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright you've all convinced me to give it another chance. I must have let my bias prevent me from looking at the work fairly when I read it years back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 14:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally all that book was about was rich people being self centered assholes. The entire novel was basically just an episode of the Kardashians. I really don't get how anyone could find its one dimensional characters "enthralling" but then again, people *do* watch the Kardashians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 04:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an EMT: getting old REALLY sucks and you really need to enjoy your life while you're young and be as compassionate and giving as you can possibly be, because when your 16+ hour workday is primarily helping over a dozen random people who can't even sit up on their own and will be dead in a few months, you're forced to confront the ugly truths you'd usually like to avoid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jason Isbell: Relatively Easy (acoustic Americana/blues folk/country) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 19:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 15:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an EMT I can attest that in the US, they cannot take you by force if you are an adult unless you are a convict, in an altered mental state, or declared to be dangerous by police. If they forced you to go, that's kidnapping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 04:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally had this happen every other time I would run that shortcut back in the beginning  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 19:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Hustle. Critically acclaimed film that won an Oscar. Literally just people whining and bitching about nothing. Pointless movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 04:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cthulhu lies in Ryleh, located at the point in the Pacific Ocean furthest from all continental shores, why is he rising out of the Baltic?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 04:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cthulhu is located in Ryleh, approximately located below the point in the Pacific Ocean that is furthest from all continental shores. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alright, can we please just decide on a damn meta level already? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 05:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So since I get answers ranging from 80 to 100 to 110 to 120 to 130 to 150 and so on, can someone please tell me where I need to stop leveling in order to get summons? I'm trying to work out my build but honestly I'm afraid I'm going over the meta level for most PvP players.
Edit: I'm mostly just wondering what level I need to be to get the most connections. I don't want to be running around and never getting summons because I'm in the wrong bracket  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 20:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's something I forgot, the charging port. Granted this seems to be a universal tech problem. All my old phones bricked after the charging ports eventually wore down. Had to position my first controller a certain way to get it to charge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help with DS4 battery life and sticks peeling/not responding to forward input? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 08:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is the third controller I've had, which doesn't see any throwing onto the floor or other abuse that should cause it to be damaged, and yet they all only seem to hold a charge for maybe a couple hours at a time (ex: I just charged mine for an hour, came back, played for a couple, and it died again), and more importantly, the rubber on the sticks peels off after minor usage, and eventually the left stick won't respond when pushed forward (which basically renders it unusable). Given this is not the first, or even second controller to give me problems, is this a common experience? How do you usually compensate for these problems? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 10:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember those two, they took a couple days or practice. The problem I'm finding here is that the lack of dodgability from her attacks and the fact that she's phasing through pillars completely as opposed to simply attacking through them, coupled with the fact that the lock on mechanic isn't functioning during this fight, is what's making me question if something is wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 09:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stats in order:
Lvl 94, Hollow 99
Vig 23
Att 21
End 19
Vit 10
STR 15
Dex 20
Int 10
Fth 30
Luck 35 (40 with hollowed weapon)

I've been trying to maintain a build that mixes bleeding with great chaos fireball as a basic ranged attack and miracles to buff, to see if I can mix a bleed/faith build. Works thus far, only found a roadblock at this fight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Honestly **** the Dancer of Boreal Valley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 09:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This boss is completely impossible. I don't know if my copy of the game is bugged but holy crap there is literally nothing I can do to this boss. I've tried bleed, I've tried lightning, I've tried pyromancy, and while I can do damage, there is absolutely no way I can not be hit by her combos. If she does a grab while I'm using a melee weapon with Carthus Rogue/Lightning enchant, I can't roll away from her, as if I roll left, right, or back, she still connects. If I happen to get out of the way in time, she always defends her flanks by a three hit slash, slam, slash combo or some variation that always manages to land a hit if you dodge the first part of it, as she follows up by doing an attack right where you dodged to. So I tried to keep her threaded around the pillar, only she can not only attack through these pillars with perfect accuracy and *just* the range she needs to do a double stab attack, but she can even walk right through the pillar itself and double tap me dead with one of her slam/slash combos that I can't dodge away from. It doesn't help that when I try to bleed her with Dorhys' Gnawing, the lock on mechanic won't trigger, so I have to free aim when she is standing right on top of me doing some manner of combo that I won't be able to dodge if I cast the spell. More often than not, my character will stop, spin around, and fire the spell in the complete opposite direction, then proceed to get pounded into the ground. This game hasn't been a cakewalk but I don't know what I'm supposed to do with an enemy that can close distance instantly, has too many combos to make a greatshield or dodging viable, can attack behind herself, and can both attack and walk through the pillars I am being told she shouldn't be able to get through, and where the lock-on mechanic that lets me hit her with spells absolutely refuses lock on, and free fires in the most arbitrary direction. 
Before I just give up on this game, what do I try next? None of the strategies I've been offered work, and given that she doesn't merely attack, but actually walk through pillars, and is immune to the lock-on mechanic, I'm wondering if I'm perhaps bugged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 02:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it's in regards to Sam himself saying that reality is limited to consciousness. He spoke of this in the End of Faith podcast 1. The notion I'm encountering is the idea that this means that consciousness is a predicate for existence, and that science can never address or solve the mystery of consciousness. Furthermore, if consciousness is a predicate, this would mean some form of consciousness has always existed. Can we still reconcile this with atheism if true, or can Sam refute these claims and further explain his notions that he spoke of in the first part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 15:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is at the very least provisionally related, certainly it is to the book itself. He actually spoke of this already himself in the first podcast. I was wondering if he could further elaborate on how this idea of consciousness as a predicate to existence might relate to the topic of the book:atheism. Specifically, can he refute it or justify atheism if we claim there must always have been consciousness? Maybe Sam would not see this as pertaining enough, and would rather answer it elsewhere, or find it boring, but I'll stand by my opinion that it's related, and leave it to his prerogative.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 04:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you please comment on the biggest dilemma I am personally pondering in my philosophy undergraduate pursuits: the information theory of the universe and the notion that reality only exists so long as there is consciousness to perceive it, and how to reconcile this notion with athiesm or outright counter the notion?

For some possibly needed context: the theory (as explained to me) is that science cannot assert anything about a reality outside our consciousness, only what we appear to perceive. Given this, we cannot truly say that there are objects separate from us that we are witnessing; you yourself say that our outside experience and our thoughts occupy the same "space". Thus, I am facing two notions: reality does not exist without consciousness, and thus there must always have been some sort of consciousness, and that there is not an "outside world" but rather a two dimensional plane of information that we conceptualize as the three dimensional reality we perceive. Can we counter the theory that existence requires consciousness and if not, how must we look at the Big Bang from now on? Is this a problem for atheism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 00:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply, meant a lot. I owe you a few drinks sometime.

D D? Seriously? I knew there was a bit of geek floating around in there, haha!= If you ever want to play again, I'll dig out my old gear, wherever it is. Some of the best nights of my childhood were spent in the Forgotten Realms, fighting mind flayers. 

I hate those damn things... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 00:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Ben, I hope you wont mind if I get this sappy shit out of the way before I ask you a question, but I think its worth saying, even if I hate getting emotional. Skip to the last bit otherwise.

Your music has been a huge help in getting through some tough times, and Ive seen my fair share, from abuse as a kid to just plain bad luck and stupid choices. The past few years Ive gone from letting it drag me down to letting it turn me into a not-so-great human being. Ive done a lot of things I regret in those years, and still struggle with kicking the booze and cigarettes. 

However, listening to your stuff give me something to identify with and made me feel a hell of a lot better, in fact I think it gave me an outlet in music that kept me from doing some really permanently stupid things. It even got me to try my hand at it myself (which is arguably bad for everyone that has to hear me, haha) I guess Ive taken to idolizing you and the guys; I dunno if thats weird, but hey, its how it is.  Ive been to many of your shows in Boston these past few years and weve talked each time over smokes. Last time I was there during the Seat of Our Pants tour I kind of imposed upon you and shared my gratitude and trouble with you, especially concerning recent heartbreak and the coming death of my father (which came just a couple months later). Let me tell you, I havent had more than a few genuinely supportive figures in my life, but your understanding and empathy really meant a lot to me, even for those short moments, and I thank you for that (you even carried out a request for me, which was awesome). That and my regret over not letting my father die with a better image of me really gave me a kick to the ass about getting my shit together, or at least care enough to try.

As far as a question, Id just be fine knowing about your hobbies outside of music, or whatever plans you have for the future. You guys all seem to tour endlessly, but you must have some things you like doing outside of all that. Games? Reading? Politics? Other Music?

(P.S. See you in Boston in October! You better play some of this awesome new stuff.)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm on the run but you NEED to listen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 02:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know where to begin

Long story short, I'm a med student. Or, was.

I was accepted into a research program with some important people. I don't know why, I'm not the perfect student, but I guess I impressed someone. 

We were studying a pathogen of some sorts that one of them had found out. It's remarkable. It's seemingly a common cold variant, so obviously it's a widespread thing. Yes, you might have it.

Why should you care?

We were studying this pathogen after one of the heads of the project picked up on something weird- a lot of convicted murderers had this new pathogen floating around in their system. I don't know how to explain this quickly, but it seems that the pathogen wasn't just a cold virus- it's attacking the brain. Most of the people that get it (there were a couple of people that had it that didn't display any personality change) would start to become increasingly violent and irrational. Nothing anyone tried had any sort of effect on deterring this. It was like it was physically changing the brain pathways. 

The thing is that the people who had it for long periods of time were becoming more and more dementia-ridden and crazy. Some of them even died from it. Autopsies seemed to show that it's working almost like Alzheimer's- it's....breaking down parts of the brain.

I'm running out of time, I'm sorry, this is incoherent. Shit.

Look, when they found out what this was doing they decided to do tests on other people. I thought they simply already had it, but I found out that they were actually GIVING it to people that didn't already carry it. They had plenty of people to test it on:this is a some sort of common cold-level infection- a lot of people probably have it. 


Obviously I protested this. The experiments were just getting too shady for me. The implications are of course troubling, but at the time I wasn't going to just sit back and let this shit happen. 

I was promptly sat down in an office surrounded by several men and told that I needed to shut up. That's the polite way of saying it at least. I don't know what the hell I'd gotten into, but all these guys that I was having drinks with before were now telling me that if I didn't keep my mouth shut that there would be consequences. "This is a private project, it's important we don't attract too much attention. We don't want any of our findings to be lost because someone is telling stories outside of class."

I'm getting funny looks about my appearance. I haven't bathed in a while. I should leave soon.

Look, so I went home and confided about it to my fiance. She was appalled of course, and this might seem strange but she was uncharacteristically irrational in her anger over it. She demanded I do something about it, she was absolutely livid about it. 

I think it was at this point that I realized something was probably horribly wrong. Come to think of it I had been feeling a bit off for a while before. Oh fuck maybe I am responsible.

I'm too shaky to think straight. Please bear with me.

Look, ever since I had started protesting about everything my girlfriend had been getting more and more angry and impatient with me every time I was at home. It wasn't just at home- we live in a town where there's growing crime, so it's inevitable for crazy shit to happen sometimes. But she was getting really agitated with everyone. She was put on suspension from work towards the end because she got into a fight with a man that she worked with. She just blew up and started swinging at him. He was being a creep, I'll admit and she's always been a straight shooter. It's just that she's never been physically aggressive.

Even at home she was starting to be a bit physical. I'd have to tell her to calm down and watch her hands a few times. One time we were taking a walk and got into an argument, and she just started slapping and swearing. I had to hold her arms and tell her to stop, and that's when the white knights came to "rescue" her. The cops ended up stopping by, and she calmed down and admitted it was her and that everything was fine. We were given a firm warning and sent home. 


The point where everything blew up was when I decided that I should try and tell someone. I started writing down everything I could about what was going on and trying to find evidence. I never did find enough- I didn't get the chance.


You might have heard about this on the news, but it happened in a city where there's a good amount of crime, and the hot topic right now is police and blacks. 

I came home and she was standing in the kitchen in her underwear. There was stuff thrown all around, and she looked like a mess. She'd been hospitalized before for being bipolar but it had never been this bad. I think I was starting to realize what was going on right about now.

I obviously asked her what the hell was going on, but she didn't say anything. She just flipped, screaming and babbling about something I couldn't even make out, I had to grab her and tell her to calm down, and that's when she jumped on me. She just turned into an animal-biting, clawing, hitting. I had to try to get her off. But she just kept-


I'm sorry, I just...

Look, I didn't mean to hurt her, but I had to get her to stop. It was heat of the moment. I didn't mean for her to hit her head. 

It's not my fault. I don't know what happened. There's so many people from all around starting to lose it. Look at the news. The world's going mad. People are rioting and killing.

She was sick, I couldn't do anything. Please believe me, it was an accident.


Look, I'm trying to get the hell out of here. I won't say where I'm going. But look:the place I come from has a lot of people. There's even an airport. It's the perfect place for a pathogen to spread. Have you wondered why people are getting more and more crazy? That Florida face-eater, the riots all over the news, the shootings that keep happening- There's something happening. People are sick. You are probably sick. Have you noticed people around you getting more and more angry and hostile?

The worst part is they know. They know all about it. I can't prove it, I don't have the means. 

Somebody has to get the news out there- you people are all sick, and you don't even know it. It might not be as bad for you as it is for others, but I swear that you probably have it. You need to get ready. If someone doesn't do something about it this is all going to keep getting worse.


This isn't turning people into zombies, it's not some joke- it's making people irrational and violent and crazy and none of you even realize it.

There were some people we looked at that didn't have it- that doesn't mean you're safe. You need to be ready.

I'm sorry, I don't have any more time. I'll try to come back. Please.


I never meant to hurt anybody. I can't get this pulse out of my head. It's like a throbbing screech. I wish it would just stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
