<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2418</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hi guys, am after some advice regarding the tutorials, am getting steady ones and twos views not gonna quit my job and work from home yet.... lol but somebody messaged me and said they would prefer if I talked as opposed to give text guidance. Any thoughts? Am trying to grow my channel so any comments, thoughts would be appreciated :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys, am after some advice regarding the tutorials, am getting steady ones and twos views not gonna quit my job and work from home yet.... lol but somebody messaged me and said they would prefer if I talked as opposed to give text guidance. Any thoughts? Am trying to grow my channel so any comments, thoughts would be appreciated :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photoshop Tutorial - remove anything from an image in Photoshop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photoshop Tutorial - Remove people from an image </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't resize a gif image, when you open this in Photoshop it will flatten the image and unfortunately you will lose the animation, if it's not a complicated gif you could redo this in photoshop, but you would need the orig images or something similar to go off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's a single page that needs printed on both sides then you would send one side to the printer initially and then put the printed side back into the printer, probably printed side down (depends on your printer).

 Firstly, print out both sides separately and then staple them together to form your invitation. That way you should know the correct orientation for printing. Hopefully that makes sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photoshop cc 2017 tutorial - How to remove a person from an image </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about this one?
[Imgur](http://i.imgur.com/7D5KJPZ.jpg)

or this one?
[World map one colour](http://i.imgur.com/XNSkdnJ.jpg)

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
