<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1565</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 16:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that's a stupid question at all. Not everyone on these forums are pro traders, and questions like this benefit numerous people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Stockhouse is more appropriately called Shithouse, due to all the spamming and pumping that goes on there. It's a total jungle and you have to be VERY careful about what you believe. I actually think this subreddit is a better place for real discussions than those bullboards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 22:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having $1MM by the age of 34 from investing is called gambling and getting lucky, not playing it safe. Keep that up and he will be 36 and back with his parents.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 22:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like OAS, or Old Age Security. You do not pay into his directly like CPP (Canada Pension Plan) as it comes directly out of the general revenues of the Gov of Canada. Funny thing is, if you have more than $70K in total income or more when you you get it, the government starts taking OAS back from you because you are too rich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 22:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So not being depressed means you're happier. Got it! Who the fuck 1) thinks this shit up and 2) actually reports it as if they have made some miraculous discovery?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 13:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to Valet at fancy steak houses in T.O. back in the late 90's, early 2000's. We had a regular who was fairly well known to be affiliated with the mob, and he kept a 9mm under his seat. I think of all the times I parked his car, and reached my hand under the seat to see if it was still there. It wasn't until years later that I realized I had put my fingerprints all over the damn thing many times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 13:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little Johnny's dead and gone, he won't be seen no more. For what he thought was H2O, was H2SO4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
