<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3297</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the most bad-ass scenes of any cartoon series and one of my favorite moments from the entire Star Wars franchise - the introduction of General Grievous in Genndy Tartakovsky's "Clone Wars" adaptation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favorite stories in the Star Wars franchise? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 04:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone, I want to make this post to suggest my favorite stories to those who might be interested, as well as to see what other people would consider to be the best stories in the entire Star Wars franchise. So, here are mine:

* Episodes I-VI of the Star Wars films

* Star Wars: Clone Wars (Tartakovsky's series)

* Star Wars: The Clone Wars (the 3D series)

* The Courtship of Princess Leia

* Rogue One

* Star Wars Legacy

* Knights of the Old Republic 1 and 2

* The Force Unleashed

* The Thrawn Trilogy

* Labyrinth of Evil and the novelization of Revenge of the Sith

So, what are your favorites?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's take time to remember how terrifying the Ewoks actually are in the scope of the Star Wars saga. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 21:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 343, pretty please balance the ground-to-air combat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 21:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what change happened, but it feels like recently the Warzone modes are totally and completely won by Wasps and Banshees as soon as a team is able to spawn them. If there's any way to balance that, I'd be in 100% agreement with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enjoyed Rogue One. It reminded me of a different great Star Wars tale set between the PT and the OT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 05:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Technically, "Merry Christmas" is still a correct saying to say for most Americans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 16:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which game should I pick up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 00:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got some money for a game, and I was wondering if any of you guys happen to have any recommendations. I'm thinking about getting Titanfall 2, battlefield 1, or dead rising 4. Anybody have any high recommendations among those games, or other games of a similar nature? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Tucker's dance in Rush Hour 2 is among my favorite moments in cinema. One of my favorite films </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 14:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your GOTY for 2016? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 21:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been a crazy year. Really. 

The upside is that we've had a pretty varied and interesting year for video games. Of course, there are still releases waiting to come out, like The Last Guardian and Dead Rising 4, but I'm interested in seeing what everyone else has at the top of their list. So what are your picks for their "Best Games" for the year? 

Here are mine:

* Quantum Break
* Deus Ex: Mankind Divided
* Gears of War 4
* SUPERHOT
* Inside </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Excellent show! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 05:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like a cross between "Firefly" and "Dollhouse" where a space-faring crew have to deal with existentialism and identity, while being pursued by pasts their not fully aware of that takes them to fascinating places as characters. A great main cast with fascinating themes and I was impressed with their ability to kill off characters for the sake of character development and story and not just shock value (shame, Game of Thrones). 

I'm just wrapping up season 2 right now, and I hope season 3 keeps up the stellar quality of writing, mystery, action, and characterizations. This is easily alongside The Expanse as one of the best sci-fi shows in recent memory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recommendation on which game I should get? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 03:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone. I'm looking for a new game and wanted to get people's opinions on what's currently out. I'm interested in a good single-player, but I'd also loved a good multiplayer if there's an active community

I'm deciding between these games, and I'll only be getting one:
* Watch Dogs 2
* Dishonored 2
* Titanfall 2
* Battlefield 1

Thank you for your input! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movie deserves a remake/reboot/readaptation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 17:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all know that classic films often get updated in Hollywood these days, much to the dismay of fans of those time weathered movies. But what about the films that had potential to be great films, but we're just executed poorly?

"In Time" starts with an interesting premise of time = money, but never evolves into anything interesting, and character inconsistencies, a lacking plot, and no interesting explored ideas keep it from being a classic sci-fi film. On the other side, films like "Starship Troopers" or "The Count of Monte Cristo" are noticeably different from their source material, despite being good films (in my opinion) and some they want to see adapted differently so that they stick closer to either the content or the spirit of the source material.

What films would you like to see get a second attempt at life on the silver screen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Story related question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 01:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do Corvo and/or Emily have their own character arc in the game or do they mostly stay the same as characters until the end? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ONLY real problem I have with the story options in Witcher 3: Wild Hunt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 00:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wish the developers could have crafted a way to end the Yen romance BEFORE the Last Wish side-quest since I was dead-set on Triss being my romantic interest. It's hearbreaking to see Yen so destroyed seeing that she still had feelings for Geralt and not have any way to avoid that moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't hate Jar Jar Binks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 23:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like Jar Jar in The Phantom Menace. I think he's annoying, portrayed as overly incompetent, and a lot of times, his comedic antics are either not funny or inappropriate for the scene. That being said, I don't hate him as a character, and I personally think he gets way too much derision. In Phantom Menace, he helps Obi-Wan and Qui-gon believing that he owes them his life after saving him and keeps to his beliefs even when they tell him that it's not necessary, he's willing to suffer corporal punishment for bringing in outsiders (without knowing whether or not he'd get out of the punishment), and (despite the unnecessary comical moments that don't land AT ALL) he was willing to go INTO COMBAT for what he believed in, especially for the possibility of peace between the Gungans and the Naboo.

There are FAR more characters who I find insultingly irritating as characters who aren't intended to be so: Zach from "The Strain" TV show, Bella from the "Twilight" films, Marie from "Breaking Bad," Jax from "Sons of Anarchy," Rose from the Metal Gear Solid games (seriously, she's the absolute worst). Jar Jar is poorly written for the most part, but at least he's self-sacrificing, considerate, friendly and brave (when not being an idiot).

Also, can we at least acknowledge that Lucas had enough clarity and respect for the public to dial back Jar Jar to almost absolute zero in episode 2 and 3 because of how he was received?

I know the prequels are all flawed (spectacularly in some instances), but this particular mark stuck out to me. No. Jar Jar is not a great character. He's not even a "good character", but at least he has some redeemable qualities to him that I feel that a lot of people don't consider. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AWESOME Metal cover of Spider-man TAS theme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 03:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Luigis Mansion: A Case Study in Spooktacular Characterization </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 23:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The Empire Strikes Back" is an old movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 20:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The Empire Strikes Back" is an old movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 20:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Luigis Mansion: A Case Study in Spooktacular Characterization </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 17:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Luigis Mansion: A Case Study in Spooktacular Characterization </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 17:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commute to the Light </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 15:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Master of the Mystic End Credits (Audio Only) from Doctor Strange </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marvel: Every Note a Symphony -- RESPONSE VIDEO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fallout's Folly: How Fallout 4 Makes Romance Hollow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 02:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fallout's Folly: How Fallout 4 Makes Romance Hollow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 02:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Thoughts on Frame Rates... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 06:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everything Wrong With "Everything Wrong With The Last of Us" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 06:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captain America: Civil War - Tragedian Stucture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 02:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Captain America: Civil War - Tragedian Stucture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 02:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shaed - Running Through the Fields [alternative rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "BioShock: The Collection" review  "You and Me, kid. Were going places." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 22:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BioShock: The Collection review  "You and Me, kid. Were going places." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 21:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favorite weird law? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 02:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some weird things that science can't explain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 18:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the best video games of the seventh generation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 02:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pokemon Go: Live in Austin, Texas! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 22:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ivan Ooze is the PG version of Deadpool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 04:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Mass Effect is the Most Important Science Fiction Universe of Our Generation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 22:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The dog thought she could get away with a dip in the pond. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 02:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If money wasn't a concern, what would be your dream job? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 18:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some of your favorite movies of the 90's? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 18:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Ready Player One" review... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 02:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I sometimes wonder how many users registered to this website have passed... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 02:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey, guys! I just wanted to share a video I made long ago when Korey and cargill were on "A Couple of Cold Ones". Please let me know what you think </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 20:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump committed a felony violation of the Logan Act by asking Russian hackers for help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 22:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "TUN: Blame of Thrones": Does the "Game of Thrones" TV series lose the spirit of the novels? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 23:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EVERYTHING] "TUN: Blame of Thrones." Do you think that this user is correct in how the "tone" of the books is conveyed in the show? What are your opinions on the matter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 22:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everything Wrong With CinemaSins - Y'know, Generally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 17:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Jessica Jones" review and commentary... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Remember The 90's?" - The Incredible Shrinking Matt   Jacquie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 15:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holy shit, "The Big Short" was eye-opening </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 07:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm mad as Hell, and I have no idea what to do about that. Great performances and terrific filmmaking aside, I'm still so incredibly shocked after all this time that the bankers got away with it with minimal ramifications (especially with absolutely no guidelines concerning the bail out) and the government did FUCKING NOTHING after the collapse. And it's STILL going on with the "Bespoke Tranche Opportunity".

I want to fucking punch somebody.

Post-edit: To those saying "it's sad that you learned something from a movie", you should understand the concept of "argument from personal incredulity".

Post-edit 2: Revolutions - I also genuinely enjoyed the filmmaking that included the editing, sound design, visual presentation, and oddly engrossing juxtaposition between retro long the story and breaking the fourth wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This subreddit is incredible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 09:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of these people commenting and leaving their own impressions and perspectives about the games and the books, and it's not rife with "the games/books are SOOO MUCH BETTER" argument sections. 

Thank God for a more mature subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Smart Guys" is one of the funniest and well-made American comedies in years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 19:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Better with Age: "Nothin' but bits" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 21:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Better with Age: "Nothin' but bits" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 20:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Better with Age: "Nothin' but bits" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 20:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Story Doesn't Matter? (aka "Ignore the Pepperoni") </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 22:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Story Doesn't Matter? (aka "Ignore the Pepperoni") </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 19:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Talking to Myself: The Daisy Dilemma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 01:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox stuck in tree (Fox is alright). This little guy was chasing a squirrel and lodged his head in a tree. He was freed by Fairfax County Animal control. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 02:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's a favorite small side-character that's always stuck with you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 23:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, one of the joys in video game RPGs is discovering smaller characters who just brighten up the world or add something interesting to the game overall, even if they don't have a huge part in the narrative.

One of my favorites has to be Sir Roderick Ponce Von Fontlebottom the Magnificent Bastard from "Jade Empire". A pompous and arrogant Englishman extolling the virtues of his home country to the "uneducated". Yet, he was also something of a charming rogue who wasn't quite without likable personality.

What about you? Which side-characters do you remember fondly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What phenomena can't science explain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 07:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Besides fixing bugs and miscellaneous problems, I would ask CD Projekt Red for only ONE more thing for Witcher 3: Wild Hunt as an update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 04:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I LOVE Witcher 3: Wild Hunt and its expansions, the only other thing I would ask of the developers would be to allow us the ability to change which background we want for the "main menu". You know that part where Geralt is in deep meditation while scrolling the menu? I would love for their to be an option to choose between the vanilla game, Hearts of Stone, and the Blood and Wine versions of Geralt kneeling in deep meditation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top 10 Games of the Year....so far... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 22:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, here's how my list is shaping up:

* Quantum Break (my GOTY at the moment given that terrific time-traveling narrative)
* SUPERHOT
* Doom
* Oxenfree
* That Dragon, Cancer

Special mention to Uncharted 4, Overwatch, and "Blood and Wine" (I don't think this one may count, however, given that it's DLC for another game, but it's still AMAZING!!!!)

What about you? What are your choices? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everything Wrong With "Everything Wrong With Avengers: Age of Ultron" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 23:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everything Wrong With "Everything Wrong With Sherlock Holmes" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 23:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a lot to be excited about with E3. For me? it's returning to smack down some zombies with this goof. He's covered wars, y'know. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 08:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York court allows police to cover up mass surveillance operations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 17:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think that the Marc Webb "Spider-man" films were incredibly underrated... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 09:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel that both of "The Amazing Spider-man" films were both undervalued for their quality. The first one had an excellent examination of the role of vigilantism, justice, and vengeance and how that actually evolved into a mature understanding what crime-fighting actually is (especially how it tied into Peter's own personal vendetta against the man who killed Uncle Ben).

The second film I thought was a terrific examination of the roles of hope vs. hopelessness, nihilism, trust, and community. I also thought that everyone had a great performance in these films.

So far, Andrew Garfield is my favorite Peter Parker AND Spider-man on screen, and I am so glad that SONY decided to got ahead and take a chance on the risky material of these two films.

I'm looking forward to Tom Holland and Spider-man: Homecoming in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30 Minutes or Less: "The Social Network" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 21:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My review of "Doom" (2016)... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 21:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: why isn't solar power more utilized in the United States? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 18:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "True Romance" - The movie where Gary Oldman plays the role of a Rastafarian pimp and has one of the best scenes in an already amazing film </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 08:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My review of "The Nice Guys" - a terrific return to the crime genre for Shane Black </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 08:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A fun parody of "Shenmue" in "Sleeping Dogs" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 08:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a bad game that you'd like see remade? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 07:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not every video game can be the chart-topping critic-loved game of the year, and sometimes their execution is just totally off, although at their core lies a beating heart of interesting ideas.

What's a game that you liked in theory, but in practice, was a messy pile of either mediocrity or downright bad quality and would love to see a studio remake it?

For me, while the Kane and Lynch series is tempting, I gotta go with "Eat Lead: the Return of Matt Hazard". A few moment of particularly engaging brilliance here and there along with some good music and solid voice work makes me sad that the game we ended up getting was a little less of the "Who Framed Roger Rabbit" of video games, and turned out more like "Cool World".

What is your 'redemption game' you'd like to see be made? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most 90's phrase you can think of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 21:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quantum Break is one of my contenders for Game of the Year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 08:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love time traveling stories. I love time traveling narratives that actually work with the genre for tension building, expectations, mystery, wonder, and character development. Quantum Break has that by the boat load. The actual question of whether or not time traveling itself could ever be free of a 'closed-loop' is something I found intoxicating in the minute discussions of predestination and free will. 

This game is all about focusing on using the mechanics, presentation, and even the audio design for the sake of the narrative. A great cast of characters with damn good writing and motivations only cement the painful contemplations of what time travel and "the end of time" mean for each and every single one of them.

The very fact that you can influence the story arc in particularly meaningful ways for the world and characters is something absolutely fantastic and MUST be commended for the hard working people at Remedy. 

The cast is a wonderfully diverse and strongly acted group of characters who really make the ensemble dynamic work. Shawn Ashmore, Courtney Hope, Aidan Gillen, Dominic Monaghan, Lance Reddick, and everyone in the production is fantastic and memorable. 

As a narrative guy, I applaud Remedy for making a game that really pushes great narrative storytelling in video games, and wanted to express that feeling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you consider ground zeros and the phantom pain to be one game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 08:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, I think metal gear solid five is a hell of a lot better once you taking to the idea that ground zeroes and the phantom pain are all one game just separated into two different parts.

I really think that Kojima productions could've even naturally added to the game by reusing assets from ground zeroes like camp zero.

It also changes how you see Boss by contrast to venom seeing how much of an overall darker character the OG boss is where "silencing people" out of inconvenience is totally acceptable to him in Ground Zeroes with Venom being far more action oriented and forgiving to others. A more "optimistic" version of Big Boss.

I would have loved to have cassette tapes about them arguing over identity and even waxing philosophy, like classic Metal Gear usually does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doctor Strange screenwriter (C. Robert Cargill) on the problems with adapting "The Ancient One" and the accusations of white-washing. A very interesting and complicated issue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 07:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My review of "Smart Guys" - a definite must watch for Normal Boots fans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 00:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Smart Guys" is one of the funniest shows in years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 17:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Quantum Break" review (a.k.a. "Time-after-Time") </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 06:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favorite fan poster? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 05:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> URL links would be nice :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know where I can listen to the Alien Isolation archive logs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 05:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone. I love audio logs that are well made in games like BioShock or Dead Space. I was wondering if anyone here happens to know a youtube video or a website where one could listen to all of the audio logs in the game? Thanks for taking the time to write back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think the overall idea of Metal Gear Solid is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 05:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The MGS universe is many things: inventive, imaginative, political, philosophical, playful, downright bonkers, etc.

If there is a central overall theme or idea that encompasses the entire saga (or at least MGS1 and later) what do you think it is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quantum Break is one Hell of a time travel narrative </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 20:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it might be one of the only time travel stories of recent memory that's entirely a closed loop narrative, but doesn't make the "inevitability" the only central component, and relies more on the mystery of what the characters discover.

Remedy knocked it out of the park with this game :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you be angry if they put in a "easy mode" for Dark Souls? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 00:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For future "Souls" games (including the upcoming Dark Souls 3), how would you feel if they put in a "easy mode" for players who don't have the ability/time/patience to master game mechanics?

For myself, I wouldn't see the harm in doing so (especially since it would be a good "gateway difficulty" for new players to enjoy the experience and have the chance to become addicted to the gameplay, but I'd like to hear your opinions on the subject. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you categorize Dark Souls? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 17:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What "kind" of game, or genre, do you think Dark souls belongs to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you tried Lord of the Fallen yet? Impressions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 06:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone. I downloaded the Xbox monthly Gold free game which was Lords of the Fallen. It's clearly inspired by the overall style and world design (general layout and design, etc. rather than visuals. I would say it's more similar looking to Darksiders 1 and 2) as well as some gameplay elements.

For those of you who are "From Software" fans, did you play this game, and, if so, did you enjoy it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are two types of futures.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 01:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One where our descendants will wonder how we did something so primitive as get water out of a tap, and another where they'll marvel about how we could get water out of a tap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where SOMA falters (in my humble opinion) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 20:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Halo 5 analysis from a fan who loved Halo 4. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 08:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all. 

I know Halo 5 is a divisive game. I really like it, but even I got to admit that the story wasn't as good as Halo 4's narrative, in my humble opinion. Haruspis is a writer who wrote a lengthy analysis of why Halo 4's narrative was so spectacular when analyzing tropes, motifs, themes, characters, lore, and overall storytelling (opinions I agree with); he also analyzes media and other content concerning the Halo universe and was excited to review Halo 5, and was personally crushed with the end result.

Overall, I agree with him that while there is a number of good things to occur with the story of Halo 5 (Osiris team, seeing more of the universe, and actually bringing civiliazations and civilians to the forefront with the non-combat levels) and like a few things he did not mention (that being the writing of the Warden, Roland getting more say in the conversation, the interesting story hook of the AIs rising up, the narrative bookend of Halsey emotionally reuniting with Chief, etc), however, I do admit that there are a good deal of problems which include HOW 343 set up the story (not primarily associated with the marketing) and other issues. 

I suggest you check it out, and I would to hear your impressions on how you felt where the game succeeded, failed, or had mixed results. Of course, these articles will be primarily focused on the story aspects of the game, so gameplay elements would probably be saved for another time.

[Halo 5: The Bad](https://haruspis.wordpress.com/2015/12/10/halo-5-a-compendium-of-lies/)

[Halo 5: The Good](https://haruspis.wordpress.com/2015/12/19/what-i-liked-about-halo-5/)

... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There should be websites that translates foreign songs into different languages, but also into a matching rhyming scheme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 16:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't tell you how many times I've listened to a foreign language song, loving the melody, but being disappointed that, when looking at it in English, the rhyming translations impede the 'feeling' of the song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would anyone else be as interested in I am if they made a Halo RPG? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 03:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given how much universe, lore, and character building 343 Industries has going on with games, comics, novels, etc. would anybody as interested as I would be if they decided to make a Halo RPG?

Maybe take the role of an Oni operative going from planet to planet dealing with rebel factions, human/Elite relations, stopping Kig-yar scavenger parties, discovering Forerunner tech, etc.

If they ever did do a Halo RPG, what would you like for them to include or explore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Possible Spoilers]Quick question: Did MCU/Netflix version of Daredevil kill anyone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 01:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was listening to someone talking about how Daredevil's origin with Stick is different since in the comics he left because Matt killed out of revenge rather than because he was getting emotionally attached to him.

Did Daredevil happen to kill anyone in the show? 

Post-Edit: Gotcha, Nobu's on the "debatable" side of the issue and the mobster he pushed into the dumpster, but nothing really definitive in terms of his morality of whether or not he allows himself to kill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did the one Crab say to another greedy Crab that was eating all of the mussels? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 17:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop being so shellfish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What property do you want see be adapted into a game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 01:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ask this to you lovely Reddit users out there:

A) Which property do you want to see adapted (or readapted), and why?

B) Which developer do want handling the game, and for what particular reason?

For myself, I would love to see TellTale adapt the cult-classic series Firefly (or maybe Serenity since FOX won't let go of the name and are just sitting on it like a Dragon on his gold hoard). The gray morality, great dialog, and classic characters would make for a thrilling romp.

... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brian Reed gets way too much hate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 02:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just completing Halo 5 again, and while I understand the disappointment in not having as amazing of a script as Halo 4, I think Brian Reed has made huge improvements as a writer since Spartan Ops and delivered a good story (thought a little light on character arcs and themes). However, the way people are talking about him on the Halo threads, one might think he enjoys destroying family tombstones for fun.

I've only experienced his work through the Halo games, and while he's not my favorite writer, he's certainly not the worst one possible to take the reigns for this entry, and Halo 5 was (mostly) well-executed, including interactions between characters, and really is more rewarding with repeated viewings.

I can respect someone having problems with story, or with how too damn subtle implications are made in the narrative, but I just think that the hatred thrown against this guy is ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Halo 5 Spoilers] Questions I have about Halo 5's story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 20:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all. I really liked Halo 5's story, but I was wondering if someone wouldn't mind filling in some details that I may have missed in the game, and with some of the surrounding media.

* Why are the Prometheans attacking the Covenant and humans? 

* Why didn't Cortana just warn populated colonies to leave so that she could raise the Guardians with no casualties?

* Is Chief aware of the smear campaign ONI did against him? 

* How did Chief find out where the Guardian was?

Thanks for taking the time to read and respond. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is a surprisingly larger amount of character development when you listen to your squad mates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 23:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't realize how much great bits of characterization you can get if you wait maybe 15-20 seconds to hear the squad chat with one another. I just wanted to share this in case that others were like me were looking for lore or character-building outside of cutscenes, talking with NPCs, or intel items. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Way too subtle storytelling in Halo 5. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 20:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of the comments about Halo 5's story either making large leaps or not explaining story I feel comes down to the fact that a lot of information is conveyed by implication that the player only starts to notice when they're replaying the game several times.

For instance, when Master Chief talks about Cortana on Meridian, it's the UNSC's response which causes him to question them. After his report, the UNSC officer tells him that another team is already being dispatched to the mission. The implication here is that they knew Cortana was on Meridian (in some form or another as they don't question his discovery), and that they've already chosen another team as the UNSC or ONI don't trust Blue Team, meaning that plan had been in the works for a while.

Likewise, when Halsey is finally back aboard the Infinity (although she doesn't seem to have much feelings towards the UNSC being responsible for the loss of her arm, nor does anyone seem interested in the other Janus key), her reference to her being in constant communication including what she said before taking her away from Osiris ("What has she done? How far has it already gone?") is a subtle implication that she's been talking about Cortana to the UNSC for some time.

The story is there, however, the big problem is that, unlike a book that can take time to analyze instantaneous thoughts of characters, these styles of custscenes can't offer up glimpses of what our protagonists are thinking or how their information immediately relates to the story without a really heavy-handed "story translator" character to either explain things or have things explained to.

While I didn't think Halo 5 was as well written as brilliantly as Halo 4 (although Brian Reed did a good job and has come a long way from Spartan Ops), I still think it's a good yarn that just takes one pass too many to really understand what's going on. 

Also, side-question out of curiosity. Did anyone happen to catch why Cortana was activating all of the Guardians immediately without giving much warning to the colonies?

Post-edit: I have no collected and listened to all of the game's audio logs, so the answers to some of my questions may be there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you recommend Dark Souls 2: SOTFS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 23:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone.

I completed Dark Souls a while back and I was thinking about picking up the new Dark Souls remastering for the new generation of games.

While I liked the first Dark Souls, I wasn't over the moon about it. For those who have played DS2, is it worth the purchase? If it's not better than the original game, I probably won't pick it up and while there are lots of reviewers out there who've analyzed this game, I tend to agree with a lot of opinions in this subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What video game world would you like to see a return to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 03:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing the fanfare and celebration of Oddworld: Abe's Odyssey being released free this week, I began to wonder which universe I would love to see a return to, personally.

For me, I would have to either go with the world of Crimson Skies: High Road to Revenge (a 'diesel-punk' setting where the U.S. fractured after WW1) or Jade Empire (a terrific mash-up of far Eastern cultures, lore, and traditions). Both are universes that have so much potential for storytelling and with great presentations.

What about you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There always seems to be a direct correlation between how incredible a piece of music is in games and it being apart of an unfun water level </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 15:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MGSV Spoilers]*Maybe spoiler-ish?* Question about the "Happy Birthday" song.[/MGSV Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 19:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone, I just checked out the cool little easter egg of the Mother Base crew celebrating Big Boss' birthday. I assume that the little song they sing was used in lieu of the most common birthday song (since those jack-holes at Warner/Chappell Music decided to trademark it, even though it was in the public domain). 

Has Konami trademarked that particular "Happy Birthday" song? It's the one time I've heard a 'replacement Happy Birthday song' that was actually just as simple and catchy as the original. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best Main Menu of All Time! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 16:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your Top 5 favorite video game stories off the top of your head? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 20:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are mine:

* Red Dead Redemption
* Spec Ops: The Line
* Halo 4
* The Wolf Among Us (Season 1)
* BioShock Infinite

Just a few, and I know there are PLENTY of great narratives out there.  What are yours? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is a PC-exclusive a Microsoft exclusive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 17:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, this is my question.  If a PC is running on a Microsoft operating system and if that game was also running on the Xbox One, wouldn't that make it a Microsoft exclusive?  

I understand there are ways to emulate a Mac or other operating system into running PC games, but I'm talking about games that were intended for a particular system and not through emulation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What popular game could you not get into? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 18:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, everyone.  I think we've all had that experience of a hugely popular game (either by 'hardcore' players, the public at large, or just generally well-respected and well-received) and just feeling like the game just never gels correctly with you.

Any particular video games that come to mind?

... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Doctor's happy day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 14:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teach me how to leave Gotham in Ashes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 12:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
