<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2746</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Explain Haas "machine parts" to me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 19:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gene Haas says he wants to use F1 to promote his machine parts business internationally. What, exactly, is a machine part? Parts for a machine, obviously. Examples? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 00:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 04:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too await F1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 01:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried. Though Fox is not any part of my Bing news sources, Cortana still presents me with those headlines. Hopefully she'll learn. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 21:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had my news preferences set through News app for awhile, but so far Cortana isn't paying attention to them. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I tell Cortana not to use Fox news as a source? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 14:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love checking my morning update and reading the news that Cortana provides, but how can I curate her sources?  Bing News allows that, and I'm hoping that Cortana will one day be able to do the same, if she can't already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Rosberg and Hamilton live in the same apartment building . . . awkward. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 18:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The FIA's titanium skid plates . . . </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 23:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 20:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. I'd like to see the money a team saves by processing 25 TF of data instead of 30. Can it be that substantial? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> F1 n00b's suggestion to the FIA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 04:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The FIA should be empowered to make decisions regarding only two things: (1) safety, and (2) scheduling.

If the fans and drivers want different power units, they should have whatever bloody power units they desire, regardless of the decibel level or environmental impact.  If the fans and drivers hate the idea of standing re-starts, then by god, the FIA should not consider standing re-starts.  

I'm fairly new to the sport, but it seems as if the FIA does a lot more tinkering (meddling?) with the regulations than the governing body of any other sport.  

So, FIA, outside of safety issues and the scheduling of events, if the fans, teams, and drivers don't like it, then don't do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 22:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where is the NBC Sports F1 studio located? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-22 21:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do Leigh Diffey and the guys provide commentary remotely, or does their studio set move from one race locale to the next?  I know that Will Buxton is physically on site at each race (I wish I had his job!), but where are the "play-by-play" commentators located during the race?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 18:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was paraphrasing Hemingway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 13:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Auto racing, mountain climbing, and bullfighting are sports. Everything else is a game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 05:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. I did not know any of this. Thanks for the info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House painters of Reddit: How do I use painter's tape effectively? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 07:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No matter how thoroughly I press down on that blue tape, my edges just aren't crisp when I remove it.  Any pro tips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why restrict time in wind tunnels? Why does the FIA care how many hours a team logs in testing their car in this manner? To keep costs down? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 05:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is Mike Mearls and how did he get in charge of D D? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 04:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I can see, Mearls had a few publishing credits during the d20 craze, but otherwise he seems to have come out of nowhere before being hired by WotC to help orchestrate 4E.  I don't exactly have my finger on the pulse of the game anymore, but I would have expected a bigger name to be the lead designer of D D Next, especially considering that 4E was the least successful of the editions.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 00:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try it, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 16:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This worked. Thanks for the tip; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I sign out of Maps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 04:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Here Drive and Maps apps have no way to sign out. I need to sign in as a different user to see me favorites. How do I do that in the app? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 23:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll give it a try!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Music app suddenly doesn't open. Stuck on "loading . . ." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 21:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done a soft reset, but the Music app has developed a weird new problem that I can't correct.  When I open it, it just says "Loading . . ." but it never loads.  The app doesn't allow me to uninstall it, so I can't fix it that way.  What's going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 17:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ["The Last of Us" theme](http://i.imgur.com/7q6nRVH) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did I explain "clean air" correctly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 01:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fairly new to F1, and when a friend asked what it meant to be "driving in clean air," I rattled off an explanation as to what I THINK it means.  In a nutshell:  On straightaways, downforce doesn't matter, and a car can benefit from drafting behind another car.  But on the corners, a car does not want to be behind other cars, because downforce means everything when cornering, and all that "stirred up" air plays havoc on those parts of the car designed to maximize downforce.

Is that more or less accurate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 01:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does a soft reset adjust the battery's charge from 38% to 100%?  The 38% was a false reading, and the reset corrected it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My phone's "The Last of Us" start screen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 22:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 18:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are HERE Maps favorites saved in the cloud? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 16:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I eventually move from my trusty Lumia 920 to the next big WP8.1 device, will I still have access to my favorites on HERE Drive after I log in to my Nokia account? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens to used tyres? Do the teams recycle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 14:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a lot of rubber, man.  Where do these poor tyres go, once they've nobly served their purpose? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 15:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the Glance feature work after 8.1? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 15:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Glance. I hope it doesn't go away after I update. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 17:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't know TableTop? Or Will Wheaton? And you're on Reddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 01:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why I found this so funny. Props! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a "spending limit" or "salary cap" in F1? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 02:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In American baseball, small-market teams like the Kansas City Royals (payroll $81 million) can rarely compete with wealthy teams like the Yankees (payroll $225 million).  Is the same generally true in F1?

Sorry for he n00b question; I'm still learning the sport. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 01:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I see.  Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 23:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you explain what you mean by the additional 60 million dollars? (Thanks; I'm still learning the sport.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 23:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like NBC is my new best friend.  Thanks to everyone for the help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a new fan from America, how do I get connected to the F1 community? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 22:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm becoming increasing enamored of Formula 1 racing, but the North American sports-news media (ESPN, etc.) doesn't offer much coverage of the sport.  Any tips on how I can watch the most races/events and otherwise stay informed?  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When playing "Thief," everything I encounter says "missing wrench." How in the Nine Hells do I get a bloody wrench? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 20:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 02:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, "victim mode" makes sense to me.

I guess I've always looked at the violence as so counter-productive to what they were trying to achieve . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Sochi terrorist threats. More generally, why do religious extremists resort to ultra-violent acts when their religious texts seem, overall, to advocate peace? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 01:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-25 15:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your "only" is misplaced in this sentence. It should not be modifying the word "popular." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A submarine showed up at my house in GTAV. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 01:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 20:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thing here. Ugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
