<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1499</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 09:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here for the laughs, little programming experience. What is recursion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 09:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm here for the laughs and prod is being mentioned quite often, what is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 09:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hasbrown what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 08:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this was /r/programmerhumor  light hearted and fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 04:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah so her lawyers failed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not meaning that dollars are meant as the only source of wealth. For me wealth comes from a variety of sources. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is something I forgot about.  But could that be written off in their taxes? Provided they kept receipts (I don't know if you need to keep them but I keep them for a while in case of an audit) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright will check it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if one earns 60k a year and has 5 kids what is their tax? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh so in the end she was executed not for high treason but simply  onconspired to murder? A charge that would apply to all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start with playing support, at worst your adc will hate you, and it's one of the more forgiving roles of the game, try not to die, ward, try not to die while warding, protect your adc, maybe roam mid if you have the champ t do it and bot is in good shape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow arguing on a technicality is when you know you are screwed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very prudent and pointed reply, the hell no response brought a smile to my lips </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's ironic about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still wealth, I am not going to mind being paid in dollars even if there is no backing behind it. (Other then the US government guaranteeing it will accept it for taxes.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure if they can navigate the tax code or somehow pay someone to navigate it for them, but if they are poor chances are they don't have the time to navigate it themselves, nor the money to pay others to do so. 

So theoretically they pay nothing but in reality they pay sticker price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Previous draw netted me 2 BSB and 2 supers, BSB for cloud and serioth (super-long katana dude) so I was happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 10:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's buggy but good enough quality to save this thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got so at the command level was where it was decided. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know how to post a picture but if some one would show me I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would kill to get rid of the ton of medica I have, I have 4 healer burst soul breaks that I know of: Aerith, Garnet, Lenna, (the one smitten with Ziddane) Ekko and only God knows how many other medica that are only super or unique. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4/11 4 super soul breaks
None I could care about (still super so I would say worth) I guess Irvine: Hyper Sniper was the best of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dam dingos, heard they can be brutal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were they happy to help? Or more like sorry it's my job? I heard part of the reason for gas chambers and such were the people who staffed the killing squads that would take people into rural areas and kill them, suffered from alcoholism and depression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dam 1.65% that's really high </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sad that communism the ideal was drastically different from communism the practice (it was just a dictatorship) people saw the ideal but were herded into a dictatorship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad as in body count?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot had been said rather vaguely could you post some sources or at least a wiki link to specific things you are talking about? Much appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With things such as Mcarthy and the scare, I think the USSR,s name was used as a tool to manipulate people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lenin opposed Stalin, but on the note of murderous revolutionaries, I think those that are labeled as revolutions tend to be bloody, of course there are exceptions. Lenin had a different course than the one Stalin had, so at the least it would have turned out differently.

Edit: minor grammar correction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valentine's Day was around before Al Capone, but I assume this is a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 10:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read that as Rammus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 10:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's a fake, it broke after the third swing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember equipping it on a lv 6 with a lv 89 doing all the work, I look away and apparently my lv 6 got confused and hit my lv 89... on the plus side during battle of the big bridge even the weapon was really really useful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ward first before doing the strat, also the TP disadvantage isn't that big unless you are trying something risky but why do risky things when ahead? (It's like chess you use one small advantage to keep your self ahead without doing any risky things, you only try risky things when behind) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like https://www.reddit.com/r/HistoryAnecdotes/
And beware often Ancedotes are trumped up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it costs gold and you need to buy it from a shop... which can be far depending where you are (mid lane, south jung, and north Jung) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you don't really get hurt by the strat, as any CS you miss is made up by the jungle monster xp. It's actually a good thing to do bc you get a buff and you hurt the enemy jungler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will learn our peaceful ways, *by force*

https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=0Ig2qZEiNv8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 10:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a thing for whatever odd reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 10:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey we now have satellites, GPS, better solar panels, material engineering, programming, and so much more, all these "little" things that were needed to get you out in space and thus were developed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 10:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For awhile the ancient civilization of Hittites were thought to be mere fantasies but then evidence was uncovered, and then more, and now it's for sure a civilization  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 10:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not know this it's pretty wow, I knew the link with lead, intelligence, and violence but it never hit me to think about leaded gas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 09:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was the soft cap always so low... crap all this time I was gunning for 480 or so attack with shout </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 09:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope they coded that one to register as if you got the chest even if you didn't. Gotta thank the DEVs for the hind sight, other wise it would be a shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 09:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aye </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 08:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pickpockets, muggers, people dashing into your house taking something and dashing out (weirdest thing ever) and the occasional misplaced wallet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 08:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be a great gift  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 08:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any *truly* self-learning software that can go from zero experience with how to train a dog to play dead to becoming a guru on it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 09:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder how much power that would require  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With bard e it's 100% reproducible on the walls at mid that lead into the river, you will float up pretty high and back down, it's not a major thing though bc is issuing a move command sends you immediately back to the ground.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would go in as an engineer, if no one spawned I would hijack it, if some one spawned shoot the cockpit, if I failed use a rocket launcher to blow it up.

Fun fact my first 3 kills in a jet in BF3 were roadkills due to me failing on learning how to fly it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 11:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BF3 is notorious in my play throughs for enemies riding jets/helicopters to the enemy base and destroying the enemy aircraft on spawn until they can steal it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 11:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That really perked my interest, that and cutting down trees to make a path, and the shieldboarding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 05:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For banks they need to update for security reasons no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 05:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard that the online community is very nice. How hard is it to climb ranks? How much is the fee? And how does the actual battles compare to monster hunter MP? Or is it closer to turn based XII? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FCC didn't get gutted yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember googling Comcast customer service once would bring up images of Nazi swastikas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the pros, cons, and compare it to monster hunter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> X, it's fairly linear so you can't mess up too bad; if you want open world go with XII, you can go to so many places and the story of each place is pretty interesting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 11:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We cleared the asbestos ourselves for the home we live in, didn't follow all safety procedures but close enough. If you have the time, and I mean a good deal of time, it's not too difficult to clear it yourself and lay a new ceiling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 11:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 10:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welp I now want to know (also just starting out) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 10:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other guy just flew </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly thought mid-sized was 100k vs 120k or so battles but that's bc I play on modded super galaxies that are like 10 times bigger the default option. (I don't really play late game, just que a bunch of things and go eat) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They live off energy, so they squeeze a planet dry of all forms of energy. Chemical energy too I assume, so humans are fair game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you lead them to your enemies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dam same model as mine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First 2 min I thought so as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 08:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who downvoted you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 08:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's giving me "page not found" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 07:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's kinda of "I fixed it, but if it breaks again not my problem" (I have 0 expirance with JavaScript.)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 07:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed this thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 07:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also a bit lost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 07:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was such a word really used? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 07:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dam it you triggered the auto-mod </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 07:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is mentioned in various other texts, so he did exist historically but just as Jesus lived historically it's the what they did with their lives and their meaning that is in doubt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 07:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weren't there more than one Judahs in the Bible? Mayhaps something to do with the historical kingdom of Judah? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just this BSB and now only if I could get shout... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without his burst is hopeless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stupid and funny stuff you do in FFRK... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 11:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you ever do some things that make you feel stupid? Like bring a fire focused team with chain firaga and the like vs ifrit? I had just made a mage team vs Dark Bahmit with everything working out until Dark Bahmit self-castes reflect and I realized that I don't have a dispel, despite the battle description saying he casts reflect. I had to laugh at my self for that one. Any one else has such stupid funny moments to share? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just as I was about to go for a 11 pull on the lucky draw... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 09:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... servers undergo maintance. And I was grinding and refilling stamina all day and then for a hour+ final stretch. Got 50 mirthyl, already in the relic draw screen... boom maintance notice.

Maybe it's a sign that I shouldn't pull, my last 6 or so pulls were trash 1/11 pulls. Think I should pull for the lucky draw (I lack good mage BSB), go for the tactics (I don't have shout and have shit tactics synergy), or save?

Edit: thanks for the advice, I will save for later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How and why does one lose their appetite? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 11:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RAGE DAM THIS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 03:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please help with torment boss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 10:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried many things, lv 75+ mage team, 4 white mages and Titus with his BSB (because I have a shit ton of medica relics but not much else), 2 white mages and 3 lv 85-99 fighters, I just can't beat it. I have enough grouth eggs to take 2 characters from lv1 to lv 99, and the spread crystals to break level caps, just tell me how to beat this thing!
The water fish one (gusinio?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terra OSB good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 09:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have terra OSB but I only use her vs bosses weak vs fire, and in my mage A-team. Is she good enough to justify boosting her to lv 99 and using her more? I currently value Ex-Death with the SSB that gives M-blink and grand cross as better than her outside of fire vs Ice fights.

 Also what is a better RW Aerith White Materia or Terra OSB?

Edit: thanks for all the advice and comments guys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lenna Phoenix of tycoon vs Aeroth White materia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is better to use as a sole white mage, lenna and Phoenix of tycoon or Aerith white materia? Specifically which is better in multiplayer raid. 

Bonus points for telling me which is better for me to use as my RW.

Edit: corrected Aeroth to Aerith </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help with when to enslave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 08:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>    I tried to make slaves a while back and failed, so I gave up instead doing things like purging and etc. but now I want to enslave but no idea when is it a good idea, and how to maintain slavery without rebellion and etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't find ultimate mega thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 10:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can my beat that dam ultima weapon, can someone toss me a link to the mega thread? I couldn't find it.

That or tell me what you did to beat it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wall first and then Cast shell? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 09:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard if you cast wall and shell in the wrong order one cancels the other. What is the right order Bc I am just trying to squeeze a win on the ultimate weapon losing with 7% hp remaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a romantic tragedy book with preferably some comedy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 07:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My little sister came to me for book advice and I failed miserably blindsided by thinking she would like what I like. 

She read and liked the divergent series, hunger games, and fault in our stars. Thank you for any and all advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help picking for an A team... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 05:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What champs dot you use for your A team? I used to just choose whatever character I had a soul break, but now I have a good amount of soul break equipment and while it's quite lacking (for example nothing for terra) it's more or less a good amount.

That brings me now to choose based on stats and etc. But I have little knowledge in this area and was hoping for 2-3 A team examples 

Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> About to read LotR, do I need to read the hobbit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 10:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was gifted all of the Lord of the Rings books, I plan to read them, but should I read The Hobbit before hand?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> why the hell can I not colonize a system yet the AI can!? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 05:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     Pretty much I messing around in one game where I all but won, had a fleet power of 200k and my tech was equivalent compared to the awakened fallen empire next door (I don't even own the leviathan DLC!) so I decided to terraform an entire system into juicy Gaia worlds and when they were all terraformed AI rebellion occurred. No big deal, I crushed it but the AI rebellion borders extended over my Gaia worlds and while I was fighting a vassal colonized it! So I loaded an earlier save and I rushed colony ships to take it first but the game wouldn't let me, due to the system being in another empires borders... However I watched my vassal colonize it moments later thinking wtf? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federations are OP due to a bug? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 08:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was RPing as the Dune Space Guild where I only would play with 1 planet, to make up for the pitiful excuse of a fleet I made a Federation. Federations get a separate fleet cap and when you are president of a federation you control the fleet and can add more ships. 

I just spammed built a bunch of ships for the federation until L I ran out of minerals, when I started it was at 28/56 fleet cap. Once all the ships were built it was at... 283/60 fleet. The game doesn't allow you to add ships to the Federation fleet if you are at the fleet cap, but it looks like if you que the order for the ships before you go above the fleet cap, the ships will still be produced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Playing on the highest graphics... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 05:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play on the highest graphics possible because of a beefy gaming PC, but late game I get like everyone else annoying freeze that last usually 2-10 sec, and sometimes during auto save as much as 1 min. If I lower my settings would it eliminate or at least reduce these "freezes"?

Edit: thanks for all the advice, now I somewhat know what the problem is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ranked is down? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 05:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Books with Chem, math, or engineering </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 00:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fiction or non-fiction just must play a major role in the book. An example of a fiction book would be The Periodic Table by Primo Levi (a story of how a holocoust surviver lived through the holocoust via his skills with chemistry) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sectors suck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much after conquering most of the Galaxy without using sectors, I conquered and subdued a 4 planet ring world and made him cede all his planets, I did not want to bother managing these planets as since I was running individualist ethic I couldn't just purge them all, I wanted nothin other than the space ports so I made my first sector to manage these 4 planets, big mistake. After a few months while I'm in another war with a FE and 3 inferior empires, I get a notification that all 4 ring world planets are rebelling against me no big thing, I get rebellions every 5 min form my other planets but I station armies to deal with it, but the rebels on these planets were gene warriors... And all 4 succeed, with a 22-23k fleet each, my entire navy combined is 70-80k, and I am already in a war with around 50k total as my enemy... Why can't the sector manage 4 planets properly after I left it a ton of credits and minerals to develop military? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
