<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3097</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What could that be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol he still uses it with CoA for low/medium level opponents  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but he also needed 1.5 years to master gear 4. Also, I think Tankman vs Cracker was kinda like old Luffy all over again lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you also have to factor in that he currently battling much more experienced people that himself, you can't expect him to be holding back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How could he do that without a timeskip ? (Honest question, no sarcasm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think there's going to be a gear 5 at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that for Luffy to do that, he'd need at least  another timeskip. We se Zoro training basically every moment he's awake and I believe he's nowhere near Garp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Luffy's next power up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everybody, what do you guys think is Luffy's next power up is going to be
1) A new G4 form

2) G5

3) Awakening 

4) Other

If you can, could you also explain what this new power would work?

Edit: thanks everyone for the replies! 

Seems like a lot of people's sentiment is MG2GA (Make Gear 2 Great Again) but I don't think that would be possible. 

We have to factor in that Luffy is currently punching above his weight by meddling with the Yonko who are both stronger and more experienced than him, so a huge power spike is honestly to be expected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robin loosing her battle to her parasitic breasts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
