<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3191</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Brittish withdrawal from the EU is like a guy breaking up with his girlfriend and telling her you still want a friends with benefits arrangement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 17:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the Queen of England a welfare mom? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 17:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why didn't the Canadians join the American revolution? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 17:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why was the Canada experience so different? Did they have local governments with elected leaders? Did the Brittish raise taxes on them as well to cover the costs of the Seven Years War? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The chaos in UK would be a good time for Argentina to take Falklands again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 11:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does it really hurt Flowers development if he moves to LT for a year and the Giants bring in Eugene Monroe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 22:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand you are usually facing the better pass rushing on the blind side, but is the technique any different ? Are there different schemes and things?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is the prime minister elected and elections work in the UK? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 21:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think Sam learns in Old Towne? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 07:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EVERYTHING] How will Dany find out who you know who is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 04:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That whisper reveal was stupid....

Jon will get lit on fire some how and not get hurt. The dragons will acknowledge him as the blood of the dragon. I expect to see Jon riding a dragon too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would Brittish voters be swayed if the Queen took a stance on issues? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 19:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Common Historical Inaccuracies in Fantasy Books </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 18:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most fantasy takes place in a western medievil world, but you are welcome to discuss fantasy that takes place in other settings. If you do please list the series since these are less common. Also please list whether this is common in 'TV/Movies' or books. 

Fantasy in general:
1. Too Rich: This bugged me about Wheel of Time. Gold isn't money. The white tower was too wealthy. They did not have a big area to draw taxes from. They didn't do anything to earn money and get paid. Set up health clinics? Help farmers grow crops? Help build stuff? Don't give me the 'they accrued wealth over centuries' they spent it too and currency isn't money. It just leads to inflation.

Most people in general is too healthy and too wealthy. 

2. Lack of Disease: Yeah. People didn't bath much. No antibiotics. They just basically ignore this. Plagues were alot more common in the ancient world. 

3. Food for Armies: The armies are too big and can't be fed. How the hell do the Orcs in Lord of the Rings eat? Same with Trollocs? They are huge and likely require alot of calories. 

4. Not enough farmers: In the ancient world I think 90% of the people were involved in growing and producing food. There are a few books where they use magic to improve crop yields, etc.. but they don't talk about it much. 

5. Game of Thrones one: No way you can keep food from spoiling for a 5 year winter. What about trees? if you have a long winter with nothing growing you would cut down a massive number. Sapplings won't grow back that fast? I think plants and animals in a westeros with evolution would be very different. How do boars live through a 5 year winter? What about building repairs? Buildings take alot more damage in the winter. A large part of many summers is repairing them. Who repairs in a 5 year winter?
 

TV/Movies: 
Alot of these I got from Youtube channels The Metatron and Lindyeige

Comstumes
1. Fake Leather Armor: This cheap garbage wouldn't stop anything. 
2. Leather Armband: Makes guys look tough. Useless
3. Backscabbards: Arm isn't long enough to get the sword out and how do you get the thing back in? 
4. Metal Sound when drawing swords: This would mean the scabard is metal and if you used it you would ruin the edge. It actually sounds more like moving furniture on carpets. 
5. Great Helms + Late Medievil Armor: Full plate was not developed until 1420. The Great Helms were 400 years obsolete and used by Crusaders. You can't open in the front and its hard to 
breath in them. 1400s helmets do NOT look as cool. They have beaks in the front. This is so you have more room for your breath. This was likely a big advance, but is rarely talked about. 
6. Chain Coifs: You hit someone upside the head with a lump of iron like a sword you will crack their skill open. They had padding under the coifs. This would not look cool. 
7. Full armor and no helmet: Cause they want you to know who the hero is. Head is the most vulnerable part of your body. 

Environment:
1. Torches: Day time torches? Why? Too many inside. Who lights new ones every 30 minutes? Only modern technology allows torches without alot of smoke. You would die from smoke. Plus you would 
lose night blindness outside. 
2. Dirt Road with 2 dirt lanes: Modern road. If you had a horse pulling a cart, the whole road would be dirt. 

Combat:
1. Arrows are too effective: Yeah they didn't work like artillery like we see in Lord of the Rings. If archers were that effective, why do they have anything else? 

2. Fire Arrows: Arrow would make the arrows go out and the type of arrows needed to light would not be armor piercing. 

3. Archers are not Strong enough: Archers were actually ripped. Warbows require a ton of strength and stamina to pull. They may have been physically stronger than melee soldiers

4. Cavalry Stops: Advantage of cavalry is you move fast and you get to run people down and stomp on them with a horse. Once you stop you are less mobile and people can kill your horse. 

If cavalry stops in the middle of foot soldiers they would get slaughted. Everyone would hit the horse to know them down and then kill them. 

5. Everyone Breaks up: Formation and order defeats armors that break up. When the Romans fought like they did at the beginning of Gladiator they got slaughtered. Their fighting style was designed
to work in an ordered fashion. Gladius is not a slashing weapon and has limited reach. It was a stabbing weapon and most effective in large organized battles. 

6. Water: Don't people get thirsty? There had to be people passing waterskins up through the ranks. You would get incredibly thirsty. 


Late edition: too many people are literate. If you are a scratch farmer or a blacksmith you likely wont be able to read. Paper was rare back then too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How about a Stickied post with links to authors who post here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 18:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author Name, link to u/author link to web page. 

I think authors would like this and fans as well. There will be alot of the 'self promotion' authors who post links to a book no one has read. However, I think people will be able to find authors they like. Authors take time out of their day to post on here and often make good contributions to this forum. Authors can just add a reply to their info with links. Periodically a moderator can come in and just add them to the top post. Delete any other posts other than from authors. Limit authors to 1 post each, UNLESS they change their user or website link etc. Its not a self promotion post. If an author makes repeated self promotion posts in the thread take him out of the list at the top. This shouldn't happen too often. 

What do people think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would happen if the Queen vetoed the Brexit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 03:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the American Revolution(AMEXit) happened today how would it affect global markets and would American Express sponsor it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 03:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions from an American about Scottish independence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 18:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is non political. I just dont know how this works. Not looking for a political argument. If my questions are silly, please understand, we dont get alot of details over here.

On an ipad so please excuse typos. You get a very small screen. 

1. Didnt Scotland merge with England in the early 1600s when the Queen of England named the King of Scotland her heir? What mechanism allows for separation? Is this a new rule? 

2. If #1 is true, why has there been so little moving around in the UK to the point that Scotland has such a separate identity. In the US people move alot. I have lived in 6 states. There is some identifying by region , but far, far less. The UK is much smaller. I am surprised that there hant been more movement. This movement would decrease Scotland identity. So my assumption people tend to stay closer to home. I went to college 250 miles north, then afyer graduation moved 1000 miles away. This is not uncommon. If I look up people I went to high school with virtually everyone has moved far away and I didnt grow up in a poor area you instictively want to leave.

3. How do you expect to split up the UK national debt? I dont think the rest of the UK will take it all on.

4. From what I read more tax dollars flow into Scotland than out. Is this true? If so how do you plan to make up for it? What are the major issues?

5. Why do Scotts who want to leave, want to leave? Is it more political? South is more conservative? Conservatives in Brittain dont seem to be all that conservative to an American. 

6. Why is the EU more important to you than Southern UK? I am not clear on the issues that lead UK to leave the EU. I dont know alot about the immigration issue which seemed to be the big one. 

7. Wouldnt it cost alot of money to break up? you need to fund a military, lots of governing bodies, etc...

8. If Scotland leaves will you also kick the Queen to the curb?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What time do the Brexit polls close and when will the vote be tabulated? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 22:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could found a religion what would it be and what would you worship? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 04:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your opinion about Smart guns? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 01:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> would you be concerned if you were issued a gu that only you could fire?

What is your opninion about these to regular citizens. The NRA hates them. My opinion is that if they are stolen it would be alot harder for criminals to use them?



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else not realize that you can be prosecuted for not turning someone in who planned a murder like Orlando shooters wife? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 18:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Is the crime in Florida that the Orlando club shooter is being unvestigated fir violating a good Samaritan law? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 02:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the difference between a CB and a Free Safety in the modern NFL? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 18:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talking about roles. I think safeties tend to be larger. FS is primarily responsible for coverage right? I know the jobs overlap. I also think there is a difference depending on whether its more of a cover 2 zone or a man cover defense as well.

In theory shouldnt a corner and FS be able to move back and forth? I would think more so in zone. 

This is strictly a technical question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fortune 100 company just eliminated paid time off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 03:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do people want to be moderators on reddit or any other online location when it is not paid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 03:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ait Force loses 100,000 inspector general reports in database crash because they don't believe in backups </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 01:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do gorillas perceive eye contact as threatening? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 03:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Donald Trump have a hotwife fetish? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 18:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:if the US Olympic committee is a private organization, how did Jimmy Carter have the power to boycott the 1980 Olympics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 07:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have tried to google this and I cannot find out why the Zolympic Committee didnt just ignore him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Odds that Winds of Winter will be out before Game of Thrones Season 7? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 04:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That will be 6 years since the last book. Same time it took for Dance with Dragons. If it isnt, I dont think it will ever get written. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why did it take until the Renaissance for truly life like paintings when lifelike statues date to antiquity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 19:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know its related to second and third point perspective. Why did it take so long to develop? Arent there artists out there that have natural talent and can draw a lifelike face without eing taught? How come we disnt see that before the Renaissance and yet saw really detailed and lifelike statues? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think Donald Trump is a psychopath? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 06:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which currently living individuals would the world be better off if they were dead? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 20:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I troll Washington Redskin fans by calling them racists because I am from Brooklyn and I dont tell them I am a life long New York Giants fan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 16:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This Redskins are racist bullshit is troll gold. I live in the DC area and I roleplay as an SJW, just to get Redskin fans into a flaming rage. I also call them mysogynists for having cheerleaders. The Giants have never had cheerleaders. They get so whiny and pissy about. Red faced. Cry like bitches. God dam this is fucking fun. 

Everyone should try it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Secret Trump University Training Video LEAKED!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 16:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How come the fraud case aginst Trump University is civil and not criminal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 00:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are really good, but not well known youtube channels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 05:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: what is so much better about Monsanto genetically engineered seeds that farmers are willing to rent seeds? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 01:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The more conservative Donald Trumps VP pick, the more likely conservatives will impeach himand remove him from office if he wins. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 04:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla Works Workers on Visas and pays them less than minimum wage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 20:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kitten Scientist Issue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 00:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain how triggers work? I see 0 to 1. 

Trading has all of sudden stopped working with my current reset. I am using tampermonkey in chrome. I can't trade with anyone. I am trying to trade with Zebras/Dragons which are all seasons and the trades never fire. I have the resources necessary because I can manually trade. 

I have tried playing with the trigger to see if that fixes it. Everyone else works. I have refreshed. Closed opened Chrome, Enabled disabled Kitten Scientist. Enabled/Disabled trading. Tried trades with others. Trading worked just fine until 2 days ago. I dont know what happened.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Game Layout change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 18:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Please have all resources that gain and lose resource (such as coins gained from banks and used by scientists) show how much they are gaining and losing plus the %. You will probably need to move them under the resources that use storage.

2. Please put the resources that are not in storage in alphabetical order or some way that makes it easier to find what I need. 

3. Please have the numbers uses commas and an option for scientific notation. Its going to be a while until I need scientific notation, but even at 1m+ of something, its hard to read without commas. 

thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about autokrafting and workshop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 18:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Autocrafting is when buildings such as banks crafting gold into coins operates? 

I saw a post in chat from Morpheox that says these buildings always take into account the 'multicraft rate'. This is the craft efficiency we get above work bench labelled items crafted right? 

So does this mean that if we also have 1 workshop with +10% autocraft our craft rate is

ItemsCrafted*(1+Autocraft bonus from workshop) * the crafting rate of the building? 

Request for Morpheox: Could you have items like 'coins' that have autocraft on it say how much they are gaining or losing from scientists like you do for the capped items? The screen layout would need to change and they would probably need to move under the items that have storage limits, but its easier to follow. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How old does a grave have to be for it to be considered archeology to dig it up instead of grave robbing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 08:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please Reduce Sailor Requirement for trades </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 18:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trading with Ships has limited use. There is a timer and you have to buy supplies which use planks. Its completely useless when you have a large fleet. IT doesn't make sense to leave a large number of Population basically 'idle' as Sailors. We should only need enough sailors to do trades for the supplies we are carrying.

If I am trading 2500 Copper for a few hundred tin. I shouldnt need Sailors for my entire 12 Ship Fleet. There is a cost of 5 Coins every time you add a sailor. So there is a cost built into move them back and forth. I can make the same trade when I have 2 Galleys. Why do I need more sailors with 12? I should only need all the sailors for fights since all ships are sent. 

If you need this many sailors than trading is useless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enhancement requests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 22:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a few.

1. Itsaguess has performance issues: Could be related to how many buildings, resources, toggles are on. This can be improved by having an option with a timer. So you can opt to have this stuff calcualte say every 5-10 seconds. Easiest way to implement this is with a sleep function. So give an option that can have the loops sleep for 5-10 seconds. Then just multiple the resource gain by the time the code slept. 

2. Loops: Not a javascript coder... but if resources and toggle buildings run from multiple loops in the code, this can lead to more resources being used. If its possible to refactor to 1 driver loop with a case statement that calls other functions. That could reduce CPU load. 

3. Heirlooms, diamonds, and any military drops. This shoudl be impacted by attack/power, HP like regular rewards are. Random factor added in is a good idea. 

4. Stats Tab: One that says how many total Legacy you earned is a good one. Lets people compare where they are in chat. Easier to talk. When I hear someone saying I'm at this tech. Whether its worth me going for it depends on how much legacy I have compared to them. 

Some ideas for Stats:
-- current reset length
-- total play time
-- avg reset/max reset time
-- total Legacy
-- max legacy in a reset, avg legacy

5. Achievements: This is more for fun. Doesn't have to add bonuses if you think that would be overpowering. Could add some points with it to compare. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for good Fantasy/History related Youtube channels? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 18:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know about a few of them. I am wondering if anyone knows anymore. I am open to a wide variety. The best way to describe what I am  looking for is by listing sites that I like. I am looking for book reviews, etc... More educational channels. I am rather addicted to youtube education channels.

I am also interested in channels that focus on elements in fantasy and historical books/TV Shows that are or are not realistic. The channels below have some videos on that. 

I am open to a wide variety. So please post channels you like. 

Linedybeige
I am Shad
Metratron
Knyght Errant
ScholarGladiator (good info, but presentation is a little dry). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where is the kittens game save file? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 21:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to set up an autobackup of the save file. I dont want to rely on manually exporting. I looked in the Chrome cookies directory, but its not there. I am on windows 8. Cookies directory is the same on windows 7/8.

I did a search for 'kittens' at the google level directory. Nothing. 

C:\Users\your_username\AppData\Local\Google\Chrome\User Data\Default\ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where does the game save when we press the save file? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 18:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am using chrome. I looked in my chrome cookie directory, but I cannot find a file with 'keepcraft' or some derivative in the name. I have google drive and I want to get our save file added to an auto-backup so I Can restore if anything happens. I am on windows 8.1, but the Cookies go to the smse directory in windows 7 and 8. 

I tried searching for it at the top level google directory and its not there. 

C:\Users\your_username\AppData\Local\Google\Chrome\User Data\Default\

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attack Power on Expeditions affect on rewards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 19:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know the formula? There was some discussion in the chat. For example it looks like hierloom drops and diamond drops are strictly based on % chance per expedition. So maximize expeditions to get more rewards. 

Really looking for a few things
1. formula for how rewards are calculated on fights
2. formula for how strong enemies are (I know there is a random function to add variance). 

Trying to do the following:
1. calculate optimum strategy for rewards. So roughly how many diamonds./heirlooms per hour, rewards for fights and non-fights depending, how many farmers I need to support this to balance it out. 
2. Help decide where to allocate tech. Since military tech increases attack power. Might be a good idea to stop allocating after a while and focus on others depending on where I am in the game. 

I think we can spreadsheet this.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fantasy Tropes that are meant to bring realizing, but never actually happened </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 06:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just saw some videos on Lindybeige about torches. I thought this was really interesting. 

I am not talking about any fantasy tropes. Just tropes in fantasy that authors add to make you think its a setting in the real time period they are referencing, but is just made up BS. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MPaj8lR786s
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HQZqbGME5HY
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LMhMrnWslQs

Here is one about dungeon ceilings. This is something from RPGs. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pKJAWDVx5_Q

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens if a bound delegate at the Republican/Democratic convention violates the rules and does not vote for required choose on the first ballot or does not show up for the ballot ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 01:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reporting in the press has been inconsistent on this. I saw some reporters saying this is 'illegal'. I don't think laws govern conventions. I think its against the rules. So what happens if a Trump/Clinton delegate votes for Cruz/Sanders on the first ballot and violates the rules? Do they just throw the vote out and kick the delegate out? 

Is the 'majority rules' on the first ballot based on a majority of delegates that vote or a majority of all delegates? What happens if enough delegates choose not to show up for the first ballot and there are not enough delegates left to give Clinton/Trump a majority?

This is not going to happen. I am just trying to understand the rules better? I am not looking for a political argument here. I am just trying to understand the rules. I have googled it, but I can't find 'consequences on delegates for violating rules or not showing up'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What would happen if a bound delegate at the Democratic/Republican conventions violate the rules and vote for someone they are not supposed to on the first ballot or simply don't show up for the first ballot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 01:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are marketers affected by any bonuses? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 21:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see marketers raise glass, etc... do they get any bonuses? Someone in chat said you get some kind of craft bonus with marketers. Can someone explain? They are very expensive. I want to see if they are worth it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> any reason to build more than one ziggurat or megalith? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 00:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont see anything in the wiki about benefits of building more?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> help understanding metaphysics price ratios? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 19:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So per other threads this reduces the costs of buildings. I see 1% for the first one, etc... how does that work? How much does 1% help?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Medic heal formula? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 18:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I added a medic. It heals less than 10 HP per round. That is worthless. What is the formula for much a medic heals?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about craft efficiency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 00:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My craft efficiency is 8%. I have 13 Workbenches
13*.08=1.04 which explains my 2.05 crafts

In leaders I added a level to Elisia which added 5% craft efficiency. 
That got me to a whopping 2.1 crafts. 

It doesn't look like it actually adds to craft efficiency. Instead it just adds 5% to your total. This is misleadng. 

IS this the same effect with the mastery legacy? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Efficient way to progress after resetting a few times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 17:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paragon: 164
Karma: 21

So I have hit declining returns. It looks like accumulating Apocrypha for resets should be my next goal and I should go longer on a reset. However, aquiring faith is very slow even if i use most of my kittens in faith and I build up my Chapels.

What do people usually do at this point?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is on the roster at Tackle and Guard? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 20:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know about the 3 starters we held over from last year. Newhouse was probably the worst tackle in the league last year. What do they have on the roster? The odds of getting someone you would want to start next season this late in the draft is unlikely. What do they have on the roster? Hopefully its people healthy...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enhancement Request: Track Wins/Losses Rewards expeditions please? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 19:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its really tedious to try to figure out what to raise HP or Attack and whether its worth adding more of a certain type of units to offset with Farmers. I dont think many people want this to be a monster spreadsheet game where we have to keep typing stuff in. Can we track the following:

1. when we hover over expedition, tell us how much food production we need to attack as soon as Morale hits the mark necessary to attack. I end up having to punch it into a calculator to check to see if its high enough and if i want to adjust farmers. Its a pain. 

2. can you track a log of rewards from expeditions? Such as rewards per fight, rewards per hour and the history of it? This way its easier to measure what we want to do with our troops?

3. Can you track wins/losses as well?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Factories strike me as ridiculously expensive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 18:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What am I missing? You get a 6% craft bonus with a workshop upgrade. That is the same as you get for a workshop? When you open them up they are FAR more expensive than continuing to upgrade your workshop? I have reset 2 before so this is the first time I am moving beyond concrete huts to check out some more stuff in the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enhancement Request: Please show us how long until we have resources to build something like in kittens game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 21:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Kittens game when you hover over something you want to build it shows you how long it will take until you are able to build it. This is a nice convenience thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enhancement Request: Ability to set how much of Shipyards, Foundry, Kiln, etc... to use </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 19:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a feature from Kittens game. Buildings like Smelters, etc... you have a plus/minus sign next to them. You may have 10 levels in them, but may only want to use 5 at that time because the number of resources they require are too high.

With Shipyard since it uses 40 wood/sec I may want to raise it a level, but can't afford to keep it on at all times at that l evel. I may have to switch around workers. Also, i may want to raise it to exclusive use it with 'rush economy' then set it to lower when letting the game run. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wayward Roguelike new early access game to review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 06:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The developers have an interesting approach. You can play the game for free on their website... if you like it you can buy the 2.0 version. I have played it for free for years. I think this is a game people will end up liking. It just went up for sale in early access. Its an old school survival roguelike. Its hard. I have played it a while and still suck at it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game with kittens scientist crashes periodically in chrome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 17:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It goes to an 'awe snap' page. Is there a way to turn on logging in chrome to see if its kitten scientist or something else? 

Also, can someone give me a command i can run from tampermonkey to automatically enable kitten scientist? I can turn on an auto-reload periodically, but kitten scientist always comes up disabled when the page reloads. This is likely the easiest fix.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> how do you create a village? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 23:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not covered in the tutorial. I read the faq. It points to the tutorial. I am guessing you need to buy a certain number of legislators. I have bought 10. Can someone tell me what you do with legislators and how to get a village? Its not covered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the ideal army mix to maximize rewards to attack frequency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 18:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I go all pikeman I get enough morale to attack every 25 seconds. If I add swordsman and knights I attack less, but more attack so bigger rewards. Anyone work out the ideal ratios to maximize rewards/second?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bug Report: Buildings showing up red </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 18:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was a stealth release. At first buildings and techs would show up with red text if your warehouse was not big enough to store resources. This is a nice feature. Now they are red if you dont have enough resources currently. This isnt any differnet than when tehy were grey if you didnt have enough resources currently. 

Please change this to
Greyed out if you dont have enough resources
Red if your storage isnt big enough to stockpile enough resources to build it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some questions about the game mechanics from someone who read the wiki </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 18:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have not reset. I played last year and reset once, but then lost my save. I am playing again. Instead of writing lots of posts and causing a mess, I'm going to post questions here. Ill probably edit the top post with dates in case I have new ones. I have read the wiki. I am using kitten scientist. 

Trade Ships: I wiki states how much they help with getting titanium in trades zebras. They also increase your storage capacity. Do they help in other ways with trade or anything else? I saw some references (I cant find the link) about how trade ships help with trade success. Was it only referring to titanium or other parts of trades?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are updates to the game in bitbucket recently but not release? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 19:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see quite a few commits in March and April of this year, but the last release was 9 months ago. Anyone know what is going on? I see a variety of people adding fixes. Are people just pulling the code and running it on their PCs? 

https://bitbucket.org/bloodrizer/kitten-game/commits/all

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help understanding when to use mints from wiki </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 18:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://bloodrizer.ru/games/kittens/wiki/index.php?page=Buildings redirect=no

I dont understand what the catpower cap has to do with mint effectiveness. Mints reduce the amount of catpower/second which reduces how often you can hunt. I dont understand what the 'catpower cap' which I take to mean the total amount of catpower you can store has to do with this?

Also the wiki mentions cap for ivory in the field next to this. This looks incomplete. What was the wiki trying to say?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please add a way to respec legacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 17:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am ok if it costs legacy to do so. I did not read the wiki carefully when I did my first prestige. The first two legacy branches i picked were Motivation and Depot. Now that I look at the game, depot is likely one of the last branches I would want to pick. Making a mistake like this early really slows down my game, due to how expensive makes other branches. 

We should lose legacy for respeccing, legacy, but it needs to be available. It takes time to learn the game and the mechanism for increasing cost isn't clear on the game page.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When to prestige? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 18:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prestiged the first time when I had 70 legacy points. Got me about a 10% boost to production. Not a whole lot. The game doesn't tell you how much legacy you get when you prestige. Is there a good number of legacy points? I see some people below wait a month to prestige. That seems like a while. I was able to get up to have the option to prestige in about 8-10 hours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What mods work with the latest version? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 16:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went here and downloaded some utility  mods. All but one did not work.  got LUA errors when I started the game. I googled that and it said that its not compatible with .12.9 and up. I filted by mods in .11 and .12. How do I find mods that are compatible with the latest version?

http://www.factoriomods.com/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> how does the kitten scientist trigger mechanic work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 23:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not sure what the values between 0 and 1 actually mean? I lowered my build trigger to .01. My expectation was that it would trigger to build immmediately, but it never built. Can someone help me understand this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> kitten extrapolation not working for me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 16:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played last year. My save game is gone so I started over. I am using both kitten scientist and kitten extrapolation in chrome. tampermonkey shows both kitten extrapolation and kitten scientist running. I have refreshed the page.

The chart about food usage does not show up. I used kitten extrapolation last year and it worked. I dont know what is going on. Tampermonkey is showing its active. I have refreshed. I have run through several years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> cant build town center </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 13:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 20 blocks, 5 structures, and 3 coins. the game shows me meeting all requirements, but the town structure is still greyed out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feature Request: Limit animations to improve performance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 20:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am using Chrome. It usually has the best performance. When I get to insane with skip 50 on after 150-200 Waves, I start having performance issues with the game stuttering. 

The same thing happens with a similiar Kongregate Game called Undying Spider. In that game there is an option to 'condense' the animations. I think this game needs the same option. There is just too much going on on the screen. We dont need to see it all. 

Can we get an option to limit the number of blocks displayed on screen? And limit other animations?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about darkness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 22:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This seems to be the only thing that matters against really tough bosses since they have so much HP, your 'damage' doesn't matter. This reduces damage by a percentage. 

1. Do the bonus elemental damage skills such as bonus damage to universal work with darkness? Not sure since Darkness isn't called 'damage' its a 'reduce'. So 25% extra on that. do you reduce by 25% more?

2. Does Impetus increase the amount of HP reduction from Darkness or is it just for 'damage'?

3. What about skills like incinerate that increases 'damage amplification'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to get blueprints and unlock insane? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 18:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Headquarters I see you need more blueprints. I dont see it explained in game how to get them?

How do you unlock insane ? I am up to level 85 on hard. Is it getting to a certain level on hard?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sharks Game Questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 18:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. How do you get more than 1 essence when you prestige?
2. Having trouble understanding what different rules for different worlds means... 
-- Known Modifiers: So if this is below 100, does that mean it only does 33% of normal?
-- Do climate levels matter much? I have run into ice, etc... is that based on climate level? 
-- When it says planetary income and planetary boost. How is it calculator. if I have a planetary income of .05 for something what does that mean? or a boost of 1. what does that mean?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are people throughout the Middle East considered Arabs? Didn't the arab population come from the Arabian Peninsula? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 06:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know there were Arab conquests in the 600s. Were there really enough Arabs to intermarry with all the people there to make one ethnic group? What ethnic groups were in these areas before the Arab conquest?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I always die in a day or two </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 20:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The monsters always tend to get stronger before I do. I spend the first day getting general items to try to get fresh water, etc... then make sort of a base near rocks to wall off at night. But the monsters always get stronger before I do. any tips?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Few questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 20:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Experience points: This is confusing. I can create a building that goes in say forestry, but get experience points for civil. Anyone have this figured out? How much EXP do you get for working in the buildings? you seem to get some.

2. Any other way to get marble other than if a trader comes to town? 

3. is it better to get lots of exp and tech points and filling out my build space before going up to the next city level (village - hamlet, etc...)

4. I have the military council. I have not attacked yet. Anyway to spy on villages to see what I need to send to attack? Is it worth attacking early? 

5. Pause: How do you pause the game?

6. Wine and Mead: What do you do with it other than sell it? 

7. Is it more profitable to trade with market or look for contracts? What are the most profitable items to sell? I have surplus herbs, so I sell that, but not sure if i should build more products like candles and sell those.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does autohire work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 20:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to council and put my auto-hire at 180 for orchards. I get new unemployed and they stay unemployed. I have open spots in my orchards.

Also leave jobs out of season doesn't seem to work either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The last Republican presidential candidate to win without a Bush on the ticket was Richard Nixon in 1972. The last Republican to win without a Bush or a Nixon on the ticket was Herbert Hoover the man who made the Great Depression... Truly Great </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 03:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] Make night time less dark and make buildings vanish while laying down bus routes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 20:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cities: Skylines Mods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 19:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Civilization 5: Aurora pantheon bonus Faith from Tundra not working </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 19:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have civ 5 with Gods and Kings expansion. I just picked Aurora pantheon. The one where you get +1 faith from each tundra without a forest. My captial has 3 tundra without forest with in its borders. I am still at +2 Faith (one for each City). What is wrong?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: Han Solo was original supposed to die in Return of the Jedi and the Rebels were supposed to be in tatters, but it was changed so Lucas could sell more toys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 20:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lesson for Beckham: How LT Responded to being Bountied </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 23:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't get any personal fouls. An offensive player can't hit like this, but Buddy Ryan learned a lesson. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6y7QTvNAwms

Beckham needs a Mike Singletary to Vernon Davis moment. Can't win with him. The hope Beckham doesn't appeal. He is going to lose. The last thing we need is for the suspension to get pushed to next season. The Giants should bench him for the final game too. They are not going to make the playoffs.

3 Personal Fouls? Other teams are going to target him now. They know what gets under his skin. Its going to get worse. He needs to learn to control himself. 




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coughlin is done. This is his last season coaching in the league </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 21:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He knew it. Its likely why he didn't pull Beckam. He has to go. I think Jerry Reese should go too, but the Giants don't fire GMs. I am 41 and there have been 4 GMs in my life time. You can argue that George Young's retirement was a firing, but he had been there for 20 years and was pretty old. I don't know if the guy who Young replaced in the 1970s was fired. 

Ben McAdoo: I hope they replace Coughlin with McAdoo. He will likely get Head Coaching interviews after this season. 

I hope Jerry Reese is gone too, but the Giants don't fire GMs. I am 41 and they have had 4 GMs that I can remember. Was the guy before George Young fired in the 1970s? You can argue that George Young's retirement was a firing, but he was old and had been there for 20 years. 

Reese has done a terrible job aquiring talent. Not just horrible drafting, but bad Free Agent decisions. He overpays for mediocre players then doesn't leave any money to resign Linvale Joseph. Seriously? His contract wasn't that big. 

Reese and Coughlin share a philosophy on drafting. We need a new philosophy and a change. I want to see Ben McAdoo get the Head Coaching job. He is going 

His philosohpy of 'TOTALLY' ignore Linebacker, only works if you have stud pass rushers, which the Giants were not able to reload on. 

I also question managements conditioning program since over the last 15 years the Giants have probably had the most injury issues in the league (no data, but they always seem to be at the top). They routinely have guys come back to early from injuries and get back to back injuries. 2nd injury almost always leads to the player not producing as well. They brought Hakeem Nicks back early repeatedly in 2012. Remeber the 500 yard Eli game against Tampa Bay in 2012? That was Nicks last big game. He got hurt again, then got hurt a few more and then he lost it. He was a Hall of Fame Talent.

I also question Victor Cruz's rehab program. Wouldn't surprise me if they had him run too soon. They tend to do that. Other teams use more modern science for conditioning and rehab. 

Reese has done a terrible job drafting. Bad decisions in free agency(Linvale Joseph anyone?). Bad management decisions with guys coming back too early just to get hurt again. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What changes at harder difficulties? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 17:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do mobs just get stronger? More resistant? Or does it do more. Im in act 3 at level 8 on normal and its easy. I did not google any min/max strategies and don't want to. I am confident alot of my choices are 'weak', but its more fun to figure it out myself. The biggest over powered thing I ended up doing(without realizing it ) is to make my Main character Moon Godlike Wizard. I saw that godlikes are not popular late game. Its the 2nd wizard. Having 2 wizards nuking everything makes tough fights easier. Too easy on normal. 

What changes in harder modes? I don't want min/max tips. I'd rather stumble through and putz around to figure it out. I have alot of gold so I can always retrain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dialog option questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 17:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is benevelent, etc... It looks like if I use one 'type' rational/benevelont, cruel, alot, I get better at it right? 

How much do different dialogue options affect the game? I am thinking that ones that skill check affect the game more. I noticed this in a few places. I am also noticing that most of the options you pick have similiar outcomes. 

Also, does it pay to be a jerk in this game? Alot of games push you to be nice. If you are a meany you get less rewards.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> possible to get back to defiance bay in act 3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 17:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have atleast 1 quest (for Fyrga) where I have to go back to defiance bay. I can't get back to it because of the riot. Can I complete these quests or are they gone? If I can later on, don't tell me when or how please. This game is not that hard, so please don't give spoilers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Issue with playing in Windows Mode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 18:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Windows 8.1

In options, I don't have full screen checked. I am using 1920x1600 Graphics. I do not see a border for windows mode. The only way to minimize the screen is to use the windows key. In Windows 8.1, this brings up the splash screen and I can do a search for 'chrome' or a browser to get back to the window. 

Shouldn't I be able to get borders? Asking, because I use 2 monitors and I want to watch football games over the web today on my second monitor. Having issues getting 2 screens to work. 

Typically when you don't do do 'full screen' its in Windows mode. This seems different in pillars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about picking clever/honest, etc... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 19:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am having trouble figuring out how this works. I see in my party I have numbers next to clever, honest. They don't seem to go up when I choose them. 

So does this mean if i use 'clever' alot I will get better at it? How much do these different choices change the game?

There also seems to be a big difference between a skill check speech choice and clever/honest, etc right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about White Marsh DLC and playing with Adeventurers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 19:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. I am in Act 2. Game is ok. Its not great. Clearly made on a smaller budget. Does the white marsh DLC only add new quests and areas? Or does it enhance the existing game play as well? I saw somewhere that White Marsh 2 DLC (not out yet) will enhance the Stronghold. 

2. I am playing on regular. I have 2 Adventurers (paladin and rogue). I put the priest and Chanter Companions into my Stronghold. I noticed there is some chatting and plot points with companions that you dont get with Adventurers. Am I missing alot by using adventurers? I doubt I am. I am just trying out different classes/race combos, etc... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finished Play through Thoughts about Mods to make replay more fun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 19:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finished at level 62. So I did alot of side quests. I did not visit all areas on map. I won with the Railroad because I googled it and I liked being able to blow up Prydwen and nuke the institute. B
rotherhood win looks like the coolest final battle though. Did alot of settlements, but did not pay alot of attention to it. I started on normal up to hard, then very hard. Very hard wasn't that hard at level 62. 
Bethesda games always feel like unpolished games. They put alot of money into big worlds and making it highly moddable then don't spend time on the polish. That is where the modders really come in. 
Running Skyrim with 150-200 mods really changes the feel of the game. For those of you who don't know there is a site called Skyrim Step that shows you how to do this without crashing. 


http://wiki.step-project.com/Main_Page


Going to leave off the obvious: Im on a PC and this is 64 bit please jack up these mediocre graphics. Since all PC players with mid range systems and up want that. I built my PC 3.5 years ago and I handled ultra with no issues. 

The game was fun but the world all randomly respawned and the fights were random. So it didn't have 'meaning'. My actions didn't really affect the world. I am hoping the creation kit gives modders the tools to do that. 
I also expect that most of my ideas if not all modders already thought of. I figure I would just chat anyway. 

Mods for replayability. 

1. Actions have affect on Commonwealth: Everything is randomized and respawns. Brotherhood vertibird fighting with me is neat at first, but it doesn't affect the world. Make these kinds of fights affect the world. Brotherhood can take over parts of it. Affects settlements ability to trade. Weakens other factions. vice/versa.

2. Non Playable Factions do more: Gunners/Raiders/Super Mutants: They fight each other, but its all random and respawns so its meaningless. Make them be part of the world and have how they do and who you fight with mean something. 

3. Settlement Enhancement: I expect this to be heavily overhauled. Just adding one thing. Please do it in a way that we can use this with other mods. Make the attacks on settlements less random and more meaningful. Settlements feel like a half finished beta. Modders should be able to fix this. Not to mention, a menu system for assigning setttlers, or have them just decide to farm on their own. Would be good if the creation kit has a way for the settlers to actually build up the town. This type of mod may take a while. I'm sure if its possible, someone will do it. 
Make settlement walls destructible too. 

4. More Monsters Spawned: Consoles may not be able to take more stuff to fight. My PC sure can. Even at the end, I didnt think there were too many enemies. 

5. Noise has more range: If I start shooting, its loud. Make everything in the area charge at me. I don't want to be able to sneak up on them. You can add AI to assume that Humanoids have raiders and can call each other. Make them all come at me. Console may not be able to handle this, but PCs can. Modding is mainly for PC. 

5. SkyUI for fallout 4. Most popular mod on nexus. Inventory has same weakness as vanilla skyrim.

6. VATs only target enemies: Make it a switch. We all use it to find enemies, but its a nuissance to move through allies like settlers to get to bad guys. This just makes it more user friendly. 

7. Deathclaws: They are barely in the game. How about a mod for deathclaw invasion? I'm sure someone will do this. 

8. Smarter AI: Enemies should use cover more. I'd like to see them flank. Give them more exlosives.  Give them fatman on harder levels. More stimpaks to heal. Trick me with different tactics. 
There is a Skyrim mod for this. I can't remember the name. I am pretty sure people will do that here. 

9. Text List of Areas: Its hard to find areas on the  map if I know the name but don't remember where it is. Give me a text area I can search for it to find it. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there random encounters or respawns? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 19:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am asking because if not there is a fixed amount of EXP and a fixed amount of gold. I am at Cad Nua. So I am not that far into the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to keep track of completed quests? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 00:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In most games when you complete a quest or a task, it gets marked as completed. This game does not appear to do this. I have to read them again to see oh this appears to be complete. Is there anyway to only show quests/tasks that are not yet finished?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which weapons do Big Guns/Explosives/Pistols/Rifles/automatic perk affect? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 21:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minigun: This is automatic and a big gun. Does it get a bonus from both? 
Fat Man/Missile Launcher: Explosive and Big Gun. I think its big gun. I dont have any big gun yet and I have level 3 explosives. My missiles launchers even modded out dont do alot of damage. 

My best weapon:
Legendary Shotgun with explosive shells that do 15 damage. This is modded to 204 damage. It seems like it does an obscene amount of explosive damage well beyond the 15 damage. I have taken out multiple turrets with 1 shot that blew up and multiple targets. I took down a Legendary Mirelurk Queen on Hard with just a few shots. 
So I am wondering if its getting bonuses from both Explosive and Rifles. I think it must due to the amount of explosive damage it does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are minute men quests completely random? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 21:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ghoul troubles
kidnapping
you are under attack. 

I have 150 defense at my castle, 49 water and 15 food creation. Been attached 3 times. 
I saw a post on here that says that if your defense is double your food+water this avoids kidnapping. I am noticing alot of kidpappings at Sanctuary hills where I pump out purified water even though I have a 200+ defense. 

I don't do any of the random settlement quests other than 'you are under attack' cause that one is easy and its fun action. The others are just boring to do over and over again and seem pointless. 

My settlements don't get attacked alot. Attacks can also be buggy. One of them got the 'being attacked quest'. I went there. kept sleeping for 7 days and wandered around for 20 minutes. No attack. Left, then said I failed it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do settlement walls do anything? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 19:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I occassionally get a little message such and such settlement is under attack. If I go to a settlement I have walls around and leave 1 opening loaded with turrets, all my settlers run outside the damn walls anyway. Walls don't add to defense rating. I am not sure they do anything. 

What do others think?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> cant build the recruitment beacon at airport settlement? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 01:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't show up when I go to the category. Is this a bug or can you not put a recruitment beacon here?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Consequences to failing the endless settlement quests? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 22:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no interest in doing endless 'help with ghouls' and kidnapping quests, so I just let them fail. Are there any consequences? A little happiness drop. Other than that I think I can ignore them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you really need walls to defend settlements? Attacks are so weak </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 00:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Attacks seem to be really weak. Are walls necessary at all? They seem to fight off most attacks without trouble. Walls don't add to the Defense. So I dont know it gets added into the simulation. When I have to go to a town to fight, the attacks are pretty easy. This is on normal difficulty. I am guessing attacks get alot tougher on high difficulty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [F04] Mod Request: Highlight Corpses So we can find the damn things </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 21:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I ignore happiness? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 20:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a number of settlements. I do the quests mainly to get the easy EXP. I do the minimum for the settlement. Set up trade route, recruit, food, etc... a few turrets, scavenging stations, etc... A few of the smaller ones Ill build walls. I have a few shops at Sanctuary Hills for convenience and I make a bunch of purified water. 

Does happiness matter at all? Wiki says that settlers will be less 'productive'? At what? All they can do is get food, scavenge for scraps (and this is not alot). What are they less productive at? Do I have to care about this at all? I don't have caravans yet. I dont know if that changes later on. 

The settlement stuff is rudimentary with a poor interface. So its pretty annoying to use. So I am just doing the minimum. Is there any reason for me to care about happiness?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giants Fan: Can Coples Play in a 4-3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 21:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a Jets fan too, but I am not local to New York for years and been a fair weather fan recently. They kinda sucked the last few years. So I wasn't paying attention. 

Giants defense is garbage. So its kick the tires in my opinion. Can Coplies play in a 4-3? In a 3-4 typically one of the outside linebackers is more of a standup DE. I don't know if Coples can play in space. He doesn't seem to rush the passer too well either. Well he wouldn't be any different than anyone else on the giants. 

Does he play the run well at all? He was supposed to be a pash rusher, but didn't show much right? I am not sure how the Jets used him. If they used him more in coverage or not. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you do with prewar money? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 20:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its listed as junk, but I saw in another thread that it shouldn't be junk. What do you do with it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't sell items to trader I made in Sanctuary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 16:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I crafted a Trader and assigned a settler. When I go to barter, it shows my trader doesn't have any items and that I don't have any items to sell. How does this work?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WHat do you do with cutting fluid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 21:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It says something about used for scrapping. The only way I can scrap is either in a gun/armor station or in build mode at a settlement and drop items on the floor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about Provisioners and Equipping Companions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 05:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. How do I make followers use items I give them. I gave dogmeat dog armor and a dog collar. He isn't wearing it. 

2. I am not quite sure how provisioners work. What do they share? They dont seem to share miscellanous items. My expecation was that I could craft in one settlement if i set up a supply line to another settlement that has needed items. Do I have to actually give items to the provisioner so that it meets me at the new settlement? I am a bit lost on this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FO4 Mod Request]: Settlement Management Interface </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 19:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sure someone will do this. I figured I'd start a thread to discuss ideas. Its really tedious now. 

1. Central interface that shows all my settlements, who is at them, and their tasks. This is current to the last time I was at the settlement. Interface shows all resources, turrets, etc.. built and who is assigned to them. If a person can be assigned to more things. 

2. When you enter a settlement you can give commands to settlements on what to do gather, defense' instead of having to find them and the resource. 

3. Also shows supply routes set  up. 

4. shows stores. 

Its so tedious now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Settlement Bottlecap generation and Settlers building up Settlements. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 19:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. I have Local Leader 1, Ill raise local leader to 2 at my next level so I can make shops. I'm level 7. Doing it early cause I am curious how it works. So it looks like the in game reason for settlements is to get more bottlecaps. You can also have crafting stations for weapon/armor mods, food, chems, but you only need that at 1 settlement. 

So it looks like settlements become bottle cap generators. Uh... is there anything to spend these bottle caps on ? Or do they just accumulate? 

2. In sanctuary hills I see settlers slowly building it up. Very slowly. Does this ever amount to anything? I would expect mods for this in the future. But in vanilla game. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens if you dont go in the vault at the beginning? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 23:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens if you just keep running around outside? Will the nukes come and game over?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> any reason to raise crafting or blacksmith above 5? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 21:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually have it at 1, but I have 3 items to raise Crafting and 3 to raise blacksmith. Is there ever a reason to get more than 5? I am at level 9 now. Just went to Luculla Forest. I have not done the Church yet in Cyseal because I wanted to explore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something wrong with the Giants and constant injuries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 21:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If IBM had taught Deep Blue to talk dirty, there would still be a Congressman Weiner. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 06:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't cheat on his wife. He just talked dirty to random women.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are people getting the game early? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 23:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some might be bethesda employees, but they are likely under heavy NDAs and can get in legal trouble if they leak this. Who has the game early? IS it people getting the CDs out of the boxes shipped to gamestop or something?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> dissappointed no New England Patriots stadium in Fallout Map </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 03:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a Jets fan. I want to nuke that place. I hope someone mods one in, so can blow 'deflate it' with a nuke. 

We need a Mod for a Mutant Bill Bellicheck and Tom Braday as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fucker stop spamming other chats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 17:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How fast would I have to travel to notice time dilation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 18:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> worth it to delay finishing map to get more AP? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 18:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To unlock castles you need to select the castle. Later in a map you get alot more AP. Due to all the bonuses and dungeons you have accrued. Is it worth it not clear the final castle to get more AP? I have prestiged 3 times. 

WIth my current build I did not prestige and did  anew map to see if i got more AP. I did. wondering if in the future if its worth it to just camp on an area when and accumulate more dungeons? If I keep levelling and adding monsters to each room, etc... is that the best way to jack up AP?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> fast dragon sacrifice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 18:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw the post about opening the rift inside the dragon nest. That helps alot. Is there a way to get rid of the are you sure popup when you sacrifice a dragon? that slows me down quite a bit. I know this goes away when sacrifice gets automate, but i have a ways to go for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> how much time for each tick? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 20:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did a search on the wiki. I see reference to per second, per minute, and per tick. I dont see time references with how long a tick is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Formula for number of gems that miners find. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 01:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont understand this formula. I googled gaussian function and it looks like a normal distribution. I see a formula at the top which is based on number of miners, then i see a guassian distribution and mentioning 4 gems. Can someone punch in the formula.

is it the first function with some distribution? I dont get the guassian part with 4 normal gems, etc... 
 (# miners)0.2 * 748576 gems 

er 

"Miners have a chance to find (# miners)0.2 * 748576 gems (gem calculated using Gaussian curve with 4 (normal gem) mean, 1.5 standard deviation)" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> how to sacrifice goblins for learn from the fallen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 21:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have smelting pit at level 8. I have well over 5000 steel. I Have 'sent in' far more than 100k goblins. I checked the wiki. I see references to 'sacrificing goblins' no instructions on how that actually works. How do i sacrifice goblins to the smelter?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> about exchange rate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 20:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so if the exchange rate is over 100 its a good trade right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> did mage tower requirements change? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 16:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> per Wiki 280 Mages, 250 M Stone, 1 Qi Mana. I have all that. I dont have the ability to create the mage tower.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> alchemist conversion speed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 02:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought 21 alchemist. I am testing them out. Put the max gold you can into the alchemist to convert. I have all of the hireling 12x upgrades other than wyvern. It doesn't look like anything is happening. I dont see anything getting 'converted'? It just shows the gold I moved over. I don't see anything going on. 

How does this work?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> newbie guide? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 21:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Newbie questions. Instead of making more threads, Ill keep as much here as possible. This way there is less clutter and other new players can get referred to 1 thread.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else think the fiants are going to suck? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 08:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the giants third linebacker with jameel mclain cut? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-06 01:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beason, kennard, and who? If neason gets hurt and he always does who is his backup? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> game ruining bug in 1.0.2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 20:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> game crashed when I was in the tavern. I went to to craft and my craft skill reverted from near 100 to 0. This has ruined the game. 

WHen I restarted it was like i started over. I got the you got new skills for all skills i already had. So the save file got destroyed I was the same level and had the same items/skills, but my crafting got destroyed. 

I spent many hours on this and its totally ruined.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> lets talk about Rangers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 18:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seem to have my most success with rangers, but wondering what others thing. I am level 36. I am playing softcore. 

1. I get my ultimate and leave it. Supposedly this triples evasion. I still get hit alot. So I am guessing there is an accuracy % that mobs have that deduct from.


2. Other than Activate Barrier, the other attack typers don't seem useful.
-- riposte: -30 mp for a little damage? that isnt much
-- mana expunge uses all my mana for less damage than i do witha  crit and with a Ranger I go high dex so I am at 57% critical. Not worth it
-- sacrifice: -1583 hp to 1476 damage and bleed self. why would i use this? Maybe for a final hit at the end, but i only have 2600 HP. 
-- it should not take a turn to press D to swap skill sets. 

3. I normally just go 1,2,3. Then dodge when needed and restore mp. Then rest. I dont use the other stuff. They dont look useful. 

Does anyone know how armor works? Does every point in armor reduce damage taken by 1? 

4. Anyone know the new formulas for Dex? I know it was lowered. However without the formulas its hard to tell whether i want more dex or something else. It ismore useful to know how this scales. I have been raising strength lately to get more damage and restore damage per hit. 

5. For skills, I raise all my skills. You reduce how much you get every 5 levels and there is no 1 skill that is that essential to rangers. so I do all of them. 

I am level 36, but i cant take area 6 yet. its still hard and i still die alot in area 5. so i might have a bad build. I have not upgraded my weapon in a while. Im having trouble staying alive long enough to stockpile enough gold to change my proficiencys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Darkness, invisibility, and odds and ends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 19:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1.1 version. I am on ios

1. Darkness: only use so far is that floating eyes dont freeze you in darkness. Any other uses? Any use for light other than can see?

2. Invisibility: does this do anything. It appears useless.

3. Poly potion: do you ever change back. I had a poly potion explode that i was carrying from a wand and i dont think i will change back.

Any good levels to start trying to poly your pet?

4. Pets: how do you get them to attack. I know if level is too low they dont fight, but alot of times they just sit there.

5. Gems in staffs: any way to keep your gems that are magical from damaging pets? And how often do you get the extra damage. They seem to have to charge.

Only game i won was with a knight. Trying the dark mail wizard that gets potions. Any get dual woeld on him? Staff is 2 hamded so not sure why its there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> unnethack tip for a dwarf valkyrie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 16:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not very good at the game. I am at dwarf town level 8 with -10 AC and still have my cat. I have a magic lamp (not blessed) and one potion of holy water. 

Question 1: What to wish for? I have an unblessed magic lamp and 1 holy water. 

EQ:
Excalibur +2
Armor: Elven Chain +1, low boots, plus +3 dwarf helm, +3 small shield, +0 gauntlets of dexterity , ring of protection +1, ring of polymorph control, amulet of reflection, blessed bag of holding, 3-4 heal potions, 1 unblessed potion of gain ability, cursed scroll of enchant weapon, 1 scroll of enchant armor

attributes: str: 18/04,dex: 12, con 17, int 9, wis 12, chr 7

my sword skill is still basic. 

2. what is the best way to train dexterity? not sure. i have read the wiki, but not sure the best way. i do have a scroll of enchant armor and i could use 1 my holy water on that to enchant my guantlets of dexterity to get more dex. not sure if this is better than using a wish.

3. there is a lawful unicorn on this level and i have a few valuable gems i can throw at him for luck. however, when i try to get in a line with him, he moves. i know he stays out of melee, but he stays out of throwing as well. i dont get a straight line to him. how do i line him up to throw for luck?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> anyway to see how many uses i have on a skill? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 20:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am using unnethackplus. I know I need 200 successful uses to get from basic to skilled. is there a way to see how close I am? I use the #enhance and I can't raise. not sure if i can see in vanilla nethack eithger

I have some interface questions as well

1. anyway to get the game to alert me or something when I get hungry? I know it says hungry at the bottom, but i die alot because i just dont notice it. anyway to make the game pause or have it flash or something? 

2. same with hitpoints? anything like wimpy in MUDs to pause the game or something to say hey watch it HP is low? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> newbie dwarf valkyrie help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 20:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> been using dwarf valkyrie since its recommended to newbies on the wiki. I have used nethack 3.4 before, but have moved to unnethack for the interface enhancements. I don't get very far and usually dont make it to dwarf town

1. let my dog/cat get most kills to try to get to full grown as soon as possible
2. bypass mines to go to oracle and dip for exalibur. The problem is that Im finding that I get water demons/snakes far more often than I get excalibur and I die. The wikis says you should do this... 
3. go back up and hit the mines. Let my dog/cat kill all gnomes/dwarves. 
4. stockpile items i can't carry next to stairs. i do this because i want to do runs from dwarf town to sell as much as possible for gold. 
5. i have read about elsbreth, but not sure how to use it. 
6. when i find shops i do price identification or try to and then rename the items with buy/sell price. this is rather tedious... 

any other tips? Also about exercising. I have found my stats dont go up much. I can spend tons of time moving boulders around and get nothing. I kick doors to train dex. Not sure what else to do. 

Im not very good at the game. 

ABout the UI. Does unnethack have any features to make my HP stand out more? With the location on the screen and when I get going, its really easy to miss my low HP and then I die.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> dipping for excalibur in unnethack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 20:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a novice at nethack. I Have mainly played Valkyries due to the guide in the wiki. Am I just unlucky, but it seems like a much smaller chance to dip for excalibur in unnethack than in the vanilla nethack. I am more likely to get a water demon or snakes than I am to excalibur. I did some save scumming at the oracle to test this. Its hard to tell all the changes from unnethack to nethack. The changelog is long </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Permanently overweight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 23:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dropped all myitems and i am at 2 overweight still. I cant figure out what happenen knight level 17 . 18/49 strength. Absolutely no items </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Create monster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 18:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone found a use for this other then make some monsters to kill and possibly tame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pet polymorph </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 04:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When my pet hits a polymorph trap it doesnt always morph back and it goes to level 1. Anyone know the mechanics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pouring potions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 19:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone ever get a result from pouring potions into potions other than bless from holy water. 

Only results i get from pour are oil on items to proof them.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fountain uses and training pets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 18:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far these are the uses i have found for fountains. Any tips for anything else
1. Wish 1000 gold gets speed boots
2. Drink and hope for stats
3. Dip scrolls to make blank.

Training pets. Pets seem to die alot. Then they lose xp when healed. Seems like pets wont attack stronger monsters. So if weak i need to take them up stairs. Any else have a different idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enchant weapon blew up short sword </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 17:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is +7 the best you can go. Used an enchant and bam.

I also paid the armorer to add a strength ring. It. Was a -1 ring, but two enchants gave me a point of strength. Dont know if that influences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
