<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1272</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Daily show: Manspreading </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 16:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dude builds working Star Wars AT-AT on Space Engineers [x-post from /r/spaceengineers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 21:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 suspected jihadi cell members arrested in France </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 17:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Security Forces Raid Independent Crimean TV Station </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 16:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worst first words from a baby? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 11:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any other projects of cloning extinct animals than the mammoth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 13:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EventStatus talks about racism on video game journalism and biased coverage about current events. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 22:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finnish version of the monster in moomins compared to Japanese. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 22:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Literally the case... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 14:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans of reddit. Is there more to Vegas than gambling? Any cool stories about it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 18:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Europeans of Reddit. What's it like to live near the border of another european country? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 13:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worlds biggest plane? I raise you the worlds biggest helicopter! Carrying a plane. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 01:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> REPORT: French Police Have Identified The Three People Involved In Magazine Shooting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 21:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: [North Korea] Does Kim Yong Un know what the others were doing when he was gone a few months because of his leg? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 19:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Despite "The Interview" being removed. Here's a video that China won't remove even though North Korea requested: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 11:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [META] Was this fullmcintosh guy in this situation the whole time? Or did he drag himself into this topic because some people used his name as a joke? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 15:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first time I heard about this were people responding to random aGG crazies on twitter. And the responses were some jokes like "this person went #fullmcintosh".

A few days later this mcintosh guy appears on topics being aGG and all that etc. So I'm just wondering was he part of this from the beginning or did he join in because his name came a bit relevant and now wants to be part of this fiasco? 

EDIT: So apparently he is the owner of FemFreq, any more info about that? Is it openly out or did someone dig it up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time traveling method: Middle eastern suicide bombers are using technology to blow their society back to the past. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 14:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Sanity Sunday] Every point about the "riots are good" poster burned like napalm in the morning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 16:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Based gamer has 15 days left for their indiegogoal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 01:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any urban myths, popular or unpopular around your town or country? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 20:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Leo Steel] Anyone else spend time playing this game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 01:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two dudes trying to trick cops (x-post /r/justiceporn) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 23:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hardcore Putin (Iron Sky sequel) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 18:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apparently a satire website has made a story about Alanah Pearce being sued by one of the gamers she called out. Aaaand some of the MSM took the bait. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 18:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you read the title. A satire website has posted an article about her that she is currently being sued by one of the parents. Meanwhile some of the news websites are eating all this up. For some reason some of them tag gamergate to these stories even though Alanah Pearce has said that gamergate has nothing to do with this (I guess clickbait). Some of the news websites don't even seem to check what they are writing about. Here's one example of it:

https://web.archive.org/web/20141207172123/http://www.designntrend.com/articles/28451/20141202/gamergate-update-female-video-game-reviewer-sued-for-telling-mothers-about-their-sons-online-threats.htm

The only good thing is that there is a little hope in people because the comments are calling out on this bs (which sadly can't be viewed on the archive for some reason).

Alanah Pearce responded to these claims on twitter clearing up that she is not being sued:

https://twitter.com/Charalanahzard/status/540001186712010755

https://twitter.com/Charalanahzard/status/540544498598563842

P.S I'm not sure what the satire website she is talking about, but could be cool if someone provided with the link to the satire news story. 

P.S2 I don't know how to shorten links (that long ass Archive link looks as ugly as my scrambled eggs I cooked this morning with a hangover).

**EDIT:**
 
Thanks to HandofBane here's a shorter archive with the comments showing up: https://archive.today/seKxL . And thanks to groovegmr for linking the satire article: https://archive.today/NmvTH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Group of people getting drunk while going through different tumblr posts and other crazy topics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 13:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A page about Cultural Marxism was removed a few days ago and now has been restored back by Jimbo Wales. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 01:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Rockstar is probably handling the situation about GTA V. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 16:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Andrew Klavan: GamerGate Forever! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 16:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Next month is gonna be christmas, but be careful singing these songs! You might offend some...one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 15:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finnish sketch about current situation with Russia and Finland. [with english subs] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 20:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What fictional character would you choose to be your lawyer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 00:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interesting map of Russia behind a chocolate bar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 00:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy blows off steam through topics about ferguson, media, SJW's, IGBA, and gaming. (35 mins) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 01:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:Flappy bird. Why did so many different versions come out of that and why were they allowed to come out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 10:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What could've been done to avoid multiple fake versions to come out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poop Prank backfires (xpost from r/justiceporn) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 22:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys think about this? Are we on a burning plane going down or what? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 16:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arnold Schwarzenegger has probably killed more Columbian Guerrilla militants in the movie Collateral Damage, than the US has on the whole war on drugs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 22:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> tumblr.avi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 17:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our first contact with Alien life would probably be through radio/tv signals and we would spend the next decades of listening/watching each others sitcoms until the information of each others acknowledgment gets to each other. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 16:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Putin's Advisor: Kremlin plans to overthrow Poroshenko </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 20:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could a tardigrade be able to survive on Venus? What about Mars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 17:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Third world rich </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-18 15:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Coca cola light is considered worse for your health than normal coke. Is coca cola zero worse than coca cola light? Do they have some differences in ingredients? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 19:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you ignore the sugar amount. Is there anything else different in them or do they have the same type sweeteners? Only in different quantities or what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The reason why Terminator salvation isn't about futuristic 90's trench wars at night is because the TX almost completed its mission and managed to change the future. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 18:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to pump up your affiliates and have them promote on your behalf. (Sponsored by someone who definitely doesn't do that, duh.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 01:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cursed/live mummies are preserved zombies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 01:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian jet flew 'metres' from Swedish plane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-03 18:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any full actual picture of the U.E.S.C Marathon? Or a more detailed one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 21:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never managed to find a good one from anywhere. Anyone know if Bungie had some pictures of it or some kind of concept art? All i've seen is the small pixelated one from far in the background. Maybe someone should ask Bungie what it should look like or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After realizing the first president wasn't that popular in the federation and drank himself to death. Putin now is throwing all in to make himself a big part in history. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 10:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands join in Anti-War protests in Russia (St Petersburg, Moscow) [LIVE] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 16:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> totalbiscuit, mundanematt, becca, etc. Talking about current game journalism. [currently live] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 00:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are video games sexist? Christina Hoff Sommers disagrees. Calls SJW's as hipsters with degrees in cultural studies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 20:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heard mixed thoughts about Destiny. What do you guys think? Is it good? Are there some flaws? Yay or Nay? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 21:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transwoman gamedev silenced by feminists. Way before #gamergate event. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 18:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin's Ex-adviser: "Russia's war with Ukraine was planned 11 years ago" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 17:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finnish media baffled again as Russian media spreads weird claims that "Finland wants to join Russia" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 16:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Halonens ex-head of press: Putin used to be shy and now is ruthless. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 21:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New footage of ISIS threatening with captured jet! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 09:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How does one raid 4chan? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 18:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometime ago apparently tumblr raided 4chan and 4chan showed them how to raid. Now I'm just wondering how can 4chan be raided/angered? Throwing disgusting photos or what? (Isn't that common in that site?) Isn't that like throwing gasoline at a fire? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian MP: If the Ukrainian who painted the Moscow building into Ukrainian colors doesn't give himself up. Then innocent russians will be punished. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 21:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 100 wounded russian soldiers brought to St. Petersburg hospital from "nowhere" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 17:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian MI-24 opened fire on Ukrainian border guards killing 4 soldiers, East Ukraine. (far from Donetsk Lugansk conflicts) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 16:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lots of captured Militants/soldiers and burning tanks near Novoazovsk (from earlier conflict) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 19:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Battles near Novoazovsk, Ukraine border (far from Donetsk and Lugansk conflict) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 12:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Battle near Novoazovsk, Ukraine border (Far from Donetsk and Lugansk conflicts) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 12:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Organs in the black market. How do they end up where they need to be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 11:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do the organs end up in a new person? Does some doctor whisper to a patient that he can offer one straight away for a good price? Or do the organs end up being put back in at some shady place by some random guy or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conflicts happening in Ukraine outside of current conflict zone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 12:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mariupol Under attack and Telmanovo border captured by some kind militants:

http://www.pravda.com.ua/news/2014/08/24/7035653/

Sedove under attack from sea and land:

http://militaryMaps.info/?lat=47.0773025 lng=38.1699705 z=14 t=3

5 BMP's crossed the border from Russia to Ukraine near Ulyanivske:

https://twitter.com/EuromaidanPR/status/503253059339034626

National Guard says it has attacked The Ukr national guard says it attacked a Russian convoy near Amvrosiyevkoyu, destroying 3 KamAZ trucks. 2 Russian BTR fled the area.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mariupol attacked and Telmanovo border captured by militants (outside of conflict zone) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 12:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spot report UPDATE: Russian humanitarian aid trucks departed from the Donetsk Border Crossing Point without ICRCs escort </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 00:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man detained in St. Petersburg for wearing yellow blue cap with the word Ukraine written on it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 14:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post a good pickup line or popular line from a movie scene. Then someone else has to reply with a plot twist! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 19:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Self propelled howitzers apparently spotted in rebel area going back towards Russian border. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 10:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We need a kids react: depression quest! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 01:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about we let the kids judge if the game is actually good or not. I don't think the kids will be "sexist" or "misogynistic" for giving bad reviews. Or that they were paid for good reviews.

This needs to happen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biggest thing the whole world can do to a problem like ISIS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 10:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Current /r/gaming thread related. Moderators of this sub, your opinions about the current scandal going on this sub? And about that one of the moderators has been dragged into this scandal. [serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 21:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia FM claims Ukrainian "Aidar" battalion mining roads in Luhansk to destroy convoy and then blame insurgents. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 17:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (English)Ukraine Crisis Media Center [LIVE] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 12:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian military trucks Kamaz repainted in white for delivery of humanitarian aid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 11:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UnReal World RPG - Survival based roguelike game (Finland Survival simulator!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 01:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter / LUGANSK_TODAY: Militants tank crashed into trolleybus in Krasnodon, driver was killed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 16:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Voting, is it actually legit in any way that someone gets elected with over a 100% rate and how does that even work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 13:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just sometimes see some "honest" politicians in some countries get elected again with more than a 100%. What is it based on or how does that work? Isn't 100% always the roof? If 5 people for the same person, shouldn't it be just 100% and shouldn't go over in any way? 

I know some of the guys or many of them, who get elected with over 100% don't live in a place where their people live free or democratically. But is there something that I'm missing out about this or is it all not legit?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine separatist admits to 'executions' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 15:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia to Ban Soldier 'Selfies' to Prevent Incriminating Evidence from Going Viral </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 00:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine leaks Stalin's 'KGB secrets' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 23:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gubarev's assistant shot dead by someone unknown in Luhansk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 11:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putins Russian Spring idea was invented by Russian fascists in the 1920s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 00:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reports of toxic fumes after shelling on Ukrainian border guards from Russia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 14:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian army moving BUK systems towards Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 13:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A column of Russian military vehicles entered Ukraine through Dmytrivka </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 11:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With many claims about the rebel leaders being Ex Russian military or some retired agents. Plus a lot of volunteers from Russia. Could this news about Russian military tactics be some kind of proof of Russian intervention in Ukraine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 16:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ign7n03tXxw

The news is talking about a tactics where Russian special forces stir up domestic political problems in neighboring countries. Oddly enough, it is very similar to the problems in Ukraine right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New photo of a truck with a Buk near Snizhne taken on the morning of July 17 (Twitter) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 01:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Gun sounds in the movie Aliens, were the sounds caused from the guns or from the echoes from the corridors or other surroundings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 22:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poroshenko explained why Ukraine isn't responding to Russian shelling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 19:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia Rejects Calls for Substantial Monitoring of Russian Side of Border. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 16:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian soldier posts pictures of his units claiming " shooting Ukraine all night" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 19:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heres a link to the picture:

https://twitter.com/euromaidan/status/491997024737570816

Heres the vk link to his profile (deleted):

https://vk.com/id228257354 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian soldier posts photos claiming that his unit was shelling Ukraine all night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 19:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ITAR-TASS: Russia - Russia demands condemnation of mercenaries activity in eastern Ukraine (xpost nottheonion) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 22:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia demands condemnation of mercenaries activity in eastern Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 22:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter: Russians shelling heavily in Donetsk, Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 15:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LNR banned vehicle movements in Lugansk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 22:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter / MaximEristavi 'We don't know where #MH17 black boxes are' -Borodai </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 14:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone actually track Putin's flight that he apparently flew over Ukraine and pretty close to the malaysian flight? Or any other information about that? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 19:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dnrpress posted on twitter that they shot down a plane at the same time and place as the Malaysian plane went down. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 03:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter / Reuters: Malaysian PM Najib says if aircraft was shot down, perpetrators must be swiftly brought to justice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 23:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NATO factsheet july 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 15:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Air strikes on 5 targets in Luhansk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 15:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: When birds are in the cage and the cage is covered with a blanket. What makes them go silent? Why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 13:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they really get sleepy or do they feel as if they are punished? Or is it that simple that they calm down and fall asleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The F-35 is a huge failure because all of the billions of dollars were actually spent on a top secret super stealth fighter jet that can't be revealed to the world! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 12:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The F-35 is a huge failure because all of the billions of dollars were actually spent on a top secret super stealth fighter jet that can't be revealed to the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 11:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting rid of muscle soreness by working out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 14:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had muscle soreness once and the advice my dad gave me for it was to work it out. The idea seems crazy since it would seem to make the soreness worse, but I'm not sure since my dad used to be a gym trainer a long time ago. I would want to hear your guys opinions on this, is it a good thing or a bad thing? Any better advice?

After a long break, I thought I would start going to the gym again and this subreddit could provide a lot of help also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would the aftermath of the Yellowstone eruption/explosion look like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 12:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the worst thing people can agree to the terms and conditions without reading it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 22:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Reddit doesn't want you to post personal information. Why do some social medias require this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 20:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You aren't allowed to post yours or anyone's personal information on some subreddits or maybe allover reddit. Why? Facebook seems like a place where that is required to do? What harm would it do here compared to facebook? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone wondering what footage or info did the Russians take/destroy from some journalists when they stormed a hotel? This happened in the annexation of Crimea. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 10:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://time.com/26320/gunmen-storm-crimea-hotel-full-of-reporters-on-eve-of-referendum/

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CLw1WdS8F1c

Could there be some footage that they didn't want to spread or something? Or were they destroying evidence of them being Russian soldiers? At that time Russia was still denying that it was their troops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suppose theres a huge group of people in a huge spaceship. What is the best political system that would work in a spaceship? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 20:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the worst revenge someone has done to you or someone you know, but you or someone didn't cause it in the first place? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 11:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As in whats the worst revenge someone you know has done to the wrong person? Or did you ever make that kind of a mistake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your driving test like? Fail or pass? Did you fuck it up totally or did something interesting happen during it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 23:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why does coding create new problems in the code? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 12:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example someone changes the code to fix a problem, at the same time a new problem comes up somewhere in the code. Is there something else which makes this problem that I don't understand or what? I barely know anything about coding, but I'm interested to know why this happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, you know who did it again... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 18:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, you know who did it again... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 18:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justin Bieber probably was thinking the same before his video was posted online. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 08:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain why Duke Nukem forever ruined the series? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 10:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it exactly which ruined the game experience for you? Is the story too weird? I've seen a lot of complaints about it, but I haven't seen the reasons why this game isn't good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What is it exactly that separates the US and Russia from being actual allies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 12:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both of the countries have some differences, but the differences don't seem to be that big. They don't have a completely different view of politics like back in the cold war and how they tried to push their visions throughout the world. ( Like NK still wants this to happen.) They also don't have some religious reasons to "destroy and convert each other" ( a few countries want to).

Is it only because of the history as in their stance wouldn't change even after the fall of the soviet union?

Or is it all because of competition? Does competition achieve more than having an alliance? 

Shouldn't an alliance be more useful than two countries not liking each other pushing each other up to the point of "the war that ends all wars" for the third time? (that quote is a term for WW1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian social media is apparently spreading pictures showing american troops in Ukraine. This article traces the photo which is originally from New Orleans back in 2005. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 14:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Article talking about Russian social media posting "proof" of american troops in Ukraine. Actual photo is then traced and was originally taken from New Orleans back in 2005 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 14:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Aren't some ISP's like comcast or other ones in America considered to be the definition of a cartel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 10:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [BF4] Freezing the game and restoring corrupted files on my ps3 decided to delete my whole singleplayer campaign save... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 14:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any way to prevent this? It's a problem which comes daily when playing multiplayer and this happened when my game froze on the campaign. Is Dice, EA or whoever is in charge working on to fix this? Do they know about this or is it a problem no one can fix even? The easter sale thing seems like a ripoff now for some reason.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leaked phone call talking about creating own referendum results to be 89% or 99% instead of going through it legally. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 00:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We know that you caught someone in the act of something weird, but what is it that you got caught in the act and who caught you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 13:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> footage of pro russians beating captured/tied up men </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 16:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> live footage of pro russian forces torturing/interrogating pro unity people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 15:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/worldnews new posts currently being downvoted and upvoted with about 55 downvotes and about 35 upvotes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 13:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Noticed some similarities from the old Bungie trilogy and the upcoming game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 13:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Year old video of Russian special forces capable of stirring up domestic political problems in neighboring countries (Link to video in comments if it doesn't work in the article.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 19:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video shows of Russian strike team capable of stirring up domestic political problems in neighboring countries. (Video in comments if that doesn't work) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 17:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How my Russian parents react to Russian news compared to the vast information from the internet. (Thanks snuus for finding the right scene!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 21:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone help finding a scene from V for vendetta? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 10:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to search for the scene in the movie V for vendetta. Where people are staring at the news and are criticizing it for false with some "can you believe this crap" or "I don't think this is real" quotes. Is there actually a scene about it or did I make it up in my head? I would like to find that scene if anyone could help. 

(Sorry if this is on the wrong subreddit I should be posting, could you help by pointing out to where this question should be?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Redditors! Who has the most karma in Reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 14:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   :      13  2014   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 20:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rally in Moscow 13th of april 2014 (  :      13  2014  ) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 19:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I met my GF's classmate a while ago... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 12:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain a bit how communism works? And why and how did some communist leaders find out that worldwide communism doesn't actually work out? What is the flaw in this whole system? ELI5 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 19:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the chances that the black box signal is actually from the MH370? Does each black box send a specific signal or do they all have the same signal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 10:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seriously I can't be the only one who sees this! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 22:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: There are doctors who invent new vaccines or some kind of antibiotics and then give it a high price. How is that not different from what a cartels does by definition? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 20:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know if everyone who read this by what I meant about cartels. Since where I live its also the definition about a company being able to fully control the price of a product. Doing something like that would end up in high fines. So the way to stop that is that there needs to be another competitive company to keep the prices/quality right.. Not long ago there was someone who created a cure for some kind of hepatitis, but with a high price because of some "risks" the makers had to take. So whats the difference between these and why is this more accepted than other companies making prices for it? ELI5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian news instructions leaked? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 22:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian news instructions leaked? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 21:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why didn't they think of this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 01:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Selfish Putin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 17:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its just business </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 15:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Russia has patriotic youth camps to gain more favor for Putin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 13:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened to the protests in Russia against war? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 23:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The media was all over it for one day and nothing new about it the next day. Was it organized to be for only one day or is it still going on right now? Can someone give an explanation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russians of reddit (or anyone else who knows about this topic): What happened to the protests in Russia against war? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 22:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was all spread in one day and nothing new about it the next day. Did they stop covering it or was the protest just for one day?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would happen to all the social websites in the internet if a third world war would erupt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 15:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin gave his old watch to a ukrainian boy and at the same time told him about people living in peace in the future of Ukraine. Now the same boy is returning it and is saying: "Putin you're a liar!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 18:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Old quote from Putin which makes no sense anymore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-13 23:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why isn't there a worldwide censorship ban law? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-09 14:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why isn't there some kind of international humanitarian law about banning censorship worldwide? Is it because it's not a big issue or could it be because everyone is using censorship already? ELI5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Socially Awkward Putin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-08 22:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> National guards in Venezuela shooting at protesters. Footage shows them trying to shoot at cameraman. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 21:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> National guards shooting at protesters and try to shoot at guy behind camera </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 20:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens to the military/police/special forces after a revolution succeeds? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-21 11:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: There are many claims that the US would be very harsh on their protesters (shoot them). Was there a point in recent history which ended up with many casualties because of protests or riots? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 19:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yanukovych fires army chief and replaces him with the chief of the navy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 16:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What is the difference between a soldier and a mercenary? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 22:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't find a clear explanation enough. Both in the end get payed for doing a job which might be somewhat similar. Is there more to this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How do some old equipment keep track of time after not being used for a long period of time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 11:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example: I plugged in my old PS2 and noticed that it knew the exact time after saving a new game. So I wondering how does it keep track of time or where did it get the information of the current time if it isn't connected to the internet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember Climate Change summit back in 2009? Heres footage of Australia's statement about it. Seems its gone to a different direction compared to the recent news.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 00:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Luckily, I am not the only one with the same problem. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 17:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shouldn't reddit be covering the riots in Thailand too? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 17:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the average salary of the police attending to be riot police. How much is it higher compared to a normal police job? (Assuming that the police do get a higher payment for attending the event) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 20:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Band of brothers rally around boy, 6, to stop teasing because of the clothing he wears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 19:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Envy bear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 15:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone remember this PC game? Bungie still makes plenty of references and easter eggs of it in halo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 14:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
