<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 16:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm reading all of these, and there's so many examples of step-parents or ex-spouses, so my question is, What is the correlation between health inspectors and divorce? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 17:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I've found people look at you weird if you use 'Marry me' to get out of any awkward situation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smh I've watched the first 3 seasons in about a week's timespan and now my entire life is subconsciously narrated by Ron Howard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 15:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 22:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all I know is they just better not concentrate in my yard cuz they shit everywhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 22:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this was the essential plot line of a family guy episode from like 2 years ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 06:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are you sure that's just not an iPhone case propped up by some elaborately made paper walls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 22:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I've had mono for the last week, but it was def while watching Arrested Development when Tobias said "I just blue myself" when he was auditioning for the Blue Man Group </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 22:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't a real experience, but I get periodic dreams where I'm pooping in a school bathroom and then I look down and realize I have no clothes on, and then I have the horrifying realization that I have to get through the school butt ass naked so I can go home to get clothes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blazing Saddles, but even saying the title of the movie may get censored </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 00:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's lit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> how has Hillary not made a Hillarambe joke yet it's so there for the taking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 02:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 19:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paprika </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 19:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow that's even smaller than the role I have in my daughter's life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well today excel glitched out on me and the entire display went blank so I think they've got bigger fish to fry rn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 04:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry you prob won't have to return him, he'll just dig a hole and hid in it for a few years before you finally find him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is just a plot summary of ratatouille  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What more can you expect from the state that teaches revisionist history that excludes Jim Crow laws to its high schoolers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 19:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but was he captured tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 07:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone here better cancel that trip to Hawaii cause it looks like we're all going on the no fly list  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 06:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is very unfortunate to be an expert about something and have the last name duffus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 03:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is a very nihilistic voting policy but I appreciate it nonetheless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 03:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what a wierd rule </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 17:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he was definitely not the first ever quadriplegic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 04:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asking a magic 8 ball is usually a good place to start. It has worked so far for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 23:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> does anyone else think that he just might be the Asian Michael Jordan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 16:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And at that moment, I touched hands with the love of my life, and as I looked up to meet their gaze, I saw myself in the mirror and realized my true love had been here for my entire life"

-Excerpt from "The Narcissist Diaries," by Hugh Janus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 16:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That he to have been a painful way to die for all of the 'Vegetable Peeler Murderer's' victims </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 16:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear it gets difficult to sneak up on people when you have to stay at least 500 feet away from them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I realize Gary might not be in the debates, but there is a new hurdle. Maintain 5% so that he receives federal funding for next election cycle. If he gets that, the dream isn't dead yet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 06:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most inclusive rhetoric? Most concrete details of policies? Most trustworthy? Most favorable personality? Healthiest candidate? Least tied to PAC's and donors? Undisputed successful political career? Why is he sitting at 10% in the polls? What more does a president need to be elected? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 02:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 17:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> smh tough crowd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only baseball player a friend knew was A-Rod and he wanted to know more, so I told him Mitch Moreland #offensivethreatmitchmoreland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 15:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ryan Kavanaugh recently tweeted "1,000,000 rt's and I'll make a Harambe movie. What would be your all-star cast? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 05:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors: has anyone been in a 'Jim and Pam' style relationship where you have no doubts about marrying your spouse? Is that real? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 17:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone on my dorm floor is starting to cheat on his girlfriend. It infuriates me, what should I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 06:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you get when you cross an Egyptian and a doctor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 15:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 18:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it sucks donkey dong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 15:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I left it inside the dorm lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 15:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was asleep, but you're right, If I'm locked out, why wouldn't I use my key to get in? Brilliant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 15:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found a couch and then my other roommate came back and let me in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 15:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The beautiful University of Kansas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 15:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already used my free 'I got locked out' this semester, so now is have to pay $20 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a college freshman living in the dorms, and I went out to the lobby to hang out and my roommate who goes to bed at 11 locked me out! Ask me anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 07:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a college freshman who got locked out of my dorm because I went to hang out in the lobby of our floor and my roommate went to bed at 11 and locked me out. Ask me anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 07:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 20:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget the fact that he also opened that with a dick shot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Gary Johnson wins the election, does that mean the Libertarian party would change their abbreviation from (L) to (W) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 19:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 18:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Get the fuck out of my face" -A$AP Ferg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 18:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/harambe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 18:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cosmo, because then all the girls start talking to me becuase they all just assume I'm gay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 17:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of my homework, but at least I'm currently pursuing my degree it reddiology </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 17:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colonel Carillo in Narcos was pretty cool, but then he went and executed that kid in the street just to make a point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 17:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't necessarily torture, but when I was in eighth grade, our regular social studies teacher had a baby, so our long term sub just happened to be our school counselor the prior week. She was really a pretty weird personality, filled with weird, overused sayings like 'Hold the phone' and 'too bad, so sad, love dad' that were all used mockingly. The day she snapped tho was when she was giving us our third unscripted suicide talk that month, and someone piped up and said 'Suicide is a temporary solution to a very permanent problem,' and needless to say she lost it on us. We had a new sub once we got back from winter break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a Chem professor named Carey Johnson, and he asked if we had any questions today, and I had to resist the urge to ask 'What is Aleppo?' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 16:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People keep pointing to Dansby Swanson as one of the main reasons the Dbacks need to clean house, but everyone seems to forget that Ender Inciarte is 12th in WAR this season among all OF's. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 00:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> talk about a bad day for these to come in the mail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 00:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Talk about a bad day for these to arrive in the mail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 23:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 23:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you ever get that feeling where you do something stupid one night, but you can't really remember it because that night was super lit, but then you wake up in the morning and realize you just traded 2 of your best prospects for a horrendous pitcher? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gary Johnson doesn't know what Aleppo is, Donald Trump probably didn't either, Hillary Clinton doesn't know what classified markings are, and there is a warrant out for Jill Stein's arrest. This election is just a game of Russian Roulette, except there's a bullet in every chamber. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 20:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> *michael sees Jan's baby for he first time* "So this is Assturd" "Astrid" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 01:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 00:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A gun-toting Jew. I'm probably the first one you've heard of, because in our society we do not often find those three words paired consecutively. To add to it, I am an Orthodox Jew, complete with the full suit and the Kippah, also known as a Yamaka to the majority of the population. I even have a special tailored pocket in each one of my suit jackets for my specially engraved M1911. Like I said, I'm a gun-toting Jew.
 
On top of being a part of this extremely specific sect of society, I am a history major, specializing in the historical injustices committed against the Jewish people. Despite the unfortunate thins that have happened to my ancestors, I find the area extremely interesting.  So much so that even after I finish my daily research at the local university, I go home and watch documentaries into the ungodly hours of the night.
 
It was just another night, one of the many that follow a laborious day of investigating the genocides of my long lost cousins, and per the usual I went home and watched the first documentary I saw. This unfortunately, happened to be a holocaust documentary.
 
My job was to study instances such as the holocaust, yet every time I saw Adolf Hitler on a television set I would be filled with this insatiable rage, feeling the pent up anger for the 6 million Jews lost corse through my veins. So as he stood up, angrily spewing racial denunciations to the people of Nuremberg, I felt myself once again shake with that uncontrollable ferociousness. This time however, it was like nothing I had ever felt. 
 
 Sure, a rage like this had caused me to break a coffee table once, but this anger was so deep, so controlling, that I unconsciously pulled my gun out of my suit pocket and aimed the gun, one loaded with artificial vengeance, at the head of Adolf Hitler. 
 
I closed my eyes, I couldn't concentrate anymore. The gun was still held there, just waiting for me to make a decision.
 
The recoil of the pistol and the explosion of sound combined to augment the shock I had just experienced, but as I finally opened my eyes to see the electronic disaster I surely had caused, I instead saw 3 neat holes, and then motionless Adolf Hitler in a Nazi uniform that had much more red than usual. It appeared that I had just killed Adolf Hitler.
 
Theres no way.  Its just a television. This cannot be happening.
 
The thoughts raced through my head, but they finally came to a conclusion that if my anger was powerful en ought to get me to shoot at a television containing a man who had been dead for 70 years, then it must be powerful enough to cause me to hallucinate.
 
So I went to bed, yet as I turned my light off, I couldnt help but notice the fading of most cherished book The Diary of Anne Frank, as it always had sat on my nightstand.
 
I really need to move that book from out of the sunshine, I thought.  Nonetheless, it was a task for tomorrow, so I fell asleep. 
 

                                                               

 

When my world really began to change was when I woke up and noticed the cover of my most cherished book had gone blank, just as every other page in the book.  Wordless, it was simply bound paper, unable to tell the story of a young persecuted Jewish girl.  I tried not to think about it for fear of the consequences, so I ate breakfast and was off to work.



Once I had gotten to work, there were 3 messages on my desk phone; two from my mother, and one from a so-called Great Uncle Blumberg.  The two calls from my mother were simply chastisements for not answering this Blumberg fellows calls, and then his call turned out to be an invitation to dinner.  Considering I had not the slightest idea who he was, I did quick research, and found that he was born in Germany in the early 1930s and then emigrated to the States in the 1950s.  Why I had never heard of him, only God knows.



Acknowledging that this may have been my lifes most peculiar start to a day, but nonetheless I kept trying to carry about my own business.  However, as I opened my latest research paper, just like The Diary, it too was blank.  I turned to my primary source, a manuscript from Nazi Germany.  It too was blank. My world was changed in front of my eyes, and I was beginning to legitimately panic, so I looked up Adolf Hitler just to reassure myself that I hadnt magically caused this all. Sure enough the entry read:

            Adolf Hitler: A promising young radical politician who was assassinated shortly into his political career.  Just sixth months after taking office, he was assassinated at a rally despite his immense popularity, and it served as a further blow to German nationalism. Shortly after his death, the entirety of Germany succumbed to Soviet rule, simply because inflation was so rampant that the Germans could no longer support themselves.



I must have fainted, because when I woke up, I read it all again, and it was still all true.  The holocaust never happened, my Great Uncle had never died, and neither had Anne Frank.  I had effectively wiped out the worlds most tragic genocide with one rage fit that involved shooting a TV.  I was a changed man because of the experience, but it was apparent that the world was greatly changed as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 03:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Governor Johnson and Governor Weld, I greatly appreciate you taking the time to answer Reddit's question, and I will be voting for you in November in Kansas! My question is, what is your stance on the killing of Harambe? Was he murdered in cold blood, or killed for a phony cause? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 03:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's play Kill, Fuck, Marry: Hillary Clinton, Jill Stein, and Donald Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm researching the series, and I fully forgot that Holly treated Kevin like he had a mental disability for her first episode. This is why this show is gold. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 23:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got to he part where he says he's going to bang her. Case closed, best show ever.

EDIT: *rewatching
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 01:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was probably 5 and was having a nightmare, and I thought I woke up, but when I opened my eyes I saw a 4 foot tall version of FDR's head staring at me and I just lost my shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 17:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought people in Independence are used to it tho because of all the meth lab explosions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 17:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe with all the money were making from fracking we can start rebuilding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 06:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be honest, when I clicked on this thread I expected a mega-argument about Harambe, and it was there, and now I'm disappointed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> harambe wouldn't have ignored Lena Dunham </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 04:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 19:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> harambe loved autumn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 03:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this brings an entirely new meaning to 'stepping on legos' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you dig through her stuff you might find a personalized poem written for her called "A Farewell to that Pussy" or "My Penis Also Rises" or just something along those lines </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 01:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a Chiefs coin toss captain when I was 10 back in 2008, so I got to go went out with a few of Chiefs players and during the official coin toss and just be there to experience. Anyways, there was one Chiefs player that said hi to me and was pretty nice, but I was pretty nervous because I was about to go out there. I get out to midfield, and as all the players are shaking hands I stand there awestruck at the size of these guys. Sure enough, as I'm standing there, rather reserved, and of the five Chargers that were out there, Phillip Rivers goes out of his way to shake my hand. He was the only player in the entire huddle to do so, and to this day, it pains me to see all of the complaints that he's a whiner, and he's unappreciative. He made one kind act he didn't need to, and a lot of people don't realize what kind of impression that has on a kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 01:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 00:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jokes on them when the cop shows up and busts them for sales tax evasion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 15:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you obviously had a lame 8th grade class </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> more people have died from smoking smarties than from smoking marijuana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 05:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 04:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like they made a concerted effort to make the building look pixelated in order to confuse anyone who is trying to fly a plane into it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Updated my tinder. Bitches love Harambe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 01:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 01:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually didn't know it was possible to get 14 down votes on Reddit. I'm kind of proud of myself at this point 
*or that it was possible to get 112 but whatever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 23:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Canadians get pissed at Harold Reynolds for saying they didn't grow up playing baseball and then something good happens at a baseball game so they celebrate like it's hockey. Smh someone needs to control those Canadian fuckers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 23:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit I hope everyone in Australia is okay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 19:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darkest spots are in northeastern Arizona and Southwest South Dakota. Looks like the gov is still committed to making Native Americans suffer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 19:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk if I would agree with that assessment but I would def say that he is still a Khan-man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The honors dorm @ KU is making sure that even though Harambe is dead, the revolution shall live on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 18:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 07:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's hot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Is the world flat?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 02:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just got on an elevator with a Cardinals fan and she said my royals shirt was ugly. She leaves, and I tell her "so long 'Best Fan in Baseball.' Of course she takes it as a compliment. smh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 00:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If we don't stop them that means we're going to have lesbians growing our food which means we'll all catch the gay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 15:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 02:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Why is there a naked secretary in front of me?"

"Oh, sorry Mr. President, we had it set to 'Bill Clinton mode.'" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 19:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Harambe supported Cruz because he is so in with the family, does that mean Harambe may have been our only true source that could tell us whether or not Ted Cruz was the zodiac killer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 19:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> where does ted cruz's father fit into this story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> kasich did 5/28 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 17:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> harambe's death was perpetrated by people within our own government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 17:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that Cincinnati Zoo has deleted their twitter, I think it best to turn our Twitter attention to Gladys Porter zoo, the zoo that transferred Harambe in 2014. They enabled the killers. Had they not transferred him, he would still be alive today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 10:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> zoo fuel can't melt steel gorillas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 19:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> the cincinnati zoo made money off of the Harambe war </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 16:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I'm just a kid on that floor and he was asking us what we wanted him to ask and I knew there were some good ones out there on the internet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would be the most awkward questions for a dorm RA to ask in a get-to-know-you interview? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My RA needs suggestion for questions in the get-to-know-you interviews and I want to make them as awkward as possible: any suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 05:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 23:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TOYOTA TRIED TO WARN US BUT NONE OF US LISTENED AND NOW ITS ACTUALLY HAPPENING </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WHEN WILL IT STOP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 23:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would've just randomly abducted a different gorilla then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had the opportunity to save Harambe, would you save him or would you let him die so that the concept of Harambe could live on forever? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 03:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had the opportunity to save Harambe, would you, or would you let him die so that the meme of Harambe could live on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 01:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 22:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost my virginity to this album yesterday. The best part is: the sex lasted the duration of entire fucking album </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just had sex for the entire duration of the blond album. I felt the urge to cry at the end, but I'm fairly certain it was just cuz that album is so fuckin beautiful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 09:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 21:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Killing innocent gorillas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 19:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk who this candidate is, but 'undecided' is beating Trump nationally among voters under the age of 25 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 04:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My father dropped out of high school halfway through his junior year after getting a girl pregnant. He began working two, three jobs, ended up getting divorced. He tried going to college at a for profit school, but ran out of money. Sure enough, his first real career was as a store manager at QuikTrip, and he kept climbing stores. He started from the bottom of the totem pole, so he had people be beaten down in his parking lots, and experienced quite a few scary moments. He was never robbed, but he had his stores robbed twice. Once with a stick, once with an uzi. However, despite working in this rough setting, he was able to start programming while working there back in the 80's, and learned to be thrifty with computers as the industry popped up. He came on as tech support in a few jobs, and after gaining experience, he moved to a lower level manager, and then a mid-level manager, and now he is CIO at a 200 person company, which is basically head of IT and a few other departments. It was truly 10 years of 70 hour work-weeks, complimented by the luck of an industry popping up around him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 04:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without a doubt, jerking off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 04:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought my car was stolen and then I hit the panic button and the car was 15 feet from me and scared the shit out of me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 04:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't ever go to the Cincinnati Zoo. Ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone who thinks a Green Party candidate should be in the debate cycle, just watch this laughable display of debate skills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 00:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 23:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the Suns season is basically already over but you can still make a change by changing the Suns gorilla's name to Harambe https://www.change.org/p/ryan-mcdonough-change-the- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Petition: Change the Suns Gorilla's name to Harambe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 22:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rex Hudler is talking about how high school players are harder to predict than college players. Is he supporting sabermetrics? WE ARE THE ROYALS. SABERMETRICS ARE THE DEVIL. WE WANT ANSWERS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 00:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You're beautiful" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 05:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people called him a monster, some called him a beautiful beast, and some called him a distant relative. What I called him? Food. 

The obsession began in the 1980's. I had always been poor, raised in a single parent household after my father died, but after taking advantage of a market inefficiency during the energy crisis of the late 1970's, I became very wealthy.  With the ridiculous sum of wealth, I retired immediately, and began to find ways to entertain myself. After experimenting for a time, I joined a posh country club, met a few friends, and after a time we got very comfortable with each other. We were all rich, and we were all bored with the mundane life of the bourgeoisie, so at the suggestion of one of the friends, we decided to go big game hunting in Africa. He had already planned his dream hunt, so we followed his lead.

It was the spring of 1986 when we landed in Brazzaville, the capital of Congo, and we were eager to assert our dominance over the most powerful mammals in the world. I did not know much about hunting at that point in time, but when I learned we were going to the Congo, I was fairly surprised, for the lack of true big game throughout African jungles. I voiced my concerns to the friend who had planned it all, Reginald, but he said there was a surprise he had up his sleeve.

It was the first day, and off we went into the Congo jungle, looking for the prey that was unbeknownst to me. I was initially shocked to find the lack of necessary documentation, such as tags and such, but the guide assured us that the Congo government used an honors system, one that trusted citizens to use their own judgment. 

After just a day, we came upon a Silver-backed Gorilla. I was in awe of the beautiful creature, sitting in the sunny opening, grazing on the dense foliage. It was truly a picturesque sight, until it was violently interrupted by the report of the .50 caliber hunting rifle, and then the thud of the formerly majestic gorilla.

"What the fuck was that?" I frustratedly screamed, knowing the extreme consequences of killing such a protected animal.

"This is real hunting my friend," answered the guide, in broken English, as both he and Reginald maniacally grinned. Shocked, I went back to the tent, puked, and sat by myself, pondering me the events that had just unfolded.

Approximately two hours later however, the group came back, dragging the gorilla. Before the entire group had even let go of the fallen beast, the guide pulled a knife out of his pocket, and lunged for the gorilla's chest. After a minute of crude surgery, he pulled out the still warm heart of the beast.

"In our country, we take a bite of the warm heart of the first kill. Our ancestors have done it for thousands of years, and now it is your turn."

I still had a little bit left in the tank, so I turned, puked again at the suggestion of this appalling savagery, but after hotline hostile badgering, I was forced to take a bit out of the half eaten heart. 

Flies buzzed, and as I sank my teeth into the heart, the blood smeared onto my face. However, instead of the expected gag, the taste was glorious. Truly, it was my heroin. I took another bite, and then another, until Reginald peeled the piece away from me. I realized the savagery I had just indulged in, wiped my face off apologized, and went back to my tent.

As I fell asleep, I knew how hollow the apology truly was. I was addicted to the taste, to the thrill, to the concept of it all. I was a man, but for this glorious moment, I was one happy savage.

The gluttonous happiness quickly faded, as that was the only glimpse of a gorilla we got for the rest of the trip. The taste of the blood lingered even as I boarded the flight back to the states, and I realized that I would be back, and very soon and often. 

Sure enough, I was back every year for the next 13 years. The taste, the hunt, it was all exhilarating, and no law made by the hand of man could keep me back from my addiction. 

Just as I was planning my 2000 trip, the 15th anniversary of the original tasting, I was caught in the .com bust. Every major asset I held was in some way tied to it, so I lost everything I had. I stayed with Reginald for a time, and some of the others from the original crew, but because I had lost my money, I was no longer interesting to them.

Thus, I was left poor, lonely, and struggling with an unsustainable addiction. I had burned through the last of my riches, and after nearly ending up in the street, I realized it was necessary to get a job. 

After seeing a flyer, and with my addiction in mind, I decided to apply to the Cincinnati zoo. I knew it would be dangerous considering my past experiences, but the crave of gorilla gave me the perturbed concept that I would get an opportunity to strike and succeed in my quest to eat once again.

15 years of miserable work in the primate section of the zoo left me cold, desperate, and hungry to strike. Thus came the fateful day of May 28, 2016.

After feeding the gorilla in the exhibit, I was walking around the viewing area of the closure, when I experienced a seemingly spoiled, bratty child nagging his mother. He couldn't have been but 5 years old, but was continually begging for attention while his mother took care of his siblings, but after a few unfruitful attempts, he finally ran off to view the gorilla.

He was dangerously hanging over the edge of the enclosure, with both of his feet even leaving the ground multiple times as he hung onto the single restraining bar. As he precariously balanced on the bar, I saw my opportunity to strike, so I gave him a helping shove.

The screams followed. There were many, but because I was he closest zoo staffer, I was quickly alerted of the accident and was forced into action. The gorilla, Harambe, was easily spooked, and after hearing the screams, took the child into her protective custody, dragging him around the enclosure. Knowing the procedure for this absolutely unthinkable scenario, I eagerly gathered the gun and returned to the exhibit. 

The time to act was that moment, and after a fearful consensus from all the primate experts, they agreed a tranquilizer would be dangerous for the child, so the killing of the gorilla to save the boy would be necessary. As soon I heard the confirmation of my hopes, I shouldered the rifle, and fired the shot I had fired so many time in my past, one that pierced through the gorilla's skull, killing it immediately.

Everyone was traumatized, but being the professional I was, I realized I needed to distance the body from the scene. There was a crematorium, but that would not be necessary, so in the excitement of the crises, I was able to take the body to my car and leave immediately, knowing I would never come back.

After taking the first bite, I immediately knew the 15 years of work was easily worth it. Harambe was delicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 02:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just do coke instead of drinking it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 08:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was another death. I had never met them, nor did they sound like the kind of person I would hang around. Sure, I felt that twinge of guilt that I could've done something, like  stick up just once for the kid who was bullied throughout elementary, or even reach out to him to console him. But no one does that. That's why I didn't do it.

The speaker, through his tears, was beginning to get rather droll, as I had heard the speech before. If I had to guess, 600 kids in that auditorium were in tears, and the other 300 were on their phones. Needless to say, the hollow guilt got to be too much, so I joined the latter demographic.

The little blue bird greeted me. To be honest, that was what I liked most about Twitter. Every time I opened the app, someone greeted me. Never in my life had someone gone out of there way to talk to me, even just saying hi or such, so I kept going back to Twitter, searching for the implicit approval I had never received in real life.

The problem got worse and worse. After starting my first Twitter account, I saw the stagnation in it, and viewed social media icons with envy. They had what I wanted, they had thousands of people adoring everything they said. Just even the facade of acceptance would satisfy me, just for me to have the impression of being liked once.

Surely, a second Twitter account would solve my problems of unimportance. Besides, personal accounts never get popular. Everyone knows that. With this seeming fact in mind, I started a baseball Twitter account. It seemed real, and it was from the heart, but still no one seemed to like it. So I created another one.

It was a clich account, very similar to Dory as many would've said, but it seemed as if everyone liked that so that's what I wanted to be. It was hollow and practically stole other people's intellectual property, but at this point, I just wanted to achieve happiness, because my pursuit through a social life was not going much better.

After being desperate and going for a girl who was way out of my league, I was no longer the bystander to the vicious ridicule, but instead now I was the victim. Why would I ever do something so stupid? Everyone else seemed to have a point, why would she ever want me? What did I have to offer?  Why would anyone want me? Obviously my real personality did not interest anyone, and apparently my fake, manufactured one hadn't either.

I figured the ridicule would stop, but it didn't. I heard the voices at day, and then after a few weeks, I heard the voices at night too.

"Why would you do something like that? Who do you think you are, Steve Holt?"

"She goes to prom with star athletes not losers."

"I gotta give you credit man, if I were you, I would've killed myself by now."

Sleep became restless: it became impossible to sleep more that two hours at a time for me. My grades, something I had always been able to hold onto in times of vain, began to slip along with my sanity. Those I had always pleased and felt accepted by, my parents, began to turn on me. It was pretty apparent that because I was no longer the successful child I once was, they hated me now. Sure enough, I was searching for their approval now too.

After a restless nights sleep, and a torturous day at school, I was tired. Tired from the pain, tired from the lack of sleep, and tired from all of the expectation I had failed to meet. I simply wanted to sleep, even if it meant more pain, but as I crept quietly into the house, I found my report card taped to my door, with a menacing note from my parents demanding that they call as soon as I get home.

Following an expletive laced rant, followed by dry, emotionless responses from yours truly, I was told to take a hard look in the mirror and find out what I was made of. So I did.

As I slinked into the bathroom, I stared at myself for a good couple minutes, questioning life's meaning, and questioning where my place was in it. I looked down, shut my eyes, tried to block out the voices, but as always, I failed. When I opened my eyes however, the first thing I saw was the shining glint of the razor, beckoning me to find out what I was made of.

Turns out I was made of hollow pain, and a lot of blood.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> harambe put the rill in gorilla </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 08:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt a twinge of pain on a sunny afternoon, and I had no idea what had come of me. As I was still young and nave, I simply dismissed it as a growing pain, one of many in my growth and progress to adulthood. However, looking back, it was the first time I had ever felt it, and to this date it has been the only time I have felt it.

It wasn't a sharp pain, it was simply a pain in the darkest depths of my body; one so deep I could not locate it, but one that reverberated hopelessness throughout my entire being. I even remember the exact time it happened it was such a harrowing pain, one that interrupted my late May afternoon, one that had been previously filled with with joy.

That joy, just as all of my hope in life, quickly faded away as I began to feel an inalienable loneliness put my psyche into a stranglehold. I had never had a partner, even a girlfriend for the slightest minute, yet it felt like my wife of 50 years had died. Even though I had always been alone, this mysterious presence had been with me. Of course, until that fateful May afternoon.

The loneliness turned into depression, and after a low point coming in the form of unbridled tears behind a locked door, I was convinced to seek help. I saw a therapist, and while I struggled to voice my loss of a divine partner, it became apparent to all those sitting around me that I was borderline clinically insane.

Sure enough, I was prescribed the modern fix to most all problems, yet as I took the mountain of pills each day, I did not feel a reduction in the loneliness, but instead just a hollow numbness. It did alleviate the mental pain some, yet the underlying crevasse that had divided my life continued to grow.

It was just two months later, in late July, after all of the counseling, the pills, the pain, the lonely suffering, the calls to the psychiatrist, the sleepless nights, is when it came to an end. It was not by my own decision, but instead just a twist of fate, as if my life blew about in the breeze, tossed around by the current of the world around me. 

Driving southbound, the truck driver chose an ill tie me to text, and as I waited within the confines of the median to merge into oncoming traffic, the wheel of the truck slowly drifted into my direction. With 40 tons of weight behind it, I was dead on impact, but it made no difference to me, as life had been over for weeks already. 

However, for the first time in almost 2 months, the dull pain seceded. The hollowness was replaced by wholesomeness, and all else that was twisted in my sick, deranged mind was seemingly mended as I drifted towards the white light. I found myself with an overwhelmingly large presence, one that took away the loneliness, as I truly knew it was the one I had lost in law may. As I turned to see the one whose loss had caused me so much pain, I looked into its large, brown eyes, it's overly hairy faced, only to realize I was not staring into the face of any divine being, but instead Harambe, who had found work as God's messenger from the world to the Pearly Gates. As I turned to him, he embraced me with the warmest hug I had ever felt, and at that moment, I knew that he was the best friend I never had, but I needed ever so dearly. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 18:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I've taken from this post is that this ad is proof that Hitler faked his death in the bunker in Berlin and snuck into America and lived here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Mock Trial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 05:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
