<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3535</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 10:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, you're right in regards to the boots on the ground thing. I just hope Activision doesn't toss IW to the wayside. There was a lot of good stuff in there that I think warrants a sequel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 07:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has Activision said anything about making another Infinite Warfare? I hope they realize they had a pretty good game on their hands and would be willing to try again in few years, after the "we want to go back to the boots of the ground" hype dies down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [COD] Why Should COD go back to WWII </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 07:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 07:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually hoping for a return to a modern day setting. I think COD is getting progressively better at telling stories in their campaigns and I would want COD to try their hand at telling a story in the vain of  Medal Of Honor:Warfighter, but obviously much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion, the campaign doesn't get enough recognition or praise. Although, it defiantly had its plot holes and flaws, I really found myself attached to the characters, the missions, both primary and side missions, were really fun and tried have some deeper commentary with discussions about the nature of leadership. Overall, I would say its been one of the better campaigns out of the recent COD releases. 

Another aspect of IW that shined was the, for lack of a better term, military aspect. The military consultants were the MVPs of the dev team because of how well they were able to implement actual naval terminology and military shorthand into the dialog without having it feel forced or hamper the storytelling and make the Retribution feel like a legitimate naval warship only in space.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 08:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did read everything you wrote (twice), and thanks for the great insight. My problem with the don't drink the Kool-Aid bit is that the Kool-Aid would include the lessons about integrity and adhering to the Navy's core values of Honor, Courage, and Commitment. In fact, Xavier uses an example of a candidate lying about a uniform inspection to the instructors, and then coming clean about it as what not to do, yet something like integrity is essential to surviving BUD/S and being a productive member of the teams.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I definitely want to go the Officer route.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info both on the SEAL billet and OCS. Do you know what the odds are for getting a billet for EOD?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that OCS wasn't the greatest from others, but mainly I was referring to the book.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 08:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I wasn't posing a choice so much as I was looking for input about advice I found in a book written by a SEAL officer and OCS grad which basically said, to paraphrase, OCS sucks and you shouldn't really try if you want to be a SEAL. I don't necessarily agree with that, and was looking for input/other points of view. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually got that line from the book "Breaking BUD/S" which was written by a SEAL Officer who graduated from OCS, which was why I wondered if it had any validity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pros and Cons of OCS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now I'm in my second year of college with the intention of applying to OCS with a billet for either Naval Special Warfare or EOD. So far, I've heard varying viewpoints on OCS, with a lot of them saying that OCS is a pointless, stupid process full of fat uninspired candidates and that if you're going in with a SpecWar or EOD billet, then you shouldn't make much of an effort to be a leader or buy into any of the stuff you're taught there. 

Now, maybe its the eternal optimist in me, but I don't think that OCS is as bad as its made out to be, and even if it is, you should make the best effort possible, especially if you have a SpecWar or EOD billet and set an example for your classmates. 

So, what I'm asking is can someone break down the pros and cons of OCS and explain the dos and don'ts as well as what kind of candidate you should strive to be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 10:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what I'm not getting is what counts as big navy bullshit? Is it the ship related stuff a SEAL wouldn't have need for or is it the stuff about the navy's core values? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breaking BUD/S and OCS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently bought the book "Breaking BUD/S" by d.h. xavier a few days ago as a go to guide for the whole BUD/S application process. I'm halfway through and so far its been extremely helpful, detailed, and honest. The only issue I have came when the author discussed surviving OCS. Long story short, according to the Xavier, OCS is a pointless, stupid process worse than hell week full of fat, uninspired candidates and that if you're a candidate with a SpecWar billet, you shouldn't really try to make a an effort to be a leader or buy into any of the stuff you're taught there.

 Now, I haven't been to OCS, so I can't say whether or not what the author says has any sort of validity, but even it is as bad a process as he makes it out to be, wouldn't you still want to perform to the best of your ability and be an example to your classmates, especially if you've got a SpecWar billet? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if I'm intending to go the Officer route but haven't gotten to the point where I can apply for OCS, which is where I would get medical cleared? Do I wait until I can apply for OCS to contact a mentor, or should I do it as soon as possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Benefits of a SEAL mentor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was recently on sealswcc.com and found the email address in order to find the contact info for a local SEAL mentor. Now, I'm a bit of a ways off from applying to to BUD/S and mentors are under no obligation to train you, so what are some of the benefits of knowing your local SEAL mentor, specifically for someone looking to become an officer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the advice. Since you mentioned it, can you discuss the relationship and/or the differences between NSW and big Navy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, I want to say thank you guys for being honest with your responses. Hearing it from guys who have gone through/are going through the process really helps.

Secondly, since it was mentioned that NSW gets O's from the street, the Academy, ROTC, and OCS, what can an OCS guy do to be competitive for SOAS selection when compared to guys from ROTC or the Academy? Would getting in contact with a local SEAL mentor help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 02:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I would think NSW would want O's that have had prior leadership experience more than guys off the street. My biggest concern with just trying out for BUD/S is not being prepared enough. I get that there's no such thing as being 100% prepared for BUD/S, but going into it, I want to be the best I can possibly be, not just for myself, but also for the other students.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Considering going SWO before SEALs. Is this advisable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently in my second year of college with the intention of going the OCS route and eventually getting into BUD/S. However, I'm considering going into Surface Warfare beforehand in order improve on both my leadership abilities and my physical fitness. Is this an better idea than trying to go straight into BUD/S right out of OCS?

Additionally, I'm also looking into the Baccalaureate Degree Completion Program (BDCP), but I haven't been able to turn up recent or in depth information. Can anyone inform me about the specifics of the program or if it even exists anymore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark Meer and Jennifer Hale voice npc's who are having a conversation on the Nexus, you go up to interact with them and they say "excuse me we're having a conversation, do you mind". and as you leave, they say "damn new guys", "I know, right"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And can there be a Kett with two long antennas who's constantly trying to steal that recipe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 02:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. I'll willingly admit that the ST races could be formidable in a space conflict, but its the fact that the Federation, and by extension, Starfleet, aren't in the Business of fighting wars, whereas the ME species have been fighting each other for centuries. Who do you think would win a fight, the guy who took a few self defense classes or the guy whose been fighting professionally since he was a kid. There's also the fact that for the most part Starfleet wouldn't do anything they consider to be unethical or immoral to an enemy, but the ME species don't necessarily have that problem, as you can see with the Genophage, the destruction of the Alpha Relay in Arrival, ect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 01:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never really got into DS9, but if you're talking about the dominion war, then sure that's one example, but look at all the stuff the Romulans managed to to the Federation and get away with in TNG and Voyager (kidnapping Starfleet crew members and using them to assassinate a Klingon govt. official, taking over a ship and killing the entire crew, ect.), or the alternate universe in the TNG episode "Yesterday's Enterprise", where the Klingons have effectively defeated the Federation, or the Enterprise C in that very same episode which was destroyed and its crew were captured by Romulans, or all the times on Voyager where the ship had been taken over or nearly destroyed, or the Equinox from Seasons 5 and 6 of Voyager, which had its entire crew killed by what were essentially space slugs, or all the ships the Borg destroyed in "The Best of both Worlds". Also, the species and groups that have managed to do this to the Federation were primarily Naval forces, and didn't have the ground forces or specialized units like the STG, Asari Commandos, Spectres, or N7s So if Starfleet can barley deal with species that don't have dedicated fighting forces, imagine how they'll fare against ones that do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 01:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see Cerberus being like Waylund-Yutani and attempt to study and weaponize the Xenomorphs, until it blows up in their faces and they send Shepard in to clean up the whole mess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 01:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Cerberus got their hands on Shepard's body, the first organ they replaced was the liver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 00:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure the Enterprise has firepower and like I said, they could probably give the Alliance a run for its money, but when you include the other species and factions, the Federation doesn't last more than a month. What does the Federation do when the Geth introduce viruses into their ship computers, or when the Krogan drop asteroids on Federation planets, or the Batarians start using terror attacks, or the Salarians release plagues that effect Vulcan or Ferengi biology, or Cerberus starts kidnapping and experimenting on Federation citizens, or the Rachni reproduce faster than Starlet can destroy them, or the Quarians start retrofitting Starfleet technology and using it against them? These are the things the Milky Way species have done in war, and Federation has never encountered anyone who does any of this. So while yes, they may have the technological advantage, they've got nothing on the Milky way Species tactically.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Alliance could take on the Federation and if not win, give them a run for their money. My reasoning is that despite the Federation's advanced technology, Starfleet is not a military organization, so they wouldn't be prepared for the strategy and tactics the Alliance would employ, plus they have no ground forces or equivalent to biotics or the N7s. And although the Federation has encountered and fought against militarized species in the Romulans, Klingons and so on, they either win by the skin of their teeth or outright lose (in the TNG episode "Yesterday's enterprise", the Federation is for the most part wiped out by the Klingons)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its the same with Allers in ME3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you thinking of Brooks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The weird shove off is in both ME2 and ME3, mainly when Shep is at a counter and you choose to leave. Another weird interrupt animation is in the beginning of ME3 is when you choose to interrupt James, and he does this 'whatever man' waive at you. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me its the drinking animation. I don't drink, so can anyone tell me if they've seen anyone aggressively shaking their head as if they're a dog that just got sprayed with water after they've downed a glass of something at a bar. 

And the punching animations. When Shepard punches the reporter in ME1, the way he/she swings their arm is both hilarious and nonsensical(it looks like a slap with a closed hand) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Occasionally, that happens too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rather than an Omega like station getting infected by the Necromorphs, I would want to see Omega itself get infected. Imagine a group of Mercs coming back to Omega from a job to raid a base of this mysterious group that's been kidnapping settlers in the Terminus systems and as part of their payment, they decide to bring back this large obelisk that they think is just decoration and intend to sell once they get back. Eventually, they get the back and that obelisk starts to glow, and pretty soon, Omega gets overrun with the necromorph virus with only Afterlife being the last safe refuge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, it was a semi-casual, so only one future weapon per person. We saved the heavy weapons and omni blades for prom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, for as much as people make fun of dancing Shep (and rightfully so), a few of my friends and I tried dancing like Shepard at a school dance, and we actually got complimented on our dancing skills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your least favorite/most humorous character animation in the ME trilogy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What sci-fi property would you want to see crossover into the ME universe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been topic of endless debate between my friends and me, and I wanted to get some outside opinions. Personally, I would like to see the Predator or the Cylons from Battlestar Galactica.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what little we've seen of the Nomad, I think it'll be easier to control. I can't wait for Youtube videos of players drifting or doing donuts in it. 

Fast   Furious: Andromeda Drift </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think we'll see villainous pathfinders, so much as Pathfinders that made difficult choices. Imagine if we found out that one of the Pathfinders destroyed a native village or city in order to gain access to resources their species needs or to defend their settlement against an attack and we have either negotiate a truce Star Trek style or aid our fellow Pathfinder in fighting off the natives. Those kind of morally ambiguous choices are what I hope to find in the game.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there will be. I read somewhere that there are going to be quests where you discover what happened to the other Arks, so at some point you'll probably encounter the other Pathfinders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pathfinders in ME:A </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 23:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the more exciting aspects of the ME:A lore I'm looking forward to exploring is that of the Pathfinders. I think one of the coolest parts of the lore in the original trilogy were the specters but i felt like we never got to learn about or explore that side of the universe beyond a couple of codex entries or meeting a few specters that either immediately die or are killed by us. With the Pathfinders, I hope Bioware give us the opportunity to explore and learn this really cool idea. What ideas for the Pathfinders would you like to see in Andromeda or what aspect of them would you like to explore once Andromeda releases? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gamespot feels like Andromeda is being rushed. Does anyone agree, and if so, why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 22:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got done watching an segment of Gamespot's The Lobby and the topic was wether ME:A was being rushed due to both the March 21 release date and the lack of any kind of extended gameplay footage. In regards to the lack of gameplay, I feel like Bioware is playing it close to the vest in order to give players a feeling of surprise when they first play. As for the release date, they've had their eye on a first quarter 2017 release date for a while now not mention the fact that its been in development for 5 years now.  

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Pb8QJEWCTZc t=230s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 08:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  6. Spectre status 
 7. Tuchanka heat 
 8. Shepard-Commander (produced by Legion) 
 9. Problematic (guest track feat. Mordin) 
10. Vermire (tribute to either Kaiden or Ashley) 
11. Ah, yes, "Reapers" (Council diss track) 


I meant to add on to your list but 6-9 keep changing to 1-4


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pitch a Commander Shepard mixtape </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 04:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other day, I'm going through my 7th ME3 playthrough while listening to Pandora, and after an hour or so, I had a somewhat humorous thought:"What if Commander Shepard made a mixtape?" So I wanted to see if anyone could pitch few track names, a title or anything (I imagine one or two would be diss tracks towards Udina or the council) 

"I'm Commander Shepard and this is the most fire mixtape on the citadel" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 02:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought a show about the merc groups would be a combination of Black Sails and the Sopranos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 21:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Miami Vice had neon colored suits, so I assume there will be neon colored armor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pitch a TV series based in the Mass Effect universe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been getting into and watching a lot of discussion regarding the constant failures of video game movies in the wake of Assassin's Creed's release. I believe that one of the problems is the that a lot of video game stories and universes don't work when reworked and compressed into hour and a half or two hour runtimes, and that long form storytelling would work for a lot of these properties, which leads into my question: If a major TV network or streaming service got the rights to make a show in the ME universe, where/ when would it be set, who would it follow, and what network or service would you like to see it on? A few of my ideas are: 

1. A show about the Terminus Systems mercenary groups (Blood Pack, Blue Sons, Eclipse) set before and maybe a little after ME2. I think there's a lot left to explore in that part of the ME universe, and I can see it exploring the cultures of the groups, their role on Omega and their interactions with Aria and their rivalries with one another. 

2. A show focusing on Cerberus. It would have to be pre ME3, but  I could see it having a vibe similar to shows like Homeland or 24, where you focus on one agent and the various missions he/or she takes. It would also allow us to further explore the shadowy covert side of the ME universe  

3. A show focusing on Anderson. I can see it beginning right after the First Contact War, and have it show what led to his nomination for the Spectres, the events of the book Revelations, and eventually him becoming the first captain of the Normandy. It would also allow us to see the beginnings of the ME universe as we know it. We could see the origins of human biotics, the start of groups like Cerberus and the Terra Firma party, humanity learning to integrate itself into the larger galactic community, the start of hostilities between humans and batarians, etc. 

As for networks, I would like to see it on either HBO or Netflix.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 06:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough point, but I still would have liked to have seen a good balance between covert missions to find the catalyst and major planet wide battles. I think games like Halo: Reach had a good balance where in some missions you were conducting recon at night and others where you were fighting in cities that were getting glassed by the Covenant. 

On a somewhat humorous side note, did Shepard punch some Alliance admiral in the face before the trilogy, because after three games of becoming the first human Spectre and saving the galaxy numerous times, he (or she) still hasn't gotten promoted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 02:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough point, but even SOF units see front line combat at some point. But its not just in regards to missions (I'll get to that later), but also in other aspects of the overall game, such as: 

1. The aesthetics: I know that gritty and dirty visuals aren't the Mass Effect style, but I felt like in a war against an armada of nigh indestructible machines who take over entire star systems at a time, there should have been more, for lack of a better term, grime in ME3's visuals. Say what you will about the overall movie, but I think Rogue One did a good job of showing how dirty (literally) war can be with things like dirt on weapons and armor, vehicles that look scuffed and scratched and dented from use and constant battles. I think it would have fit in more with the story of ME3 than the usual clean and shiny visuals of the series. 

2. The missions: Referring to my point at the beginning, even if the crew of the Normandy are considered to be a Special Operations team, even they would see some frontline combat at some point in the war, especially since Shepard is the most knowledgeable person in the galaxy in regards to the Reapers. The thing is that I just felt like we didn't see or participate in enough of those major battles occurring throughout the galaxy to really feel like I was in this  conflict. I wish we could have gotten more things like the final battle in London, or the fall of Thessia or the opening in Vancouver. This could could have also been done by adding more variety to those side missions Hackett gives you. Imagine doing stuff like rescuing downed pilots, infiltrating Cerberus ships to steal intel, calling in airstrikes on enemy positions, stuff that a Special Operations team would do in a real war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Mass Effect 3 feel like a proper war story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 22:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently on my 7th or so play through of ME3, and something that I realized during the first hour or so is that I don't think ME3 tells a very good war story. What do you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 05:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like the idea of making the conflict between the Alliance and the Batarians a central part of the trilogy, but what I would is make the "Bring down the sky" DLC an actual side quest in ME 1 and the outcome of that, either stopping the Batarians who hijacked the asteroid or your failure to do so, would result in increased tensions going into ME2.  

In terms of Cerberus, I would either go with a version of the original concept for them introduced in ME1 where they're a secret division of Alliance Intelligence tasked with preventing another event like the First Contact War and making sure Humanity stays influential in galactic politics, or they're a Private Military Contractor ran by TIM, who was a former N7 soldier and First Contact War veteran (I realize in ME canon, Anderson was the First N7 recruit, but I would rewrite it so that he was one of the first) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 00:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although I agree that overall role of Cerberus in ME3 made no sense, one aspect that I thought had potential was the idea that some members were defecting to join the Alliance. I think rather than turn Cerberus into a bargain bin version of the Empire from Star Wars, they should have run with that idea and turned it into a full fledged civil war between those who agree with the 'humanity first at all costs' mentality (led by the Illusive Man) and those who became disillusioned with the lengths TIM is willing to go to achieve his goals, such as attempting to use the Collector base (probably led by Miranda and/or Jacob) and depending on whose side you agree with, you aid them in various side missions (an example would be during the side mission to retrieve the Ex-Cerberus scientists, you either help them escape and join the Alliance, or transmit their location to TIM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could rewrite any part of the Mass Effect story/lore, what would it be and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 23:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you could rewrite any part of the Mass Effect trilogy or the lore (characters, organizations, events in and out of the games) what would you rewrite it as, and why?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
