<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3428</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 10:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember reading your comments back when I was more of a lurker on this sub.  Your salt drove my hatred. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 23:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That battle made me the saltiest man alive. I spent years in the comment section of that video.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 06:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In that movie he travels to all the houses by going through mirrors. Mirror Master anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 06:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After that fight I became the saltiest man alive.  I am Salt Man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 22:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here it is](https://www.reddit.com/r/whowouldwin/comments/2v3z11/death_battle_40_gaara_vs_toph/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 21:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 19:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Toph IS THE GREATEST EARTHBENDER OF ALL TIME!!!!!!!!!^/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 19:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know of your good work on the Gaara vs Toph post sir.  RIP in pepperonis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 19:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They keep mentioning speed and durability at the end of these last couple of death battles, and I am like where was that during Gaara vs. Toph. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the Zoom crashing the party idea. :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 07:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Loses to someone way less powerful than Superman) "I am just as good of a hero as him." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 06:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please no.  The show is actually pretty bad, and the characters(at least for me) are annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 21:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree. By the end of the first episode of the Flash I was hooked, but I just cannot get into this show. I had big expectations for this show, but it seems to be falling flat on all fronts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 03:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again plot induced stupidity. Why people with guns always walk right up to the main character so they can grab the gun, why villains fight the hero one at a time, why people always miss/ never shoot there guns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 00:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was purely plot induced stupidity. Fighting skills don't matter when you have super speed in less you are fighting someone of equal speed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 08:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cloud and Sephiroth are from Final Fantasy 7 which has never been on a nintendo console. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 23:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because the writers don't know how superspeed and fighting work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 19:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wouldn't matter if he knew how to fight, Zoom is just so much faster than him. If it looks like Barry is moving in slow motion to Zoom, Barry couldn't hit him. This was a big problem in Flash vs Arrow because it showed Arrow moving in slow motion, so there was really no way(no matter how much martial arts training Arrow had) for Arrow to hit Barry.  If you saw DoFP Quicksilver just tapped people at super speed for them to go flying, because speed Force equals Mass times Acceleration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 03:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone explain why(in the story) Superman doesn't talk to Supergirl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 08:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh a fellow speedster, your smart, but your not that smart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 20:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am pretty sure she is only other hero besides Superman, because they haven't referenced the Justice League or any other characters. It also doesn't take place in the Flash/Arrow universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 08:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure Superman is the only hero because Kara says "There isn't just one hero anymore".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 08:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say Flash. I like sci-fi powers and Earth 2 more than Oliver back on the island. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 19:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good old ATBP. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 05:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya but that is time travel. They can both time travel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 01:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does take the doctor time to turn his dials and what not. It also takes a few seconds for the tardis to dissapear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 22:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did say everyone and everything would be destroyed in Goku and Beerus' attack, which includes them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 22:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They explained that the shockwaves became more powerful the further away they went. It only knocked people down on earth soooooo... I don't know how that makes any sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 22:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can physics be real if our eyes aren't real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 22:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "angle of the punch" excuse for why there are no longer shockwaves when they punch is still funny and makes no sense.  Like how would matching the angle of a punch cancel a universe busting attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 22:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would also say Superman would win if he was bloodlusted.  Even with Goku's new universal feat he is slower and less durable(they said the shockwaves from their punches were the weakest at the point of origin). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 22:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's about his only "feat". No new durability, speed, or reaction speed feats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 22:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there is no time travel shenanigans than I say Flash. IIRC he beat a teleporter in a race, but I don't know if he absorbed the speed from everyone on earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 22:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya that never happens. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 22:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In episode 12 many characters believe his clash with Beerus will destroy the universe. The shock waves from their clash destroy a planet pretty far away, but that is all the destruction adds up to before they stop the shock waves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goku vs. Superman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 22:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since Goku has gotten more feats from Dragon Ball Super, how do you think he would fair against Post Crisis Superman?

Round 1: In-character

Round 2: Bloodlusted

[Goku respect thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/respectthreads/comments/28um3t/respect_son_gokuu_dragonball/)

[Superman respect thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/respectthreads/comments/2a9uba/respect_superman/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 22:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Viktor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 20:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll rek some kids. Name is Glorious Waldo Phoenix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 22:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 20:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the worst video game you have ever played.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
