<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3788</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 13:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am pretty sure you can return your loan funds within a specified time and avoid any interest and fees. Obviously this is not concrete info, I apologize for that. You are the captain of your own life-don't be afraid to choose a different course then what is laid before you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 12:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am getting my Brokers License and will begin selling homes/commercial real estate. I have struggled with what to do post-bar and don't have that much legal experience. Regardless, I set up my loan repayment and got instantly angry; I am not willing to do just about anything to get this shit paid! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 12:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go check out Dave Ramsey on Youtube. You literally are at the most important point in your life and don't even know it. PM me if you want to talk about the idea of law school, careers, and student loans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 22:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I drove 1h to school. I would suggest getting a 40gal tub and put it in your trunk. This way you can keep all of you law school materials all in one safe spot; I swear by this. I kept everything I needed in my tub and it was perfect from 1L to the Bar Exam!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 18:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I know quite a lot about how tax law works, but your right I don't have the time to waste figuring it out. Thank you for your input.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 16:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the honest response. I agree with you entirely, with any type of business scaling is a big part of success. I do have a lot of drive and I feel as if I'm stuck at a point right now to determine what to do. I have a handful of mentors that I have talked with on their starting story, but they are all so different with very little overlap. I know I can take bite of each and create my own, but I feel that inevitably it's just going to be a learning experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 15:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know and understand this. How do you use your network when it comes time to? Do you say "Hey I have a guy for that!" Then because your client is already infront of you they are more inclined to seek "your guy" what their needs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 23:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was a diamond. haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 22:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did and it did not scratch the surface of the stone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 21:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! What about the one with the like rock growth inside it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 21:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see. That is perfect idea actually. Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 21:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That came about 6 months too late!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 20:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh for sure. How would you suggest networking? I was going to join the local Bar Association and a BMI Group.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Check Out My Rock Collection! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 20:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [My Rock Collection] (http://imgur.com/a/VzTft)

I have been collection for well over twenty years. My parents bought rocks to surround our house as landscaping. I have clocked thousands of hours out digging for my next find. I love rocks, and everywhere I go, I ALWAYS bring a handful of rocks with me!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 20:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I have not done anything yet, still plotting out the business plan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 20:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok perfect thank you for that site. Good idea on the sub s, I can see how that would be beneficial.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 20:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I was wondering about a few other things as well. I love real property law and I want to get my brokers license. I have a buddy who want to create a business to flip houses. Also, I was thinking about opening a property management business. I understand this will take a added level of conflict of interest and keeping the lines clear-what do you think? I focused on Business Transactions and Formation, Real Property, Bankruptcy, and Estate Planning in law school; I also have a bachelors degree in criminal justice. I just feel like I have so many areas of practice I could offer to a potential client, is that normal? or am I over-shooting?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Check out my Rock Collection, help me identify what type of rock they are! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 20:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [My Rock Collection] (http://imgur.com/a/VzTft)

I have been collection for well over twenty years. My parents bought rocks to surround our house as landscaping. I have clocked thousands of hours out digging for my next find. I love rocks, and everywhere I go, I ALWAYS bring a handful of rocks with me!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 19:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect! My Wife's cousin actually just graduated with a Masters in Accounting and is obtaining his licenses now. Would it be wise to open a business with him? Me and him are super close so there wouldn't be any BS; its at the point where I could ask him and he would say yes. I think it is a smart move.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 18:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took Themis as a commercial course to prepare for the July 2016 Bar Exam; the course was $1500. I paid out of pocket for it and it is not attached to my student loans.Therefore, I would argue that as a supplement to obtaining licensing by the state, I had to purchase it as a business expense. Check this deduction out. Basically if you create a business, there are certain exceptions that you can write off if you meet the requirements. I am going to write everything off: Costs, Telephone Plan, Printer, Supplies, etc. [Outline of Start Up Business Deductions](https://www.sba.gov/blogs/startup-cost-tax-deductions-how-write-expense-starting-your-business) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 13:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am having the same issue. My last name is "Cochrane" and there is a "Cochran Law" in my state and their services touch my region; but, they do not practice any of the same areas as I would. Also, they are very niche in what they offer. Not sure what to name it either. Always thought of Cochrane Law, but I don't want potential clients getting confused about the "E" on Cochrane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 13:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just scanned the Attorneys near me and I am not a fan of the search system honestly. I feel as though the "younger" Attorneys were in the last few pages...right next to the "Disciplined" attorneys. I don't see the value.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Start Up Business Deductions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 12:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, I am a recent graduate and just sat for the July Bar. I am gearing up to open an office in a rural/rapidly expanding area with very little competition. I am curious if anyone had written off the costs associated with sitting for the bar? I know your not permitted to write off your student loan debt, but since I would be "starting up" a business, I would like to write off the costs of my commercial course as part of the $50,000 start up costs. Also, is it important to know a reliable CPA? Thanks in advance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 02:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took Sales the term before I studied for the Bar Exam and LOVED it. I was so thankful I took it before the exam. We covered Contracts 1+2 and ran through Article 2, 3, and 4 of the UCC. I glazed over the "Advanced Sales" section of my bar review because it was so fresh in my mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 15:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is...your an Engineer, your capable of putting yourself in a position you know you can work in and learn. There is always a way to fix something, it just depends on how you look at it. I have my JD, just sat for the July Bar, and I want to go back and get dual Engineering Degree. The cool thing about being an attorney, its obvious, but the more you know the more you can call your gross income. Plus, you become extremely valuable because of your education. I am 27, and even if it takes me 20 years to get all that schooling, I would be 47 with plenty of time to reap the benefits. You can do anything you want to honestly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 15:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It Depends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 19:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I graduated with an Engineer who went into IP. He was roughly 50-55 and had been an Engineer for wel over 20 years; he just wanted something new and that extra security that comes with the added title. That being said...do what's right for you. Your goals, finances, etc. Make sure you have everything in line. You could also find an IP firm near you and possibly work for them to get a feel for what they/job would have to offer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 19:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you have a claim for IIED.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 19:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would piggyback of this. You have to want to be an Attorney, and you have to like your current position-you just want to mash them together to create a super career.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 19:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to be a dick, but genuinely help, sentence format and writing skills is big. Learning how to write like an Attorney is HUGE. Don't be afraid to be you and join in on some type of Moot Court or Editorial Staff to work your way up throughout law school. Don't be afraid to be wrong; so long as there is a good faith valued argument-you are generally never wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took a Federal Adminstrative Law class in Law School. I did find it interesting it was a pre-requisite for an Energy Law class I wanted to take. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 19:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Handwriting is scientifically better for memorization. I wrote all my notes out for the Bar Exam and went through 24 pens in 3 months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 19:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you just sparked an interest for me...I am from Michigan and there are a few firms in my area that practice this type of law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 18:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did like Themis, but I will piggyback off this response to wait and make a definite conclusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 06:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude id love a farm especially because all these contracting multiple choices are always about buying wheat or corn in installments lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 06:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude soo lazy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 19:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pre-ordered mine on Amazon, don't have the physical copy yet. I figured I read all the other ones growing up, might as well read this one as well; should be interesting. Haha it is better than what I have been reading the past 3.5 yrs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 16:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That new book comes out this weekend I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 02:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it really depends on what words you used, so...It depends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 16:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, its just not worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 15:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is strict liability;like GG, game over son. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 15:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just caught a Pinsur at 433 got his ass! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 15:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure he/she probably zoned out,ost their capacity, and just was having their eyes wonder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 15:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already have 3 new apps on my IPhone. Haha I'm back world! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 15:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's insanity. Honestly I don't get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 15:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea. Glad that is over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 14:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My head was down, but rumor has it, some kid got escorted out by three Proctors for cheating. He just picked his application for Starbucks up today! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 13:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAHA, dude same thought! My wife goes to work early and I used to get up with her and start studying from 6-8pm when she got home; I had nothing to do this morning! I was lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 12:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is MICHIGAN...should be interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 12:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all are, even if we say were not. Have faith you have done what needs to be done, that is all you can do at this point. Just keep refreshing on the things you feel you don't know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 00:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh..shh don't tell me that now. haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 13:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am at the same point. We should all take it easy, you know if you have been doing work; I just feel like I have so much in my head I can't pinpoint it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 13:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 03:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will just throw my extra ear plugs in my nose holes...next issue please. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 03:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scenario 1: Person next to you blows chunks......You say nothing and just keep typing as you glance over; thinking to yourself, "damn was that hearsay or non-hearsay, shi...oh yeah non-hearsay..."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 03:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could that go to Common Plan as well?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 03:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MI rules state you cannot remove your laptop from your seat until all 6 hours are up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 15:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a Goldmine...jeez glad I went down that rabbit hole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 14:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't take this exam...ATTACK IT! Good luck to everyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 14:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For HS Exceptions where the Declarant is Unavailable, you have "Admission of Party Opponent"-that is Non-HS; it should be Statement Against Interest for Unavailable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 14:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best advice I have heard so far: Pause, don't just jump into a question thinking it is one thing; pause. Let the facts and call filter through your brain, let your brain pick it apart. You can save a lot of time and headache if you PAUSE and FILTER what is asked of you. Also, if you don't know what is asked, just write something down; the graders cannot give you points for a blank page.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 00:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: Back to studying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 00:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, dude-we totally grew up in the same era! haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 00:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bhahaha! Your brain needed it! It just shut down on itself and tricked your body into going to sleep to restart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 21:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really just want to fall asleep. I have hit a wall and it is disturbing me, badly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 19:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think they themselves understand the law...or they just don't know how to read.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 18:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, bingo! That exactly where I was going in my head, even if it was worded poorly, you got it. All I would need is some Actual Implied Authority and a house in the middle of the Amazon with a nice fishin' hole near by...I would be content.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 18:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 points for Gryffindor!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 18:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GREAT defenses! Ok, plot twist. What if the tribe formed a proper corporation and elected the tribe elders to the board of directors. Then, each member of the tribe has disposed of their interest in the AP'd land to the corporation. The Corporation's Board of Directors takes the interests in exchange for shares in the corporation. The board then gave me a quitclaim deed to hold in trust as their Trustee for the benefit of the shareholders of the Corporation. As Trustee I have sole discretion on making distributions to the shareholders of any profits made in connection to the property, and the trust also includes a spendthrift provision. What now?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a good trick, try and tie your interest with something they are focused on; I did this for my position. I went through the first website and basically took key taglines they used on different pages and incorporated them into my cover letter; got a call back three days after submitting it. It puts them in a frame of thought that you are not going to need coaching to jump on the bandwagon; your already on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh...well they would just throw me a quick quitclaim deed...I will throw them some banana tree seeds ("value" in South America) and now I am a Bona Fide Purchaser for Value. Boom, I will just tack their time and seek quite title for myself. haha-now were in business! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 17:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True..true..BUT, what if it wasn't? lol WHAT IF, they forgot to write that into the legislation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is key! After our wedding, my wife and I woke up late to leave for the airport; literally we were SO glad we packed a few days before and were the last ones walking onto the plane! I would NOT want to feel that feeling for this thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same plan, except I watch Lincoln Lawyer before I take exams. I will be thoroughly enjoying multiple slices of pizza while I read everything I have written out and/or typed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 16:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just find an indigenous tribe and be their "God." Bring a Black's Law Dictionary and teach them all the law. Assuming (and hoping) South America follows US Property Law, stake a claim for Adverse Possession over all the property they have used for the past x years (insert statutory period). Then, once you have obtained marketable title, use the land to mine for "Jungle Gold" and other fantastic ventures...so you can pay off your student loan debt. lmao I need to take this thing and END THIS MADNESS!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 13:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Focus on writing essays. That will help you study and bring together the law. Plus, the essay answers are a blank page if you don't will it up, where the MBE gives you the answer you just have to use some dedicated focus to deduct to the correct one. You still got time just focus on your worst topics and go from there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 13:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have posted this before, but I am sure it got lost on here. Here is something, if not everything you should know, for A3. You have to think of it...in order: (1) Do you have a Negotiable Instrument? (2) If you have a Neg Inst, was the Neg Inst Negotiated? Key is number (3) The party who the Note/Draft (Promissory Note/Check) was negotiated to, are they a Holder in Due Course (Bona Fide Purchaser for Value)? From there it just depends on the issue. Watch for the shelter rule, endorsement issues, good faith issues, if you want to go deeper you can learn the Real and Personal Defenses, and possibly accommodation party liability/underlying liability for the Maker/Drawer/Drawee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 13:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the neighbor could sue the landlord to enforce the covenant. First you have to go through an analysis to see what they were suing for (Damages/Injunction), depending on that you would then go through Covenant/Equitable Servitude to see it the LL is bound. Then if LL is bound, T2 is committing waste (you could argue all 3 types, I would). Where T1 subleases to T2, there is essentially a new contract, T2 is the tenant of T1. T2 would be in privity of contract and privity of estate with T1. The LL can enforce the covenant through T1 because T1 is still in privity of contract with LL. Even if T1 assigned the lease to T2, who also assumed all the duties T1 was obligated to perform per the OG contract with LL, absent a novation in favor of T1, T1 would still be liable under the contract for T2's failure to perform the assumed obligations and the waste they committed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 13:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. Sometimes you forget, it is easy to get swept up on the struggle, this is spot on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 02:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ratification. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 23:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just read an outline for your worst in the morning, do your stuff, then read another outline before you go to bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 23:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't want to see the first essay and be like "FUCK should have STUDIED THAT!!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 22:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your gonna do find, just stop doing MBE stuff and focus on your worst essay topics. Just like with the MBE, the more you do the better you will become; you got this man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 21:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha..true that! Great point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 20:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right there with you, I can tell I am slowing down. I am really struggling on getting anything new done, and I am having trouble refining what I do know. FCUK! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 17:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear Themis, I am not doing 8% each day until the exam; I "Flex-Studied."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 01:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EXACTLY!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 00:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought a new computer for this exact reason. Luckily it was your power cord, I am still getting used to this new keyboard. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 00:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as am I. Don't think about "peaking" the information is in your brain somewhere. Your body will drop in all the adrenaline it has when you take the test and your going to find shit in your brain you didn't even know was there.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 00:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Disclaimer: Not Bragging or anything, only trying to help* I go to bed at 930-10pm max. I get up at 6am and start my studying by 7. It is a mind over matter kinda of thing where your body is tricked into working longer because its light out; my dad used to do it in Alaska when they had 12hr of light/dark. It has helped me pull longer hours for the past 3 months. You have to go to bed early though, that is the key.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 21:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 19:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, there is also a timer you can enable. There is no 20 min set, but I set mine for 10 min intervals; that way I can keep on some type of pace. I don't know how annoying it will be, but you hit that first 10 min mark you know its hustle time for the remaining 10.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 19:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 14/21. For #10 where is that law? Obviously Civ Pro, but I cannot put my finger on it. I know sanctions are discretionary for improper certification.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 17:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is an interesting issue, maybe something write about when all this bullshit is over. I mean lets just hope no one makes a Pokestop to steal children...sadly, I've heard of a case already where some thugs made one with the intent to rob people who came to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 17:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I guess I was worried it was going to be all on the computer like these practice essays are. I guess I should consider the time it takes to juggle the info between my notes, writing, and then going back to the fact pattern to see if I missed anything. I am like you, normally just write it in the law in the margin, and then underline the facts I will use to support it. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 17:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, you too! We got this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 16:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Michigan in East Lansing. Someone was hoping I was from NY because of my username. haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 15:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfection! Thank you for that tidbit, def. eased some nerves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 14:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I typically am as well, but if I am typing do I get a hard copy of the exam? I figured the exam was on the exam software.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 13:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to be fun. Do you say fuck it and just not worry about spelling? I sure they know that we would run any document we work on in reality through spellcheck...or should I just plug into the matrix now and upload Webster's and Black's Law along with all this other bullllllll... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 13:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone have a secret to taking notes for facts your going to use on your essays? Depending on the length of the essay, I am taking 4-5 mins to read it twice, to pull out what facts I want, and to organize my answer. Is that too long? Average? Not sure if there was a more sufficient way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 13:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know its elementary but over time Iv learn to REALLLLLY pay attention to the flow of Evidence and Contract questions. If there is someone on the stand more or less it's going to be impeachment or hearsay; then you just have to look for either the witness testifying (Hearsay) or questioning the witness (Impeachment). I still struggle with it sometimes because of all the distracting answers and facts, but this has helped me boost my score a little bit. There is a flow to it and it's easy to jump from problem to problem forgetting to stop and clear the slate before hitting a new problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 13:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same boat man. Key is fill in every bubble after making the best deduction, and write bullshit even if you don't know what to write about. Just don't give up. We don't know what's coming...do we ever though? No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
