<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2240</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 22:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes perfect sense. I just emailed you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 19:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, I love it! Very clever, very funny stuff. I thoroughly enjoyed it. I would love to post there if you would like to have it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 03:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now, just here. Hopefully one day I can find another good place to post - do you know of any? 
I am on YouTube also: you can follow this link for my video attempts at comedy!
https://www.youtube.com/user/subject2240 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 00:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have no idea how much that means to me, thank you so much! It's feedback like that that keeps me going. I hope you continue enjoying! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teenager Regrets Accepting Crazy Aunt's Friend Request </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 01:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BETHESDA, MD  Jake Mayer, 15, received a Facebook friend request from Sheila Abernathy, his crazy aunt, last week. Facing external pressure, Jake was forced into accepting the request, at which point chaos ensued.
	I hate my crazy aunt! began a frustrated Mayer. She shares all those viral posts, like Share this if you hate cancer, or I love my mother. Like this in 5 minutes or else you hate your mother. I mean, how can she fall for that? Its unbearable Ms. Abernathy also uses Facebook to express political views, explained Jake. I always see those posts that have President Obamas face with a red X over it and says, Not my President!  its 2015 for crying out loud, get over it! Mayer continued by saying he receives about seven requests a day for Facebook games such as FarmVille, Candy Crush Saga, and Pet Shop Story.
	Its not the incessant posting that annoys Mayer so much. Jake stated that its his aunts nonstop perusing of his profile that bothers him most. He explains how no aspect of his profile remained safe. His aunt, who lives in Colorado Springs, Colorado, constantly likes his photos and checks in on his life. Every day is a new crappy question! Hows school? How are your parents? Whos this person? It never ends! exclaimed a frustrated Mayer. Jake also expressed his disgruntlement over his aunts tendency to end every post with, XOXO LOVE AUNT SHEILA. I know who you are, and I know you love me, so just stop doing that! yelled Mayer. However, the biggest blow was yet to come.
     In April, Mayer was tagged in a picture with Jackie Richter, his classmate and love interest. The photo showed the two smiling together at a table in their schools lunchroom. When the picture made its way onto Jakes wall, his aunt posted a comment that opened up a sea of awkwardness at Chester A. Arthur High School, the school Jake currently attends. On the photo, Ms. Abernathy posted the following comment: Whos that girl in your picture? My future niece-in-law? LOL! XOXO LOVE AUNT SHEILA. Students at the high school dubbed it the comment heard round the lunchroom.
     I was mortified, a shell-shocked Mayer barely got out. His peers shared the same sentiments. I felt so bad for him; I was embarrassed vicariously through him! Mayers best friend, Peter Sarlo, explained. Sarlo continued, stating how Jake was bullied in the lunchroom for the two weeks following the event. Fortunately for Jake, his crush did not view the situation the same way. I dont know, began Ms. Richter, I thought it was cute in a weird kind of way. Despite a bout of bad luck, Jake seems to have dodged a bullet in that regard, though hes had no romantic luck with his crush.
     Jake ended by saying his extreme fears for the future. My parents wont let me block my aunt, or unfriend her, so I guess Ill just have to love with it, and pray she wont embarrass me again. Ms. Abernathy only released one statement on the matter: I just love my not-so-much-of-a-baby-anymore-nephew Jake! With three years still left in his high school career for Mr. Mayer, the only certain is that his future at Arthur High School may turn out to be quite bleak.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservatives Pleased With Ruining Of Exam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 06:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NEW YORK, NY  Conservatives can once again sleep well at night knowing that the AP U.S. History exam has been ruined to their liking. The test wasnt patriotic enough, and now we can rest assured that Americas students are learning about the real America, and not all the ugly parts of our countrys past, stated Walter Banks, the main propagator for the movement.
	The movement started in Texas because of the 2014 changes to the exams standards. The test dangerously focused on controversial issues of American history, such as slavery. Yeah, we dont really love those parts, said Mr. Banks, so we decided its best to tweak them. According to the movements followers, the 2014 revision gave the test an agenda, increasing an emphasis on slavery and negative aspects of American history. Mr. Banks continued, This country is supposed to be the guiding light for the rest of the world! Its our God-given right to be superior, and to be a leader for all nations, and we lose that right when our negativity is displayed to the world. Theres a reason its American exceptionalism, and not Canadian exceptionalism or British exceptionalism.
	This statement thoroughly angered American exceptionalism. Thats ridiculous! Dont blame me for your desire to try and feel superior, you wackjob! said an angered American exceptionalism. American exceptionalism went on to say that it fears the new exam could pollute the minds of the youth and give a false impression of American history to todays students. The most alarming opinions, however, stem directly from the source: the exam.
	The exam has had a difficult time since the change. I know that I might be ruining the future of this country, and thus the world! a distraught AP U.S. History exam disclosed. Following the change, the exam is on the road to alcoholism, and has become a shut-in. I cant show my face to people! Im a giant lie! I dont know how Im supposed to live with myself finished the exam. Authorities have been encouraged by the exams family to keep an eye on it, in order to prevent any life-threatening (or fatal) incidents.
	When asked if he is pleased with his work, Mr. Banks gave just one word: very. He continued, We are extremely happy with the result. With this success, we are not going to stop at History. We are going to decrease the emphasis on evolution in the Biology exam, and remove altogether the Calculus exam, solely for the fact that its hard. Together, we will take back the American education system! 
      China and Finland could not be reached for comment, because they were in too much shock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> African Lion To Zambia: Peace Out, Cub Scout </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 03:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LUSAKA, ZAMBIA  Baxter, a lion living in the Zambian savanna, has decided to take his future into his own paws and move to New York. In light of the senseless killing of Cecil the Lion in nearby Zimbabwe, in addition to general poaching, Baxter realized that savanna life isnt for him.
     Baxters discovery of the fragility of life made him feel the need to pursue his dreams of the theatre. I dabbled in community theatre shows around the savanna, but there were no performers who could inspire me to grow. I need that challenge and a change of scenery, explained Baxter. Baxter was a frequent performer at the Lusaka Savanna Theatre, and some of his favorite parts include The Phantom in The Phantom of the Opera, Tony in West Side Story, and Munkustrap in Cats. However, Baxter claims hes ready to put that all behind him and move on to the worlds biggest stage: Broadway.
     I have a cousin in Brooklyn, so I figured I could crash with him until I get on my four paws and support myself, said Baxter. I know it can be rough to be an animal getting on Broadway, but I plan on making some cash to take classes and make connections. I know its not easy, but I really want it, and thats what matters, finished Baxter.
     The difficulty for animals getting onto Broadway is a recognized fact. Oliver, the canine known for originating the part of Annies dog in Annie, toiled for seven years before landing the role. When his tenure in the show expired, Olivers life went on a downward spiral, as detailed in his autobiography, The Sun Wont Come Out Tomorrow: No Easy Street (Penguin Random House).
Despite all of this, Baxter remains positive. Yeah, I know about Olivers story, but I still have to know what could happen  I cant live with what ifs! Baxter expounded. To support animals like Baxter and special animals unlike Baxter, be sure to visit www.wildcru.org.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stacy's Mom Still Upset With Neighborhood Boys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 01:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WAYNE, NJ  Dolores Peters, the notoriously hot mother of Stacy Peters, still holds a grudge with the Wayne boys who broke the news of her good-looks to the world. In 2003, the band Fountains of Wayne released their hit record, Welcome Interstate Managers. The third track on the album, a song entitled Stacys Mom, skyrocketed the band to the top of the charts and put Waynes hottest mom in the spotlight.
     I watched those boys grow up! I cannot believe what they did to me, to my life. Not just the message, but referencing my divorce when it was still so fresh a wound for our familythat hurt the most, an outraged Mrs. Peters said. After the release of the song, crowds flocked to 3645 Kent Avenue, home of the Peters family, to catch a glimpse of the Helen of Troy of New Jersey. Ew, what creeps! complained Stacy Peters. I invited them over for like, one chemistry study sesh and this is what they do?! Shes like so much older than them, and theyre gross. Pervs! she continued. While the women of the Peters family are irate, others dont see the situation in the same way.
     My songwriting mentor always told me to write from my heart, so I did, explained songwriter Chris Collingwood. He continued, I went to Stacys house for a chemistry review session. I got bored with the material, so I started daydreaming and realized how weird it was that Stacy is so plain, but her mom is so hot. That thought, mixed with the notion of writing from the heart, made the choice obvious. I feel kinda bad that theyre pissed, but I wouldnt change anything. Eli Baker, a friend of the band and Wayne resident, agreed with the bands message and added that shes totally bangin!
     New Jersey plans to move on from the incident. Governor Chris Christie stated that he hopes the olive branch will be extended and that both parties can live comfortably together, or as comfortably as one can live in the hellhole that is Wayne, New Jersey. The governor acknowledges that music feuds can get quite ugly, and he remains optimistic that the state can avoid a situation like Michael Jackson and Billie Jean Hannon, the inspiration for the smash hit Billie Jean. Only time will tell what happens, and though it might be wrong, 12 years later were all still in love with Stacys mom.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 23:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hair would probably make a better President, for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TLC Runs Out Of Weird Crap To Air </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 04:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SILVER SPRING, MD  The television network TLC announced that they have officially run out of new, unnecessarily strange ideas to air. Network executives explained today that, following the premiere of a show about unnaturally tall women, the well has run dry. It all started with Jon and Kate Plus Eight  once we lost Jon and were stuck with just that horrible mother, things went downhill, explained TLC spokeswoman Jodi Avalon. Then came the whole ordeal with Honey Boo Boos mother. Top it all off with the Duggars? Our credibility plummeted. Ms. Avalon stated that a decreasing credibility leads to an immediate need for more ideas, which in turn hinders production in the long-run.
	The network has hit almost every genre unknown to man. We got Amish kids who dont want to be Amish anymore; Eskimos who want to leave the Eskimo lifestyle; babies; breakups; sex stories; funny AND serious 911 calls; little people; giant people; transgender people; bad tattoos; weird addictions; random ER visitswe figured we couldnt lose! explained network president Larry Garner. Its hitting us hard now, we have no new ideas to show, and a lot of our old ideas cant be put on re-runs becauseyou knowlawsuits, the president expounded.
	Network executives are not the only ones affected by the terminated output. Long-time TLC viewers are fed-up with the network as well. Everyone needs a little TLC? Ha! Not anymore! said Jamie Summers of Cleveland, Ohio. I used to watch the network every morning, afternoon, and night. But now Im a truTV girl  Id watch those improbable jokesters or whatever the show is called over TLCs dreck any day! Ms. Summers stated. Brian Hannon of San Diego, California, also expressed unhappiness with the network. Yeah, it sucks, Mr. Hannon described. I mean, I like seeing their stuffI dont know, I just get tired of the same old shows. I want something new and fresh. Like, cant they air meaningful shows? Eh, who am I kidding? Im still gonna watch the show about the giant women, he finished.
	So whats next for the network in danger? TLC representatives claim that old ideas might be revamped. Weve got a dozen shows about people with mental health issues, so why not take it to a new level  dogs with OCD! Whats their day-to-day like? Can they get treatment? Will they accept treatment? Its brilliant! an excited President Garner explained. If thats not your things, Ive got one better  obese koalas! Theyre so cute and cuddly, a show about koalas that have more to love in my mind screams winner! While President Larry Garner is excited for the changes, reactions from the viewers remain to be seen. The season premiere for Paw-sitive Change: A Dogs Journey to OCD Recovery is set for some time next year.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 04:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either way, it'd be quite the ticket! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Names Hair His Running Mate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 02:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NEW YORK, NY  Just days after announcing his candidacy for President, billionaire Donald Trump has officially named his hair his running mate. Weve been together through thick and thin, and we need to stick together now more than ever, Trump explained. 
     Trump raises a good point: together, the two have built luxury hotels across the globe, amassing unspeakable wealth and becoming moguls in the industry. Donald took me in, gave me a home, taught me everything I know, explained Donalds hair. The hair continued, When I heard he was running for President, I pitched some of my ideas to him and he loved them. He even included them in his speech! Said Donald, All that stuff about Mexico and the wall? That was all the hairs idea. Its truly a brilliant entity. 
     Pollsters said the inclusion of the hair as his running mate shoots Trump straight to the forefront of the race. No one has ever attempted anything like this, explains Gabe Winter of the Pew Research Center. Martin Van Buren toyed with the idea, but never followed through. If Trump makes this ticket officialwe could be looking at our first hair Vice President, finished Winter.
     This news really brought a smile to Trumps running mate. JFK was the first Catholic President, Obama was the first Black President, imagine me as the first hair Vice President! Trump, too, was all smiles about the big news. If theres one thing I love, said Trump, its making history. Also, money. Im really rich. Only time will tell what happens for this potentially historic duo with 2016 quickly approaching, but this is undoubtedly the pair to observe in the upcoming caucuses and debates.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doctor Cured Of Ebola Misses The Attention </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 01:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ESSEX, ENGLAND  Dr. Steven Samsonite, of England, spent two months tending to Ebola victims in Uganda before being transported to the United States for treatment after contracting the virus. Now healthy, Dr. Samsonite has developed a strong case of depression. When youre sick, everyone is like, Hey! Theres the sick hero doctor! Lets love him and give him a lot of attention! Now, Im just like everyone else again, lamented Dr. Samsonite. 
     The situation isnt just affecting the British doctor: his girlfriend of two years, Julia Irving, is feeling the struggle emotionally. I used to be special, too! Ms. Irving explained. People used to give me sympathy and food. Now Im just the average girlfriend. Do you know how hard that is? Dr. Samsonite gave us further insight into his depression. To see Julia so upset crushes me. But, justjust being normal is what hurts the most. Being a normy, an Average Joe if you will, is what disappoints us daily. To be in a market and hear, Cash or credit? instead of, This ones on us, Dr. Miracle-Performer! affects the psyche quite deeply. 
     So what does this disheartened couple have in store for the future? I think Im gonna go back to Uganda and somehow get infected again. I think its best for both of us. Ms. Irving agreed, adding, I dont want him to go away again, but this is what couples do. You make sacrifices for each other. Its why I love this man so much! What a truly inspiring story of enduring love.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman Admits Tinder Match Not As Great As Expected </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 08:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CHICAGO, IL  23-year-old Bridget Fowler of Chicago faced disappointment at the discovery that Todd Baxter, her Tinder match, was not as exciting in person. The discovery took place at Menschs Kosher Deli, on Chicagos South Side. His pictures looked so exciting! exclaimed Fowler. A college graduate, with a puppy, who went to Africa? Um, have you heard of being the total package? Swipe right! Fowlers dreams were soon to be dashed. She describes, When we first met in person, he was wearing a Cubs shirt and jeans. He was soaverage. Like, where was the Africa? And the puppy? And college? We each got sandwiches and he paid. It was painfully normal. 
     Todd did not agree with this. I had a great time, he said. She was fun, but a little ditzy. The whole time she kept asking me about Africa, even though I told her countless times I work at a nearby zooI guess shes not a very good listener. Despite that, I had a really good time, and I hope to see her again soon. Fowler did not have the same sentiments. Again? Hah, no thank you. I think once was enough with Tad, or whatever his name is. He was such a liar! I was all like, Oh my gawd tell me about the Taj Mahal! and he was just like, Bridget, Ive told you like, ten times that I work at a zoo. That wasnt from Africa, that was just me with an elephant in our zoo. Ugh, I hate liars! I met a new guy on Tinder, anyway. His name is Bobby, and he has a picture of him surfing, so he must be a lifeguard!  Fingers crossed with him  maybe the thirty-fifth time is the charm! 
     Todd met a woman named Stephanie through his best friend, and the two have been dating for about three weeks. Meeting someone through a friend is way better than trying an app! Getting to talk to them and get to know them in person instead of through a screen is super greatwho wouldve guessed?! Stephanie is a nurse who does Zumba and is a really great listener. I think thats what she said, I wasnt paying attention. We really complement each other, Baxter pointed out. Despite improbable odds, love lives on in The Windy City.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Local Man Cuddled To Death </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 08:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PARAMUS, NJ  Tragedy struck a New Jersey town today when Steve Wilmore, a 47-year old man from Paramus, was cuddled to death. The suspected culprit is Sophia, Wilmores 4-year old daughter. Shes a very affectionate childshe doesnt yet understand the havoc that she can cause, explained Tania Miller, who has lived next door to the Wilmore family for ten years now. Wilmores wife, Tammy, explained the whole situation while fighting back tears. This is almost expected, sort of a long time coming, she started, Sophia has been aggressive with him for a while now: the tight hugs, the tackling, giving him plastic foodI just cant believe its come to this. 
     Paramus police chief Sal Abattiello also weighed in on the issue. Toddler-related deaths have been on the rise in the last decade, Abattiello explained. Abattiello continued, Our calls used to be the interesting ones: domestic abuse, drugs, petty larceny, but now its all toddlers. Whether the kid strangled the parents, caused them to choke during a toy-shoving incident, or tripped them with some toy, these toddlers need to be stopped. 
     And stopping toddlers is precisely whats happening. The Paramus town board is cracking down on toddler abuse of elders. Susan Stanton, president of the town board, is proposing big measures to mend the situation. For too long this has been going on! exclaimed Ms. Stanton, Out with the old, in with the new  that deals with clothes, or food cans, but not members of society, and toddlers need to learn that. Its time we come together as a community and end this madness now. So what comes next for the community in mourning? Ive lived here my whole life, said Chief Abattiello, and I know that this community comes together in good times and in bad. Were closer now than weve ever been, and were finally ready to end toddler tyranny. Sophia could not be reached for comment.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blind Man Unimpressed By Aurora Borealis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 03:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> REYKJAVIK, ICELAND  53-year-old Gil Collins, a blind man from Evansville, Indiana, had scathing reviews of his vacation in Iceland. I didnt even want to go; my wife wanted to go. If it was up to me, we wouldve been sitting on the beaches of Cancun. But we all know its always up to the wife. I just didnt think it would be THIS bad, Collins ranted. I dont know what his big fuss was all about, it was a lovely time! exclaimed Gils wife, Nancy. Yeah, I bet she said she had a great time, said Gil. She always has a good time. Shes a walking ray of sunshine who finds the good even in the worst trip. I kid you not, she had a good time in Brazil  and it wasnt even Carnival. According to Gils wife, Mr. Collins has difficulty in seeing the good in every vacation. We went to the Grand Canyon  he called it a useless hole in the ground. The Statue of Liberty  he called her some green whore! I just dont know what his problem is.
	Reykjavik Mayor Dagur B. Eggertsson was flabbergasted by this whole story. We make a lot of money each year in tourism. I dont know what this man isnt seeing that our millions of other visitors do. Mr. Collins wanted to clarify his case for Mayor Eggertsson. Ive seen better lights on a drug trip.  Keep your godless, freak nature lights, you socialist bastard. When asked if they would ever go on vacation again, the happy coupled agreed they would, but this time theyll let Mr. Collins choose the best place to go. Im thinking maybe Disney? said Mr. Collins. I dont know why, but I have a thing for animals pretending to be people. Funny stuff! Its why that Entourage show gets me every time. By asserting himself and his desires, Mr. Collins is proving to be a hero for both blind persons, and husbands, across the globe.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Area Boy Admits He Took Grocery Bagger Job To Pay For College </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 03:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AKRON, OH  17-year-old Jacob Lewis has been a grocery bagger at the local A P since he was 13 years old. The community always believed he was there for so long because he loved helping his fellow citizens. Lewis admitted today that he had an ulterior motive for taking the job. I just wanted to get some money for a car and collegeI didnt see what was so wrong about it. But now everyone hates meI shouldnt have lied. I cant believe what Ive done.  Ive been shopping there nearly my whole life, said 82-year-old Betty Jones, and Ive never seen a bagger like him. Hes never broken an egg or squashed bread. But now Ill never use him again!  The news rocked the supermarket. We were so shocked by this revelation, said A P manager Tom Johnson, we had to close the store down for the rest of the day. That hasnt been done at this store since the Cuban Missile Crisis. But Lewis employer isnt the only one surprised by this whole story. I always thought he was a good dude, said one of Lewis friends, who asked we not reveal his identity to his shame of being associated with the miscreant, but I guess I was wrong.  To lie to a whole community like this? Not cool, bro, not cool. The local school district is being investigated following the news of what Lewis has been up to. Cecilia Brown, the superintendent for Lewis school district, released a comment. Ive known him for a while.  He is a good student and a top-notch athlete.  This kind of lying and deceit is not something Id expect from him.  Some of his neer-do-well friends, maybe, but not him. This is going to have to go on his record. I dont know how colleges will accept him now. Yet the community heartbreak hit closer than his store or school: it hit his home. How can I trust him again? asked his sobbing mother, Eleanor. All these years I thought he did this menial job out of love, just to find out hes doing it to better himself? How do I explain this to his younger siblings?  Things are very tense right now. What does the future hold for this young man?  Yeah, hell still be employed here, said Johnson. Hes the best bagger Ive ever seen: he can bag even the toughest of customers in two minutes flat without breaking an egg or popping open a yogurt. Well probably just give him a mean nickname, like Sir Lies-A-Lot or something. Were terrible at giving nicknames, but huge fans of Babys Got Back, so were pretty proud of that one continued Johnson. An elated Jacob reflected on that news. Im so honored I can keep my job there. Id say Im glad because I love it, but since Im not lying anymore, Ill say its because Im only $52.76 away from a 2009 Honda Civic! Hopefully this community can mend its broken pieces, and that there will no longer be a figurative clean-up on aisle four. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
