<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2947</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 15:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 nerf in months woo, lets all wait another 4-5 months for the next weapon balance Lol... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 11:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Social engineer? Doesn't take a genius to manipulate 13/14 yr olds Lol... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 11:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I trust the devs that they would accurately buff/nerf weapons, They would most likely do some testing with it first, to see what works. 
I dont necessarily agree with the ruining other peoples builds, as the majority of builds would stay strong even after weapon updates. Its just nice to add color to the pvp side of the game is all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When will we see much needed weapon balancing? pvp is dying. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 11:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I Remember this was talked about in the osrs streams awhile back about buffing the acb special attack, and some other weapons.

The Current meta right now for pures is ballista to gmaul which is extremely broken.
It also gets quite boring having the exact same meta for a very long time. 

Would love to see the meta change by buffing some weapons like the acb, dragon longsword, dragon mace.

Its not to say that they dont do weapon balancing, but they come very frugally, I Remember they buffed the crystal halbard, buffed the abyssal dagger special attack, And nerfed the blowpipe speed. 

But other than those 3 its been a very long time since they have changed up weapon stats which is why i feel the wilderness is dying a bit.

Post your thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 10:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found the name buyer/seller </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 19:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God you're fat as fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
