<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject322</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your biggest "What did I do" moment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 03:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Inked people of reddit If your tattoo became real, what would the result be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 22:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you call a Muslim who is also a pilot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 20:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greg if you're a friend, Gregory if you were introduced, Mr. Abdalla if you're doing business with one another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best insult you've ever heard? (Or even better, delivered. Feel free to humble brag.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 20:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When does 3+10=1? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 10:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made this up as a bonus question on a math test. We had to stump our teacher with a math problem!

Edit 1: In Junior high. Over ten years ago now.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hero league team thread, post your rank, and time zone. Find some buddies! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 05:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Oh yee lords of pizza, I return with my weekly offering, on this my day of worship. Would that I be blessed by your divinity! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 02:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We shall begin with this peasant's insulting mistake to ye oh lords http://i.imgur.com/gvHOU17.jpg

Then, this this former celebrity's descent into Pizza worship! His are the hymns of your greatness! 
http://i.imgur.com/H1W8RYz.jpg

This guide on how to get laid, as truly Pizza is the only afrodisiac man needs http://i.imgur.com/5eGYeIm.jpg

Or this tale, of how your missionaries go above and beyond their station to 
bring joy to your worshipers! 
http://imgur.com/a/FodFS?gallery

And this recipe to cater to your finger food needs! 
http://imgur.com/a/Hj9Vb?gallery

And take this photo, showing that even our most adored worship at your plate! http://i.imgur.com/PfozKEX.jpg?1

And this, the only accurate predictor of your people's preference in online communities http://i.imgur.com/wYwl9nh.jpg

And here ye, even our pets share our love of your greatness! http://i.imgur.com/ZAJhaZt.png

Here you see that Random acts of your greatness transcends the borders of this site! http://imgur.com/a/YMUgl?gallery

One of the greatest failings of humanity http://i.imgur.com/Uo2JyAi.jpg

And this blasphemer's theft from your priests! Strike him down with a saucey vengeance! http://i.imgur.com/K9zOMj6.webm

And when all else fails, when you know not what topping to order, the answer is obvious to all! http://i.imgur.com/1KgUFWd.jpg

This slightly nsfw tale of how one of your missionaries grew wise to those trying to avoid paying tribute! http://i.imgur.com/jPn4TbL.jpg

And this rendition of what I wish more than life itself for my future! http://i.imgur.com/Z69iRLJ.gif

How I envy this worshiper her challenges! 
http://i.imgur.com/FaDKTvR.jpg

And here, the most sensual display of pizza any has ever beheld! http://i.imgur.com/UzqfR9e.gif

How your priests prepare your greatness around the globe! http://imgur.com/t/pizza/MdCQX

And here I have found that even the most holy of holies is a worshiper at YOUR temple! 
http://i.imgur.com/WzTn5PK.webm

 And to further warm thine heart! 
http://i.imgur.com/haJVGLC.jpg

 And here oh great ones! The miracle of birth in motion! http://i.imgur.com/KCDx1vF.webm

 And here you see the heroisim of your preiests as one of your worshipers uses prayer to reach out! http://imgur.com/a/I9PHi?gallery

 Now we see one of your worshiper's in their finest vestments! http://i.imgur.com/KC2o02z.jpg

 This radical proves that there is no wrong way to order pizza. http://i.imgur.com/F5UGmEN.png

 And this youthful worshiper using your glory to save the life of a loved one! http://i.imgur.com/nJGkSmL.jpg?1

And lastly, this comic, that extols the greatness and love that is pizza. http://imgur.com/gallery/pxvC6

Please oh great pizza lords! Hear the humble prayers of this student, tired of rice beans and homemade fry's. Grace him with your cheesy glory! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 24 [M4F] Toronto - Warning, full sentences ahead! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 02:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, hey clicked on my link did you? Dandy. 

But hey, listen, I could go on and on about myself - Tell you about my hobbies like reading. How I devour novels within hours of buying one. I could tell you how I absolutely love day dreaming, or that I enjoy long, long walks (Sometimes both at the same time.). My favorite style of music? Geek Rock. Not that you'll hear it from me. Or how I was working with a rocking tech company a few months ago, Nerf Wars were one of many office hazards. If I was embarrassed about the fact, I'd probably try to hide the fact I like gaming, video and table top, but if someone were to ask me. I'd probably let them know. 

You may also hear rumours that I'm a fantastic cook. Not that I'll confirm them, but I'd be lying if I denied them. Haha 

Maybe I could tell you about how I love watching videos from TED.com, or that I really enjoy listening to comedians as I work? Nah. I'll keep that to myself too. How about the fact that I'm a huge comic book geek, and I enjoy telling people about all the easter eggs in the movie we just watched? No no. I might come off as too nerdy if I told you that! 

Ohh I know. How about that I love hiking and camping? A good beer, and a campfire is a good night in my book. Hmm... But if I said that, then you might start thinking I was a rugged outdoorsy type. Which I'm not. I just like certain things like that, I don't do them often enough for my liking though. Ok. Well. I guess I'll keep my mouth shut for now.

- So yeah. Those are just some of things I wont tell you at the moment. Wouldn't want to waste your time eh? Anyway. If you got through all that, I think I'd like to know about you now.

Recent picture:
http://i.imgur.com/UyaYE73.jpg



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does your SO do, that bothers the the heck out of you, but isn't bad enough that you'd ever want to break up over it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 22:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's not often I get photo's taken of me,this is one of maybe a half dozen I've had in over a year, and my favourite. I'd love to see it drawn! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 02:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You fell asleep normally, but you wake up 500 years later, something happened when you went to sleep that made all humans disappear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 21:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I [24 M] am a massive extrovert. I've moved to a new city where I haven't made any real connections. Today, out of nowhere I just got crushed by this loneliness on my chest all of a sudden. Like I could physically feel it. Any suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 01:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so a quick run down. I'm new in Toronto. Been here since January. I've made a lot of "friends" people who I enjoy spending time with when I can, and they seem to enjoy my company when we're around. I don't put "friends" in quotes because they're bad people or anything like that. The opposite. The folks I'm referring too are great! 

But I never get invited out anywhere, and whenever I invite anyone they're often busy. The only time I get any real connection with folks is for dates. I'm really really good with gals. 

But I've never really met anyone who wants to see me regularly, who seems to want more than something physical with me. And I can't stand anymore fwb situations. 

I'm intelligent, I'm friendly, I go out of my way to help people whenever I can, and like I say. People seem to love having me around. But clearly there is something awful about me that no one will tell me about so I can fix it.

This one girl, who has been my best friend since I moved here, she couldn't even make time for me three weeks ago when my grandfather died. The only person who did was a gal I've been seeing, but I've only gotten like two texts from her since then. 

TL:DR People don't ever seem to want to spend time with me or ever think about me, and it's been eight months. I'm alone in this city and it's crushing me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whenever someone says "If you don't have a solution, don't complain" they never give a solution to make the other person want to not complain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 18:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First we lose Duke for Sgt Hammer, and now we lose Egon for the Medic? Why are starcraft heroes being shunted aside for these basic units? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 21:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I say lose, I know full well we might get these characters. But Sgt Hammer and Medic fill the roles that Edmund Duke and Egon Stentman would. So the /need/ for those characters is much less now. Does anyone else find this lame or is it just me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help with SQL queries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 21:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there folks, I'm Tom. This community has been a great help in my programming education so far. So thank you for that. Now, I have a specific question. I need to create a bunch of SQL queries. I'm going to post them at the end here, and I was just wondering which terms I should look up to accomplish each of these. I'll be working while checking this page, so even if you can only help me with one of the ten, that'd be great. This is the last stretch of my project, and I'm having a wee bit of trouble. Not a ton, but enough that I figured reaching out couldn't hurt. Thank you for your time!

6.	Create the following TEN queries (Use any tables and data of your choice). Provide the SQL script (statements) in your project report and also include the result set screenshots (copy the clipboard Image)
Create a SELECT query that uses a condition in the WHERE Clause. 2)
Create a SELECT query that joins at least four tables
3)Create a SELECT query that uses an Aggregate function.
4)Create a SELECT query that includes an ORDER BY Clause.
5)Create a SELECT query that includes GROUP BY and HAVING Clauses.
6)Create a VIEW that is based on at least THREE Tables.
7)Create a SELECT query that includes an OUTER JOIN
8)Create a SELECT query that includes a SUB QUERY.
9)Create a SELECT query that uses a SELF JOIN.
10)Create a SELECT query that uses the CASE conditional structure.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] I have never had Chipotle in my life, and I've just moved to Toronto, the first city I've lived in that has it. Care to suggest what I should have first? Or expose me to your favourite? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 21:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [personal issues]I [24 M] have been curious to ask. R/Relationships, where does being friendly turn into cheating for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 18:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Ohhh hear me ye lords of pizza. Please accept my humble offerings of pizza themed memes and information, and hear my prayers for a pie of my own! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 22:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We shall begin with this peasant's insulting mistake to ye oh lords
http://i.imgur.com/gvHOU17.jpg

Then, this this former celebrity's descent into Pizza worship! His are the hymns of your greatness!
http://i.imgur.com/H1W8RYz.jpg

This guide on how to get laid, as truly Pizza is the only afrodisiac man needs
http://i.imgur.com/5eGYeIm.jpg

Or this tale, of how your missionaries go above and beyond their station to bring joy to your worshipers!
http://imgur.com/a/FodFS?gallery

And this recipie to cater to your finger food needs!
http://imgur.com/a/Hj9Vb?gallery

And take this photo, showing that even our most adored worship at your plate! 
http://i.imgur.com/PfozKEX.jpg?1

And this, the only accurate predictor of your people's preference in online communities
http://i.imgur.com/wYwl9nh.jpg

And here ye, even our pets share our love of your greatness!
http://i.imgur.com/ZAJhaZt.png

Here you see that Random acts of your greatness transcends the borders of this site!
http://imgur.com/a/YMUgl?gallery

One of the greatest failings of humanity
http://i.imgur.com/Uo2JyAi.jpg

And this blasphemer's theft from your priests! Strike him down with a saucey vengeance! 
http://i.imgur.com/K9zOMj6.webm

And when all else fails, when you know not what topping to order, the answer is obvious to all!
http://i.imgur.com/1KgUFWd.jpg

This slightly nsfw tale of how one of your missionaries grew wise to those trying to avoid paying tribute!
http://i.imgur.com/jPn4TbL.jpg

And this rendition of what I wish more than life itself for my future!
http://i.imgur.com/Z69iRLJ.gif

How I envy this worshiper her challenges!
http://i.imgur.com/FaDKTvR.jpg

And here, the most sensual display of pizza any has ever beheld!
http://i.imgur.com/UzqfR9e.gif

How your priests prepare your greatness around the globe!
http://imgur.com/t/pizza/MdCQX

And lastly, this comic, that extols the greatness and love pizza has.
http://imgur.com/gallery/pxvC6

Please oh great pizza lords! Hear the humble prayers of this student, tired of rice beans and homemade fry's. Grace him with your cheesy glory!

Edit: And here I have found that even the most holy of holies is a worshiper at YOUR temple! 
http://i.imgur.com/WzTn5PK.webm

Edit 2: And to further warm thine heart!
http://i.imgur.com/haJVGLC.jpg

Edit 3: And here oh great ones! The miracle of birth in motion!
http://i.imgur.com/KCDx1vF.webm

Edit 4: And here you see the heroisim of your preiests as one of your worshipers uses prayer to reach out!
http://imgur.com/a/I9PHi?gallery

Edit 5: Now we see one of your worshiper's in their finest vestments!
http://i.imgur.com/KC2o02z.jpg

Edit 6: This radical proves that there is no wrong way to order pizza.
http://i.imgur.com/F5UGmEN.png

Edit 7: And this youthful worshiper using your glory to save the life of a loved one!
http://i.imgur.com/nJGkSmL.jpg?1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Screen constantly flickering black, followed by light lag? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 19:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The issue is in the title. Any suggestions? Anyone else having this trouble? It just started the last few games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only player's I've ever seen refuse to switch in hero league no matter the map or their team's picks, are people who play Sylvanas. Is there any traits you've noticed among players who play certain heroes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 15:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a little known piece of media(Books, games movies, music, shows etc) that you adore? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 20:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [M4F] From Nova Scotia and new in Town. Hope you don't mind accents! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 01:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there I'm Tom. I'm 24 and 6'3

http://i.imgur.com/XTpgvMK.jpg

That's a recent photo of me. Like inside of a month.

Anyway. I love comics, games, dancing and cooking. Put a book in my hand and I'll read for hours. (Or until it's done. I've got nothing against Dr. Suess.) 

I'm lookin' for a like minded gal to date, and have some great conversation with. Anyone up for something this weekend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the dumbest or most awkward thing you've said or done on a first date, and were still able to land a second? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 22:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] I'm new in Toronto and was invited to a potluck in a park, what's a good easy to travel (No car. Will use the subway) picnic potluck food? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 21:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to play online but I'm having issues with windows ten notnhaving WiFi! Any suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 17:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't find any WiFi networks, windows 10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 17:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, in windows eight, this lovely little side bar thing could be swipped out and I could see all the WiFi signals beaming around my head (Of which there were many). I used it to connect to the router my building aet up on my floor. Sometimes it would connect to the worse connection on the floor below. Never a problem, I just needed to disconnect from that signal and reccconect to the good one.

My problem is, I disconnected from my poor signal as usual, and not only did it not reconnect instantly, I can't find ANY signals now. 

I'm posting this from my smart phone using the connection I want, and the computer is not in airplane mode. Help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have been trying to find a Copy of Fallen Haven for years. Does anyone remember this old game, and do you have your own "White Whale" of a retro game you've been hunting for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 15:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman is arrested while claiming she has all the rights of a U.S citizen and needs to follow no laws. (Head phone warning.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 14:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What game would you love to see made and by which company and why? Be as detailed as you like! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 18:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] I'd like to find some good songs for Karaoke. What are your favourites? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 01:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I pre purchased legacy of the void, how do I access the beta content? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 01:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You click random. The theme of which ever subreddit you just found is your new fetish. How screwed are you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 18:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my girlfriend tells me she's not wearing anything under her skirt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 18:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Java help please. Tabs and forums. Thank you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 19:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey folks. I have a project due next Tuesday. Very simple stuff, I've almost got it all done, I just need to know two different bits of code so I can bring it all together. And of course if you have any extra advice, I'd love to hear it. I want to learn, and become a great web developer.

Basically I need to make a page that looks a lot like the one done in the gallery below. You'll see my current version as well.

http://imgur.com/a/yXaJz#0

Thank you for your time, even if you only read this.

Here is exactly what the project asks for, by the by.

"Follow these steps:
 Search the web for a product of your choice and capture some pictures, product description and
features for your project

 Your page must contain a header, a footer indicating your copyright, a title, a comment line in the
header indicating your group number and the student ID and name of all group members. Please use
CSS to style your page.

 The main content area must be separated in two divisions where the left division occupies approximately 1/3 of the content area and shows an image of your product and at least one link to a web site where a visitor to your page can purchase the product.

 The right hand side of the content area must contain three clickable tabs so when a visitor to your page clicks on any of the tab, the appropriate content shows up. That functionality must be implemented using Javascript and the DOM discussed in the lecture.

 The third tab must contain a registration form similar to the one shown above. Using Javascript, validate province, postal code, email, password and age. The register now button must show an alert box containing the data entered by the user.

 Upload your file to the gblearn account of one of group members public_html/comp1231/project.

Double check your work by pointing your browser to w5xxxxxx.gblearn.com and clicking at the relevant
link." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What weird way that people wouldn't expect, do you improve meals or snacks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 18:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's a batman boner comic I made, by using real batman comic pages! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 05:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We should be able allow our party members/friends under level 10, access to any hero we have bought. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 03:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have friends who want to learn the game, but they hate the hero rotation. I've been playing for awhile, so I have a great selection. Once they can spend the time playing all these great heroes, they'll know who they love to play. 

What do you all think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Introduction to Functions in JS 12/13 stall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 21:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what the site wants me to input

Instructions
Write a function named sleepCheck that takes the parameter numHours
Inside the function, write an if statement where if the number of hours of sleep is greater than or equal to 8, the computer will return "You're getting plenty of sleep! Maybe even too much!";.
Otherwise (else) if the number of hours of sleep is less than 8, have the computer return "Get some more shut eye!";
Then call the function with different hours of sleep

Call the function with 10 hours of sleep, like this: sleepCheck(10);
Call the function with 5 hours of sleep.
Call the function with 8 hours of sleep.


This is my code

var sleepCheck = function (numHours) {
    
if numHours = 8 {
      return "You're getting plenty of sleep! Maybe even too much!";
    }
    else {
        return "Get some more shut eye!";
    }
};

console.log(sleepCheck(10));

console.log(sleepCheck(5));

console.log(sleepCheck(8));


It says there is a problem with my syntax. Help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have a spot of trouble with functions in Code Acedmy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 23:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what they want

Instructions
Write a function named sleepCheck that takes the parameter numHours
Inside the function, write an if statement where if the number of hours of sleep is greater than or equal to 8, the computer will return "You're getting plenty of sleep! Maybe even too much!";.
Otherwise (else) if the number of hours of sleep is less than 8, have the computer return "Get some more shut eye!";
Then call the function with different hours of sleep

Call the function with 10 hours of sleep, like this: sleepCheck(10);
Call the function with 5 hours of sleep.
Call the function with 8 hours of sleep.


This is what I have

var sleepCheck = function (numHours) {
    
    if numHours = 8 {
      return "You're getting plenty of sleep! /n Maybe even too much!";
    }
    else numHours = 8 {
        return "Get some more shut eye!";
    }
};

console.log(sleepCheck(10));

console.log(sleepCheck(5));

console.log(sleepCheck(8));

And Codeacedmy says I have a problem with my syntax.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On any front page post about cops, racism, body acceptance, or feminism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 16:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What comes to mind? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 20:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 months ago I made a comic out of old batman strips show casing the old use of the word boner, I shared it with Imgur, now it's reddit's turn! (x/post with r/funny) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 19:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 months ago I made a comic out of old batman strips show casing the old use of the word boner, I shared it with Imgur, now it's reddit's turn! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 18:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whenever you use the phrase "No offense" everything you say afterwards immediately becomes more offensive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 02:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]I haven't see anything mind blowing lately, so Reddit, what's the most mind blowing fact you know? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 20:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a big fan of mecha anime, are there any newer ones? And I also really dig compititon style anime. Beyblade, Yugioh, the original Dragonball, but I like when all the characters can compete, and not just the main. I also like it when they take themselves more seriously than not. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 23:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some I've enjoyed recently
The Gundam Build Fighters series
and Aldnoah Zero
I also recently watched FMA all the way for the first time.

Zach bell was okay, but there was too much humor. I really dug Shaman King (Haven't finished it, maybe I'll check that out again.)

So I am okay with humor. EVERYONE loves a good laugh here and there. And anything too grimdark is annoying. Like Bleach I didn't dig. Ichigo was painful to try and root for most of the time.

Honestly you can suggest other Anime that I might not have even thought of too. I've been outta the loop for awhile. Thank you all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] I'm a big fan of mecha anime, are there any newer ones? And I also really dig compititon style anime. Beyblade, Yugioh, the original Dragonball, but I like when all the characters can compete, and not just the main. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 20:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [wp] Good guy greg is missing/in danger, and it's up to the other memes to save him! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 20:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were to make a dating site drinking game, what things would you have that make your players "Take a drink"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 04:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were to make a dating site drinking game, what sights would make you "Take a drink" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 04:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nova Scotian in Toronto, looking to get out for the evening </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 21:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it helps to know, I'm 6'3, pretty geeky, love to dance, and I'd like to think I'm a pretty clever conversationalist. But that's for you to decide eh?

I study at George brown, for Computer science. I want to run my own startup soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 24 [M4R] Toronto, Ontario - Nova Scotian who's new in town, looking to get out tonight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 20:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missed classes due to a death in the family, not sure how to do my prelab! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 17:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys. So I took a week and a few days off because a death in the family, and I've been rushing to catch up. I'm caught up in Data Base, Math, and Business, but not Java. Our prelab is easy apparently, but I don't get it! 

"Write the code for a constructor function named GamingConsole that takes three Parameters: Manufacturer, model, year, and creates a GamingConsole object as described above"

There's also a bunch of html hoo hah. But I can do that easily. Now, we aren't marked on our prelabs, but we need them or else we can't do the lab test (Which is soon.) Can anyone help me figure this out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have Diablo, so the new bundle costs me 13.99 for just the skin. The skin alone costs 9.99 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 19:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a new Sub called random acts of cooking! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/RAofC/

The whole point of the sub is to connect people who enjoy home cooked meals! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you wish people just "understood" or were at least taught in schools before hitting the real world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 13 Russian boy sent to jail due to size of his penis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 01:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Satoru Iwata passes away at 55 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 11:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 24 [M4F] Toronto, Ontario - New in town, looking to explore the summer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 23:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there, I'm new in Town, from Nova Scotia. Bit of an accent, and I'm 6'3 and slim. I love to dance, read, cook, and trying new things are all fantastic. I've been volunteering with the Fringe Festival the last few weeks, and it's been a blast.

What I'm looking for, is someone to wander around the city with, even better if we can get a little lost, and discover new things. Or if you know this town like the back of your hand, someone to show me the hidden gems. I've got recent photos as well, so I look forward to chatting with you all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 24 [M4F] Down Town Toronto - New in town, looking to explore the summer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 23:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there, I'm new in Town, from Nova Scotia. Bit of an accent, and I'm 6'3 and slim. I love to dance, read, cook, and trying new things are all fantastic. I've been volunteering with the Fringe Festival the last few weeks, and it's been a blast.

What I'm looking for, is someone to wander around the city with, even better if we can get a little lost, and discover new things. Or if you know this town like the back of your hand, someone to show me the hidden gems. I've got recent photos as well, so I look forward to chatting with you all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the worst possible thing you can think of, to say to someone in your very first message on a dating site? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 14:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Armoured core in real life! America VS Japan! Who else is psyched? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 17:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a white Professor thinks that all white people should commit suicide. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 18:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me [24 m] with my best first date ever [26 F] She's from a culture that doesn't celebrate homosexuality, she supports it, but because I'm Bi, thinks she will be unable to fulfill me if we're together. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 17:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so, we went on a date. It. Was. Stellar. We both had an amazing time. We even went to a pride parade, and she thought it was beautiful! She wishes her home country could celebrate like that. So it's not that she's homophobic. But around the end of the date, she found out I was bi. I didn't think it would be a big deal.

But now she is concerned that she cannot fulfill me in the way I need, and doesn't want to hold me back. This is a case of her just not understanding how it all works, she's even admitted as much, and I don't hold it against her.

And before anyone says "She's just using this as an excuse to cancel" /she/ made the second date before she found out about my sexuality. It would have been easier if I just kept my mouth shut, because if I'm with her, that part of me wouldn't matter. I'm happy to be monogamous with one gender or another. 

Can anyone give me advice on how to let her know that that is the case? I've tried saying that I wouldn't need that part of me, but she's so unsure.



   
**tl;dr**: Because of cultural differences based on sexual needs. I might be missing out on an amazing and enriching relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Which meme do you just not understand becoming a meme? (It doesn't need to be purely computer based. Any sort of Meme) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 19:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby shoes, never worn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 04:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] I have always thought the phrase "I wouldn't do that for a million dollars" was silly. So I want to know Reddit, what would you DO for a Million dollars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 00:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 24 [M4F] Toronto - New in the city, clever and kinky </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 20:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there, so I'm Tom. Came to the city from a small town for school, looking to explore it with some fun people. Like I mentioned above, I am a bit kinky, D of D/s by the by. But that's not my end goal.

I'm hunting for someone clever and ambitious, who digs going out, exploring and doing new things.
 
http://i.imgur.com/C1SrC8t.jpg

That's me, by the by. I usually have glasses on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] I am tired but can't sleep. HELP! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 07:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Student in Toronto Ontario, tired of canned food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 21:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy. I try to be frugal in my living, I buy food for a nice meal about once a month, and live on cereal or canned food that I find on sale, which isn't a bad life! I'm not starving or anything, but I've been dying for some pizza lately. If anyone would like to send me a treat, I'd mightily appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Considering that the Summer is here, and we sometimes get stumped for meal ideals, here's a list of picnic meals you can put together for a fun day out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 21:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi guys. I'm learning Java Script. (Yay) But I'm stuck on a small problem. It's silly, because I'm sure I'm over looking something simple but I just have no idea! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 15:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3. Using JavaScript embedded in the body of the HTML, perform the following operations:
a. Write the code for a function mixUp(word) that returns the permuted word.
b. Prompt the user for a word, invoke your function, and show the result using document.write.


I've got the rest of the lab. Just this one part is giving me a problem. How would you go about doing it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just finished a Semester of CSS and HTML 5, I want to get better, where to go from here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 00:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy. So, I really like web development. It's fun! But the stuff we developed for our HTML and CSS classes are super simple, and I'm not quite sure where to go from here. 

I've got these basic skills, and I want to advance them. Now, I want to keep in mind that I want to advance my HTML and CSS skills. I'm in a Javascript course this semester so I'll be picking up things there.

So I'm not a novice with no clue, but I'm at that stage in my skills where I don't know quite which direction to go. And just building webpages without any real goal doesn't seem to do much to advance my skills, since I don't really know what I can do, or when I see an effect that I want to achieve, how to do it.

Thank you all for listening, and for any advice you have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Toronto][M4A](Teaching)(Can host) Well, since I'm the one who made it, I may as well be the first to take the plunge. I'd love to teach you how to make something unique based on your tastes! Improv cooking is my specialty. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 03:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Computer that is teaching itself to play Super Mario World! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 03:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/RandomActsofCooking Have you ever wanted to be able to order dinner guests just like that pizza you accidentally left on the counter last night? Well. Here it is! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 21:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/RandomActsofCooking Have you ever wanted to be able to order dinner guests just like that pizza you accidentally left on the counter last night? Well. Here it is! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/RandomActsofCooking Have you ever wanted to be able to order dinner guests just like that pizza you accidentally left on the counter last night? Well. Here it is! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What's some obscure song or entire genre that you'd love to expose more people too? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 01:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Elctro Swing](Yeah it's a thing) Bad Boy Goodman by Tape Five </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 01:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What is a story you've always wanted to tell, whether it be something you're proud of, or ashamed of, but never had the opportunity because it would have felt like bragging, or whining? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 01:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What's the worst thing you'd do for a Klondike bar? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 16:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] The bigots were right. The gay agenda is real, and it's bigger than anyone ever imagined. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 15:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what does a liquidity ratio of zero mean? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 15:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] If someone thinks they're a narcissist, and need some kind of (Nonmedical) support group where they can talk and try to improve themselves, are there any subreddits or websites based on that? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 03:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] A classmate of mine wants examples of corruption, so my question to you Reddit, is what are some of the most blatant, and the most subtle examples that a lot of people over look? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 19:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The person who invented the shower, had the first ever shower thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 04:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How different companies handle the "Post apocalyptic shooter genre" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 19:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What conversations would be great or terrible to have? Are there any that would be both? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As for my submission, this topic will be a great one to have! When I realized this,  I posted it to Shower thoughts, but then thought this group would be even better to talk to about it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A conversation about conversations that would be terrible or great to have, would be a great conversation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9 out of 10 people make up 90% of the population </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 15:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT, want to watch two subreddits at the same time? Listen to the Mallard! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 17:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me [24 M] with my Classmate [2? F] we started as good buddies, I asked her out, now she hates me, what happened? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 16:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I met this gal at Orientation in January. We hit it off, talking about games and the such. We continue going to class, and we joke around, talk all the time. Pretty great pals! 

Anyway, I think she's cute, but also smart, engaging, fashion forward, and ambitious. So I decide to ask her out, since we get a long so well. She turns me down, and that's that. I'm fine with it to each their own and all that Jazz, don't get pouty or anything, and I try to continue as normal right?

But it's several months in and she has been nothing but toxic too me since. Telling me not to talk to her, shooting me dirty looks every time I smile at her or wave, deleting posts from our class room group on facebook(She's the admin) and she made this guy that I got on okay with start to hate me too when they started dating soon after. (The reason she gave me for saying no was that she didn't want to date while going to school, so them dating was an extra slap on the face I guess. But I just took it as she was trying to spare my feelings, so I didn't hold it against her.)

I honestly haven't acted any differently since I asked her out. Always behaving just like when we were buddies, and at first I wanted that friendship back, now I just want her to stop being so mean too me, I mean, I'm stuck in class with her for three years. No amount of Dirty looks will change that!

   
**tl;dr**: I asked a girl out, now she hates me. What gives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I clicked the button. What now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 22:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by washing a pot too vigorously </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 16:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is more of a "yadda yadda F'd up last week" deal, but it didn't pan out as a real F up until recently.

So, I work in a bar kitchen, and if you're at the bar itself, there are a few seats where a customer can look over and just see into the kitchen. I'm asked to clean out the gravy pot, the thing that the gravy is kept heated in all day, and gets really caked on at the end of the day. 

So. I'm talking with my boss, who is on the other side of the partition while I'm just really giving it to this gravy stain, he leaves to check on a customer. So I'm just standing here, applying some elbow grease and steel wool to the stain, and a woman looks over the partition and we lock eyes, still cleaning I smile at her and continue before turning my eyes away. 

She later reports me for being obscene. Because she couldn't see me from the waist down. My boss had a good laugh at it, and to this day I hear at least one "Buy that pot some dinner before you clean it today" joke. 

Tl;Dr: I look like I'm whipping up a batch of "Special sauce" in the kitchen from the angle of my customer. Boss thinks its hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm having trouble figuring out what formulas I should use (esspecially for 4) can someone help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 02:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://docs.google.com/document/d/1EcVKG5fmv7eCB3wilKPeC-2Hos9FKRpzFmxQ6CONP5M/edit

I don't need answers if you don't feel like it. I mostly just want to know the "how". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't figure out the formula to solve these simple problems. Can anyone help? I don't need the answers, just how to figure it out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 01:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Animal facts for you and (not) your kids! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 03:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What minor things can you do, that help your focus to study/work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 20:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find if I have a game I can play, but put the characters on auto, I'm able to work and just tab back into it every now and then to check and adjust. It helps me get more productive because I get distracted less by other things.

But I want to be a better student. Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should board games and video games have their own sections? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 22:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] If you could pick a religion to follow and you were guaranteed to have its afterlife scenario actually happen when you die, what would you pick? (you would have to follow ALL the rules and morals) this is just for fun, nobody get offended please </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 16:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something you wish everyone understood about your job, or one misconception everyone has? (Serious) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 14:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is one thing you wish everyone knew about you immediately when you meet them?(serious) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 14:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, a fear, something you're proud of, a quality that people misinterpret, something awkward that you hate explains but often comes up, etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL our Teddy bears came to life to protect us from monsters under our beds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 05:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that you can kill 4 people drunk driving if your parents are rich </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 00:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CSI be like "The murder is in this picture. Zoom and enhance" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 16:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you be willing to draw this photo commemorating me getting my first Tattoo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 08:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does subscribing to Netflix help support the content I enjoy [ALL] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 21:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi. I've subscribed and am watching Daredevil. I want to see more Marvel stuff like this. So I want to know, how is my subscription helping encourage more content along these lines? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to support marvel, how does my subscribing and watching dare devil help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 21:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It has become impossible to make a trust worthy looking ad on the internet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 16:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heroes of the Dorm (MOBA tournament, prize three years college tuition.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 22:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there guys and gals. I'm Thomas McMullin, student a George Brown College's Casa Loma Campus and Captain of the "CasaLoma Knights" one of the teams representing George Brown College in the Heroes of the Storm "Heroes of the Dorm" tournament. 

Is there anyone here, who would like to play a Moba and win Three years college tuition?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I use iframe to embed my videos I get this result. Any advice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 03:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If someone from the 1800s were to arrive in the modern day, and it was your job to guide them. What would you find most difficult to explain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 19:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My foreign friend mentioned that the word "OK" looks like a little man. Now I can't not see him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 05:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Character creation for noobs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 04:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys. I'm doing a game of Pathfinder for Complete noobs, none of them even know how to make their own sheets or anything.

I was going to make a dozen characters myself, than I thought "I'd just make a predictable set."

So, I come to you guys. Can you help me make more than your standard fare, standard adventures?

Rules are, anything from core or advanced race or class 20 point buy.

No third party, they are new after all. Try not to min max, just make something fun. (Add back story if you want. I'll give rewards to players who follow it.)

I've got four done now, I'm still working on more. But I'd love to have extras so I can kill my players without feeling bad. Haha

Edit 1: Oh and all level ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I use a monster from the monster manual in my children's book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 03:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there. A friend and I want to do a children's book, and I would like to use an Aboleth in it. Does anyone know if I would be able to do that? Or is it copyright protected? 

Because, it's used in both Pathfinder and DnD, so I'm not sure.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some video game valentines for all you lovers out there </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 01:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First World DM troubles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 07:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were playing a DnD game, what neat stuff would you like to see? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 09:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a game I'm running, and I love homebrewing stuff. That means making it up from scratch for those not in the know this link has some details on what I've done. 

http://imgur.com/gallery/4Nypm

ANYWAY! Like the title says, what crazy nonsense would you enjoy seeing if you were a player? 

OR if you have been a table top player, what's some great stuff you've seen done?

Also, Sci-Fi is permitted. They're already helping an alien girl put her ship back together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many paper clips are in this Jar? (Math problem!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 03:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys. I have the chance to win 500 dollars for my college if I can figure out how many paper clips are in this jar.

http://c.studentawards.com/countforcash/images/jar.jpg

It gives measurements though!

The Jar: 6.5 litre capacity 
Length and width of 1 paperclip: 2 x 0.5 inches

I don't deserve this money more than anyone else who would be guessing at the riddle. (And it says guess.) All I can say is, I'm going for my future, and I want to take every shot I can to make it doable. 

If you guys could help me here, that would be great. And you don't even need to solve it. Just tell me what math equations I would need to use and I will do the work myself. I just don't know where to start on a problem like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moving to Toronto for school, might need work/a place to live. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 22:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there folks. Late December/Early January I'll be living in Toronto for School at George Brown College. I cannot wait!

I'm currently in the system to be funded for my education, but it hasn't been confirmed yet, so if that's not the case I will need to get a Job to work while I go to school, and though I don't have a budget yet, I at least need to look at affordable housing situations, to at least start planning.

So, does anyone know where I can look for a good part time job to have while I go to school/good neighborhoods or anyone looking for a room mate in January near the George Brown College Campus?

And if it turns out funding or what not falls through, and I have trouble finding a job, does anyone know resources I can look into so I have a place to stay for a few nights while I get myself on my feet? I've got friends but I'd rather not impose on them. And this is a chance to finally take hold of my future, so I'll live on the streets if I have too.

TL:DR - I have plans, but if they fall through, I need to make sure I have all my bases covered. Any tips for a student living in Toronto
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moving to Toronto for school might need a job/place to live </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 22:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there folks. Late December/Early January I'll be living in Toronto for School at George Brown College. I cannot wait!

I'm currently in the system to be funded for my education, but it hasn't been confirmed yet, so if that's not the case I will need to get a Job to work while I go to school, and though I don't have a budget yet, I at least need to look at affordable housing situations, to at least start planning.

So, does anyone know where I can look for a good part time job to have while I go to school/good neighborhoods or anyone looking for a room mate in January near the George Brown College Campus?

And if it turns out funding or what not falls through, and I have trouble finding a job, does anyone know resources I can look into so I have a place to stay for a few nights while I get myself on my feet? I've got friends but I'd rather not impose on them. And this is a chance to finally take hold of my future, so I'll live on the streets if I have too.

TL:DR - I have plans, but if they fall through, I need to make sure I have all my bases covered. Any tips for a student living in Toronto?

Edit 1: It's near the Casa Loma Campus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IamA (Dungeon Master(Table top games)) AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-30 20:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Organic Map? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 10:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys. I was wondering if anyone new of any maps that were Organic? I'm doing a game on Roll20 and I want to do a scenario, where the team has to enter a giant creature to kill a clutch of parasites before they become too prolific. 

It's super easy to find most fantasy maps with free resources, but I'm at a loss for this one. I can't even find a paid version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best joke with a twist you know? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 18:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like it sounds like the punchline is going to be obvious, but there's a twist to throw the "audience" off. (Keep the twist PG please. Like it might sound like a dirty story about a guy being hard while a girl sits on him, turns out he's a chair. That's a green text story, not my own joke by the way.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to build good encounters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 06:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys. Are there any resources I can use that will auto generate monsters for my group to encounter. I want to try my hand at DMing, but I have no idea how to do encounters. My style would be much more story and puzzle oriented.

When I make encounters. They're either over or under powered. (I've done a few test games. But nothing solid.)

Plus I want to do it more off the seat. Rather than plan things, right out. (Like I'll make a general story and stuff they can follow, and quests they can do) but I'd like them to be able to explore the world as they want. So that would involve me being able to generate quick encounters.

Any suggestions?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got accepted to a Programmer Analyst Course, my future starts now! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 21:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm heading to George Brown in Toronto! I'm so excited! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 20:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ballad of Ogmaw Childgutter [Pathfinder][Mythic Adventures] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 05:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you enter the tavern in the outcast city of Gobarian, you hear a Gnomish bard strumming his lute and he begins to tell a tale of the might God King, Ogmaw Childgutter.

Ogmaw had set out with his two Chorts, Zorn, and Xorn. A man of mystery, Ogmaw could disappear without a trace right in front of your eyes. (Hellcat stealth feat.)

He brought the brothers on a quest, to prove to the world one thing.

Goblins could be heroes too.

That's right. Ogmaw Childgutter, our God King. Was a Goblin. A rogue by trade. Master of the Kukuri, Ogmaw could slay any foe.

Having a feat of Leadership, he gained first Zorn, then upon a blessing from a magic Gem, Xorn arrived to aid him. For Ogmaw's tale became Mythic. (Champion, Crusader Path Ability. Plus Mythic Leadership.)

As Ogmaw gather his allies. A Minor God, Susano, a Child Terror, Kaimusume. (No literally. One shotted an Eldritch Abomination at like level 9. So broken.), the ever loyal Dragon Knight Azai Azreal, Grand Diplomat to the Goblin King, and the treacherous Varion. A summoner of Dubious intent.

Ogmaw fought with these brave allies, felling Susanos sister to claim both the Earth and Wind Gem. Wielding the earth Gem, Ogmaw carved a mountain into a castle, and city, he also erected a great wall all around the Nation of Goberian. Soon he had three hundered followers, their wives and husbands, the merchants and other trades people who came to tend to this flock, and his kingdom steadily grew. Welcoming everything from Kobolds to Ogres. Any who wanted a fresh start with a grand society.

TL;DR

Got a Goblin Rogue in a Mythic Campagin, used leadership to turn it into a mini kingmaker campagin. Took Mythic Ablities to become Immortal and a Divine Source for Clerics. 

The story of how a Goblin became a God King. (The Goblin word for king is "David Bowie.") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't want the real answer. Just by first impressions, what do you think this subreddit is about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-22 01:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What be a Pirates favorite letter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 17:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ye all must be willin' to guess Arrrr. 

But ye be wrong! 

It be the Sea! 

Yearha har har har </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti Litter Biker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 17:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game keeps sending me to the credits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 02:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys. The game wont register when I press the start button (PS3) and just keeps sending me to the credits. Anyone else having this problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fantasy character shares the truth about being happy for someone you love </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 21:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The line is from "The Great Hunt" from the Wheel of time Series. Chapter 48.
-
-
-
-
-
-
-
-
"I will hate the man you choose because he is not me, and love him if he makes you smile." - Lan Mandragoran from Robert Jordan's Wheel of Time series.

(The Great Hunt Chapter 48)

This has become very relevant for me lately. What do you all think?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your thoughts on #Wordshurt An interactive video from the government of Canada </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 21:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (CA)(Global) Government assistance programs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 15:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi folks. I saw the super popular post on the "IDA" in America, and got to thinking, what kind of things are there to help Canadians? Then I also thought, hell, what kind of things are there to help the global population at large? Post which government programs are little known, that could help give you a leg up in your nation, and I'll edit this post so people have a quick reference point.


Canada:

Did you know E.I will pay for your college education?(Not University) And still give you E.I so long as you attend school? With all luck that's what I'll be doing this January. 

United States of America:

Individual Development Account - For every dollar you put in, the government gives you three. (Up to 3k) over a three year period. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> East Coast Canuck looking to Communicate! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 21:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello ladies and Gentlemen. I'm Thomas, pleasure to meet you all. I've decided I want to reach out into the world wide web and chat with some potential new friends. 

I'd rather this go over email, rather than by address. My hand writing is not exactly well suited for communication. Haha

Anyway, I like games, love books, I enjoy to laugh and learn. Ladies or gentlemen, so long as we hit it off I'm fine with chatting. 

We could learn about one another, share stories, and funny videos. Talk about the latest happenings in our countries and share our views on the political goings on across the globe! What ever strikes our fancy.

Now, one rule I'd like to have, that goes for both you and I, one email weekly minimum. Conversations can really lose their steam after much longer than that.

Have a lovely day!

Oh, I'm also 23, if you're looking to communicate with someone within your own age bracket.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Set different alarm clock tones for each day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 15:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Isn't it a waste, that the subscribers are called "MCU Fans" and not True Believers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 04:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems way more fitting for Marvel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With all the NES style retro games, some friends and I thought... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 14:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/Wq1uMLZ.gif

The SNES deserved some love. This system carried more than a few of us through our childhoods, and it had some fantastic art. With more power than the SNES people could get really creative with pushing it to it's limits, and push it they did. Much to the joy of anyone who frequents these communities. 

In doing what they did, the SNES revolutionized most styles of games. Most notable the Platformer and the RPG. The former, is what my friends and I are working on. 

An SNES style platformer called "Michelle, Ma Belle". I say friends, but we're really strangers that have come from all corners of the internet, with one goal. To make a game. Hobbiysts doing it for fun, we've got programmers, writers, musicians, and as you can see from the link at the start there, talented artists. It's been a lot of fun so far, and we've just started. We've got a forum if anyone else wants to join (But this isn't a recruitment thread, so if there's interest I'll add our link.), but I wanted to come here, to this bastion of the SNES and ask. 

"What made the SNES era platformers great?"

Our model so far is following mostly the Megaman/Megaman X series of games, but though we're following in the style of the SNES, we're limited only by what our computers can do. So, what features made, and more importantly broke, your favourite platformers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, let's make a game! Part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 19:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so, this thread was originally over at /r/gamedev but I'm not allowed to recruit over there. That was my mistake. The mods were very nice (LordNed specifically) and he pointed me here. So... here I am, and here's the original post.

----------------------------------------



Hello ladies and gentlemen of Reddit. I am the Creative Director of Thing in a Box Studios. A brand spankin' new hobbyist group where a bunch of amateurs haven gotten together to create games. We started on the Escapist forums because someone said they were bored and wanted to make a game, and I wanted to make sure as many folks who wanted the opportunity to help produce a game, had the chance.

So I'll lay it out for you here.

We've got Artists We've got Programmers We've got Musicians And we've got Writers
And our first game is well underway. (We're planning on an october release date.)
So this post is not a "Come do our work for us" kind of thing. It's a "Want to come have fun, learn new things, and help us make a better thing" kind of thing.

The game we're working on right now is called "Michelle, Ma Belle" it's about a little girl who needs to use her Shamanic Abilities to stop dark spirits from taking over the world. It's a platformer along the lines of Megaman, when Michelle defeats the enemy Totem Spirits, she gains new power and new forms. (And our sprite artist, Twosage, he is a genie. He's got some amazing SNES style sprites for our use. Michelle is so cute!)
Anyway. For those of you that want to learn new things, who might be studying programming and want to practice/have something cool on their portfolio, to those people who want to see their art come to life visually or in audio, and most importantly, to those people who want to have fun, meet new people and make something cool. Come on down.

And for people with more experience, that could teach us? We'd love for you to come over, take part, and help us grow. Even if it's just with one post for a list of "Tips" you'd like to give us.

We're looking forward to seeing you there.

Also, feel free to AMA.

Edit: http://w11.zetaboards.com/GameDevExperiment/index/

Forgot the link. HAH!

Edit 2: Hey folks. I'm totally ok with it if you want to downvote the thread, that's the whole point of Reddit, to 
make it so the more interesting things reach the top right? But I'd also love if you'd let me know afterwards what about this thread bugs you. It's the only way I can improve it so I can reach more folks like Azexp, who'd like some practice, or to learn new things.

Edit 3: Here's our Github info, and where you can go on our forums to sign up to contribute
https://github.com/Ylla-/TotemQuest/ here is the thread where you can ask to contribute. http://w11.zetaboards.com/GameDevExperiment/topic/10491050/4/#new

Edit 4: This game is free ware, not commercial. We really are just doing this for fun. And there's not a lot to show yet, as we're early in the project. (We've got a gameplay engine, you can even test it in a prototype stage. On our Github)

And we've got story we've worked on, (Which you're welcome to contribute too.) and some of the best sprite work I've seen for a game of this style. I hope to see you all there!

Edit 5: For the development section, our members have voted on having it viewable by members only. Just thought I'd give you folks a heads up about that now, since some folks seem to have been upset by being surprised by that fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Reddit, we're making a freeware game to share with the world! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 18:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, this thread is being posted over here, because one fellow "InteractionArtist" invited me to share it with you guys. I've already got it on another subreddit.

The original is here http://redd.it/2etdxr 

-----------

Hello ladies and gentlemen of Reddit. I am the Creative Director of Thing in a Box Studios. A brand spankin' new hobbyist group where a bunch of amateurs haven gotten together to create games. We started on the Escapist forums because someone said they were bored and wanted to make a game, and I wanted to make sure as many folks who wanted the opportunity to help produce a game, had the chance.

So I'll lay it out for you here.

We've got Artists We've got Programmers We've got Musicians And we've got Writers
And our first game is well underway. (We're planning on an october release date.)
So this post is not a "Come do our work for us" kind of thing. It's a "Want to come have fun, learn new things, and help us make a better thing" kind of thing.

The game we're working on right now is called "Michelle, Ma Belle" it's about a little girl who needs to use her Shamanic Abilities to stop dark spirits from taking over the world. It's a platformer along the lines of Megaman, when Michelle defeats the enemy Totem Spirits, she gains new power and new forms. (And our sprite artist, Twosage, he is a genie. He's got some amazing SNES style sprites for our use. Michelle is so cute!)

Anyway. For those of you that want to learn new things, who might be studying programming and want to practice/have something cool on their portfolio, to those people who want to see their art come to life visually or in audio, and most importantly, to those people who want to have fun, meet new people and make something cool. Come on down.

And for people with more experience, that could teach us? We'd love for you to come over, take part, and help us grow. Even if it's just with one post for a list of "Tips" you'd like to give us.

We're looking forward to seeing you there.

Also, feel free to AMA.

Edit: http://w11.zetaboards.com/GameDevExperiment/index/

Forgot the link. HAH!

Edit 2: Hey folks. I'm totally ok with it if you want to downvote the thread, that's the whole point of Reddit, to 
make it so the more interesting things reach the top right? But I'd also love if you'd let me know afterwards what about this thread bugs you. It's the only way I can improve it so I can reach more folks like Azexp, who'd like some practice, or to learn new things.

Edit 3: Here's our Github info, and where you can go on our forums to sign up to contribute

https://github.com/Ylla-/TotemQuest/ here is the thread where you can ask to contribute. 

http://w11.zetaboards.com/GameDevExperiment/topic/10491050/4/#new

Edit 4: This game is free ware, not commercial. We really are just doing this for fun. And there's not a lot to show yet, as we're early in the project. (We've got a gameplay engine, you can even test it in a prototype stage. On our Github)

And we've got story we've worked on, (Which you're welcome to contribute too.) and some of the best sprite work I've seen for a game of this style. I hope to see you all there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] How do I find out if a part of a song is copyrighted? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 15:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, let's make a game! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 14:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can a level 1 sorcerer, cast level 4 spells and help with a build </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 15:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a Human Sorcerer, for my level 1, I take the favoured class bonus, to take a 4th level spell, 

Favoured class bonus text - "Add one spell known from the sorcerer spell list. This spell must be at least one level below the highest spell level the sorcerer /can/ cast."

Rules for a sorcerer to learn and cast a spell - "To learn or /cast/ a spell, a sorcerer must have a Charisma score equal to at least 10 + the spell level."

My Charisma Score is 20, making my Modifier + 5, which gives me 1 5th level spell per day as per the ability score modifier table.

So, I take it that the highest level spell I can cast is 5, because I have 1 per day. Does that mean, with my favoured class bonus, the highest level spell I can learn at the moment is 4th?

Alright, so, I prefer to rp with my character, rather than Min Max. I've got this shy little farm girl, 7 wisdom, doesn't know squat about the world. Suddenly, comes into her own as a sorcerer do to ancient blood. What I'd love to do, is have three bloodlines in her. Via Cross Blooded and the Eldricth heritage feats.

One stipulation is, I want her to have the "Impossible" blood line, as one of hers. She's going to be an item crafter. 

What are two other blood lines that I should go for? What would be some good spells and feats? Traits? (I'm probably going to go with the traits that make it cheaper for me to make things, and I'm going to make a ton of wands, because I've never used wands. Any tips on those too?) I'm starting at level one, so I don't need the whole build. Just a good starting point.

OH! And the DM is totally open to fair homebrew stuff, and 3rd party material. No guns. Not that I want to use any anyway. lol

Thanks for your help Reddit!

EDIT: Ok, so I've got that sorted out, thanks to some very knowledgable people. 

Now, can anyone suggest a good build for me to work on? Starting at level 1 with the Impossible Bloodline.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ok Runners, I need your help to be the best looking Face ever! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 23:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm new and going to start a game next Monday, they need a Face. Incidently that is my favorite style of character. BUT I've only ever played Shadow Run Returns as far as knowing how the system goes. So I'm thinking Shaman. Thoughts. Ideas. Suggestions? Keep in mind I know little to no Slang. And even less about the system. Reading the book as we speak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
