<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1101</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 03:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he saw a movie once? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 03:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Canadian and was produced for dirt cheap by a team of maybe 13 people. So they'd just fart out a season whenever Canada's Comedy Central needed half-hours to fill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 02:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> World War Zimmerman and The Hobbit are probably tied for first.

Zimmerman because it wasn't funny, felt like it would never end, and is a perfect representation of modern South Park's baseline idiocy.

The Hobbit because of its sloppy storytelling, bad running gags, and dated message. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 01:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude you're the first person i've ever seen on reddit mention that show. [my username is from kevin spencer.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fo2zU-OdtYA) show is atrocious. but it's like so obscure. even though it went for 7 seasons. ahahaha can't believe it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 22:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...

...

...

...lol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 16:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/southpark is an echo chamber. This episode sucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 16:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, he did American Dad! a few years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 16:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm surprised. This sub is very hyperbolic with its love. So I like seeing some negativity at the top just for once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 01:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> um this thread is NOT home!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 01:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not relevant. Could you wait until you get home to bust out your Avatar hateboner? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 23:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um... I think it's pretty silly they're announcing every cameo filmed. I'm hardly upset about it, and it has nothing to do with /r/movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 23:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not about spoilers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 21:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they have to announe every damn cameo? Publicity overdose right here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 19:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess its sort of relevant, but the fact that it's #1 right now is pretty bizarre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 19:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sharknado 3 being my personal favorite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 18:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone that was in my fifth grade class once said they had a crush on me, but they admitted that like 6 years later. Am I cool yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 16:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/rickandmorty is the worst TV show subreddit in existance. I challenge anyone to find a more hyperbolic and embarassing circlejerk anywhere on this site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 16:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grilfriend, more like Amazon, xD

...have we really regressed to the point that fucking "I have a girlfriend" is a phrase that has to be looked at with skepticism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> south park season 17 proof of purchase gets owned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 01:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 23:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see the problem. Oh no, a... dick gravestone. How dare someone memorialize someone positively. Did he write it from beyond the grave? Who cares?

There are many reasons to dislike Bob Kane, but I don't think shitting on his gravestone is the best way to get that across </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 19:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's it even relevant outside of lazily parroting SP for upboats? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 04:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i saw it too. We're all cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another zero substance AskReddit post on the front page... sigh. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 23:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 20:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Freedom Isn't Free" is a common idiom. So it's likely Team America just got it from that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 19:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm able to enjoy the older episodes though, and NO, I don't get every reference. 

So the increasing US-centric news dependance just makes me sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 19:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad excuse.

Source: not American, dig tons of American shows without having to "adapt". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 17:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Carbon monoxide makin me choke" - Weird Al's parents </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 03:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds deeper and less mushmouthed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 17:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's been the show for at least the past nine seasons. Are you really surprised? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 13:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you 100%. And I thought the show fell off spectacularly during the second and third quarters of the season, too, so I ain't biased, I swear it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 08:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like crap. Another topical issue, what fun. Can't wait for SP to take a brave stanc... lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 22:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw an article the other day titled "Why Aren't More Black Voters Feeling the Bern?"

...oof. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Martian The Martian The Martian The Martian The Martian The Martian The Martian The Martian The Martian The Martian The Martian The Martian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 20:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 18:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes, it wasn't meant to be funny. I too was gripped by the drama Phil being an unlikable jackass every episode... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 16:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the first one is definitely a joke. Peter says "this is like when I got that expired coupon" and then it does a cutaway to him fighting the chicken elaborately. The length is the joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 17:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did. (from Oliver Twist, though) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 14:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's his middle name. His first name was Granville. What would you pick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 01:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 17:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He isn't though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 15:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Glover was born in 1964 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 19:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the creators have said it wasn't. To get laughter, they'd play pre-taped episodes for an audience.

If you want a show that NEVER used an audience, look no further than ALF. The format of the show (the ALF puppet was prone to frequent malfunctions, and had to placed in specially made trap doors so the puppeteer could operate it) meant that taping in front of a live audience would've been severely impractical, as scenes as simple as ALF talking to someone might require as much as 15 takes just to get right. Because of this, all laughter was insert during planned pauses during audio post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 06:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baking Bad is a Family Guy episode, and well, the character of Joe is in it. So I guess his comment stands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 06:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMDB can disable that itself. https://secure.imdb.com/register-imdb/siteprefs - under "Number of TV episodes from the same series to display" select "None". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 00:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These two are the ones that have thrown me the most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 23:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> everything appears nominal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are two TV shows that people might be surprised to know were once both airing new episodes at the same time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 23:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Family Guy and Mystery Science Theater 3000 is my most interesting one. 

They seem so far apart... but not really, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 21:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a chrome app for this. https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/imdb-hide-episode-spoiler/chiakepmphnoipoamanblmjmnigmgbkh?hl=en

I think a Redditor made it, actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 06:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's generally thought of as the last truly great film noir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 21:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 18:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds bad. No wonder Reddit never talks about him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 17:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Havent heard of him. Does he have any overlooked gems under his belt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 21:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> older = old??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 18:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah especially when there are a lot of people OVER 76 who are still making films. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 04:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/wescraven/status/638161499043688448 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 19:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still gettin' that sweet comment karma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 08:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 08:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the unwritten rules of Reddit is that trashing South Park instantly nets you downvotes.

Personally I think it was consistently funny up until season 6 or 7 or so, then it began to fumble a bit by season 10, and now it's just wildly hit-and-miss, with the worst episodes ("The Hobbit"/"World War Zimmerman") being borderline unwatchable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 16:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They made Stan a fuckin moron last season. Like that subplot where he makes people invisible by snapping, what the hell was that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 16:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. It was canned after season 2 but the decision was reversed last-minute. Then, after season 3, it was canned for good, but Adult Swim reruns and DVDs were doing so well they brought it back, and it hasn't been canned again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 23:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to be happy about this, but the TBS season was a marked decline over the FOX seasons. There was just a continuous feel of staleness throughout the entire thing. I'll wait to see if the next season is good before getting excited about this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 09:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree. Vote Mark Bair 1933. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 05:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 03:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adult Swim tweeted it out with a picture of a pair of glasses, with the text "These goggles will help you see the end". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 01:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe somebody'll repost it and reap more karma than I? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 01:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 18:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Don't learn anything about the gunman! Turn off the TV if there's gunman coverage!" Seems like he doesn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 22:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked Cinema Sins until they made all their videos 20+ minutes. Watching a video that long that's ENTIRELY nitpicks is just tiring. And the videos used to have a jokey, non-serious vibe, but now they're fully committed tojust nitpicking seriously. There are occasional good jokes/observations but it just gets tiring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 18:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not comfortable to fully say that. I think Summit and Lionsgate are just bad at marketing. Their movie Child 44 was based on a book and also bombed like crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 18:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Landis isn't being very objective here. To paraphrase: "American Ultra is, honestly, a good movie. The fact that it bombed obviously means the end of original ideas as we know it."

Uh, let's see. It tried to market Kristen Stewart to an audience generally against Kristen Stewart (and what box office credence does she have outside of Twilight - which was already established and didn't depend on her?) and Eisenberg is pretty hit and miss fo most people. It got rather poor reviews. The marketing was pretty sparse. These all seem like legitimate reasons for a movie to fail.

So what if your movie has "big stars, a fun idea, and honestly, [was] a good movie..." (his words)? All the above factors seem like reasons a movie would bomb. There's very little here that has ANY sort of draw. I definitely believe he's shifting the blame a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 18:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yet it bombed because horror fans will go see any kind of crap and because more marketing was put behind Hitman.

This doesn't seem to be comparable to "original ideas don't make bank!" though. I think the piss marketing for this movie did it in. Didn't even know it existed until I saw a preview for it at the theater... like two days ago. (And I don't want to see it because it looks bad.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 17:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kaydyn is an orgy of letters. No two Ys should ever be that close, and the fact that the second Y is a substitute (the Y DIDN'T NEED TO BE THERE) is inexcusable. Michael sounds nice and the letters all go together moderately well. I'm a sucker for "ae"s, one of the better looking letter combination in this English language of ours. But if you're a Kaydyn fan, it's OK! We still have people trying to ruin it by pulling a Kaydyn and sticking a Y in there (looking at YOU, Mychael Danna). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 08:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Simpsons as a whole is monstrously influential. It may have gotten bad, but the influence it had (and the phenomenal first eight or so seadons) is still active today. It's earned its stripes.

Rick and Morty never would've existed without The Simpsons, and it is unlikely that it will have even a quarter of an impact The Simpsons did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 08:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? Why can't a new show be fucking awesome and worthy of acclaim until proven shitty in a later season? e.g. Lost, Dexter.

A show in its first season is still growing. These high ratings are not represantive of a GREAT SHOW, just a first season that turned out to be really good. Whereas with shows like The Simpsons, the entire show has been scrutinized and ends up with an 8, because this is something that can be accurately judged. Rick and Morty being so high is a circlejerky embarassment. It has one season and a second season is currently airing. All that can be judged is a show that's still brand new and still growing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 23:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It still shows up, but it never gets far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 23:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Around two years ago it was almost inescapable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 22:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sort of clashes with the TIL rules which state not to repost TILs that have made it high up in the past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 20:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a legitimate point. I feel that even though it is likely someone will see a heavily-reposted TIL for the first time on the 72548th repost, it doesn't justify regurgitating unoriginal TILs tons of times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 20:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FWIW I haven't defended piracy, so it's not the same people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 20:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh come on, I never said anything about being MAJORLY distressed by a repost. I just think it's irritating, because I've seen this way more than twice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 19:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you might as well post it here now. ;'| </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 19:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this always comes up. "I wouldn't have seen it if this wasn't reposted." But seriously? There's a possibility someone out there hasn't seen the Steve Buscemi 9/11 firefighter TIL... doesn't mean it's not an unoriginal and oversaturated thing to post. I think there should be a limit to how many times a TIL can be posted, because, hell, even posting the same TIL every day might result in someone seeing it for the first time after the 3rd day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 09:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever movies that just came out are brought up in recent threads, Man from UNCLE is seemingly always mentioned as being an Overlooked Gem that you should Totally See to fight the studios.

BTW, in the time it took you to read this comment, you could have seen Man from UNCLE 816572057529682 times, shame on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 08:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit sucked this show's dick for over a year

Wait, that stopped? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 06:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, the presence of Angry Video Game Nerd at #87... this list should not be taken with much credence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 06:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too high imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 05:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gnomeo   Juliet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 08:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well according to wiki his name is "Jerry S. Parr". Close enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 16:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS SUB HAS LITERLY BECOME SRS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 08:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, this is the simple one that makes me feel old. For reference, I started my IMDB account in May 1999, and I recently had a conversation with a guy who was born in May 2001. This guy, who is fully lucid and can make concious decisions, is younger than my fucking IMDB account, what the fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 01:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I agree. I think Dewey Cox is decent but it meanders a bit and wears out its welcome by the end (the arduous extended cut isn't any better). I WANTED to discuss that aspect of the movie, but nope, it's just people regurgitating "the wrong kid died" over and over.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 16:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...what was the meaning before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 03:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not negative... it's just probably the reason why it's not getting tons of upvotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 01:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's not a very original thought and has been in EVERY thread related to AM? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 16:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like it got deleted though before it got very far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A "The Big Bang Theory" assistant director is suing for age discrimination after his workload was reduced without agreement, his job was given to younger people, and he was eventually terminated despite no provided instances in which his performance was insufficient. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 04:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 19:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Most of the people in this 1936 movie are dead. When you watch this movie, you are seeing dead people act."

...who cares? (and it's not true anyway) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 19:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only sitcom I know of that didn't use a live studio audience but still had a laugh track is ALF. Are there really that many that never had actual audiences? I'd imagine the actual number has tapered off in recent years, because really the only multi-cam sitcoms with laugh tracks airing today are Chuck Lorre shows, and those are all filmed live with audiences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 19:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh... like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 21:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least most of the comments are callin OP out for his BS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 17:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the replies to that comment is Alec Sokolow (who co-wrote both Garf movies) calling Bill Murray out for lying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> cedric the entertainer/sally struthers sex tape leaked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 04:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Straight Outta Compton: Universal offers to reimburse theaters for extra security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 03:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man in minion costume gets what he deserves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 04:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Farley version of Shrek leaked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 02:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> minion gets owned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 04:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
