<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2469</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 14:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is how to master the graphic tablet in 3 steps. 
https://youtu.be/40j97KX0V6s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new shampoo brand :P, digital painting, 500MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 20:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 07:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're welcome, though it's rather "who risks nothing gets nothing"... because it is an investment system that still risks to collapse at any time...lol...but I love my hobby so I decided to risk it and if it doesn't work, I'd just say "I deserved the exposure". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Engelsrufer, Digital Painting, 500MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 20:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 21:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was pretty hilarious, I think you summarised things well but you need to be more expressive, need to practice more on how to sound natural :) ...good luck with your channel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I failed to draw Rihanna but I still drew someone :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 15:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] How to make digital painting with Clip Studio Paint Pro (Basics) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 10:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 08:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're welcome :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lotus Elf, Digital Painting, 500MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 07:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 15:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think there is any specific rules that you should follow...but I think it's better to wait to have more subscribers before inviting people to follow on social medias. I used annotation to tell my views to follow me on my SMs but it was pretty useless. You can always link those media to your channel and the visitor will see the link in the corner of your channel art. It's better to grow social media following separately by being active on them, and then plugging your videos there will give you additional views :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 01:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> then you should focus first on how to get more subs then, post video frequently and regularly...share your stuff though social medias (Facebook, google+, ....)...it's difficult to know how you grow if you haven't even started to grow yet...lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Valentine special Part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 22:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Special valentine comics part 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 22:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 22:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the best measure is the number of active subscribers...that is the percentage of video views/likes/comments you get from your subscribers...if people are subscribing but are not watching then that's gonna slow you down instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 20:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at the "Ad impressions" and "Ad clicks" in your google adsense account, number of views are meaningless if those are small or zero...if you haven't linked and adsense account, this might be the time to do so as it is very informative and that's the only way for you to get money anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mermaid in the Moonlight, Digital Media, 500MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 19:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 19:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome ^_^ ... you're the one to judge what works the best for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 06:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes...and you can have multiple adgroup in one campaign...all of my ads are in-display so I make the cost per clicks really cheap (ex: max 0.05$). It means only people who are really interested click on it and we only pay when they watch at least 30s.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 22:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really can't understand why you making this kind of video...I didn't get or understand any messages you try to convey with it, all I saw was 3D characters punching each other :-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 16:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you mean 30s not 30 minutes ^_^ ... well, your message in the video is pretty clear, good luck with your giveaway.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Midnight Butterflies, Digital Painting, 200MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 21:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 00:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well it was kind of funny but your title is a bit misleading...do not start with such a long sentence at the beginning it feels like the video is not narrated...you talk about 18 reasons but I couldn't count them...you should have some counting system such at 1st reason... ,2nd reason..., 3rd...   you are talking too fast and with no breaks couldn't follow anything and you only talk about yourself all the time. You ONLY put the motivation for other people in the end so I think this video is more about how YOU love yourself and not at all telling the other people about why they should love themselves...I understand you are focusing on you to give the example, but it's really misleading...at least state what the people should do first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 14:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really depends on what you think would be the best and on what is your audience expectation...though it is often advised to have a separate channel for different projects...However, I think if you have your diverse content from the very beginning and build your audience upon that expectation, i.e. expectation of many themes then it should be fine...but if you started out with only "Topic A" from the beginning and then switch to/add "Topic B" midway, you will make your subscribers re-evaluate the reason they sign up for your channel, it's fine if they like "Topic B" but you risk to loose them if they don't like it...so another theme or another topic that they didn't sign up from the beginning is always subjected to re-evaluation...hope this helps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 06:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is Manga Studio 5 or Clip studio Paint pro by Smith Micro :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 13:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK :) lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 12:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, that's really pretty :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 11:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My advices would be straight on this issue...DO NOT motivate them!!! ... If you are the only ones doing the work, just walk out of that group, it's not about friendship anymore, you decided to open the channel together, so why would you do all the work while all the others slack off? that's unfair and unhealthy...I would advice to just walk away from that group...opening an account is as simple as having a google mail, so right now that you are still small, I suggest you walk away and create your own, it's together from the beginning or nothing at all...I would be pissed off if I were in that kind of group, I would have left a long long long time ago :) ... hope this helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 11:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol...I think your message is for excellentsamuraid, right! you replied to my comment :) but I understand you are on your mobile so it's just an accident. 
Those people who just spend their time spreading negativity must be banned from online, I always say if one can't say something constructive or nice, then one should just not say anything :-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 10:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that's quite a long post you have there...even though I empathise with your feelings I cannot say I agree with your plans...I think youtube is one of the most stressful and hardest online business, so if your moral is not straight hard rock, you gonna get more depression...you cannot go and market your channel with the mind set that you want some compassion from others, keep working hard on the quality even if you do not have the means, I saw some of your vids and I have to say that you got to shorten them and behave more lively while speaking, if you sound so bored then the the viewers are not gonna give you their time of the day. We all know that we need a certain amount of active subscribers to boost our channel up, now can you imaging 1000 people subscribing just because you want their compassion? that is impossible, you may reach 20 or 50 people but those are not gonna help you if they didn't subscribe out of their own will...Now for the depression part, boosting self confidence and self esteem is what you need...try out some guided meditations, there are many on youtube that helps you to lift your self esteem and confidence. Do some sports, even running in the park can help...you should make and post your videos with the mindset that you ARE already SATISFIED and you do not care about views or subscriptions of whatever, because you enjoyed making the videos...then promote your videos one by one in social networks, there are plenty you can use, but remember there is something called karma...if you do not give feedback to anyone you cannot expect anyone to give you back...it doesn't have to be a one to one exchange, but just the more you give, the more you receive....Hope this helps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 08:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks delicious :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 16:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I drew Adele in a new pose using 2 reference pictures ... would love some feedbacks :)
https://youtu.be/8lk93bvrgsE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 09:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderful art, I love the spiky shape :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 09:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing :) ...though this kind of thing is really not my cup of tea, just to make sure I don't destroy anything...I always ask somebody else to take care of my hardware materials ... lol ... some closed caption would have been useful though, and maybe next time, you could include some steps into it...something like Step 1 ... , Step 2..., ... it would make your video lighter and more engaging...and then summarise the steps at the end of the video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 12:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) yes, these are my fanart practices </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3rd Art Journey (currently at 6th), Digital Painting, 64.5mMB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 07:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 20:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice painting ^_^ ... I enjoyed the process...it was informative, I didn't know there was so much blending techniques involved in oil paintings :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 16:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are doing pretty good so far considering you aren't using any ads but still got so many subscribers in a few month...I don't really have anything to suggest except that you should perhaps take one step back make some deep video assessment and try to understand the reason you got so many subscribers in the first place...perhaps repeating the same process would help you get back on the run :D ... if your channel wasn't appealing enough in the first place, why would all those people subscribe...keep uploading content on a regular basis and do not worry about the views, your best statistics would be when 10% of your subscribers watch your new uploads (according to some advices I found) ... hope this helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 10:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sorry but I'm gonna have to disagree with the type of content you are making and monetising...there are more things than music to worry about...for one, you are putting tones of footage cut and pieces from other videos and that's just heading straight to copyright infringement claims...second, you are totally absent, type of videos like that are meant to be narrated and all there is are text for us to read, so it is highly unattractive, mainly because we have to read the long text and follow the video at the same time...I suggest you start narrating your stuff and include closed captions...Hope this helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 10:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Video Creators (Tim Shmoyer) explained that no matter the number of subscriber you have, you are not gonna get all of them to watch your new uploads, in fact he said that a statistic of 10% views coming from subscribers is already really good...which means if you have 1K subscribers then 100 views is already really good.
I think changing content type all the time is not a healthy way to grow a channel...but since you decided to settle for animation, I guess you should be fine...and wow, you've been on youtube since 2006, but still haven't reached your goal, I applause your perseverance  ^_^ ...I've been only there for 7 months and already giving myself some ultimatum because it's totally nerve wracking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 15:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> either it's an error from youtube or you really just need to wait :D ... wait a a few and see if it gets fixed...sometimes after I upload my vids, the quality is really low, but after a day or two they turn to the good quality I made them...the system processing is a bit lagging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Halloween candies, digital art, 500MB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 15:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 14:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well as you said, it is impossible to please everyone...that's indeed just the game, and we all have to swallow the bitter test :) I guess it would be better if you focus producing content similar to those that gets more views and people like though. But most of all you should also just enjoy doing your stuff so that you do not get disappointed by whatever outcome is.

I often use google Adwords to advertise my stuff, but overall I get a like-dislike ratio of 4:1 on my videos, i.e. I get 1 dislike every time I get 4 likes. There is really nothing I can do about the dislike since I don't know what their really disliked about my vids, but I always enjoy making more and more video and make sure to make the best videos I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 16:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always start with the outlines of the face, then the eyebrows - the nose - the lips - the eyes in the end, but I go back and forth and correct as I go ^_^
To cure an art block, you should take a break, do not even force yourself to draw anything, go out often and breath fresh air...wait for the block to go away by itself :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 16:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> beautiful 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 06:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many layers of cosmetics...lol ...it can't possibly be healthy ...  it was funny and engaging, you seem to be comfortable with the camera...I don't really have anything to suggest since it is not my domain but good luck with your channel :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 23:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds good and original, though it's not something I would listen too many times...if possible I'd rather you focus on making the lyrics's pronunciation, it's a bit hard to understand the synthesiser, though I see you already noticed that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 17:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was really hilarious ... I personally think you should stick with cooking vids and continue putting all your humours there ... lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 19:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderful video, thank you very much for sharing, it was highly informative and very enjoyable at the same time ^_^. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 20:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice parody :) ... keep up the good work 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 07:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much for the feedback. I'll check on video length in the future :) ... and yes selling some tshirt would be great, I'll make sure to do that when I'm more settled on youtube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 07:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much :) ...yes, I was far from the mic, in fact I didn't plan on recording my voice in the beginning, but I just suddenly felt like doing it...so I just used my computer mic, but I got a microphone now and I think it should be fine...I'll invest more on the video length in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Review Video] This is my first tutorial on digital painting so I would like to get some criticism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 19:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello all,

Here is my first tutorial on digital painting. It targets anyone who is really just starting out digital paintings, so it's a tutorial for super beginners
https://youtu.be/9y2xUqZ2qK8

I decided to add a new type of content to my channel to attract more audience. I was really nervous while recording it and I couldn't get over it so I'm no longer sure about the quality of my voice. The sound might be a bit off because didn't use a microphone, I recorded directly with my computer, though I went to buy a microphone today.
In general I think I did my best with it so I like it anyhow but I still would like other people's opinion. 

Two reviews I did today:
https://www.reddit.com/r/youtubers/comments/41uynf/channel_critique_i_did_a_week_of_daily_videos/
https://www.reddit.com/r/youtubers/comments/41uyak/review_video_the_big_cheat_cookie_challenge/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 19:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are doing pretty good with respect to the number of views you got this week...you get hundreds of views with 7 videos in one week instead 1 video in months. I really wish I could do the same, but it's impossible for me. I read somewhere that posting a video as often as possible is one of the key to success...so I think you should just keep this up if you can. I also think the video lengths, the sounds and thumbnails are quite fine.

I'll just spend a bit more time to think more about the short stories to tell if I were you. The thing is for example, you have the video about "tee" but it's really just you preparing and drinking your tee...maybe add a bit more to that story, for example "why you drink tee?" "why not coffee?" or put a small gag in there. I also remarked for your video on hiking that you spend 3/4 of the video inside the car, which is not really what I would call hiking... I would skip that whole car thing and just post shoot from the mountain.

If you keep this up and try out many things, you'll increase your chance to get a viral video and that will be when everything turns into your favour. Hope this helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 15:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I was rather talking about fictional story that are invented by you...I meant how about you invent fictional stories to narrate on your channel...but I do understand that that's what you wanna focus on, it was just a suggestion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 13:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean youtube automatically detects the term "Word War 2" and decides that it's not eligible for monetisation? what if you try remove it from the title and key words and description, if it is still not eligible after that, the problem is surely something else. But I also suspect youtube checks the content of the audio, in that case try to make another video talking about the "World War 2" but replace it with another term. Or maybe it is just that the knowledge of "World War 2" is considered as something not to make profit of since any informations about history and the past might have already been published somewhere. So youtube assumes by default that you are not bringing anything new. How about working on FICTIONAL characters and stories instead?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 04:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you very much for the feedback...I'll check on them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 18:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to live in there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 11:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do not look at the views, look at the ad "Impression", you do not get paid per views but "per ad views"... If you have 500 views but 0 ad impression number then you are not earning anything...and even when you have ad impressions, look at the number of clicks, usually on my account even when there is ad impression the money I get is almost nothing when the number of clicks is 0, and it drastically increases when I get clicks...  I don't really understand how their algorithm work, because the analytic on youtube is different, however the total earning is relatively the same so I don't bother about it.

Hope this helps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 08:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you very much for the advice :) ... I'll see what I can do about this...the greatest problem when it comes to tutorials is that, there are already so many other youtubers that are doing them so great...I am even still following them...lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 22:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really understand what you mean by fast-paced...it looks like a normal paced video to me...and the cartoons are pretty static...have you ever heard about the channel of "watchwellcast", link here https://www.youtube.com/user/watchwellcast

I think you can learn one or two things from them :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 18:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry but the tittle confused me quite a bit..."Never quit" is a too broad term for the content you are showing on this video...but oh well, great save anyways :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 18:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, so here is my show off of the month, would love to hear some feedbacks about it...it's the second part of my drawing process of a "Lotus Elf"... feel free to look in my channel if you wanna see the other parts https://youtu.be/KMAWRv4E3Eo
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 17:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much the the feedback...I'm really glad you liked them :)

lol...actually I only have a very few of these slightly sexually suggestive stuff but SADLY these are the videos that obtain the most clicks and views via Adwords, which I absolutely need in order to get a maximum exposure...I tried to change them but everything collapsed so I'll have to keep them for a while but I'll make sure not to overdo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 17:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much for the feedback and the compliment...I'll make sure to elaborate on these points :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Channel Critique] Tell me what you think about my channel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 12:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello guys,

I've been regularly posting video for around 5 months. It's basically an art channel picturing the evolution of my artwork and at some point I hope to be able to give some tutorials.

I'm just wondering what you think about it and if you could give some advise for improvement.
https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCTXfr3wxAMV5TezyqYP7INg
Most of my views so far comes from advertisements I bought via google Adwords because I just decided to invest money in it...

Here are two reviews I did
https://www.reddit.com/r/youtubers/comments/40ecx3/review_video_just_starting_and_would_love_some/
https://www.reddit.com/r/youtubers/comments/40h33z/review_video_raynjay_gaming_first_video/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 21:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are pretty good so far...you are comfortable with the camera and your voice is pretty organic...keep up the good work :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 21:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, I like your channel, not really my stuff of interest but your videos are pretty cool (watched some). Here is my channel

https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCTXfr3wxAMV5TezyqYP7INg

Send me a private message there if you want me to draw your cartoon character...you should also send me an example of what you are looking for thought otherwise it will just look like those in the video bellow

https://youtu.be/l-m_ioqYm9k

It's for free but I'll have a couple of conditions that I prefer discussing on youtube private message.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 20:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll save play time if you do not list these ingredients in your video...I think you should just put all the ingredients together in a single short shot and go directly into the cooking...the ingredients can be written in the description and lead your views to read the description  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 20:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was cute, thanks for sharing :)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 20:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I hate putting words into my videos, I prefer using youtube annotations...but then again annotations are not that appealing :) ... well you are welcome, hard work pay off one says and good luck for your challenge of 1 videos a week ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 19:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they fit perfectly with each other...as an artist, I could say it's really inspiring :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 19:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your channel about? Could you link it here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 19:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the quality is good and the graphic is awesome too...but you should relax a bit more while speaking do not end up sounding like a robot :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 19:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's some really cute game ... it reminds me of angry birds...

The video graphic looks good and I think it is OK to be goofy and laugh around it make it look real, just be yourself.

One thing I can say though is that the voice of your girlfriend is much lauder than yours, maybe it's a mic problem...it kind of break the balance...I think your mic level is good enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 19:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mmmmhhh...I'm not sure I got what you wanted to say in the video, you say summary of what you did in year 2015 but I don't really get what you mean by these short scenes...did you mean it was what you did in your private life or what you did in your videos? 

Beside that you wrote June 2016 instead of 2015 or am I just seeing wrong...lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 02:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really familiar with gaming videos...but I think I could say that your narration sounds good and the video looks good in general...However, I think the video is too long, it's really risky to have it so long because it will impact your watch time, try to do some research on ideal video length, I read somewhere that around 5 min would be the best...though I never could keep mine so short, so I break them down in consistent pieces and try keep each one under 10 min as much as possible. Also try to be a little bit more lively while speaking, if you are too calm like that the whole time, all the more in an action game, you risk to make the viewers loose focus.  
Hope this helped, cheers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 20:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been using a Huion H610 pro for almost a year now, and it works just fine for me...that tablet is under $100.

The only most tricky and "must" part is that one has to meticulously follow the driver installation manual...but I got that really carefully :) ... though there are unboxing tutorials and more reviews online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 20:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of course...that's only natural :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 18:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 16:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha...really hilarious, now I am thinking about responding to spam emails as well when I get bored ... lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 16:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing shots, the music is also really calming...definitely added to my liked videos. Thank you for sharing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 15:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So cute...thanks for sharing...I love cats so very much and he is so adorable :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
