<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2728</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im late as hell, but when i was a kid i lived in a house that had woods right next to them, legit 20 meteres or so from the left side of our house. My brothers and i would often explore it along with our bestfriend who was also our neighbour. Well one day it was me, my older brother, and neighbour. I remember we got some type of lightsaber looking toys and were excited to play with them in the woods. Well were walking when all of a sudden we see a hunter, dressed on old looking hunting gear which seemed extremely odd i forget the weapon he was carrying but we froze and stared at eachother for quite sometime. All of a sudden he started sprinting towards us and we were sprinting the fuck out of there, all i remember is seeing him get stuck in some old rusty animal trap and start yelling in pain. When i returned sometime later the trap was still there extemely rusty. I have no idea what to make of the situation. I know over the years the the memory changed and everything may not be 100% accurate but my brother remembers it as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanna know what you did but i feel like its better if i didnt know lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the one thing you have done in your life that was purely adrenaline driven and you couldnt believe you could physcically accomplish after the fact? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your best and most nostalgic childhood memory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you were smart about it and got away, who knows what would have happened if you didnt react how you did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this questions is asked fairly often, however, i realized everyone has had these experiences and i can never get enough of reading/hearing them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the scariest and/or most unexplainable event you have ever experienced? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just busted the biggest nut of all time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Learning shit is for nerds and jocks, and last time i checked...im have a pussy." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol i was watching  chat went crazy and that was only like 5 minutes ago surprised its already on reddit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone just called pocket queens the dishwashers.......LMAO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rodney Dangerfield - No Respect (1995) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 07:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh damn no way haha thanks! This is pretty good but along with this i was think also a 'war dogs' type of movie set up in that style. That would be fucking cool to see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like a good idea to us but think about it they dont give a shit about ps3 servers or games anymore. They didnt care about fixing the hacks a few years back when ps3 was the main gaming system so why would they care about it now when there ps4 servers and games to worry about. Its just not worth it for them. Theres a higher chance that they will remaster mw2 rather than fixing an old game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silk road </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just me or does anyone else think a movie about the creation of silk road and ross ulbricht would be interesting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly the only game mode u csn play without it being ruined by hackers is ffa. I still play once in a while for that nostalgic feeling but its not the same. The days where i used to play for hours on end with my friends on the other end of the mic are over, even though i hate to admit it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This tripped me out considering I have a final tomorrow... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 05:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 16:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If ur talking about being one of those people who mods in mw2...I hate you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 03:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How'd you do that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 02:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot to mention removing painkiller and adding theatre mode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 21:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully take out noob tubes, but keep everything else the same. Can't fuck with a classic. Adding maps is the most I would hope for, but other than that I would be happy to be playing with no hackers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 05:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guaranteed that kids railing his wife </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 20:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to wait till the weekend I would be down to quickscope what's ur psn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 01:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would do that but that would mean switching to a completely new system and stuff. Like I'm Reay used to this and don't play enough to do the switch. But honestly I fucking dominate when there's no hackers lol. People think I have aim bot but I don't which is funny haha.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 17:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf lol
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 17:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol so bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> why hack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 17:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mw2 hackers on ps3 why do you do it? I get on mw2 about once or twice a week for some nostalgia of the good ol mw2 days but 99% of the games are ruined by hackers (super jump, aim bot etc.). Honestly, this hacking has been going on for a few years and I can't believe it's still going on. This shit actually pisses me off I just want to play mw2 with no hackers. Why do you guys do this shit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 19:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now people can be alcoholics without the side effects. So, they would have no reason to quit lol.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 01:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the kid in the Bluejays hat the one from stranger things
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salma Hayek in the movie "From Dusk till Dawn". Best scene I have ever watched. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 04:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
