<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject354</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 14:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the last picture ever taken before entropy consumes the universe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 00:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe what we think are aliens are actually time tourists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How was Willie Nelson able to get away with smoking a joint on top of the white house </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 17:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 22:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its experimental. I can believe what you say about the grading, i havent finished editing it yet let alone grading. i just needed to put something out for my own sanity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Im on MDMA right now! what is you guys best come down combatant?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 00:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my usual cure is a sugary cup of tea and a fag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 00:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i will upload a proper trailer that properly explores the themes in a few weeks. this teaser was purely for setting a tone... also letting people who knew i was making a film know that i actually finished it and didnt bottle out :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 00:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i quit a practical film and film history degree. i felt like I was just waiting for somethign to happen. now i know for sure that you can only learn about making films by actually DOING. this is my first film but im calling it my "how not to make a film" film </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 00:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please do!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-23 02:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is just how we english talk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-19 18:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FINALLY! i thought i was insane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-19 18:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mistley here...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 12:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the thumbnail made me think this was someones crack supply and pipe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poor guy doesn't even realise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 00:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 17:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tetris vision is killer. I'd close my eyes and see blocks falling in perfect sequences. made me feel like a right loser </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cooking Question Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 23:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 14:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 19 and next week I start shooting my first feature film. It's been incredibly stressful for the last year, trying to orchestrate the whole thing and get the money together. It's nearly here though. I'm excited but also very scared because i feel like i shouldn't (and probably don't) know what i'm doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
