<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3065</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 05:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had me at eating rations out of Agnes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 05:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might do this when I get home.  You don't work at a grocery store do you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 05:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DUKE NUKEM!  He is the original zombie killer so he should know his shit by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 05:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask yourself this question:  Do you want to suck an old dirty cock while taking it in the ass or would you prefer to suck a nice clean cock with good side benefits?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 04:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends what you want out of life for yourself and your future family.  Did your parents go to college?  If so, then they might be disappointed that you didn't go.  I didn't go to college, my father got an associates in auto mechanics but he didn't have any expectations for me because he was busy drinking.  So anyway I joined the military and it was the best thing I could have done.  The last thing I wanted to do was 4 more years of school and I had to get away from my loser friends.  I joined the Air Force and became a mechanic and recently retired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 04:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 10 yo daughter likes playing Minecraft and she made a killing zoo with all the different animals in the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 02:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think OP is an alien taking a poll on how we would react if they were to drop by.  If you do decide to drop by, please bring gifts.  We are a couple centuries past shiny beads so a teleporting device would be cool, otherwise we may not believe you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 06:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife is from a small podunk town in Texas that had two brothers strike it rich with the whole fracking thing (I think they invented it).  Anyway they are billionaires and decided to build an airport to fly in 747's so it's a long runway.  They ended up making the runway longer than necessary so their kids could max out their cars top speed.  They also built a recording studio in town and I've never seen anyone there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 02:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Don't look a gift horse in the mouth"  If someone gives you a free horse, don't examine the condition of its teeth in front of the person who is giving it to you.  Not sure what the intended meaning is unless someone is literally gifting you a horse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 02:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you don't go hiking enough?  With hiking shoes you get way better traction and ankle support than with biking shoes or regular running shoes.  Also hiking a good line is similar to hiking a good line but you have to see where each footstep is going to land.  After a while it becomes instinctive like riding a good downhill route.  I can run across stuff that I would never be able to ride across. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 01:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been riding MTB's for 19 years (if that matters).  I ride very similar rocky trails and my front tire is a CST BFT, this tire is awesome!  Every time I go out I am impressed with the way this thing sticks.  I just aim for where I want to go and it does it.  On the rear I run an old school WTB velociraptor, traction like none other while climbing on rocks.  Other tires spin out but the big paddle like lugs down the center just keep biting in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 01:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now you will smell the milk before you drink it...for the rest of your life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 06:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course since I was in the Air Force my deployment was considered the Army or Marines vacation.  Those guys had it way WAY harder than I will ever know.  I did 20 years and never once was shot at or was in any danger.  Much respect for those guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 06:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> drowning, I hate water over my head </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 05:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of the extensive training for chemical warfare thank god.  We had entire exercises that would last for a week where we had to play like we were being attacked with nerve agent.  Although I was deployed to an island in the Indian Ocean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 02:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ANAL CARNAGE  cuz ur gonna get fucked m8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 02:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ANAL CARNAGE  cuz ur gonna get fucked m8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 02:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old ladies and gay guys hit on me all the time, my wife thinks it's funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 02:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good news!  They have classes in college for that.  I took one and now I don't have any problem speaking in front of a large group.  They made a video of my first speech and made me watch it, very eye opening.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 01:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was tweaking according to the military channel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 01:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can speed read.  The first and last sentences in a paragraph are the most important, the shit in between is mostly filler to support the intro and conclusion.  Also the first and last paragraph on each page is the most important, again the rest is filler.  Don't try to vocalize each word in your mind, your brain can process that shit way faster than you can speak it.  Look for numbers and proper nouns, those might be important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 01:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is nothing to say, I like my life the way it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 02:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No that's not the same place, the one you found is up by Amarillo, the one I was talking about was near St. Jo.  http://trails.mtbr.com/cat/united-states-trails/texas-trails/texas-dallas/trail/the-breaks-at-bar-h-mountain-bike-ranch/prd_170485_4581crx.aspx

It's probably still closed which is a shame because it was a cool place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are the bar H ranch MTB trails in St Jo still closed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 15:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did some riding there years ago and want to go back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 06:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea that shit was funny at first and then I slowly became one of the assholes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 05:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if you think you are a fat cow, dress nice.  I've seen some really sexy big girls and they were all dressed nice.  That means no sweat pants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 05:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ear plugs for sure!  I never realized how much the noise effected me until I used them once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 05:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They look like lumber jacks to me.  My guess is retro truck driver look is next with the plaid sleeveless shirt and sweet trucker hat...but you never know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 05:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assless chaps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 05:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and my friends were partying out at the cliff overlooking Lake Michigan.  There was a house down the shore where they were constructing a building so they had some heavy equipment and other stuff around the place.  We decided to do a covert raid on the place in the middle of the night to see what we could snatch.  I found a box of nails and stuck them in the dirt facing up all the way across their driveway.  Then I got in the backhoe and proceeded to piss all over the interior of it.  About this time I hear a loud crashing sound (friend tried to smash out the large front window of the house) and a bulldozer starting up (other friend was gonna try and drive it off the cliff).  I freak out and run back to my jeep and they all show up shortly after.  We all jump in my jeep and haul ass out of there.  By pure coincidence we get back to the main road and a cop car goes flying by right in front of us so we chuck the vodka bottle out the back and I proceed to get the fuck out of there.  So the cop doesn't even come after us but I'm still driving all over the damn countryside like I'm being chased because it was fun.  Anyway there was a sweet jump coming up at the bottom of the hill over some train tracks so I decide to hit it full speed.  I forgot the road splits off in a Y right on the other side so when we landed we were going too fast to make the corner so I stuffed it in this guys front yard.  I bash my face on the steering wheel and only see dirt flying.  My buddy in the back seat rams his face in the back of my seat and bloodied his nose really good.  Next day come to find out that backhoe and dozer belong to my bosses husbands company and she is asking us if we knew anything about it (we all worked at the grocery store together).  I've been through this drill before and I pretended like I knew nothing.  There are a lot more stupid shit stories we used to do but that one sticks out.  A couple random things...slashing tires for no reason, shooting out windows with bb guns, turfing rich people's lawns with my jeep (ideal yard was on a corner), stealing shit from the store....once we put all the fighting fish together in the pet section, they fucked each other up.  Drove out onto a baseball field with the intention of tearing that shit up, instinctively I looked around first and a fucking cop was watching us.  Slowly drove out of there and of course got pulled over and my buddy was freaking out cause he had an oz of weed on him and a big ass knife...I talked my way out of it.  Broke my brothers back in my jeep.  Almost burned up my girlfriend in my jeep (accidentally).  I never got caught but some of my friends did...one is still in prison 20 years later cause he helped kill someone.  I got the fuck out of there and joined the military, best decision I ever made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 04:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have KFC in Germany, it's not bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 02:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vagina </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 02:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep your dog on a leash!  Next time I see him out im gonna fingerbang his ass! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 02:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From nose picking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 02:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's an alien, it should know better than to break into my house and try to anal probe me.  Therefore I would view it as an immediate threat and choke it out with its own puny alien stick arms.  Then I would lock it in my gun safe after getting the ole mossberg 500 out then go looking for more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 02:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was drunk and jumped on my buddies motorcycle without a helmet for a quick night ride.  Came around a corner and 3 deer were standing right in front of me.  I didn't have time to stop so I aimed for the gap between them and made that shit!  Needless to say I turned my ass around and slowly went back to the house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 02:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had this crazy bitch that worked for me and she used this one on me...I wrote her ass up lol!  I really wanted her gone but she knew how to ride the fine line and I was not experienced enough to end her.  If she tried that shit now...BAM fuck her right in the pussy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 19:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Texas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 17:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also ambidextrous...was taking a dump when I saw your comment so I had to try.  It was a little awkward but I got it done with no mess lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 17:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can write backwards with my non dominant hand...in cursive! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 17:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you see yourself in 5 years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 17:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to go look...reminds me of tutting.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 16:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever tried it?  You might like it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 06:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol it works good for making grilled sandwiches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 05:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm 41 if that is aged enough...pretty much twice as old as you lol.  Anyway, picture yourself being my age.  Think of the worse case scenario health wise (300lbs, diabetes, heart problem, hair falling out, kidney stones, liver transplant lol) and do everything you can to keep that from happening.  If you smoke STOP NOW!  In my opinion these things are entirely avoidable but people do not take care of themselves.  Because in the end, your health is the only thing you really have.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 05:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spray butter is the shit!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 04:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I retired from the military at 39.  I get $2,000 per month for my retirement pay.  If I live to be 81 I will have been paid over $1 million dollars.  Basically I won the lottery! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 04:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You make Minecraft videos!  My kids will watch hours of Minecraft videos and then go replicate what they just watched...ALL DAY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 04:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One uppers.  Most of them don't even realize they are doing it.  I like to nonchalantly one up them back, wether it's true or not, they get the hint pretty quick usually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 03:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not the only one lol!  I have to post now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 02:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need a fat bike to ride in the snow...or studded tires.  I lived in Alaska for 4 years and found riding my MTB on snowmobile trails is almost like riding on a sidewalk.  Other things I did were cross country skiing, snow shoeing, ice skating.  It only seems cold outside until you actually get out there, that's the hardest part! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 05:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All gave some but some gave all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 05:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amsterdam!  Hookers n blow woo hoo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 05:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing, I don't even know how it works or what the point is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 05:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go sign up at the nearest Air Force or Coast Guard recruiter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 04:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You see it all the time with parents at their kids sporting events.  The parent yelling at their kid like its the damn major leagues but even if it were so, it's still a GAME.  I hate those kind of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 04:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, stop fucking around and trying to rationalize to yourself to drink more alcohol and quit drinking NOW.  Not tomorrow, not next week, RIGHT...FUCKING...NOW!  Get rid of anything you have in your house and try to find something else to do with your time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 04:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just out of curiosity, how many people have actually PM'd you "MONEY OR BOOBS"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 04:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the people who organized it were trying to get the attention of the average American citizen.  Since WWII we have been manipulating the Middle East in order to get the most oil for the lowest cost and I think these people were trying to bring this to the forefront of the American conscious.  Basically they were tired of us meddling in their affairs.  I really think they were not expecting the response we gave them, however it had a tendency to unite the "extreme" Muslims, which by the way we didnt want because we needed the oil at the time.  Fast forward 15 years...now we have fraking so we don't need to rely on the Middle East for oil like we had to in the past.  In the mean time, our military is weakened from a decade of war and China and Russia are taking advantage of the situation by taking over neighboring states and creating islands to project their power while Obama coasts out of the White House. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 04:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When buying cars the floor guy will act like he has no control over the price of the car you are trying to buy and has to constantly go to his "boss" and ask during negotiations.  Then when you are done with him you have to talk to the finance guy (btw don't ever use their financing) and he try's to load you up with all this extra crap.  You tell him no but he puts it in the paperwork anyway hoping you don't see it and the whole time he acts really busy and annoyed he has to deal with you.  Then they will try to lowball you on your trade in...don't ever trade in your car.  Sure it's convenient but pay for that convenience.  I hate car salesmen/women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 03:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got up and got my boy ready for school and walked him down to the bust stop, woke up my 2 daughters and hung out with them until they had to go to school.  Went back to bed for like an hour and a half.  Got up and made myself a cappaccino and a PBJ for me and the wife for breakfast.  Rolled out to my garage and changed out the front brakes on wife's car then took car for test drive.  While out I fill it up with gas for her and used our Kroger points to get $.20 off per gallon.  Came home and started a load of laundry then took a shower.  Put the clothes in the dryer and plucked my wife's eyebrows and chin for her (she loves that I do that for her).  Went out to eat lunch at Montana's, not going there again cuz it sucked.  Came home and hung up my laundry and got my lunch ready for work (2nd shift).  Massaged my wife's upper back cuz it was bothering her.  Got to work and sat through weekly safety meeting and listened to Alex make fun of entire presentation.  Changed brushes on 3 traction motors and also the main generator slip ring brushes.  Inspected the main gen fuses and diodes.  Now I'm chilling at work waiting for 11:25 to get here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 03:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like literally chowed down on some turds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 03:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lolz were had  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 03:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lolz were had </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 02:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would drink my own wine piss and see if it comes out stronger.  Same with my chocolate shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 02:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take 3 hits of acid and PM me in the morning.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 02:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome!  Once I got a large drink at McDonald's, you know the styrofoam one, and it sat in my truck all day in 100 degree heat and still had ice in it after 8 hours!  I paid $1.05 for mine though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck man, hopefully it will work out for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 05:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a fun trail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 02:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys have good rocket engines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 02:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way to go man!  Seems like whenever I take people out riding bad things always happen to them.  I don't even like riding with strangers because I feel bad when they crash because I feel like it was my fault for going too fast.  I guess I'm a bad teacher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 01:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We get 10 seconds in Michigan.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 17:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about would've (sounds like would of) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 17:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I always use the Enduro Max bearings on my bike, check out their website:  http://endurobearings.com/products/bearings/max/    
Find your size in the catalog then Google shop the part number for the best deal.  good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 08:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait!  Are you sure the suspension bearings are making the noise?  Maybe you have a loose bottom bracket.  Maybe you have a loose or squeaky seat or seat post.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 08:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may be surprised by how much the U.S. still makes.  http://www.marketwatch.com/story/us-manufacturing-dead-output-has-doubled-in-three-decades-2016-03-28 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 17:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could easily take that corner, they were just trying to go way too fast lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it was still bad right?  I mean the part where they were snatched from their homelands, separated from their families, stacked into cargo holds of ships like cord wood and then forced to endure the entire Atlantic crossing like that?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think this is a documentary, it's more like a Lockheed Martin commercial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a mountain biker, you can wave at me if you want to.  Also I'm a hiker, if I see a mountain biker bombing down a sweet downhill section I'll gladly move out of your way!  Sometimes I ride my bike on the road, I try to be considerate of traffic behind me and not hog the road with my slow ass.  Sometimes I drive my car down the road, I don't get mad when a slow ass biker is hogging the road, I just wait until I can pass safely.  Don't get me started on horses though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 01:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived in Vegas for a while and there is a lot of hiking in the area, I used this website to find new places:  http://www.birdandhike.com/Hike/_Hike_index.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 00:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best thing he mentioned was TUCK AND ROLL.  Don't try to break your fall by putting your arms out, that's how people get broken collar bones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 00:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been MTB'ing for 19 years, I don't worry about my bike until next time I want to ride it unless I know something broke.  It's in my garage right now covered in mud from my last ride, I'll just lube the chain and air up the tires next time I go out because it's just going to get dirty again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 00:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm bored at work so I looked around...found a router specific forum that asks your question and many people answered.  http://www.routerforums.com/general-routing/98705-need-some-help-restoring-vintage-craftsman-router-315-25050-a.html#/topics/98705?_k=n4wbkf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 01:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Added bonus, no more illegal aliens from Mexico! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 06:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, by looking at the size of the gears, the output shaft turns faster than the hand crank.  I looked up Eureka and they made all kinds of stuff so there is no telling what this was used for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 05:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second WWII, although you need to understand that it was just a continuation of unresolved issues from WWI, which in turn was a culmination of smaller issues all leading to the outbreak of the first "modern war".  I was always taught that WWI simply started because Franz Ferdinand was shot, nothing more or nothing less.  This, of course, is not the case so I had to go do some reading to find out for myself.  Additionally, to understand what is going on in the middle east, you need to have an understanding of how the two wars shaped the current countries of the area.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 06:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definately aliens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 17:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I bent it back as good as I could but it's not perfect.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 06:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe static caused by liquid transfer and not properly grounded?  Glad nobody was hurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 06:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe your rear derailure or hangar is bent a little.  Mine is tweaked a little and it acts goofy in the middle of the cassette so I just don't use those gears if possible.  I'm too cheap to buy a new one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 23:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's good you can change out the battery quickly, that way you aren't stuck in one gear out in BFE.  Also are they water proof?  There have been times I've submerged my rear derailure riding across creeks and swamps.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Locomotive traction motor change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 02:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Changing a traction motor on a GE C44ACCTE.  Nothing out of the ordinary but thought you guys might like it anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Locomotive engine failure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 05:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Changing a locomotive grid blower motor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 05:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Engine won't crank </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 01:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Temperature difference </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 02:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my lifetime I have experienced a 183 degree F temperature difference.  -60 (without wind chill) in Fairbanks Alaska and 123 degrees F (without heat index) in Las Vegas Nevada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Great, Great Grandfather's Two-Man Saw </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 00:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antique air compressor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 06:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Be nice to your cashier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 02:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to work in a grocery store as a bagger a long time ago.  One time this old lady was being really bitchy to the cashier so I dropped cans of soup she had bought on top of her grapes and smashed them.  I was imagining how pissed she would be when she got home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ouachita Challenge anyone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 01:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone planning on doing the upcoming Ouachita Challenge in April?  I have started getting back into shape for it, it's been about 10 years since I did it last lol!  I live Granbury so I ride a lot in Glenrose at the dinosaur park.  I plan on doing at least one weekly MTB ride there in the mornings (I work 2nd shift) between 9:30 and whenever.  Let me know if you want to come out and ride!  (I'm not fast) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
