<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3039</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 09:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paul Blart Mall Cop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Serious) Update/Advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 21:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, a month ago on the r/BPDSOFFA I wrote a little bit about my relationship with my BPD SO. (Can be found here: http://www.reddit.com/r/BPDSOFFA/comments/2ztwh9/my_very_first_relationship_learning_to_deal_and/ ) I recommend that for anyone who wants to know what is sort of going on. This is sort of the update on how things have been. I moved away and she went to rehab for help, she kept me updated and said she is learning more and more about BPD more than she has before which is awesome. We hit the 1 year mark a few days ago (my first relationship!) and at this stage in my life with how things are/have been with the move and her I feel content right now. She still has a few more things to do up where she is at and so that brings me to this. For those of you have lived with a BPD SO what are some advice you could give me? Her and I have lived together but with  her moving to a new state, this will be a new adventure for her. I've read around on here and different places about the risks and believe me you, I feel like I know some of them. Inside I feel this is right, not just for me but also for her and she has told me she wants this too. She wants a new life, a new start, she wants to be happy. Again, I know the risks, at least I feel like I do..I also feel like everything I've/we have been through has helped me to be ready for what is to come. The question I would love to know would be what is the best advice you could give me and what are some things her and I should do/ know before she makes the jump? I feel so much for her, we love each other and as she told me today, what we have is so strong. Who knows, maybe one day I might pop the question to her and ask her to be my wife? I'm 23 by the way and I know that is young..Not saying I'll ask her anytime soon but, hopefully at some point :) 

Anyway, if anyone would give me proper advice that would be tremendous, advice on what to do, what not to do for both her and I. She has expressed interest in going to therapy when she gets out here so that's a plus. I will defiantly have to keep you guys updated on the things to come, thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 18:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> swwwreeeeeeeyt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First post on reddit! 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 10:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
