<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2901</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An "Art" for bellum.io </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 03:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi /u/bellumiogame , I made something for you!

http://imgur.com/LHkUHtG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New "Profile" Feature </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 01:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Agar" a Diep Story, Prologue: "Liftoff" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 00:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys, let me know if you like these or if I should continue...but these stories will get very cringy, and I know your grandpas can write better and whatnot. Anyway, if you feel like reading this junk, go ahead. Also, this isn't really organized, I just do a stream of thought. So some parts might not make sense, and this plotline probably won't have a climax or anything

---

Somewhere in Diep, two days before launch

...and lets realize that this has been possible thanks to global peace, and that we will continue to seek and achieve further achievements of all diepkind.

---

D.I.E.P., the Diep Interplanetary Exploration Program, launched their biggest ship yet. It launched a Class 3 rocket to kick off the A.C.E., the Agar Colonies and Expedition.

This program was a major step forward for diepkind, and the program was focused on exploring/colonizing the planet Agar. It was a colorful planet that also orbited its star, Zeach. (Zeach was located in the galaxy of Io.) 

The planet orbited Zeach slightly farther out than the planet Diep. Although it had been difficult to collect data from the planet, scientists found out that it had about 73% percent of the mass of Diep.

The rocket consisted of many delicate parts, but its first stage was probably the most famous one. The main booster had 9 Diep International; Generation 4 Type 2 Engines: the DI-4-2.

It also had three very powerful DI-4-1 engines, each capable of a staggering 41,000 Booster Power. The total max thrust possible was a little over 258,000BP. The first stage would take it on a suborbital trajectory, and the second stage would make rendezvou with the mothership waiting in orbit.

The mothership will then take the ship to an Agar-encounter trajectory and rest it in Agar orbit. The 18 tanks would then take three descent ships down and land in different places. 4 tanks will stay onboard.

---

Day of launch	

T-minus 10 minutes...t-minus 5 minutes...fuel feed cutoff...t-minus minute

All systems running nominal, vehicle on internal power...t-minus 30 seconds...

T-minus 10, 9, 8, 7, ignition sequence start...4, 3, 2

(rumbling vibration begins)

...1, zero...

And we have liftoff! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Bug Glitch] GUI and stuff like that </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 19:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, you need to add flairs /u/bellumio 

Anyway, sometimes, you can't click on the player menus. Well, you can click, but the individual buttons actually don't work, and the sparkle and blink a lot. I don't know if anyone else has encountered this?

In addition, your allies, requested allies, and pending allies sometimes fail to show up.

I appreciate your effort, DeGhost!

Also...

##addawarningbutton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any decent "more planets" mods out there that work for 1.2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 06:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1.1 is fine too, but I can't find a good mod. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Mother" A diep.io story (kinda) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 08:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I am about to tell you will most likely make a deep impression in your heart.

---

Today I still recall that day.

My mother congratulated me, I was able to take out a pentagon for the first time without anyones help.

However, as I grew up, I started feeling a little rebellious--my mom, a manager, was just getting in my business that she shouldnt be interrupting with.

One day at Diep University, my friends were having such a blast. We had finished all our exams, and what I didnt realize was--this would probably be the most unknowingly best and exciting day of my life. Sorry, cant think of a better way to put it. So I was going back home, I was so tired. Then, before coming into the house, I realized: Well, I havent really cared about my mother in a while

Then a second thought: You know what? I really dont care. She bugs me all the time.

So when I came in, I ignored my mother trying to talk to me and went straight to rest that night. I didnt know that she was feeling so sad and rejected.

The next morning, I couldnt stand the thought that she was in my house, so I just grabbed my two squares for breakfast and dashed out, having evolved into a Tri-angle a few days ago.

Then I joined this famous club called the MG club--I didnt know what it stood for, but all the cool, kind of notorious for bullying, I guess, yeah. They all went there and hung out, and when I joined, I fit in well. Although I thought that what they were doing was wrong, I ignored it, because who cared at that time, honestly?

Then they introduded me this new kind of light drug called crasher fume--it was a version of crasher pieces, chemically modified with barrelium-2. When I started, I hated it. But I kept coming back for more--it was just strangely addicting. Soon enough, I was having up to five packs a day. If I had up to 10 a day, I could faint or even die. But I made sure that it didnt happen.

My FOV, attention span, and bullet accuracy was going down...yet, me and my MG pals wanted to go to Pentagons Field for a little ride. We arrived there, and farmed for several months to get to, yes, level 45, when we could be classified as grownups.

I was so happy being a booster--I was going lightening fast. I think my life was going downhill at that point. Then, a few days later, I hit a maze wall and had to stay in the hospital for a few weeks.

In between each week, I actually started getting my sanity back. I also began to worry about my mom--just slightly in the beginning, but a lot later. I was nervous, and regretted leaving her and making her sad.

It was a few days after I made the decision to go back home and introduce my friends to mom. I was packing my stuff, including a special alpha pentagon souvenir. Then, a friend of mine approached me and told me the following:

Um...hey, something happened.

I replied, Whats going on dude? Lets go for a short race up on that-

No, Oipeid. This is something much bigger and much more serious. I hate to break it to you...but...

But what? Tell me quickly, please.

Okay, Ill say it, your mother has been killed in the recent bosses attack.

This was a joke, I hoped.

Wha-wait...no...

I fainted, and woke up to my friends call.

MOM! ARE YOU THERE? HELLO?

I...I AM SO SORRY. I DONT--I DONT KNOW HOW I CAN...I AM JUST SO SORRY.

Still to this day, I remember that one big moment.

But Im here to tell you this story. Im alive and sane enough--at least I think so--to tell you the story. And to teach you this lesson.

Dont be like me. Dont live the life that I lived. Dont hang out with who you think you are expected to hang out with--make good friends. Make the good friends that will do the right things. Thank your dear loved ones, every day. Appreciate the life and the time you have every day.

Because remember--regret is the worst thing in the world--I know you can do good things in the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just spawned as a level 1 factory in sandbox! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 04:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have screenshot proof if you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guess what happened today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 04:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was an overseer.

I move about halfway across the map, and repel my drones so that they are going toward the other base but down.

After a long time, I know that my drones are not spawning, so I put my cursor, still right clicking, on the gray border.

My drones got a kill behind the other team's base! I got Level 45 instantly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I release... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 02:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my set of MegaProTipsForBellumIo^TM ?

No, seriously, I do have a list of pro tips that will make you much, much better at the game. Let's get this to 7 upvotes to make this happen.

Note: I'm not an upvote hungry guy, I just want to make sure that there are enough people to enjoy this privilege of being a redditor and getting help from the community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There was a poor tiny base being cornered by 3 other big bases, so I made an alliance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 22:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The little base didn't stand a chance against us four big players! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NEW UPDATE WAS A FEW HOURS AGO! IS THE DEV DEAD? WE NEED UPDATES!!! DIEPIO DEAD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 07:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Stupidity Alert] Way to disable CommNet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 06:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I've been playing KSP since...idk...2015? But I am new to this subreddit. So hello!

I started a worldsave before 1.2 and thus before CommNet. However, I keep looking through the setting yet I cannot find a way to disable CommNet. Also, it's kind of annoying as well, and I am not that good at it.

So I have already started a save, could any kind Kerbonaut here give me a step-by-step tutorial on how to disable that sucker? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You need to add a refresh/exit warning message! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 05:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the title. Sometimes you either 1. accidentally close out of the tab 2. hit refresh 3. Ctrl + W. Because of this, there have been many glitches such as: 1. losing how many mp you can get by clicking 2. losing all your plots except for bases

So please, make it like diep.io and add a warning message. This would prevent users from accidentally doing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying some /u/PlatinumPeaks style art with crappy MS Paint skills - Tri-Angle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 09:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greatest Frustration in Diep </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 09:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all...I got spawnkilled many^many times.

Then when I manage to take out a level penta by off-screen luck, I get surrounded by a bullet field of enemies! Then right after I also luckily kill another sprayer!

Then, with the slow clicking and slow upgrade panel pop-ups, I am not able to upgrade and I die.

How great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This subreddit is ded but </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 06:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> diep.io/#B82A2B5ABB306B6B30E35F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just Imagine... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 11:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An income of 30K mp/s...

100 bases all guarded in thick walls by level 10 plots...

A total cash of 250,000,000 mp...

Yeah stop daydreaming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exactly 77,777 points! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 08:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Really fun build with Octo Tank! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 21:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name yourself "Sawblade" and go with this build: 6/7/7/0/3/0/3/7

It creates a semi-strong bullet shield around you that acts as a sawblade cut. It moves fast and has full-on body damage build.

Turn auto fire on and spam-move your cursor on the screen so that the octo tank looks really like a fast-spinning blade.

Do this in Sandbox, won't prove useful in other modes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Project HelpTheDev </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 07:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We want developments added to the game, and who does that? The developer!

So I've decided to start Project HelpTheDev. Here is how is works:

If you have nothing else better to do and you are bored, disable adblock and go on diep sandbox mode.

Then, spawn, suicide, and click on ad.

Immediately Ctrl+W to close ad tab.

Repeat, you can do up to 10 ads per minute, adding up to 600 ads per minute! If at any given point in time at noon 20 or more are doing it, that is 12000 ads per minute! That's tremendous money!

So go support the developer now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Master is renamed to Factory, I guess this ensures that the dev is WITH US! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diep analogy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overseer is to manager, necromancer is to master </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome to /r/jtmsscioly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 07:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A pretty cool game to try out while diep is D.E.D... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 03:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I've been active on /r/bellumio these days.

Bellum.io is a really fun game, I think it has lots of room for improvement and potential.

Try it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Magic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 20:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And the AC was sad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 07:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just got 10,000 score </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 03:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't post images yet, but it was a really good game!

Is Nova or Rov or Jaxx or ETE or QQQ or anyone here?!!!

I literally got 10,000 last minute... my heart was shaking lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I tried to clear out all the non-pentagon shapes to make the sandbox basically a mini pentagon nest. This took a while pls gimme claps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 08:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This person is the greatest person on the subreddit ;) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 08:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This person on reddit is just the worst...no manners, no respect, just insult. Even bad at diep.io...this guy/girl is the biggest fa**ot. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 02:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is wrong with this subreddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 06:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every Predator ever---seriously, Predator needs a new look. Too much like cake. Credit to /u/Fawful49 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 06:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I will blow your mind </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 01:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How to tell which one wins if triple twin and triplet battle

Triple Twin = Triplet Win
tripletwin = tripletwin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally a diep.io update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 21:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't handle this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 03:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many good suggestions.

This includes new gamemodes, new kinds of stats, (ex: invisibility for landmine, bullet power for auto smasher, etc) new classes, changes to sandbox, etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Shameless advertisement) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 22:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Join a.reconnectmc.com for some real funzies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is SK bad and why is RDT bad? Why is there a conflict? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 17:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like it's the Russian Revolution all over again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is my average score nowadays. How about everyone else? I usually don't go for high score, it's more of the killing that is fun. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 06:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Guardian is best to use as protection and be petted by </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 06:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summoner: randomly shoots squares from four sides which may accidentally hit you.

Defender: The auto cannons and traps may hit you.

Fallen Booster: There are a crap ton of bullets, plus you can't chase it well.

Guardian: Only spawns drones from one side, and it is a triangle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some good song to play during diep.io. Especially in boss fights! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 01:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This really gets my heart going

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else remember the good old days...(comment things like my post content) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 07:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...when the 2-tdm mode had small safe zones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waiting for a new update, (2) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 03:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's just have a fun time! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 04:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, please don't just spam dominators, motherships, or ACs... they make the game no fun.

We'll have friendly battles in this server:

diep.io/#24FA9DE3BB30B4F9E29935 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So today, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 03:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a Pentashot (trying it out and comparing it to a spreadshot) almost dominating the server. My name was Soap Noodle if anyone found me.

Then, when I was randomly farming, a small unnamed level 1 tank spawned near my bullet stream and that is exactly where my cursor was. I turned off auto fire to prevent spawnkilling, but it must have tried to get away (it ran out of invincibility).

However, the bullets that did not disappear yet killed him.

I felt so bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to REALLY play diep.io while the updates are lacking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 07:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 8-bit diep.io </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 07:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else, like, think the Booster is CUTE? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 04:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why, but I think the Booster in diep is one of those cutest things that can't be explained of their cuteness.

You know, like it has a round body with the short barrel in the front and the four barrels in the back,

It's like it's a little excited child ready to go somewhere.

The Booster is so cute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Overtrapper Is Actually Good. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 06:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's talk about the Overtrapper. It's mostly a defensive tank. It may seem like a sucky tank to use, but here is why it's good: (And I'm not joking)

1. It has traps are small but can defend you quite well, especially if you are setting up a "scatter fort" to defend yourself and block bullets.

2. The traps last a long time, so you can make the defense system quite big.

3. The drones make sure (Like the Hybrid's) that you don't accidentally collide with shapes, attacks low level tanks, etc.

4. It looks cool.

I think I just summed up everything obvious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Battleships fight battleships </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 05:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smasher WR Maze </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 23:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Mazes" Lyrics - Parody of Circles by KDrew </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 07:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking for a way out

---

Moving around with my bullets gone, I see a few spawn

Tanks told me I can't stand the bullet drown

But now I run the path on the wider ground, defeating the crowd

---

While they keep teaming team mode
While they keep teaming team mode
While they keep teaming team mode

---

Moving around with my bullets gone, I see a few spawn

Tanks told me I can't stand the bullet drown

But now I run the path on the wider ground, defeating the crowd

---

While they keep teaming team mode
While they keep teaming team mode
While they keep teaming team mode
While they keep teaming team mode
While they keep teaming team mode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Little Lv1 Tank" Lyrics - Parody of Little Drummer Boy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 05:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come, they told me, pa rum pum pum pum.

A new spawned tank to see, pa rum pum pum pum.
 
Our finest shapes we bring, pa rum pum pum pum.

To lay before MG, pa rum pum pum pum, pa rum pum pum pum, pa rum pum pum pum.

---

So to honor him, pa rum pum pum pum, when we spin.

---

Little recruit, pa rum pum pum pum.

I am a peaceful tank, pa rum pum pum pum.

Let's team to dominate, pa rum pum pum pum.

We MGs spin to team, pa rum pum pum pum, pa rum pum pum pum, pa rum pum pum pum.

---

Shall I ram the tank, pa rum pum pum pum, MasterOv?

---

Boosters nodded, pa rum pum pum pum.

The Sun Knights tried their best, pa rum pum pum pum.

I rammed the tank for Ov, pa rum pum pum pum.

I maxed my movement speed, pa rum pum pum pum, pa rum pum pum pum, pa rum pum pum pum.

---

They will spin with me, pa rum pum pum pum, me and my clan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some more PPAP jokes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 04:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a diep
I have Miniclip

UGH

Rest in peace! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, Zeach gave me the link of the newly hugely updated diep.io. Read for further description. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 03:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So yesterday I received a PM from Zeach, telling me that I was one of the five lucky active redditors to receive a link to this. Apparently he didn't want the link to go public, but after a few minutes of thinking I decided to leak it.

The new diep.io "version" is so hugely updated, and it includes some of the best additions and changes that we wanted in the game. After playing a little in Sandbox (only mode available for snapshot versions) I decided the community has to see this, it's been so long.

I'm guessing this would be deleted by a moderator soon, but if any of you are reading, please don't delete this.

The link to the new diep.io version is [here](https://youtu.be/dQw4w9WgXcQ).

Enjoy playing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maybe this is why... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 05:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THERE ARE OVER A MILLION MG'S! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 02:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...in a kilogram. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What I watched an hour ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 05:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NEW "SIZE DOES MATTER" DIEP.IO TANK?!?!?! SUPER LONG BARREL'S MAX PENETRATION!!! 200K+ SCORE?!?! Diep.io Hacks / Mods! (Diep.io game / diepio game) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 22:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NEW "HEX-DECA TANK" IN DIEP.IO?!?!? EPIC NEW OP TANK!!! 500K+ SCORE!!!! Diep.io Hacks / Mods! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 22:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone link me to the list/image of colors that are used in diep.io? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 09:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is because I want to try my best at art~~using MS Paint~~. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome to this subreddit! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 04:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello!

In this subreddit, we will explore all ~~photoshopped~~ genetically mutated species on diep.io, as well as studying the tanks of diep.io. That, is diepology/diepiology.

Now, what are you waiting for? Put your diepiologist/diepologist hat on and start exploring! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone, like, make an upgrade tree? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 22:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> #DicksOutForSpikeLaunch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 06:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember when... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 05:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Triple Twin was the go-to tank and the "best" build was 0/5/0/7/7/7/7/0? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Once you get in, it's impossible to get out... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 02:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't have a mine dispenser and you are being followed by a powerful ship as strong as you, there is practically no way to escape it, it is certain death.

I think most people get what I mean, I can't really describe it well but when is happens it is very frustrating.

What is your guys's opinions on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NOT SUGGESTION] Imagine if you... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 04:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got a stat point every 100k. So if you have 1mil points, you would have racked up 43 points.

This post was a short post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 04:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm new to this subreddit, haven't played the game ever but it looks reeee^eeeee^eally interesting. I'm looking forward to playing it.

Is there anything I know? Like diep.io, which stats are prioritiy? FAQ's?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm actually... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 10:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Test (ignore) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 03:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1.6mil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The devs of agar.io released this cool new game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 02:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you flair a post? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 06:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anokuu TRIGGERED by "incorrect" build </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Types of leaderboards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The leaderboards in each server are pretty different and interesting, so I want to sum up some of the types of leaderboards just for fun. Please don't comment that this is totally useless.

Also, assume that by FFA I mean the Maze as well, and by TDM I mean both team modes (4-tdm and 2-tdm).

I did not include Domination, Sandbox, and Tag. (Just doesnt make sense)
---

[FFA] FFA TOTAL Domination:

1.4mil
45.8k
21.0k
20.8k
12.5k
10.4k
9.8k
8.3k
8.0k
7.6k

Explanation: There is one really good pro who has racked up hundreds of thousands, or even a few million points. This situation is very rare. The first place tank starts dominating the server by killing almost every tank in sight, and the only remaining tanks are a few lv 45 tanks and low-level tanks.

---

[FFA] FFA Domination:

230.3k
56.9k
32.8k
23.3k
21.6k
18.0k
17.3k
15.9k
15.8k
12.3k

Explanation: There is a top tank which has many times as much score as the second place tank. This is common, and rarely develops into TOTAL domination. From the top, the scores drastically dwindle and it shows a gentle curve down the bottom. (Description of looks)

---

[FFA or TDM] Rivalry:

403.3k
398.7k
381.5k
78.0k
67.2k
64.9k
63.9k
45.2k
39.7k
23.6k

Explanation: There may be 2, 3, or even rarely 4 top tanks that are fighting for the top score. The differences of scores between them are usually within 30k, and they rank in terms of score in the hundred thousands. Note that in TDM the top tanks might be in the same team or may be on different teams.

[FFA or TDM] Balanced:

120.4k
109.2k
100.1k
89.9k
87.5k
76.2k
68.9k
63.2k
57.8k
54.4

Explanation: The name may be misleading, but it means that the slope of the scoreboard is very even and there are no drastic changes between ranks. This is most likely to happen (telling from my research) when the server is fairly new, but not too new. For TDM, if this were to be even more balanced, the leaderboard may have a color pattern such as:

RED-BLUE-RED-RED-BLUE-BLUE-RED-BLUE-BLUE-RED (and so on with 4-tdm matches)

---

[FFA or TDM] New:

6.8k
4.2k
4.0k
3.6k
2.9k
2.1k
1.4k
970
305
130

Explanation: This occurs when there is a brand new server, hence not much score from each player and not much competition. Self-explanatory.

---

[TDM] TDM Domination:

450.9k BLUE
389.4k BLUE
302.4k BLUE
106.9k BLUE
56.3k BLUE
49.9k BLUE
47.4 k BLUE
41.4k BLUE
37.7k RED
32.8k BLUE

Explanation: This situation is a pain in the a$$ when you want to do a team turnaround. That is because when the other team has almost filled up the leaderboard guarding 95% of the map, the other team cant farm as many shapes and back at the dominant teams base even more players are thriving and supporting the team. Usually in the top 1 - 5 places, the scores are high.

---

[TDM] After/before turnaround:

450.9k BLUE
389.4k RED
302.4k BLUE
106.9k BLUE
56.3k BLUE
49.9k BLUE
47.4 k BLUE
41.4k BLUE
37.7k RED
32.8k BLUE

Yes, I did copy the score and only changed the team color because Im lazy.

Explanation: This happens after OR before a turnaround, and it is interesting because two explanations are possible:

AFTER a turnaround: The minor color tanks are the ones that survived the big attack from the turning team, which is BLUE in this scenario. They still need to be killed off in order to achieve a turnaround of top 8 - bottom 2.

BEFORE a turnaround: The player that will lead a turnaround is usually the 389.4k RED in this case. The player may rack up high score and killing the other teams tanks until he/she allows some other tanks like 37.7k RED in this example to gain a place on the leaderboard.

---

[FFA] Hacker:

20.7mil
1.5k
1.0k
960
875
567
256
105
89
35

Explanation: ...this probably wont happen, and if it does happen, it would be the worst nightmare.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They removed X-Hunter!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 02:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So they basically combined the Predator and the X-Hunter, so that the Predator now has 3 barrels. It keeps its zoom ability.

P.S.: I'm sending this with Internet Explorer, might be a little late </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost thought this was about 2b2t holy shit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 04:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fit becomes STAFF of RUSHER'S SERVER?!?!?!!?? (GONE WRONG) (GONE PRESIDENTIAL) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 04:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Anokuu is called Anokuu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 02:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She plays as necromancer. Then other players underestimated the necromancer at first and Anokuu started beating then and they said

AAAAAAAAAAAA

and some people said

NOOOOOOOOO

and when she defeated all of them they said

KUUUUUdos to you m8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whenever there is a new gamemode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 04:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got 1k score with basic tank.

GIMME WR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLEASE ADD ABILITY TO LIMIT CLASSES IN SANDBOX AND MORE OPTIMIZATIONS! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 01:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, the owner should be able to kick players or spawn in shapes and bosses.

Also there is always this one fuckhead to goes AC and does not follow rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> QUICK! I NEED A RESPONSE FASSSST </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 00:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did MoneyShit AKA MiniClip buy diep.io? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HELP] Can someone explain 2b2t now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 22:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how do I start... Oh

You know, did the Rusher war end? Fit is a lost cause, and who is he teaming up with, where did they come from and what are they called?

What is the conflict nowadays?

What's going on?

Is autism spreading further?

Someone clarify current events please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These are NOT diep.io hacks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 06:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIP - when the arena closes: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 02:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Press F5 ASAP and press Enter to refresh the page

2. Join any gamemode ASAP

3. You are almost first in that server, if you are gud you will be able to control the new server.

4. Profit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So today as a level 16 tank I got an off-screen lv 45 kill... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 06:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and it felt good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I predicted the future. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 07:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20 days ago I posted something that complained about how so many ftb spam tanks wee in this subreddit.

So I said something like "Do we need /r/diepioftb or something!?!"

But that subreddit is now 19 days old.

Possibilities:

The maker of the subreddit took my idea.

Or, it's a PURE coincidence. But if I took part, I feel proud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have some lethal dose of clan cancer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 06:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [AA][AB][AC][AD][AE][AF][AG][AH][AI][AJ][AK][AL][AM][AN][AO][AP][AQ][AR][AS][AT][AU][AV][AW][AX][AY][AZ][BA][BB][BC][BD][BE][BF][BG][BH][BI][BJ][BK][BL][BM][BN][BO][BP][BQ][BR][BS][BT][BU][BV][BW][BX][BY][BZ][CA][CB][CC][CD][CE][CF][CG][CH][CI][CJ][CK][CL][CM][CN][CO][CP][CQ][CR][CS][CT][CU][CV][CW][CX][CY][CZ][DA][DB][DC][DD][DE][DF][DG][DH][DI][DJ][DK][DL][DM][DN][DO][DP][DQ][DR][DS][DT][DU][DV][DW][DX][DY][DZ][EA][EB][EC][ED][EE][EF][EG][EH][EI][EJ][EK][EL][EM][EN][EO][EP][EQ][ER][ES][ET][EU][EV][EW][EX][EY][EZ][FA][FB][FC][FD][FE][FF][FG][FH][FI][FJ][FK][FL][FM][FN][FO][FP][FQ][FR][FS][FT][FU][FV][FW][FX][FY][FZ][GA][GB][GC][GD][GE][GF][GG][GH][GI][GJ][GK][GL][GM][GN][GO][GP][GQ][GR][GS][GT][GU][GV][GW][GX][GY][GZ][HA][HB][HC][HD][HE][HF][HG][HH][HI][HJ][HK][HL][HM][HN][HO][HP][HQ][HR][HS][HT][HU][HV][HW][HX][HY][HZ][IA][IB][IC][ID][IE][IF][IG][IH][II][IJ][IK][IL][IM][IN][IO][IP][IQ][IR][IS][IT][IU][IV][IW][IX][IY][IZ][JA][JB][JC][JD][JE][JF][JG][JH][JI][JJ][JK][JL][JM][JN][JO][JP][JQ][JR][JS][JT][JU][JV][JW][JX][JY][JZ][KA][KB][KC][KD][KE][KF][KG][KH][KI][KJ][KK][KL][KM][KN][KO][KP][KQ][KR][KS][KT][KU][KV][KW][KX][KY][KZ][LA][LB][LC][LD][LE][LF][LG][LH][LI][LJ][LK][LL][LM][LN][LO][LP][LQ][LR][LS][LT][LU][LV][LW][LX][LY][LZ][MA][MB][MC][MD][ME][MF][MG][MH][MI][MJ][MK][ML][MM][MN][MO][MP][MQ][MR][MS][MT][MU][MV][MW][MX][MY][MZ][NA][NB][NC][ND][NE][NF][NG][NH][NI][NJ][NK][NL][NM][NN][NO][NP][NQ][NR][NS][NT][NU][NV][NW][NX][NY][NZ][OA][OB][OC][OD][OE][OF][OG][OH][OI][OJ][OK][OL][OM][ON][OO][OP][OQ][OR][OS][OT][OU][OV][OW][OX][OY][OZ][PA][PB][PC][PD][PE][PF][PG][PH][PI][PJ][PK][PL][PM][PN][PO][PP][PQ][PR][PS][PT][PU][PV][PW][PX][PY][PZ][QA][QB][QC][QD][QE][QF][QG][QH][QI][QJ][QK][QL][QM][QN][QO][QP][QQ][QR][QS][QT][QU][QV][QW][QX][QY][QZ][RA][RB][RC][RD][RE][RF][RG][RH][RI][RJ][RK][RL][RM][RN][RO][RP][RQ][RR][RS][RT][RU][RV][RW][RX][RY][RZ][SA][SB][SC][SD][SE][SF][SG][SH][SI][SJ][SK][SL][SM][SN][SO][SP][SQ][SR][SS][ST][SU][SV][SW][SX][SY][SZ][TT][TB][TC][TD][TE][TF][TG][TH][TI][TJ][TK][TL][TM][TN][TO][TP][TQ][TR][TS][TT][TU][TV][TW][TX][TY][TZ][UA][UB][UC][UD][UE][UF][UG][UH][UI][UJ][UK][UL][UM][UN][UO][UP][UQ][UR][US][UT][UU][UV][UW][UX][UY][UZ][VA][VB][VC][VD][VE][VF][VG][VH][VI][VJ][VK][VL][VM][VN][VO][VP][VQ][VR][VS][VT][VU][VV][VW][VX][VY][VZ][WA][WB][WC][WD][WE][WF][WG][WH][WI][WJ][WK][WL][WM][WN][WO][WP][WQ][WR][WS][WT][WU][WV][WW][WX][WY][WZ][XA][XB][XC][XD][XE][XF][XG][XH][XI][XJ][XK][XL][XM][XN][XO][XP][XQ][XR][XS][XT][XU][XV][XW][XX][XY][XZ][YY][YB][YC][YD][YE][YF][YG][YH][YI][YJ][YK][YL][YM][YN][YO][YP][YQ][YR][YS][YT][YU][YV][YW][YX][YY][YZ][ZZ][ZB][ZC][ZD][ZE][ZF][ZG][ZH][ZI][ZJ][ZK][ZL][ZM][ZN][ZO][ZP][ZQ][ZR][ZS][ZT][ZU][ZV][ZW][ZX][ZY][ZZ] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Booster World Record - 9/17/16 - 123 million score </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 03:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Imagine... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 23:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A spread shot with the build 3/2/0/0/7/7/7/7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just realized that tall non-powered wheels look like jet engines. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 02:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Figured it out today! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Dose of Autism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 02:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fit's Future Video Titles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 05:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> December 2016

- Fit gets a RANK on the Archon
- 2b2t: The Final Completion of Fitlantis
- HyPixel 2B2T RACING - Better progress and awesome rewards
- Hardcore Fit (Ep29) - FROZEN AMPLIFIED - Killing the DRAGON
- SkyRegions: COLLEGE ISLAND - Episode 45 - FINISHING UP EVERYTHING

Onto: February 2017

- Fit becomes a STAFF on the Archon!
- 2b2t: Patrolling spawn once again
- Mineplex HUNGER GAMES - Episode 17: Teaming up with Striak
- #teamfit - JOIN US - Archon Factions - Apply!
- 100k Subs Special: NOT a face reveal

...and May 2017

- Fit PARTNERS with RUSHER on HyPixel?!!?
- 2b2t: I place two dirt blocks and walk a few blocks
- MINEPLEX HUNGER GAMES EPISODE 281: EPIC CLUTCH!
- 250k Subs Special: QUARTER MILLION!
- MINECON and VIDCON update
- Daily Vlogs with Striak: Making a Sandwich!
- Fit JOINS the Cube SMP?!?!
- 2b2t: Rusher DELETES the server </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was a tenth of a level away from Overlord when a Hybrid one-shot me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 01:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WARNING: CANCER, LETHAL DOSE! ENTER AT YOUR OWN RISK, ALL 676 COMBINATIONS OF ALPHABETICAL COMBINATIONS FOR CLAN NAMES! Credit to /u/Blo-_- FOR THE IDEA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 23:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLEASE! WE NEED THE ABILITY TO BE SANDBOX ADMINS SO WE CAN DISABLE/BAN CERTAIN CLASSES AND KICK PEOPLE OUT! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 01:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anokuu EXPOSED in Windows 10? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 23:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FIT EXPOSED IN GOOGLE DOCS! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 23:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate it when I get teamed on and bombarded by two bullet spammers from two sides. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 22:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spread Shot vs Triplet. Build both 0/0/0/7/7/7/7/5. Who wins? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 09:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be doing more of these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VERY fun story (stress relief) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 06:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello.

So I spawned in as "Fighter Pilot" to play as Fighter.

When I was not even level 15, I kill a triplet by 110% luck. The triplet, fighting with another bullet spammer, had very low health.

So I immediately upgrade to Fighter and choose the build 3/3/0/4/6/6/7/4.

As soon as I do that, a pentashot starts a fight with me. I hit a few shots, get away, hit a few shots, get away. The best shots land when the pentashot uses its vulnerable back to boost towards me with the recoil.

Since I have regen and a ton of health, my health build is pretty solid. I get the pentashot down to SERIOUSLY low health when he/she escapes. I was like "damn it"

And there is this overtrapper, and again, I take down a little of the player's health at a time when the same pentashot (now full health) comes at the two of us.

Taking much damage from the traps, the pentashot gets down to SERIOUSLY low health, again. Then I take the chance, while they are distracted, to one-shot kill the pentashot. My rear bullet also kills the overtrapper.

So obviously, I was very happy and excited! Right after, I get in a fight with the quad tank, and trust me quad tanks are slightly underrated.

The quad tank was a very experienced player and it almost got me. Then I run away to regen, when the pentashot I killed with the same name "astro" comes as a rammer basic tank and kills me.

...then while he is regenerating, I quickly respawn and conveniently spawn close to the player.

;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bored? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 19:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WHAT IS THIS? The text is yellow, I joined from another browser with the party link. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 03:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't have a backslash on my keyboard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 03:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The subreddit right now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 06:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait... the sandbox thing is super hype but I can't join it for some reason. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 05:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My reaction to the new buttons update and sandbox. Dev, thank you you are a god. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 05:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A great new game! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 06:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When your team does a turnaround and saves a stupid rammer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 06:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... is auto fire on or off? I'm pretty sure I turned it on... (not photoshopped) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 05:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Build mistake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 08:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going for a glass cannon build with the triplet.

I was about to do M+8 for movement speed but my hand slipped and the game put all points in body damage.

Fml. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost untouchable... and yes I am using the same name. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 06:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else spectate the tank that killed you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 06:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do, even if it lasts for tens of minutes. I watch for two reasons:

1. It's entertaining, almost like watching AI fight.
2. I just wanna see that bitch die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FFS! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 04:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do we need another god damned subreddit called /r/diepioftb or something? There are way too many STUPID tanks (some are good though) spamming this subreddit right now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fun story with Spread Shot (It's fucking underrated, btw. Ok maybe not underrated but OP if you're good.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 03:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, build: 0/7/0/5/7/7/7/0 (The health and bullet speed help a lot, you'll see)

And my name in-game, "Soap Noodle".

So I enter the server, then I chose twin. Then I choose Qua-no, accidentally the Triple Shot. So I farm until I get to 45, then I choose Pen-no, Spread Shot. So I was like "shit."

I didn't know Spread Shot was so good.

First, it's the perfect counter to rammers. And many others. This story contains some fun material, it may have annoyed the players but it was a hella fun for me. Here it is:

I become Spread Shot and I kill a Body Damage Booster named Foxy. Then someone--I can't remember, someone named somewhat like "claudio.xx" as an overlord tries to come at me. I get down to low health, but remember, that 7 max health helped me a lot.

So I was very low and I said to myself "Gaw I knew this tank was SHIT". But then, I realized the bullets have surprisingly high penetration! Plus the low bullet speed helped!

So I killed claudio.xx! Then a booster rammer named "Foxy" comes up to me when I'm 1/8 health, that motherfucker. But notice, rammer boosters have no bullet penetration. So I easily take out his bullets and GG, they are DONE. Why? Because they too probably thought like me that those little bullets were shit.

But they aren't. So I kill them, flanking them to expose their vulnerable side. This was the first encounter with Foxy.

Then a destroyer comes up to me and says hi. I say hi back, avoiding his bullets and taking him out easy with the little but spicy bullets.

I don't remember the exact order, but I probably killed Foxy five times--one of his/her attempts were the bullet build. Although that attempt almost killed me, I still got Foxy back. He/she was probably REALLY frustrated. I also killed this level 45 triplet many times, called Rodney or something, can't remember that well.

By this point I was 300k score, flat. I wish I took a screenshot of that number. So I keep killing and killing, realizing that this tank was OP for me.

But then, I meet claudio.xx again, this time he/she had high reload so the drones got me, just barely. The opponent's tank was down to about half health.

So after I got brutally murdered by the doritos, I spawn, upgrade to flank guard, and go to this build: 0/7/7/0/0/0/0/7 (oh yeah you know what's happening next.) I immediately go towards the leader, which was claudio.xx, and what do you think I did next? That's right, while the player was distracted with some hybrid named...ah, forgot. Then I ram the player, the player dies. Then I go to the classic booster rammer build.

I "teamed" with this guy named "cf" who was also a tri-angle rammer. After I earn his/her trust, I kill him. I was cruel, but it's FFA you teamers. Oh, I know, booster rammers are annoying. But the whole POINT for me then was having fun and annoying players. The same player, cf comes back many times as tri-angle booster, and I kill him...over...over...overlord...over...over...and over again! Much satisfaction for me, much frustration for cf!

Claudio.xx comes back again, I kill. Then after I'm halfway done to regenerating health, a destroyer kills me, however I got his health down to less than 1/4. Then, excited, he upgrades to the hybrid, getting brutally murdered by claudio.xx. So I bet he/she was probably really frustrated, since I know that feeling of getting killed immediately after the upgrade.

So yeah. End of story.

TL;DR: You should read it, but the idea is that I was being annoying as fuck and I realized that Spread Shot is OP for me. Then later I succeed in more trolling as booster rammer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Battleship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 03:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is fucking shit. Now everyone's either gonna comment "git gud" or comment "it's not so bad dumbass" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Proposal: make arenas close (for updates) every 24 hours instead of making tiny updates every hour. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 01:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Proof </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 05:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel guilt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 05:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was playing the Landmine today with the build 3/10/10/10.

Then I saw unnamed 0 points tank... I immediately drove him into the corner and SQUEEZED HIM

...

I didn't feel anything

Then I suicided to this person named "Mercator"

He was a booster rammer, by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm against AutoMod. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 06:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's time that we do something about rule #4 and AutoMod. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I allowed to contribute to ddora? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 05:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions to ask diepio players to see if they are experienced </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 04:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nerf the Fallen Booster! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 01:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God damn it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My best score with the Hurricane Sandy build using Octo Tank! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 01:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh my fucking god this AutoMod. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok read the comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Level 60 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Level 60 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sprayer = Rejected expo marker cap confirmed!?!? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 01:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I fucking quit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 23:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rammers and spawnkillers everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 21:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Why aren't traps bouncing off walls anymore?

2. Is Reload practically useless for Necromancer?

3. Why are rammers so annoying?

4. Is Santa real? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Response to Alpha Triangle, AI inspires lots! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 06:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about zombie apocalypse mode where players fight zombies!...

...or AI vs People gamemode?

:D

P.S.: My posts are short and annoying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kind of clickbait is this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 02:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm afraid AutoMod will take this down </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 20:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But anyway...

Can we have more levels beyond level 45?

AND NO, I AM NOT ASKING FOR MORE SUPER OP CLASSES.

I just want to level up beyond 45, just based on score, nothing else.

:D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first thing I do in the morning on the internet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 19:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to www.reddit.com/r/diepio

Do stuff

Go to diep.io

Play stuff

;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An interesting Octo Tank build? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 07:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never tried this build, but it seems really interesting. I will update this post if I do get to try it, but it's really hard since the build can't farm well.

So the build is:

Health Regeneration: 5
Maximum Health: 7
Body Damage: 0
Bullet Speed: 0
Bullet Penetration: 7
Bullet Damage: 7
Reload: 7
Movement Speed: 0

This focuses on having a massive bullet wall around you, excluding the bullet speed, since it is not necessary.

To prevent getting killed as much as possible (because this is kind of supposed to be an annoying build by opponents), I put some lots of points on health.

I'll call this the Tank. :D what a creative name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meetup in TDM! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 01:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! Let's do a meetup!

Name yourself [RDT](Your reddit name) and come to
diep.io/#71FE1091BB304A

Also, try to spawn in RED team.

My name will be [RDT] oi.peiD.

This expires in 30 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As soon as I log in I see this, and no, this is not photoshopped. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 19:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Message to the Developers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 07:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello devs, hope you guys are having a good time developing the game and working very hard. In fact, I want to first give a round of applause.

I am loving the updates, with many new tanks and a few minor game improvements.

However, tanks are not the only thing--how about gamemodes? Or, how about settings/options, etc?

I hope you take those words into thought, as I would assume you probably are from all those comments that requested many features.

For example, I really want private/sandbox servers added to the game.

Thanks to anyone who read.
:/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bored of AFK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 01:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, I play Overlord a lot but this time I decided to try out the Landmine.

I've been AFK as the Landmine for right now 7 minutes and 41 seconds straight (I set up a timer as soon as I realized I need to time myself)... I even had time to feed my dog and take a drink.

What's funny is that I'm second place on the leaderboard, and if I become first place, I'm screwed although the leader arrow fades. They'll know I'm a landmine, they will know that I am in the corner. What's also funny is that a little tank named "minesweeper" came to the corner and died because of me.

But I hate the invisibility delay, I counted and it seems to be about 15 seconds.

---afk for a while---

I'm now 4th place on the leaderboard, 14 minutes 9 seconds.

Oh shit
Ohhhh noooo
I meant to click on my diep.io tab but my mouse jittered and I clicked the X button instead. Now I'm out of that game.

FUUUU-*voice cracks* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overlord </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 20:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the Overlord affected by Reload at all? I'm pretty sure it speeds up the rate at which drones spawn in, but some say Reload is absolutely trash for Overlord.

Also, any tips? ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Landmines not turning invisible? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 03:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title says it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I too addicted to diep.io or is this a booster on my megaminx </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 22:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (almost) best update ever! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 03:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello devs. I know I've been criticizing a lot, but these major game changes are really what we need as players. Although I would still like a few more changes, this is awesome! Keep it on! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 08:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hacks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 08:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now listen... I'm a really good kind gamer. I don't use cheats or be dishonest or anything. (Or barely) I'm just listing out my thoughts so I can kinda get feedback and stuff. So, erm, don't ban me from the forums or anything. Ok? Right?
I don't know what to say anymore. I'm kinda straightforward.

FastFire: (mainly related to Reload) Just as the name says, it allows the tank to fire very very rapidly. For drone-controlling ships, of course, reload dictates over how frequently the drones will spawn, so same applies for them as well.

InfiPen: (mainly related to Bullet Penetration) This makes your bullet practically invincible, and it destroys every other bullet in its path.
FastSpeed: FastSpeed makes tanks accelerate to their top speed in an instant, allowing quick escapes or swift direction changes. When the player stops pressing a movement key, it decreases its speed down to 0 in an instant. In other words, fast acceleration/deceleration.

ShapeAim: Aim allows the tank's barrel (or drones) to be directly pointed (or moved to) toward the nearest polygon in the range of the bullet. Since bullets do not keep their momentum from the movement of the tank itself, this can work.

TankAim: This has priority over ShapeAim and does exactly what it says. It aims directly at players. Although players can move, it's still a benefit than blind-shooting or missing shots.

Regen: This constantly heals the tank at the normal crazy regeneration rate.

Invis: With this hack, to your screen, the tanks and the bullets/drones are shown. However, others cannot see anything. Although this may seem OP, it might make gameplay situations disadvantageous sometimes. And holy crap disadvantageous is a word.

AutoRestart: This hack automatically respawns the player (and cannot change gamemodes) and puts all the remaining stat points from death in the order that they were spent.

HitBox: Shows all player/polygon hit boxes.

AutoUp: This automatically upgrades the tank to the class that is selected.

FOV: FOV allows customizable FOV.

Tracer: The tracer creates lines directing from the player which thicken as the player gets closer to another player. The tracer only targets tanks within 1/3 of the map.

AntiPush: This eliminates any push from players or knockback from bullets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Devs, we need significant game changes and more gamemodes NOT new classes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 23:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly what the title says. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diep.io Hack Ideas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 07:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost giving up on the developers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 03:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First priorities for updates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 02:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who else agrees? God damn it.

1. Make it so players always join a FRESH Domination or Mothership game

2. Remove classes from the Sniper class branch and make them their own branch.

3. Add more GAMEMODES like sandbox and pricate servers, not new tanks. We need major game changes first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 2b2t Historical Fiction Novel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 04:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello.

First let me say that I'm a newfag who supports the veterans. If you want to hate me and tell me to go kms that's fine (because why the hell not this is a 2b2t reddit) but just keep in mind what I said.

Okay, so I've been reading a book lately, and I've been also very painfully addicted to 2b2t and its history, the recent "Incursion" with the stupid Rushers I guess.

So I wanted to combine those two together and sort of organize something that makes an EPIC written historical novel about 2b2t. Of course it'll be a minecraft novel, but not like those childish ones. This will probably be fully finished (if anyone actually listens) AFTER the current Rusher war is over. So I have some ideas written:

The Prologue will briefly tell the history of 2b2t--from its start 6 years ago. It will tell most of the important historical facts of 2b2t.
Then the main character should be Fit in my opinion, since I guess he is some kind of warhero that is leading the Veterans.
Each chapter will be based on huge impactful event, such as Fit (I want this to be told in first person) becoming a leader, TCR wanting war, the queue, xTurtle, Unicorn, Unstoppable, and some things that Fit has done. Also the recent grief of the VoW, Napkin, etc. (Damn is anyone keeping track of history here?)

Bye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pink Triangles. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 03:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/ze0LnVa

I managed to carry a pink triangle from the middle all the way to base, and it turns out it doesn't die. Since it has AI, shouldn't it be killed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 04:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hacks are allowed, so why does it say "Flying is not enabled on this server" when I try to fly?

I don't know if flyhacks are permitted here, but I haven't been able to use it and I have seen many others use flyhacks.

Please either fix this bug or tell me what's going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Saddest Moment Ever in the History of Diep.io </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 22:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I'll share the video link but a few things to keep in mind:

1. I am not a noob, nor am I a pro.
2. I had problems with uploading to YouTube so the only choice was to upload it to vid.me or something.
3. Ignore the last 6 minutes; there was that last bit of music I accidentally put in the timeline of the video editor.

Here is the video link:
https://vid.me/5MZW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you are disgustingly eager to spend those points after absent-mindedly farming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 08:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Death Screen Bugs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 20:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I'll get straight to the point. This morning I was playing, and when I died, I saw what I thought was a death screen bug.

I'll attach the image, but there are some things wrong:
1. The "Time Alive" is completely incorrect. Whenever I die, it says exactly 8 hrs 54 mins and 33 secs, which is clearly not accurate.
2. Also, if I got killed by ramming into a polygon rather than being hit by any bullet at all in the time alive, it STILL says I was killed by an unnamed tank, which should be fixed to something like "You were killed by: colliding with a polygon". I say this because the final hit that kills the player is what matters, am I right?
3. So in TDM, (and there might be more bugs with Domination and Mothership, let me know) I was a red non-upgraded tank. Then I got killed by a blue double barrel blue. But it showed what neither of us were, showing a blue non-upgraded tank. What is that tank shown supposed to be, the tank you had or the tank that killed you?

Thanks for reading, and please fix any other bugs we come across. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> O R G A N I Z A T I O N and OP crops from harvesting power </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 06:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Private Servers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 20:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
