<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2482</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 04:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that near Del Boca Vista? =D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 20:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're lucky!  That happened to a kid at Niagara Falls too.  Luckily Superman was there to fly down and save him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 19:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and then revealed it at High School Reunion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 23:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awww Jerid, why the long division? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 21:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of them is an Environmentalist? In 1990?

Yeah, you homeless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 01:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right on. =)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 23:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..and you'd still have only used less than 1% of the card </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scrub harder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me, that I've always wondered why they have Braille on drive-thru ATMs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found an old 4 GB Micro under my keyboard the other day, and thought "What the heck am I going to do with this useless piece of crap?"

I can remember when I "upgraded" to 3.5" floppies from 5.25"s.  I thought I had enough storage to last forever, with a whopping 1.44 MB in each one!  Who could use all that space! lol

Now I'd pick my teeth with a 4GB micro and toss it in the trash without thinking twice.  That 4GB micro has the same storage as almost 2.9 THOUSAND 3.5" floppies.  We're so spoiled these days.  

And just for visualization purposes, a 1 TB SD card has as much space as nearly 3/4 of a million 3.5" floppies.  
A 3.5" floppy is 3.3 mm thick.  
If you piled all the 3.5" floppies on top of each other that equaled the amount of storage in a 1 TB SD card, the pile would be 1.5 miles high.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To which your Mom replies "Or, since we're throwing threats around, you can take it out to measure it, and if it's longer than 3 inches, I'll grab it from you and bury it in your neck...you know, since we're only talking hypotheticals."

What a power-trip dick move the principal did.  Of course she knew it wasn't over 3 inches, or she wouldn't have offered to give it back.  She only said that to try and intimidate your mother and establish dominance.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "trumped up charges 

Considering the U.S. Presidential Candidates, this term has an entirely new meaning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meanwhile, out on the streets, your mom's bf...
"Stop, or I'll shoot!"
*click* *click*

Damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Passengers unite!  Tackle him!!!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 19:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read your reply and the first thought that came to my mind was "Oh man, 310, that guy was HUGE!".

Then I realized I'm 300.  Doh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  Just no.

If you think that killing innocent people is an excuse for feeling frustrated at how the system works, you are wrong.

School shooters have much deeper flaws in their psyche's than feeling frustrated at the system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 17:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question:  If it fell on   damaged my property or myself, would I be able to file a lawsuit to receive monetary compensation from China? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the voice of Buster Bunny from Tiny Toon Adventures was the voice of Starscream in the Transformers movies...also the voice of Babs Bunny is the person who plays Crazy Cat Lady in the Simpsons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 01:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 20:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not me...cancelled the day after they announced the price increase, and haven't heard a peep from them since.  

Amazon Fire Stick + Kodi/Exodus = The only cable I'll ever need </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 20:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wise...Job showed sources to back up his claims.  How bout you provide a source to your statistics for DV in active duty military families?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 20:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very wrong.  If you are operating a motor vehicle, you do have an obligation to show your documents when requested by a Law Enforcement Officer (License, Vehicle Ownership documents (registration), (and in some states insurance...not all states require insurance proof during traffic stops). 
It's part of the fine print when you sign your license.  

So, yes, you DO have an obligation to show things to the Officer should he/she ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:When one pours soda into a cup, why does the "head" of Mt Dew dissipate in seconds (almost as fast as one can pour), but the "head" of ones Coke takes minutes to dissipate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 21:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:When I pour soda into a cup, why does the "head" of my Mt Dew dissipate in seconds (almost as fast as I can pour), but the "head" of my Coke takes minutes to dissipate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 21:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I pour soda into a cup, why does the "head" of my Mt Dew dissipate in seconds (almost as fast as I can pour), but the "head" of my Coke takes minutes to dissipate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 21:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The movie Natural Born Killers.

I was a freshman in high school when it came out.  Woody was just the epitome of cool to me...those circular no-frame glasses....Yes!  i thought it was so "cool", and that the main characters in the movie were so awesome.

I watched it recently, and was appalled by all aspects of it.  The lack of empathy of the main characters, the indiscriminate killing...all of it.  Not sure why young me ever thought that killing innocent people (in a movie) was cool.  I was certainly an idiot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 18:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm not mad at it" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 01:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so old.  I don't understand any of the drug terms or references in this thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 03:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Polarized.  

LPT: 
Polar Iced = Having a Polar Bear throw a snowball at you.
Polaroid = Not someone you want to have to dance on the pole after she does her song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 04:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant Flash Fiction

[http://365tomorrows.com/2016/07/10/tradition/](http://365tomorrows.com/2016/07/10/tradition/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 00:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> M. Night Shyamalan twist:  Number 7 is why Number 5 is true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 00:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank goodness it's not an R-Type.  It would take all our quarters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 03:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's no surprise this thread floated to the front page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 02:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Prenuptial Agreement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 23:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm talking about [this](http://news.nationalgeographic.com/2016/07/radio-telescope-new-galaxies-meerkat-south-africa-space-science/), which is days old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 20:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I never understood how scientists are so sure of current models of mass in the universe.

...When just recently, they pointed the new telescope into a random area of space that they thought were only a few galaxies...and found over a thousand galaxies they didn't know were there previously because they couldn't detect them.

Well, maybe all the "missing mass" is just that we don't have sensitive enough equipment to detect it yet, as per the above example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> During lunch, what did one Soldier say to the other Soldier? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 01:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Want some Turkey? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 18:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the looks of the moon dust on the top right of the plaque....it looks like they stuck it into the ground upside down first....then said, Ooops!....and turned it right side up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 21:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=40GfFAWWb0E) is my favorite song of the entire soundtrack, and this version wasn't in the movie or the Soundtrack.  

It's just so...chill.  This is perfect music to put on loop and do homework to.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 21:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This infuriates me.  My current job, I work for a very large organization that receives emails from people throughout the world, sending us information in various formats.  We get 1000's of emails a day, from people we don't know, and that have attachments and links to download documents, etc.  
So it's almost literally our job to blindly click links and download attachments.

Our contracting company decided to do a big push on cyber awareness, and being careful...so they sent out fake malicious content that is supposed to look legitimate, and if you clicked the content, you got a warning that "had this been real, you would have just compromised the whole system...be more careful in the future, this is your last warning".

MF'ers....our entire JOB is opening this suspicious email crap!  We haven't received the second round of "test" emails yet, so who's to say what will happen when we inevitably fail their little test. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 01:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ghandi and Ponzi.  It's a foolproof scheme...and if it doesn't work out, at least it will end peacefully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 23:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drinking alcohol while pregnant.  

My alcoholic wife was pregnant with our 2nd child.  She continued to drink throughout the pregnancy, heavily.  I couldn't stop her.  I tried social services (CPS), doctors, law enforcement (least helpful), psychiatrists.  
The best I could do was get her into an involuntary psych eval for 72 hours for being a threat to herself (though not the baby).  When she was released, she started up like nothing had happened.  

No charges could be filed against her for child endangerment.  CPS would only act and file charges if the baby was born with impairments that stemmed from Alcohol Fetal Syndrome (AFS).  Law Enforcement could give a shit, because no crime was being committed, nor law being broken.  (It's not illegal to drink while you're pregnant...and there are no laws protecting a fetus from the abuse of a legal substance)

[For those wondering how it turned out]
He was born without any symptoms of AFS, so CPS basically said Oh Well.  It took three years, but I finally got a final protective order for both my kids against her, until the kids' 18th birthday...and I have full custody of them.  We were very lucky that he didn't develop any lasting problems from the 9 months of constant drinking.  She drank to blackout nearly every day of her pregnancy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 23:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to join the Coast Guard.  But I found out you have to be at least 5'8" to be able to join.

So that if your ship sinks, you can walk to shore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 23:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's absolutely ridiculous, the placement of 7-11's.  In Virginia Beach, behind Oceana Naval Station, there are two 7-11's within sight of each other on the same road, maybe only 100 yards apart. 
Here's a [LINK](https://www.google.com/maps/@36.7995672,-76.0079451,3a,75y,106.9h,80.01t/data=!3m6!1e1!3m4!1sVWV5JFgRHJxljyrg2IoO0w!2e0!7i13312!8i6656) to the Google Street View.  You can see the 7-11 Sign and Gas Pumps of the other 7-11 just down the road a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red Guy would make an awesome Halloween costume. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 22:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially rigging the yarn strands to push out whenever you talked.  Maybe wearing a red mask so you didn't have to make the yarn so thick...so you could actually see where you were going.  

It's just too bad my body type is more Duck Guy, than Red Guy.  Ha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 19:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am 99% convinced that this is a plant, just to get hits on the video.  (As has already been stated and presumed).

The reasoning...All the scraps of paper with lyrics are perfectly cut/ripped/torn so that none of the lyrics are cut off or unreadable.  Clearly a plant for this post.  
Secondly, why on earth would the lyrics be scribbled out on scraps of paper in the first place, for a professional music video production? 

I don't buy it at all.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 23:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's considered breaking the fourth wall because the character in the movie is speaking directly to you, the person watching the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is the percentage of marriages that end in divorce so often quoted as 50%? (read text for more explanation) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 21:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 00:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was about 5 or 6, in Key West FL camping in a tent with my parents.  I was a bit away from the tent by myself, throwing rocks as far as I could into the ocean, and some random dude that was walking by told me to stop throwing rocks into the ocean, or you'll fill it up and the ocean will disappear.

I had a weird subconscious fear from then on, and never threw a rock into water again until I was an adult and realized he was just messing with me back then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 18:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you mean someone isn't sitting inside the drone piloting it?  It's remotely piloted, you say?  

#dronedefinition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the one song that instantly transports you to your days at the roller rink during the 80's? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 17:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 05:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now....imagine Trump were President when all this actually happens.  

My bet, he'd say something rude and offensive about the *racial slur* fighting it out...pull out all forces from SK, and say it's not a U.S. problem...thus destroying our credibility with the entire world, turning us into an isolationist and weakening us considerably because no one trusts us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feds crack iPhone, will withdraw case against Apple </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 00:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 19:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Galaxy S7 arrived last night.  Now water balloon immune.  

*Typed from my shower on my phone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 18:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll recognize dollars as a legal form of currency for sure!  And your private army will surely stay loyal, since you're paying them with that valid and accepted currency....

smh at today's youth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 18:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would wait around for 8016 years before finally being able to post the question of "You're granted eternal life and sent back to 6000 B.C. what one thing do you bring with you, to ensure you are the emperor of the world in 2016?....and then I would read what I SHOULD have done.  

I'm on to you OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 22:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, great response, thank you.

What I am getting from this thread...the legal way to avoid any IRS involvement, would be to draw up a binding document from Mom to Daughter....that Mom is giving Daughter a loan of 50k, and the interest will be xx% (the same interest that Mom is paying on the HELOC), as well as the re-payment terms to mom (which would also match Mom's obligation to the HELOC).  

That way there is documentation that it is not a gift, and in fact a loan...hence no IRS involvement.  

Further...for clarification...if this happens, would Mom still be able to directly pay Daughter's creditors (as part of the loan) and not run into gift limits....or does Mom have to give daughter the 50k up front and let daughter pay off the creditors on her own? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 22:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are fair responses Grump.  in a normal situation, your reply would be completely accurate.

The reality is much more muddied, however.  Long story short, Jane is an abused spouse that fled from an alcoholic spouse with her children to another town...having to leave her alcoholic spouse in the home that is in both their names on the deed...though the mortgage is in Jane's name only.  Jane is having to pay that mortgage, as well as her current rent, and daily living expenses for her and the children.  Divorcing the spouse would involve alimony, dealing, and having to take on the $100k debt that is in her husbands name.  
This is also why a Home Equity loan by jane is not an option, since her husband wouldn't agree to that whatsoever.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having debt paid off by parent-trying to remain legal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 21:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friend of mine (always the case, eh?), we'll call her Jane.  

Jane is 38 y/o, single, has a $102k/year job, and has $50k in combined debt, spread amongst 4 different credit cards, and 2 other credit accounts with major retailers.  

Jane is paying approx $1,600 in combined payments on this debt every month (more than the minimum), however, Jane recently figured out it will take her approximately 12 years to pay the debt completely off at this rate.

For various reasons, Jane is not able to get a debt consolidation loan.  Unimportant why.

Jane's parent (we'll call her Janice), owns a home and is well off.  Janice gave an offer to Jane out of the blue.
Janice is willing to take a $50k Home Equity Loan out on her home, and pay off all the debt for Jane from that $50k, if Jane just agrees to pay the bill from the $50k loan.

The monthly bill for the (10 year term) loan would be only $580.  So, Jane would go from being $50k in debt, with a $1,600 monthly combined payment..and not being debt free for 12 more years....
...to being debt free (as far as credit score is concerned) and only having a $580 bill and being done in 10 years.

Should I...er, should Jane take Janice up on this offer? 

A few questions! 

-Is there anything inherently illegal about this?

-Does anything need to be reported to the IRS to make sure this is legal?  (i.e. if Jane "pays" Janice $580 a month, is that considered a "gift" in the eyes of the IRS and need to be reported?)

-If Jane decides to overpay on the loan, and instead "pays" Janice the entire $1600 a month that she used to pay, instead of the minimum $580...she will probably be able to pay off the debt in 4 or 5 years, vice 10.  Would a "payment" of $1600 a month be IRS reporting territory, even if the above question isn't?

-Some of the credit card bills are more than $10k.  Assuming that Janice doesn't transfer $50k to Jane (since that would definitely require IRS reporting, and hence, taxes on it)...If Janice paid off these credit cards for Jane directly to the credit card company (say, Jane gave Janice her login information)...would THAT constitute having to tell the IRS about it?


Thank you for any insight into this.  Jane realizes that this is a wonderful opportunity that Janice is giving her....and wants to make sure that Janice doesn't get screwed over by accidentally running afoul of the IRS.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 03:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last summer I went to sleep in my third floor bedroom apartment at about 1 am.  

I was woken by the sound of my front door being caved in by a battering ram. (at about 4:30 am)  Confused, disoriented...thinking I was dreaming.  Two firefighters were at my bedroom door a few moments after the loud bang that woke me...and then I realized I could barely see because there was smoke everywhere.  I crawl-walked out the door with them, joining the crowd outside.  

Someone in the first floor had started a fire while cooking that got out of control and ended up gutting that whole floor.
None of the fire alarms/smoke alarms in the apartment had worked.

Quite disorienting to go from peaceful sleep, to smoke filled chaos-chamber instantly (from my point of view) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 22:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> god murders ~~hundreds of people in the bible~~ every living Human and creature on Earth except for a few on a boat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 22:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just take the post down.

Then, create a fake account with a fictional name...and post it again under that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Executive Order -- Establishing Paid Sick Leave for Federal Contractors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 21:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to Executive Order
https://www.whitehouse.gov/the-press-office/2015/09/08/executive-order-establishing-paid-sick-leave-federal-contractors

I'm a Contractor...I work in Washington D.C. for a Federal Agency.  When we looked at our timecards this morning, we noticed that the company has decided to implement the Executive order early...in that we were granted 2.67 hours of sick leave for our most recent 80 hour pay period.
Cool right?

Until we noticed...that we now earned 2.67 LESS hours of the normal Paid Leave we used to get.

So, they just lowered our Earned Paid Leave...in order to Grant us the Sick Leave that the Executive Order requires.

Is this legal!?  

If I left the company and had 100 hours of paid leave earned...the company would pay me the leave they owe me on the way out the door.  
Now, with it being split, if I left the company and had 50 hours of paid leave, and 50 hours of sick leave...they wouldn't reimburse me for the sick leave. Only the paid leave.

So...essentially this Executive Order just made it easier for the company to profit off us by only half our leave being owed if we leave.  

This doesn't seem right at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
