<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3415</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I'll have to concede your first two points are true, I didn't know he had that wording on the web page and I'm happy we're in agreement about early access. 

Not saying this makes you wrong or anything but did he really get paid "millions of dollars?" I feel that might be a bit hyperbolic I know Cube World is a game a lot of people want but not that many I would guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd forgotten about the early access release. 

I'll have to see where he promised updates if you could provide a source on that it would be great. 

Besides that point early access doesn't mean you're going to get updates, in this day and age we know this. I remember before then Wollay did not want to do early access for the same reason we're having this discussion; Wollay didn't want to deal with the responsibility and if I recall correctly he made that clear when he released the early access build.

It's one guy making a big game in his spare time...the hell do you want from him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Wars: Jedi Outcast is my personal pick. A great choice if you love FPS like Doom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SWBF2 was an awesome follow up to the original BF. I played the literal shit out of the first SWBF, SWBF2 turned me off with the super OP Jedi Leaders being playable though. I would prefer and all out shooter devoid of special Jedi characters.

That being said I never got to play Dark Forces growing up but I bought it at at Goodwill a few years back and it was a blast. I love old school shooters. I own Dark Forces 2 on Steam but haven't gotten around to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duke Nukem was passed from developer to developer and the original idea was was no where near represented in the final product. 

It's impossible to compare a one man team who works on this big game in his spare time.

There are some builds that are (or were) available to download. Not a whole lot of content but you can get a feel for the game at least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he wants to release the game in a full state rather than leaking developer builds over the course of several years so the game won't fade to obscurity. 

He says so clearly in the FAQ if you bothered to read it, Cube World ain't gonna be released til Cube World is ready. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprising people don't know this...in the FAQ on the site I clearly remember these words:

"When can I buy Cube World?" 

Answer: When it's done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot to mention time lines. 

Nearly every time I've seen a developer give reasons for incomplete or buggy game is they didn't have the time to wrap up most of what they wanted to actually get to. 

Maybe what you said is true but I'm more inclined to blame the publishers wanting to get the game out before Christmas season as the main reason some games aren't in development for as long as they need to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That just completely kills gem progression and one of the limiting factors of augmenting ancients.

Was farming for gems a thing in the first place?

Unless you're playing one class with of every main stat then your gym progression becomes turning whichever ones you have excess of into the required gem. 

Gem progression is held in the legendary gems, you don't want to waste your augment on a lower level legendary gem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Wars: Jedi Outcast is where it's at tho my man. 

There some real multiplayer there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure it's special sanitizing duct tape then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cups gonna bust one day. Also you can't clean inside that crack...it might get nasty. Get a new cup! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to live there! Real creative man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 12:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't think or know this, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm still an amateur when it comes to building, but I'm proud of this Mini-Castle I made. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 07:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you know she isn't into vanilla missionary for procreation only sex? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello there, as someone who isn't a fan I can say from my perspective that it's the pop-ness of this music that makes it hard to listen to. 

Beyonce is a model, not a pop star. She should really stick to what she is actually good at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was being hyperbolic. I'm aware it makes me seem like a gaming hipster of sorts I prefer the days where every had the same skins, guns, and it was just all about the game play. 

There are games where customization is a big feature but I see a lot of games these days where I feel like such things don't belong. As long as people keep paying for them though they will be around so the most I can do is hope the fad doesn't infect my favorite games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you take inspiration from [Floppy Heroes](http://store.steampowered.com/app/480450/)?

I love physics based combat games like this. As a suggestion from someone who loves this sub-genre of fighting games if you're going to add in a multitude of weapons or items for fighting please please please balance them in a meaningful way. 

A lot of games like this wind up have a best strategy and it really takes away from the feel of a game when you have a lot of cool weapons but no real reason to use them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally have had a distaste for such a thing ever since they introduced hats in TF2. I stopped playing TF2 after loot boxes started appearing and have actively avoided nearly ALL games that use them. 

I really enjoy CS:GO but most people playing it are more concerned with what my M4 looks like as opposed to what I can do with it...so meh, hardly touch it now these days.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please heavens no.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little spacing between clickable objects is always nice, I came to this thread to tell you to just click better but then I remembered how NPC's in Terraria block everything...so you got a point. 

More space between usable objects! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if the employees have tidied up to the max already? 

What if everything is done? 

I've gotten such discussions from managers...some people work fast and will have everything clean and done. If they are going to be there for eight hours just because it doesn't take them that eight doesn't mean they still don't deserve hours. 

Otherwise you're just kicking employee moral in the balls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was cool of your manager to do. Several jobs I have worked had a "time to lean time to clean" mentality that if you weren't doing some form of busy work then you shouldn't be getting paid. 

It's all just a corporate trick to make places look busy to customers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so why get upset about people stating facts?

The problem is you're asserting steroid use without proof. I wouldn't be upset if they were indeed using steroids but you can't assert that without proving it. That was my point, you're making a false assertion without proof which would be found to be really disrespectful of the hard work those men and women put to suggest it was helped along by substances we look down on people for using. 

I'm not pretending they don't use it, I'm just assuming innocent until proven guilty. Also never said anything about anyone not working hard enough in the gym so...projection maybe? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daniel Bryan, CM Punk, AJ Styles...three recent and huge names in the pro-wrestling world that break the big muscular man stereotype and have never been confirmed to be using performance enhancing drugs. 

How can they be a necessity when the top performers in the last decade have all been moderately sized men with very achievable physiques? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of a big assumption though isn't there?

Calling steroids off the bat just because he's muscular is shorted sighted and ignorant. 

Are they are thing in the professional wrestling business? Maybe for some but performance enhancing drugs are found in a whole myriad of sports, so why is pro-wrestling the one that gets the bad rap for it?

Those dudes work their asses off and writing it off as roids is not only objectively ignorant but also hella disrespectful to everything these dudes do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are four places named "Poop"

http://us.geotargit.com/called.php?qcity=Poop all=cities part=beginning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 05:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's see...the cat is stealing the bread, hissing, being a bitch and general nuisance...I'd say yea, seems about right to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> House looks clean, cat doesn't looked malnourished, we know animals exhibit strange behaviors we can't always explain, she was very gentle with the cat the whole time, didn't yell at it when the bag busted, other cats in the video seem real calm and collected (and nice and fluffy.) I would say it's safe to assume everything is fine here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, not like he just enjoys the game on a personal level or anything. Better make sure your friends only play games that you approve of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went back and forth to Burger King six or eight times...I lost count. 

Manager would tell me "Come back tomorrow at 11am" and he would either not be there or tell me he didn't have  time for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not arguing with anything you said just wanted to point out Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater came out on the PS2 and ALL the animation is computer animation, no mocap. 

Everything is so highly polished in that game and to be a PS2 game on top of that makes it a marvel of graphical achievement for it's time.

Developer's these days have zero excuses for stuff that looks as shitty as Andromeda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The internet has a desire to assert sexuality into anything and everything. There was never any indication that LeFou was gay...in this or the original. 

It's people looking for "holes" in someone's masculinity and then asserting that they must be homosexual because they either have a great amount of respect and adoration for another man or because they have physical contact with another man, even if it is non-sexual. 

Unless LeFou explicitly states he is or has an explicit homosexual moment there is nothing to contemplate here. It's all buzz surrounding the movie and the modern social movement that is so up in everyone's business about what gender, sex, etc they are the ideas are being pushed into media as well, hence the big to do about nothing of LeFou maybe or maybe not being gay...you decide! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found a building you can glitch through in bioshock infinite, nothing useful but interesting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
