<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2840</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad wanted to call me Hassan, my mom refused because she said life would be confusing with a Hassan and a Hussain(my brother). They named me after my grandpa, Saeed. My dad is still salty after 15 years about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won't completely shut them down and immediately say no when they propose something new, and get into a shouting match with them over sometime small. Say no all you want, but you gotta justify it. I understand why he wouldn't want us to go to Pakistan, but Oman is the most peaceful Arab nation but it's "dangerous" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 09:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Communism  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 12:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> House of cards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend pissed off my other friend, to the extremes, and I somehow put them back together. I love being a peacemaker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always make sure when I'm walking down the stairs to keep my hands OUT of my pockets, this trick saved me quite a few times. I always used to walk down the stairs with my hands in my pockets, boiiii I payed for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is keeping a bike upright while riding easy, but keeping it upright when it's stationary is impossible? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started reading out of pettiness

I was in 4th grade, and my sister offhandedly mention she started the Harry Potter series when she was in the 3rd grade. Naturally, I took this as a challenge and picked up Harry Potter and the sorcerer's Stone. From there I went on to The Hunger Games, and the Inheritance Cycle, and kept picking books up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sexual abuse victims; what's your story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 13:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Write '17 in your classmates names, like style it so that all your classmates names make 17 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biology  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Touching myself vs. others touching me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I touch my thighs, it's a "normal" sensation, when someone else touchs my thighs, it's much more noticeable/electric, why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's say that Apple has 100,000$(for simplicity) now let's say they sell a percentage of 0.1% of their company(stocks) to you for 100$. Now Apple has 100,100$, which they can invest in the company. With your hundred dollars, let's say they made 900$. Now they have 101,000$. Since the company benifitted from your money, the stock is worth more. Now if you sell that 0.1% back, you'll get 101$. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, they're printing money. A lot of it. Sounds like a good idea right? Wrong. Think about it like this, country A has 100B currency, which equates to 10B US dollars. If country A decides to print another 100B currency, then the value of the currency drops by half. 
 

This is really, really bad. Let's say you have 10,000 currency, and overnight the currency dropped in value by half. Then the prices will double, but the value stays the same. This makes people extermely poor. Which worsens the economic situation, which sends them on a downward spiral. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now we know why hitler gassed them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Do it!" I shouted at Alexia. She looked a bit nervous, but we all are the first time. I grab her arm and we jump off the cliff together. She was screaming, she wished she never jumped. The ground is approaching faster and faster. We were stopped by the bungee cable and by the end we were laughing together and wanted to go for a second round. 

A few years ago in 2039, automated machines replaced all human jobs, even government jobs. They removed the concept of money from our society, and now all the humans can visit anywhere and do anything(if it's not harmful to someone else) for free. The machines can even predict which people are "made" for each. They have always had 100% accuracy. If it wasn't for the wonderful AI Alexia and I wouldn't be able to take a 3 month honeymoon in Oman, or even worse, we never would've met. 

After we finished bungee jumping, Alexia and I went to visit Marneef caves to see the natural blowholes. As we were standing on the surrounding lush hills, she lay her head on my shoulder and said "thank AI that we can be here, it's the most beautiful thing I've ever seen". I smiled and kissed the top of her head. We sat there and we're watching the sea rise and fall, and kept thinking to myself "How could've people ever lived without the Almighty AI?" We sat together until nightfall, then we had a car drive us back to the Crown Plaza hotel. 

We spent that night the same way we spent every other night, we took some dinner to the beach and had food while joking around. After we finsihed our dinner, we would cuddle together and talk of sweet nothings. We would end the night when Alexia would fall asleep on me and I would lie next to her and fall asleep with the slight, by sweet smell of her. 

We spent the remainder of the honeymoon in a similar fashion, and then returned back home. When we got home there was a letter addressed to me from The Lord AI. It specifically told me to read this all alone. I told Alexia that his Greatness AI wants me to read this alone, she smiled slightly and kissed me "You're so loyal to the AI, I'm so proud that they picked you for whatever it is they want." She kissed me again and left. I read the letter and as I progressed through it, all I wanted was to start. 

I told Alexia that I had to leave for around a month, she was really supportive and wished me well. I flew over to North Korea for the task, then flew back with the items. I entered the building, nervous, but pushed on to the main AI. I bowed to His Majesty, and told him "I have procured the requested items from Them." He replied "Thank you Comrade, please empty all the human brains into the central system, the current brains are starting to weaken" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better to be annoyed than dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take 200 pennies, heat half of them and cool the other half, place in cup, pour down the creditor's shirt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, copyright. So let's say I make a movie, and sell the universal rights of that movie to Netflix. After I sold the rights, the movie belongs to Netflix and they can do whatever they want with it, as in show it in any country they want. However, big companies like Disney wouldn't sell universal rights because they'll lose money, so they tell Netflix that they'll allow them to show Cinderella in America, but not in luxumburg. Netflix can apply for the rights in luxumburg, but Disney won't sell it/Netflix doesn't think they'll get their money back if they buy Cinderella for luxumburg.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lesotho is completely covered by South Africa. It has no borders with any other country. Kinda weird it doesn't just join South Africa.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When someone gloats over something they didn't do. "Oh look at my brother, he's in the newspaper!" Or "My dad once met bill gates!" Jesus Christ go get yourself in the newspaper or in the same room as bill gates, get a fucking life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who thinks she's the girl who played Lydia Bennet in The Lizzie Bennet Diaries? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Condoms, lube, and diapers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
