<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3605</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 16:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bruh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who let the dogs out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 01:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Tired of living in his older brother's shadow, Imgur declares war thus starting the Imgur-Redditor War. You are a soldier on the front lines, write about your experiences fighting for your site. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 00:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a very young economist who has a test on it in a week, can someone break down the fundamentals of economics, microeconomics, and macroeconomic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I know I know. I should've studied sooner but some thing or another always came up--I know this is asking for a lot but even a link to a good site that breaks things down well would be helpful. I'am so sorry to be bothering anyone who takes the time to help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hypothetically speaking, how would one go about selling their soul to someone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 01:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 18:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hints dropped by my S.O. 
I thought she had a boyfriend and the conversation went something like this... 
Me: Do you have a boyfriend? 
Her: I guess that's up to you. 
She was basically telling me "Hey. Ask me out so you can be my boyfriend." 
I learned this a year later. 
I almost missed having a girlfriend if she wasn't determined enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 17:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubt many people will this but here it goes.
We both got placed in the same religion class and I was looking for a new friend and I saw her and she seemed shy and introverted (just like me!) so I sat next to her and tried to strike a conversation. Fast forward two weeks later I told her I wanted my geometry to actually die. She laughed and turns out she also has dark humor so...that's how I began to court her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
