<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2991</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dung beetles=Garbage men </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mess with the Devil's cob, get your hair pulled out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! Look at this........GRAPH!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scales and arpeggios build finger strength and endurance as well as helping your brain to divide the hands from each other making it easier to play different things in different hands. Also if you ever want to learn concertos, there are tons of scales and arpeggios that you are expected to play perfectly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to pay more attention to the dynamics. Right off of the start it seemed rather loud. Beethoven was notorious for putting in so many dynamics and expressions throughout his pieces and it is necessary to pay close attention for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you may have overestimated me, but thank you for the info! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is clearly a saxophone..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Togas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When she says, "I just like you as a friend." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When she gives you that look! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Masters degree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm starting to look at different schools for a masters degree in collaborative piano and I'm not sure what schools to look at. Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a person ever says they are going to beat you up, reply, "you couldn't even beat your dick!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find a bunch of different music and sight and sight read and keep sight reading. You would be surprised how important that becomes later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would love to see my teacher sight read something while using this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find what inspires you for each piece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To start I'm just going to say that I don't think that it is the best event they could have come up with, but as someone who lives in the desert, this is something I really like. I have added at least eight more Pokemon to my pokedex, and still need more water types that I don't have. Plus I still need more candies to evolve other Pokemon. It may stink for you, but I would have never gotten enough magikarp candy without walking it and I really don't want to have to walk 600 kilometers to get it. Maybe instead of catching work on leveling up? With increased water Pokemon you could evolve a bunch of different ones for experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try practicing scales by going two octaves up, then switch to contrary motion for two octaves up in the right, down in the left, then two octaves up in the left down in the right, and then back together down to the starting position.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay that makes sense, thank you. Scarlatti lived towards the end of the Baroque era so his keyboard sonatas would most likely be played on the harpsichord. In this case there needs to be a sense of baroque style playing, so try to keep it light as far as the touch goes. 

As for interpretation, Baroque music is usually interpreted as very mechanical with little expression, especially Bach, or very romantic (rubato, varying dynamics, etc.). Scarlatti tends to lean towards the more romantic side, so you have tons of freedom to interpret how you would like to.

I would recommend listening to various recordings of different pianists of the sonata you want to learn to get an idea if what other people are doing, so you can formulate your own. 

Hope that helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 07:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you clarify your question? Are you asking difficulty, or stylistic as in how to play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unown and other rare Pokemon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 07:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the unown in the game yet as well as the other rare Pokemon? I heard about that maybe they are in the game and I saw the numbers in the pokedex, but are they actually in the game? Also if the unown are in the game, is there a chance that when all are caught you will receive some sort of gift? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both. I'm not sure about getting banned, it is something I would have to research.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone aware of shiny Pokemon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use All G. It allows you to sign into your account and look at all you have without screenshotting everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm waiting for a navy seal to be sitting in him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 01:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pregnant chicks getting weird combinations of sauces on a sub. Like mayo bbq ranch Italian dressing and mustard all at once.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just call it, "Explosions!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over 500 pounds of ham went down with the Titanic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they're walking on sunshine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even a woman needed to let you know he's whipped  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 05:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I see is hours of drunk entertainment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the one that randomly screams squirrel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 17:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope to God that I have a boner and that they will be super distracted by it so I can knock them out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
