<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2797</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 22:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks this is interesting and helps a lot, feel free to post any interesting things on this topic on the page   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 00:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> perturbation theory and EPR paradox. but you know they have classes on quantum that they can make you take as a grad student which are obviously pretty challenging and advanced, so its not like you need to be an expert lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 00:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Full Study) http://www.nature.com/articles/nature16989.epdf?referrer_access_token=IOi_zuNu0cQ09Jie2xmqttRgN0jAjWel9jnR3ZoTv0PWUB7snrGnPV5StPVG2ayfUUSxJ2xSPP7qsPRl_WXQ121-rG9XhUxiwD2u1XNAFKjMartPjyo5PStuXcwVX32Bj4pBJF6o2YeiLxLmtUyhdWLLMCZNIQQSuCo6AByidYctsVvX0VBs4srPjXDMWm8RN5D3hsyCjP5YxZPATqwjrHhf7n-hOWbdg0RBY_1za_I%3D tracking_referrer=www.rsc.org </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> potential new Organic chem catalyst </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 00:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 22:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/chem.200600203/full </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> presence of alpha-effect for Sn2 reactions in gas phase was found experimentally in '05, should we re-think our explanation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 22:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://pubs.acs.org/doi/abs/10.1021/ol0526930 

If the alpha-effect is to be accepted as a factor in gas-phase Sn2 reactions, we may need to re-think our explanation for its origin.


 Does anyone believe that there could be a unified, single explanation rather than contributing it to multiple factors (ie. solvent, temperature, etc) ?


 also I found an experiment where the stated magnitude of the a-effect for NH2OH was 440 while for NH2NH2/MeNHOH it was 830.


 (Second order rate constants for the SN2(P) reactions of -effect [and related]
nucleophiles with phosphate diester 4, at 25 C and ionic strength 1.0 M (KCl) ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 22:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not saying that im just wondering. I think an undergrad degree in chemistry should be fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 22:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also theoretical chem is most likely the Msc I want to go for in a little bit. Have you ever taken a computer science class or do you think I can finish undergrad without one if I want to go for that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 22:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> probably diff eq and make sure youre solid on physics I guess. You doin a dissertation?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> list of potential feeders for avic avic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 22:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anyone want to share a variety of things they have fed their avic or know can be fed to one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 22:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what does it eat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> chemistry and physics discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 22:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> people obsessed with chemistry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 21:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Podcasts for orgo 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 19:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> for those who believe there is more to be discovered in the field of chemistry /r/TheoreticalChemistry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 18:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is further research on the alpha-effect for nucleophiles necessary? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 21:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this seems difficult to conclude. I am not too confident that solvent-dependence explains the phenomenon in every case. thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> quantum lecture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 21:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> try /r/TheoreticalChemistry for discussion of current issues in modern chemistry and physics. puzzling questions and interesting links also welcome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 21:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> interesting orgo lecture from UC Irvine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 20:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is aromaticity still being researched in depth? (link responses encouraged) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 20:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How satisfied is the chem and physics community with our current understanding and utilization of aromaticity?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> are there any tried and true drills/practices you know of for developing and improving single-variable calculus skills? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 20:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> single-variable calculus can be highly frustrating during the learning process and seems to provoke a fear in many students including myself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 14:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jumped into a high level calc 1 too early and needed to sharpen up after an unfortunate break from practicing math. 3d year undergrad but I switched my major etc...   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has the nucleophilic alpha-effect in organic chemistry been fully explained? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 01:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 01:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 01:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you protonate the hydroxyl group, then it takes 2 electrons and leaves as neutral water and you have your carbocation which will be tertiary because im assuming you started with hexamethylcyclohexanol? then a hydrogen + (or proton) is lost to regenerate your acid catalyst (H3O+) and the electrons from that broken sigma bond between the carbon and the lost hydrogen will form a pi bond finally giving you hexamethylcyclohex(1,2)ene. now someone please answer my post thanks lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 01:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am just wondering if at any point a "string theorist" has stumbled with an undergrad math course, ... as in could I still potentially become one if I struggled with an undergrad course. and I won't be offended by an honest answer lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> anyone into string theory on here ever struggle with a math class? or was it just easy As from pre-algebra all the way to topology and diff eq etc </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 21:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> be honest its the internet youre really not that tough  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has the nucleophilic alpha-effect been fully explained yet? Or is there still research needing to be done? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 21:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have read that there is some confidence in the solvent-dependent hypothesis, which is justified by the lack of the phenomenon in gas phase reactions. But there is also a little confidence in the explanation that the lone pair from the adjacent nucleophile (example molecules hydrazine and hydroxylamine) is capable of stabilizing the decrease in electron density during transition states of Sn2 reactions. Has it yet been speculated that it could be due in some way to negative hyperconjugation? I am just trying to come up with a research project.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feeding Cave crickets to my pink-toe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 17:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have cave crickets in my basement that get pretty large. Im wondering if they would make a good feeder for an vicularia avicularia? thoughts? Im a beginner owner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confused about my future career </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 19:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 19:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that the explanation for dark matter/energy is going to require a mind willing to take big risks and propose completely new things. Kinda like Einstein with his gravity and relativity. Its going to be something that is at first recognized as "too far-fetched" or insane. But I seriously doubt it's going to relate to what we know now (ex: some odd explanation using quantum particles) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The process of publishing a new reaction mechanism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 08:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can anyone describe what this entails? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 21:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the wording is very careful and has a nice rhythm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 21:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> excellent use of imagery. I like the touch of surrealism too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 19:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how did you manage to go from an 18xx 5k guy in HS to an elite, since most elites are always 14-15xx 5k runners in high school and receive a ton of support the whole way. how did you work around other things in life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 19:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not only do they not flush lactate but they produce more and lactate is NOT relevant at all stop talking about lactate its just a glycolysis intermediate and if you read any exercise physiology book it will tell you that it is NOT the CAUSE of fatigue or oxygen debt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 05:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TRY 12-16x400 a little faster than 10k pace, you also should have no problem running at least 3 miles continuously at goal pace, so do 3 mile tempos in 18:00 regularly, or even 21:00 for 3 and a half. also dont be shy to do 10x 2 minutes fast 1 minute slow followed by another 30 minutes of running and 8x200 fast, probably some weight lifting and plyos too. also dont go to letsrun...trust me, JUST dont  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 23:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> burned out like Webb but probably worse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 23:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do standing leg abductions to strengthen it, anyone who tells you to stretch it has never had IT band inflammation, or they just got lucky, ice is also useless, inflammation is there for a reason, and when your body wants it gone the lymphatic system will remove it, ice inhibits the natural healing processes and stretching a damaged tissue makes it more damaged, if a piece of paper is torn... do you stretch it? no you strengthen it with tape   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 23:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you Cain fans are so ridiculous, there is nothing inspiring about her, did she overcome adversity to get to where she is? no! she got LUCKY, YES LUCK. lucky to be genetically gifted, she doesnt work any harder than girls running a 5:45 mile, not to mention she gets to use fuckin underwater treadmills and elite coaching... not fair to other teenage girls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
