<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2923</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Crazy Looking Dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 05:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 21:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> audio/video clips coming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 19:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ideas and a good interface/preamp - a UAD Apollo in my case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 00:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I would always do that if you want to spend less money... 
You don't have to be aggressive or anything. Just be frank. He'll either come down on the price or you can buy one from someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 09:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It totally looks like sim city when you zoom in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 04:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would maybe just call it "compact" instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 20:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah! Are you celebrating something, or did you get a discount? Those things aren't cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NPD] Malekko Helium MkII so far, so great </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 07:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 19:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TC Electronic Shaker... I think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 06:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuuuuughhhh... waaaannnnnt! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 01:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never played a Klon, but I've tried the Soul Food and the Archer with the same amp and guitar and the Soul Food sounded harsh and noisy compared to the Archer. Maybe it was a fluke? It's obviously subjective, but I thought I heard a pretty substantial difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 22:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Archer beats the Soul Food by a mile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 21:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, I'm a little envious of that distort knob on the Throne Room, I've never seen that one before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 20:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're talking about the small, older Semaphore, I have one and it's cool, but I ended up getting a Diamond Tremolo (tried it against the Empress first too and thought it sounded better) because of the tap tempo, subdivisions and the double tempo hold button thing. If you're talking about the bigger semaphore with tap tempo, nevermind (except for the double time hold feature). 

I know I've already posted about it, but the Uverbia is crazy good. Just want to reiterate that. I've also been using it as a distortion pedal on some recordings and it sounds so cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 04:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would prefer not to be burned. I'm not saying they're good (or original) just that they're popular, which could be lucrative if you're starting a business.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 02:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diamond makes some really good stuff. Also, Malekko, Catalinbread, Empress, Earthquaker, Subdecay... Walrus Audio, JHS, and OBNE are getting a good bit of attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 05:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> J Rockett Archer (Klone)
ScreaminFX Uverbia spring reverb
and my RE-201 Space Echo if that counts... 

if not, either the Empress Vintage Modified Superdelay for its versatility or the Analog Man ARDX20 for its... I don't even know what it is... magic maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 21:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really into it. Haven't quite figured out how to fit it on the board yet (which pedals to boot off), but if I can't do it I'll just end up setting it to the left or maybe even near the amp. It's something I'm probably going to leave on most of the time while I'm playing so I don't need super quick access to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 22:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just posted a video demo here --- https://youtu.be/Jfn-o_vJdB0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NPD] video demo of ScreaminFx Uverbia real spring reverb pedal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 22:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 01:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has a 3 spring MOD tank inside of it and a bunch of other stuff relating to the gain structure. I'm going to record a demo either later today or tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 01:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are correct! There's also an output driver inside the enclosure that can do some pretty fuzzy things to the signal making it a great pedal for psych stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 23:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Digiverb is just for scale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NPD ScreaminFX Uverbia spring reverb pedal... I've been playing with this for about 15 minutes and it sounds amazing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 23:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 09:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Analogman ardx20 is badass! It does a great job of not getting in the way of the signal and also has an fx loop allowing for a lot of extra flexibility.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 19:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got the black fountain recently... it just wasn't exactly what I was expecting and I ended up finding a good deal on the empress vintage modified superdelay on Craigslist so it got on the board instead. 

Diamond is badass! They're also really pleasant to interact with. That tremolo has got some magic in it too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 07:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty cool! Has a ton of different effects. Really unique. Some of them are totally usable and others are completely  bonkers. I never really use it because it's a desktop unit though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 03:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe direct is the left channel/mono, so it's the one to use if you're playing with one amp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 19:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The diamond tremolo is amazing. You might be able to find one used for a good price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 05:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should try putting a dummy cable out of the second output (right) on your boss super chorus. Some stereo chorus pedals will send out vibrato in one channel if you trick it into thinking it's putting out a stereo signal. That should make it more wobbly sounding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 05:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah! The colors on that one are especially cool too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got an Archer a couple of weeks ago! It's working out pretty well so far. How do you like it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boss TU-2 -- Diamond Comp -- Crowther Hot Cake -- J Rockett Archer -- Empress Vintage Modified Superdelay -- Diamond Tremolo -- Analogman ARDX20 -- EHX Cathedral

Duesenberg and Supro amp not pictured </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Current Pedalboard surrounded by alternates and oldies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 00:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 04:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The National (band) and broccoli </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 20:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to listen to Feels and Strawberry Jam too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 04:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 3 words for you:  terry cloth pants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
