<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3288</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might be, might be, but as far as I remember tyrion hasn`t really heard anything about the wall since Joer mormont died, and a lot has happened since then. And besides, I think he`s got his hands full with the impending invasion of westeros. He might not remember about the wall untill it is too late. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don`t bother reading books, Games workshop has done everything they can to suck peoples wallets dry. Go watch Arch warhammers lore videos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, Rockstar is just very good at keeping it`s card close. Nobody likes fake leaks and stuff ruining their game, so they keep their cards close. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope not. The multiplayer is messed up (at least on ps3) and the controll systems feels so stiff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, the art needs to be good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 12:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THink you might be on to something. According to the wiki some of the ancient elven cities were shook by trembles/eathquakes and the elves started to kill of the titans. Not too hard to beleive that the blights might have been a response to the elven threat. Only problem I see is the fact that the first blight only happened looooooong after Arlathan was destroyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A siege mode is a must, considerign that all the maps I have played in the beta are basically set in a siege background. They way I see the game now is more or less a waste of potential. Running to capture a, b and c and killing som people on the way is not the way to go. Give us progression in the form of siege stages where we first fight for the gate and then proceed to throw the attacked back into the sea (or whatever) or push the defenders back to the keep. Make the battles feels meaningfull. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems pretty certain, as if the dagger on tevinter wasn`t a clear enough hint, the statement that they need to hire people Solas doesn`t know basically confirms it. Since we`ve spent 3 games in or around ferelden and Orails, it seems certaint that Tevinter and other places we haven`t seen before will be the setting for the next game. Which si more than fine by me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. the World of ice and fire mentions strange things happening all across the world during the long night. No reason it wasn`t felt there. Still, since no humans survive there for long we don`t have any sources confirming or denying this. Still, the brindled men, lost cities and wierd rumors sugest that some crazy shit went down there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably wights in the forets and waters. Tormund mentions that they were being followed on their way south of the wall, and the stragglers were dissapearing. A bunch of humans sitting in one place seems like a great opportunity for the white walkers to kill some humies and add to their numbers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 11:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like people misunderstood my question, I`m not asking for similar fantasy books to a song of ice and fire, but lure books like "The world of ice and fire". Big coffe table books with art and the history and facts about the universe, like the world of the witcher and the world of thedas books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (No spoilers) Similar books to The world of ice and fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 21:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The world of ice and fire really got me into these sort of fantasy lore/universe books, telling me all about the history and places of the world. I LOVE twoiaf, and I recently bought The world of the witcher and the world of thedas, which are also very good. Are there any other books like that that you would recomend? Maybe some lore books for the lord of the rings series of warcraft maybe?

Edit: There seems to be some kind of misunderstanding here, I\m NOT asking for similar fantasy series, but for books similar the "The world of ice and fire" aka lore/history books about fantasy univeres. I already bought the world of the witcher and the world of thedas, and on another site I was recomended Warcraft chronicles, which seems pretty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Other books similar to The world of ice and fire? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 21:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope so. Just unlocked them today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 09:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it was bad. Lauged at his Hitler, dictator and ape jokes. The others ware bad. Kinda felt like neither he nor the crows was in the mood. Lacked energy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 11:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is a Samurai hero supposed to be as strong as a 3 m high fantasy green ape, og as strong as a giantlizard monster?? Warhammer is fantasy, Shogun is not.
Besides, I actually like the heroes and generals in shogun 2 better. In Warhammer I feel that all they do is fight, in Shogun they are given more command options, like setting a regroup point, giving morale boost and such. THe heroes in warhammer are cool, but they are most of the times just oversizes units with some extra abilities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 17:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I`m a big warhammer fan but to me warhammer is just a dumbed down total war. Still lots of fun, but God forbid they try to transef the warhammer mechanics to the historical total war series. My biggest fear is that creative assembly will think that because warhammer sales very very good they will think that has to do with the mechanics and dumbed down elemets instead of "Warhammer" being the big dealmaker here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 17:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well they already got their first historical advisor on board, so i somone could figure out who that person is we might learn what time period we are dealing with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 17:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, the dlcs may sell better but I don`t think they are the best "ever". Good sales doesn`t have to be good quality (even though they are good). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 17:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would require the single unit mechanic to be transfered from warhammer to shogun, and I doubt they will use anything else than the engines already in place for the older games. Besides, we already have hero units in Shogun 2, just small griups of them. No need for single hero unit when they don`t have any special abilities like in Warhammer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 15:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A "age of charlemagne" og "wrath of sparte " style dlc set during/ right before the bronze age collapse in 1200 bc, would be a perfect setting. For Attila you could have a dlc set in the 6-700 with the rise of the aravs, or even later with the byzantine- bulgar wars. LOTS of potential here, for both game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 14:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope they make more dlcs/update Rome 2 and Attila. So much potentisal still in those games and eras.! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 15:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest, if assassins creed completely dropped the "animus approach" and severed all ties to the modern world, and became more like the witcher 3 with rpg elements I would be happy. Imo the best ac game is black flag, and that is the least assasins creedy game yet. I think sticking to the old formluae only holds the series back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 15:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ancient egypt would be epic! Totally new locaes and characters, and the fact that we know so little about the time period gives the developers a lot of freedom in creating characters, events and buildings. Perhaps we can even travel to Crete and meet the minoans, babylon or nubians on other games or as different locations in the first game?
Besides, black flag was one of the best recived ac games, and that was arguably the least "assassins creedy" game ever, and setting the game in ancient Egypts, before the real formations of the assassin and templar orders let`s the developers do more with the franchise instead of binding themselves to the old formulae. Indeed, they have said that they have been inspired by the witcher 3 and it`s great sense of freedom, so this could be very, very good if done right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 16:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad they basiaclly made the citadel 2.0..
Was really hoping for something new and unique, not just reshaded me1. Don`t get me wront, I`m hyped for the game, but I`m just worried that they won`t dare to thread new paths and just stick to the old and known. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 13:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really lush and beautiful jungle planets. Just revathed Avatar for the first time in ages and wow, Pandora is perfect. Also recently bought star wars battlefront, and playing on endor gives me hope that the frostbite 3 engine can give us Pandora like planets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 10:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too actually. Most of the planets in me1 were just copy and paste with different colours. Rather want unique planets. But still hoping for more planets and unique planets wich are fun to explore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They said we could explore 100s of planets... really hope that is true. Would be epic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 13:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.gameinformer.com/b/features/archive/2016/11/16/what-mass-effect-andromedas-gameplay-takes-from-mass-effect-3s-multiplayer.aspx

Here`s the video. Like the frostbite destruction.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 16:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dissapointed... The last concept at they showed before the models looked awesome, then they just blew it....
They look like mix of the collector and the hive from Destiny, nothing new or unique at all.... Hpe they have some other cool and interesting new aliens instead of the kett. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 16:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Replaying it now, and yeah, it holds up good. Noticable fps dropws on ps3 though, and the loading times along with the elevator trips.....
but besides that it hold up great! Love the mako exploration, and the citadele just looks awesome, especially the vista areas.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope this is true instead of the so called "leaked" map. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 18:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, true, but Red dead isn`t GTA, so whatever the rules were with art from gta might not apply to red dead. Besides, the girls from the gta posters, as you said, are just random girls, the characters from the red dead poster are actual, in universe people, so why would rockstar add them if they have nothing to do with Rdr2? No, I believe the poster represents some of the people we will meet in read dead 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 15:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, if one of the charachters on the poster really is Jogn Marston ( which I still kinda doubht), we won`t see the birth of the west. Somone said that John was about 38yo when he died, so for him to be old enough to be in agang in Rdr2, we can only go back about 20 years, to 1890, when john was about 18. Some of the other charachters on the poster are older than john was in rdr1 so they could be in a game set even earlier, but from the clues we get, along with the fact that we see electric lamps and such I really doubht we will go back in time before the 1890s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 15:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine having a canoe gunfight, you paddling like a crazy while dogding bullets and fighting back against natives or something. Would be epic. Also, if they add fishing and diving we that would add to the hunting mechanism and the water could maybe hide treasure?
And who knows, we might get to fast travel across bodies of water by steamboats, just like we could with trains and stage coaches in rdr1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 15:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, i think it`s fake too. Maybe at best some of the places on the map might be real in the sense that this might have been som VERY early map concept, but I think the final map will be something else, and not this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why doubt it? We see clear native signs in the trailers and the image relase. The dreamcathcer, tha native paddling the canoe, the fact that one of the pople in the 7 gang posse is a native, I beleve we are right to hope for more native americans in the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 14:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, anything bigger than Blackwater I wouldn`t like. Don`t want wast cities byt open prarie and nature. Smaller towns and trading posts would be fine enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newspapers in Rdr2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 14:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the little things I really loved about rdr was the newspapers you could buy after major happenings in the game. It fits so perfectly into the game and was both fun and interesting to read.
In my opinion newspapers are a must for rdr2.
Side note: Rockstar really captured the style of writing in the game, as you can see from this New York times article from 1909 concerning a Native uprising: http://query.nytimes.com/mem/archive-free/pdf?res=9906E1DC1131E733A25753C3A9659C946897D6CF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 14:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really hope they add more Natives in rdr2, what little there was in rdr 1 was cool, but i would love to see more Native camps, maybe somes ambushes as you said, or maybe even a playable Native. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
