<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The original Condemned was on PC, 2 wasn't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very insightful. These guys invading the farms have hundreds of livestock at a time when the govt. is having to buy cows and goats from Turkana and Somali herders so that they don't all die in the drought. And its really suspicious that it happens in an election year. There are definitely some politically powerful people behind this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of misinformation in the comments. 

1. Kuki is a conservationist who has done a lot for Kenya's wildlife. With the national govt. not being very keen on protecting the country's wildlife, people like Kuki have been picking up the slack and doing a lot of work to protect animals in Kenya.

2. Her shooting and the raids that have been happening in Kenya have little to do with poaching and the trade in wildlife trophies. The people carrying out the attacks are not poachers, they're pastoralists. Kenya has a lot of different pastoralist communities, especially in the Northern half of the country, who have never really modernized their culture or settled down. Some of them are nomadic, some are not. These communities include the Pokot, Samburu, and the Turkana. [These communities have been fighting each other for a long time, and the only thing that has changed recently is that they have easy access to Kalashnikovs streaming in from War-torn Somalia and South Sudan](http://www.accord.org.za/ajcr-issues/%EF%BF%BCpastoral-conflict-in-kenya/).

3. The most recent raids have occurred due to friction between the tribes and the conservationists. In a country where people struggle to hold on to land that is more than an acre in size, conservationists have thousands of acres in Laikipia county. The local pastoralists consider this to be their ancestral land and that puts them at odds with the ranchers and conservationists. They are also at conflict with  African land owners in the same area, but that doesn't get much attention. In this particular year, there has been a massive drought in East Africa and this triggered the raids early this year. But we also can't ignore that this is an election year in Kenya, and security and the economy tend to go to shit when elections come close. 

4. The government response has been kinda shit. Most recently, the president deployed the army to work alongside heavily armed policemen to deal with the situation. The result has been multiple shootings of herders and their cows, but with the pastoralists still illegally occupying land. Firstly, I don't think its legal for the president to deploy the army without parliament's approval. Secondly, kenya's police officers are dumb as shit. No, seriously, [The Kenyan police does not hire people who have a C+ or above](http://www.the-star.co.ke/news/2017/03/02/lower-kcse-mean-grades-for-cops-mps-tell-interior-ministry_c1517301). 

Recruitment interviews typically go like this:

"Do you have 32 teeth and shit for brains?"

"Yurp"

"Here. Take this assault rifle, MRAP and badge and go terrorize the masses"

"Yurp".

TL:DR; It's not about poachers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The one where Pedes discussed the mating / breeding practices of a Muslim, globalist, feminist Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 10:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A month ago, one of the pedes over at T_D posted a Breitbart article discussing Germany's recent demographic changes following the mass immigration that recently occurred. In the article, [Virginia Hale reports that 36% of children under five years in Germany have a migrant background](http://www.breitbart.com/london/2016/09/21/germany-40-percent-migrant-background/). 

So the first thing that pops up for anybody with half a brain is how ridiculous those figures are. In 2011, Germany had a population of 80 million people. For the demographics of the country to change that much over the last two years, the country would have had to take in millions of refugees. Not to mention the article itself is a mess that just screams "fake news" whichever way you look at it. The first thing that pops out is the round-about links that you get with fake news articles. If you google anything about "40% German children migrants", a bunch of the results popping up are right-wing and conservative sites that link back to the Breitbart article [Example 1](http://www.dailystormer.com/genocide-at-sonic-speed-36-of-children-under-five-in-germany-have-migrant-background/), [Example 2](https://www.amren.com/news/2016/09/germany-nearly-40-per-cent-of-under-fives-now-migrant-background/). Apparently, Breitbart are the only guys to have picked up this incredible story, as not even the German media is talking about it (Fucking MSM shills). The only source that Breitbart give, on the other hand, is an article by [Michael Paulwitz](https://jungefreiheit.de/debatte/kommentar/2016/raum-ohne-volk/). Paulwitz is a German conservative journalist who runs a paper called "Junge-Freiheit". The article he wrote did talk about massive demographic changes in Germany. However, Paulwitz does not mention anything about the 36% that Breitbart themselves have. His article does not even discuss children under five in any part so that is obviously bullshit from Breitbart, especially because they provide no other source. 

But all that is not even worth talking about, its just Breitbart playing their role. The interesting part is how the pedes turned this discussion into feminism, "globalism" and the third Jihad ( I must have missed the first two Jihads). 

So the top comment goes: 

muslims already said they plan to out breed the germans.
They tell everyone what they are going to do and yet germans accept this with open arms.
Doesn't help they breed like rabbits and each male can have several wives. 

And obviously the German government is complicit in this, as it pays the Muslims to have children. 

As it happens, the pedes' high-level understanding of Muslim "breeding" practices, also helps them understand why rape is so endemic in the Muslim world. 

One of them asks: 
Serious question - I've always wondered how this works. If the population is close to 50/50, do many males go without any wives if some of them hoard up all the women?

And the answer:
This is why they rape anything with a hole in their down time. Goats or young boys as long as it can be stoned when they are done they are good to go.

And please note, Muslims "breed". Seriously, the word breed was used at least 8 times in the comments and each time in reference to the Muslims. What do Europeans do? They "have children". 


The comments get even more interesting when they go into feminism and globalism.  

The first comment on this is pretty tame and actually isn't hateful or absurd
Europe has a huge problem trying to get women and families to have children. It's a problem in a lot of first-world/developed regions. As education level, wealth, and opportunities rise women (and men) start to not want to have children. This poses a major threat to the economies that run off of taxpayer dollars, no children now means no workers later, so what did they decide to do? Immigration and Gobalism. And we saw how that turned out.

However, almost everything that follows that is a total shitshow.
Firstly, Feminism is apparently one part of the problem. 

Feminism- Globalist/communist plan to cut wages and get larger workforce. Women working during childbearing years = lower birth rate. One sided laws covering divorce and custody = Men less willing to marry = lower birth rate. Single mom households = more crime. Wonderful

A problem that is worsened by women who just don't play their role. 
Feminism is part of the reason. Women working 5 to 9 jobs removes them or delays them in the mating pool.
Then by time the woman wants to have babies, its too late either because less men interested or they lose the ability. Btw, the older the woman is when she gets pregnant, the more likely the baby will have birth defects. Women working also removes them from the household and this results in their children being raised by the state more often.
Its not a bash on women, but it just seems that its not really working too well for the long term survival of a people. The other blame is responsible adults living in a high cost of living area.. while immigrants pop out multiple children and having you pay for them via taxesm

Remember women, you're supposed to be in the mating pool, not the working pool. So if you're reading this in an office right now, shame on you. 

I could go on and on and on, but those comments are so absurd, I'd end up replicating 80% of that thread here. 

TL:DR: Women destroyed Germany by refusing to mate, thus allowing the Muslims to outbreed the Germans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditor on the T_D finds a 2013 NYT article claiming that chemical weapons are so horrible, even Hitler wouldn't use them .... except it didn't. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 11:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The aftershock of Spicer's ridiculous Hitler chemical weapons comment. A pede does some sleuthing and stumbles upon a fantastic find. A 2013 New York Times article by [Steven Erlanger](http://www.nytimes.com/2013/09/07/world/middleeast/a-weapon-seen-as-too-horrible-even-in-war.html). According to the article, Hitler abhorred the use of chemical weapons and even refused to use them himself. And so the pedes assemble. The highest comment archives the article. The next highest comment is something about the poetry of it all 

I'm starting to see a pattern here. Shit happens, Trump admin comments on it, media gets enraged, Trump admin apologize, media gets BTFO the next day by their own records.
It's like poetry. Or an eloquent waltz, and Trump is leading.

The third highest comment, though, is a winner. After much reading of the article, the pede finds: 

He literally thought they were too bad to use on civilians because of his experience with them in WW1.

But let's take a look at the article, shall we?

No Western army used gas on the battlefield during the global slaughter of World War II. Hitler, himself gassed during World War I, refused to order its use against combatants, however willing he and the Nazis were to gas noncombatant Jews, Gypsies and others.

And that is the only part of the article that talks about Hitler. It says the exact same thing that Spicer's critics have this week. Hitler DID use chemical weapons. Not to mention the argument that is there to be made about Spicer trying to degrade Assad to Hittler's level as a way of justifying the strikes last week (admittedly though, Assad is a terrible person and something needs to be done).

TL:DR; Pedes can't read for shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
