<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject350</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cloud porn over London this morning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 15:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 14:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gee.. thanks for the tip, growlers sounds good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our first Christmas in Europe! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 14:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Redditors,


Wife and I have been together for 11 years now, we have just recently moved to the UK because we always wanted to do live in London and wanted to travel Europe properly. Been here 6 months now and have been taking time out to visit nearby countries and the English countryside. It has been a dream come true, really.


We are going to Berlin on Tuesday for 5 nights so we'll be there on the 25th December. My wife loves all things Christmas and has been wanting to see Berlin for years... so Berlin at this time of the year was an obvious choice given the Christmas markets. So since we are going to be in Berlin and at her favourite time of the year I just want to make it that extra bit special by doing something super romantic besides just taking her out for a nice dinner.

Additionally, I'm hoping places will be open during the Christmas time and we'll be able to explore the city and have some fun. I've heard 24th is the BIG day and 25th is relatively "normal". Thoughts please? 


Are there any Berliners around here who could help me with some options and tips. We both like to immerse ourselves in the local culture, we LOVE food, looking forward to the Christmas cheer (or whatever is left of it by then!) and enjoy the little things in life.


My budget is approx 100 Euros for the night, if that helps. We are staying in Mitte and will be there for 5 nights.

tl;dr - couple in Christmas looking for tips of things to do and make a special night out of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 14:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, new to Reddit! Will post in Berlin. Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We need this in pubs all over the world. Full p(o)ints to England. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 10:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today I learned that pirates wore an eyepatch to circumvent the adjustment period of going from the light to the darkness below deck. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 09:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-19 19:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regular denim wearer, rare denim washer here, can confirm that no one notices your jeans are unwashed.  But they do look at you weird if you tell them you haven't washed that pair in 1 year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today I learned that there are no snakes in Ireland because they couldn't "make it" to Ireland when it geographically split from the UK 2000 years ago. Snakeless in Ireland: Blame Ice Age, Not St. Patrick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 22:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Black cab manufacturer is owned by a Chinese company </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 20:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 19:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a migrant myself I find it very annoying when migrants make no effort to assimilate into the new culture. Resorting to mixing with your own kind is arguably not the best use of your effort to move countries. Might as well just stay put. 
I've noticed this amongst most cultures although Westerners more propensity to mix in general than people from developing countries. This broad brush analysis is based on my experience of living in 3 countries over the last 10 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 18:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also makes me hungry and wantbto eat bacon all the time. And im trying to stay vegetarian asmuch as possible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-10 18:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easy as. Sweet as. Nah mate, thats the Australian in me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit is awesome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 19:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just started reading a lot more here thanks to baconreader. It makes my two hour commute easy as.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 18:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh so that explains all the chinese people with masks all over.... London and Sydney(?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
