<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2894</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me Trying to act like an adult: I think you did a great job. If I was painting myself naked I know wouldn't be able to resist adding a bit of girth and maybe an inch or six. 

I see the shoulders and belly look so well done and natural but I'm just a bit suspect on a couple things that really stand out to me. Either way well done.

The voice in my head: Yep you should paint and post. those are nice t.....female power all day. wonder if she fixed em up a bit, I know I'd add a cup or 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 14:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to wear a Saint Christopher on a necklace for years.  Then one morning I woke up and it was off the necklace but the chain was still on and the the pendent and the the little circle piece of metal that connected the pendant was in perfect condition.  No idea still to this day how it came off. 

The main reason I didn't put it back on is because the night it came off was the first night I spent with my GF who had converted to Islam a few years earlier.  In Islam I believe wearing charms is like idols and is considered wrong. I'm not saying anything pro or against any religion but it was far to odd for me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 13:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No prob </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree it seems irrational. I am still annoyed when someone doesn't stand perfectly still in silence staring at the American flag while the Anthem plays.  The hat question in particular may annoy me because I suspect you know the reason why people remove their hats and I then assume you are showing disrespect to that reason. I believe there is debate on the actual reason we remove our hats, beyond basic respect for the country. I remove mine out of respect for my fellow Veterans and their families both here and passed as an example.

I love my country and a long time ago before I came along people agreed, I believe as a sign of unity, to perform these seemingly irrational actions. It also occurs to me that we as people need more actionable events that remind us of who we are and if you go in a little deeper the great sacrifice so many people made to continue to have the freedom to stand for a moment of peace and listen to our song. 

Thanks for the question. It prompted me to answer it for myself. 

Edit: there to their (I do this daily, never learn)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At my school all the poor kids had a lunch ticket. I grew up in a poor area so poor is sort of relative because at least a 1/3rd of my friends had lunch tickets.  We would sell them for half the full value to kids with money and tell the lunch ladies we lost our ticket. Sometimes you lost that game though and had to figure out another way to get lunch. 

We were maybe a bit poorer than the other poor people but my mom was a hustler and figured things out for the most part. I'm sure she made some sacrifices I'll never know nor will my little guy because of her putting me in every sport and Boy Scouts to make sure I was in a decent place with decent people. She utilized the community well.  Free hot dog after games and if you volunteer to help you generally get the leftovers.

Edit: have to half  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canada is winning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pure evil.  I want to Google all of the above now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadely we don't offer free weed but if you find that gig I know some folks that would be very interested. In terms of hiring we are always looking for talent. If you send your info in a private message I can review and see if anything looks like it may align. I'm 100% meritocracy and won't pull strings for anyone. My thing I say is "I'd fire my own momma if she wasn't meeting the standards" Just fyi.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you do?  I don't see your resume.  I'm new so may just be my ignorance or I'm taking you literally when I shouldn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be a big deal.  Let's just hope it's "fake news".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I didn't sign anything.  They didn't tell me what to say but when I was talking to the producer it was to go over and help clarify what my thing was going to be. I still could have said anything.  My guess is they cut the camera to another feed and some massive dude crushes you and throws you on the street.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My gf had to move her seat and be a talker.  I was 6th man but they were smart to keep me on the bench.  It was Wendy Williams show. When we were in line waiting to go in they talked to us then we had to write some answers to the topics then we had to talk to a producer with our thing to say.  It was cool, they were all real nice. I'm not sure I'd do it again though because I'm someone that always gets picked out of a crowd for random shit and I'm not sure what I would actually say if I was ever on live TV. I fear I'd black out and attempt to raise an army or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you can communicate your ideas, a process exists to turn an idea into a benefit, and you know the long term vision for the organization and your personal growth in that org.  

Or unlimited free weed.  That would be good too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great lesson.  I know I'm right all the time but I'm such an asshole throughout the process no one ever wants to give me the satisfaction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The culture.  It's a traditional culture and prides itself on hard physical work and hard partying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
